A $5,000
deposit.
>> Yes, sir.
>> That is the craziest dep that is more
expensive than my 911.
>> Yeah. A car that not not a lot of people
can get.
>> You see that? I wasn't laughing.
>> We're not going to run your card. We're
just keep it as
>> So, I have to give you my credit card
and trust that you're going to not run
my card. And this is all just a trust
thing.
>> But we're usually always MSRP all the
way.
>> Well, right now you're above MSRP all
the way. I would give you $1,000 if we
agree to numbers. I don't think that's a
crazy concept. I guys, I have to take
care of this client that's been waiting
very patiently for their car. Grand
Highlander Hybrid Limited with panoramic
moon moon roof and they want a darker
interior. Okay, they want a moon roof
and they want ideally blueprint. Last
time I checked for the blue print, there
was only 85 in the country and guess
what? 47 of those being hybrid and 28 of
those. Okay, we're not finding this car.
Not that color combo. So, we need to
open up a few more colors.
like can we open today?
>> Hey, I just want to see if you guys have
a car available.
>> Brand new, use
>> uh brand new.
>> All righty. Where are the last for that
VIN number?
>> Last four VIN numbers. H is in Harry
Potter 215.
>> Grand Highlander.
>> Grand Highlander Hybrid Limited.
>> So, this one's in our allocation. It has
not arrived yet. Still in our building.
Looks like supposed to arrive next
month, meaning the middle of next month
or the beginning of September.
>> Awesome. Perfect. Well, this is the
exact one I'm looking for. Do you guys
do reservations before they come in?
>> Yeah. You're local by chance? I'm not.
I'm in Austin.
>> Oh, Texas.
>> In Texas. Nice and hot.
>> Yeah, it's hot over here. Don't worry.
>> Oh, see, it's basically the same place
then.
>> Question for you. Once this vehicle
arrives, are you able to come in and
pick it up?
>> Yeah, I mean, we're we're open to come
picking it up. Uh, if we can ship it, we
can do that, too. We can do either one.
>> Yeah. So, to do the reservation, I'll
just need a little bit of information
from you.
>> Mhm.
>> One second, please. What's a good first
name, last name for you?
>> Uh, first name Tommy, last name Makula.
M I K U L A.
>> You say a little bit slower. Sorry, I'm
not that fast of a handwriting.
>> M I K U L A
>> M cool. Is this a good number for you to
reach you at any case?
>> Yep. Perfect.
>> Yep, that's it.
>> All right. So, just to let you know, the
way we do these reservations on our
vehicles, we take a $5,000 deposit on a
debit or credit card with your name on
it, copy of your license, and a copy of
your car insurance. So, we can have that
all set up. Honestly, on the card
information, we just held your uh card
just as good faith really. We don't take
it, we don't run it or anything. A
$5,000
deposit.
>> Yes, sir.
>> That is the craziest dep that is more
expensive than my 911.
>> Oh, really?
>> $5,000 is a lot of a deposit.
>> Well, we don't, if I'm being honest with
you, we don't rent the card. We just
hold it as a basically a keepsake.
>> Say a $500,000 deposit if that's the
case. I mean, that's that's insane. I
mean, I'm authorizing you to give $5,000
off my card for a deposit on a car.
That's a huge number. Do I get something
exciting out of that? Yeah, a car that
not not a lot of people can get.
>> You see that? I wasn't laughing. So,
like like it makes sense. If you guys
are giving me some crazy deal, then
maybe the $5,000 deposit makes sense cuz
it's such a good deal that you need to
hold all my money. But what's what's the
price? What am I paying for it?
>> Let me pull up everything right now.
>> Yeah. $5,000. You You act like a casual.
That's casual.
>> Well, we do this a lot. We do a lot of
reservations for a lot of these
vehicles. We have our price at 58,061.
>> Okay. So you guys are above MSRP on it.
>> Uh we're at MSRP. Sorry.
>> MSRP on this car is 57262.
>> Check.
>> Yep. That's with our ceramic coating. So
we usually take that off.
>> It's above MSRP.
>> So
>> yeah. So we usually take that off of the
B. And I mean if this is a dealbreaker,
we'll help out the customer with it. But
we're usually always MSRP all the way.
>> Well, right now you're above MSRP all
the way. So if you want a $5,000
deposit, that is a huge commitment to
ask of anybody. I would need a better
deal than above MSRP.
>> Yeah. I'll take off that ceramic
coating. I mean, we'll be MSRP. Why
don't I mean if I'm going to give you
$5,000 of my money, why don't we take
like two grand off the car and then now
we're talking.
>> Yeah, just give me one second. Let me
see what I could possibly do.
>> All right, I'll be here. 5k deposits.
Insanity. I'm sorry. It doesn't matter.
Like a $5,000 deposit is what I would
expect to leave. Like if I was doing a
911 order and I'm buying a $200,000 car,
not on a Grand Highlander. No, the added
value package is something that people
are saying is mandatory versus a
broker's fee, which I guess actually,
let's just ask you guys. Let's just ask
the crowd opinion. You guys could pay
$900 for some paint protection. The
dealership ads on there. I bet it's the
best paint protection you ever had. Or
you can pay me $1,000 to do the entire
process for you. You don't have to do
anything at all. You sit back, relax, I
negotiate everything for you. What would
you rather pay? $900 for the paint
protection or $1,000 for somebody to
handle the service for you. Just see
which ones are questionable fees. And if
somebody wants to say my fee is
questionable, you can say that, too. I
don't care. But Sebastian says, "You
rather do it himself." Preach. I love
it. I'd rather do it myself, but
watching you is fun. I love it. Prepise.
>> All righty, boss. Still there? I'm still
here.
>> So, I just got done talking to my boss
about the whole situation. Told him
you're in Austin, Texas right now trying
to get this vehicle to reserve it for
you. Since the car is not here yet, I
mean, we're not able to work numbers
just yet. I mean, I told him, he's like,
"Just tell him we can do $1,000 good
safe for the deposit. We're not going to
run car nothing. We're just $1,000 is a
good safe."
>> So, you guys can work numbers if I buy
the car at the marked up price, but you
guys can't work numbers otherwise?
>> No. So, until the car gets here,
basically. So, even if I was willing to
buy it at the 58061, you guys wouldn't
take my money.
>> Well, we we wouldn't have it. We
wouldn't be able to take the money
because the car is not here. Get what
I'm saying? The whole car is still
hasn't even been built yet. Let me look
here. The production the build date
supposed to be on the 21st of next
month. The production confirmed was it
was confirmed it's built 619 2025. Built
start production 821 2025 and it's
supposed to arrive here hopefully next
month.
>> So, you're saying there's no way to just
reserve the car in general?
>> Well, as long I mean, like I said, I
mean, we'll take your card information.
We're not going to run it. License,
insurance, we can reserve that vehicle
that way. And then once the car comes
here, I mean, we'll do all the numbers
and everything then and there.
>> So, I have to give you $5,000 for the
faith.
>> No, no, no. So, like I said, my manager
said just do it a,000 just since the car
is not here.
>> So, I have to give you $1,000 for the
for the option to negotiate it.
>> No, to reserve the vehicle.
>> Yeah, but we're not agreeing to a price.
You just said that the price we we'll
talk about price when it gets here,
>> correct? Cuz the vehicle has been built.
Think about this from the outside.
You're asking me to pay you $1,000 to to
have the first option to talk to you
about price when the car arrives because
you just said you can't talk about price
till the car arrives.
>> Well, you getting the first keepsake
basically on the vehicle. You're the
first one to say yes. You're the first
one to say no. If you don't like the
vehicle at the end of the day, it's
you're got first dibs basically cuz if
you don't reserve the vehicle, someone
take first dibs on it and then it's a
whole different scenario.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> So, you're basically just reserving it
to be the first on it
>> and then I just trust that you guys give
me my $1,000 back when we don't agree to
numbers. Well, we're not going to run
your vehicle if I'm being honest. We're
not gonna Sorry. We're not going to run
your card. We're just keep it as
>> So, I have to give you my credit card
and trust that you're gonna not run my
card. And this is all just a trust
thing.
>> Yeah. Being completely honest with you,
yes.
>> Okay. So, I just got to trust that
you're not going to run my card. And if
you run your car, then I probably don't
have much legal standing to get my money
back because I'm reserving a car that I
don't even know the numbers on. I mean,
we have it priced at I mean, with that
90 cure on there, I mean, I have no
reason why not to discount it. Say we're
at 57262 MSRP.
>> Yeah, but you you just said you couldn't
talk numbers beforehand and said we
wouldn't be able to make any any
decision on anything until the car
arrives. So, now you're saying there's
no reason why you couldn't. Why can't we
just agree numbers beforehand, put the
deposit on, call it a day? Like, why why
play all these games?
>> I'm telling you the number I'll pay for.
No, it's no big deal, man. Like, it's no
harm feeling. I'm not mad. I'm not
disappointed. I'm just I'm just trying
to buy a car. So, like if you're like,
"Hey, Tommy, I'm sorry. We're not going
to be able to take 2 grand off MSRP.
Cool. I'll find somebody who will.
Somebody will. We all both know they
will. But the idea of I'm paying you
$1,000 for the opportunity to maybe do
it. And you don't see any reason why you
wouldn't, but you won't do it until
>> I mean, there's a real reason why you're
calling all the way from Texas here.
There's not that many being built right
now, especially with the hybrid. The
hybrids are really sought after.
>> Just just the lady really wants a blue
one. So, we're looking for the blue one.
And once we can't find a blue one,
there's other colors that we have close.
I have two grand offer one locally
that's gray. I just would prefer to get
blue because she wants blue. And you
know what? Making the lady in charge
happy is the number one goal. So, we're
looking for blue. If not, we'll go with
the second color, which is gray. She
doesn't like it two grand more plus
shipping or plus us going out all the
way to
>> So, the only way you do this vehicle is
if you do 2K off. Even then, I don't
even know if I can get numbers. Okay.
>> Yeah.
Like, I don't even see a problem with us
taking $1,000 off the the markup. So, I
can't you guys can't. It's
>> not $1,000 off. It's $7.89. Just to be
blunt with you there.
>> Yeah. I'd want two 2K off MSRP.
>> Oof.
>> Oof. Still above invoice?
>> Not really. We're at invoice.
>> No, not 2K off. You're above invoice.
>> Well, like I said, I mean, if you'd like
to reserve the vehicle, I need those
that information. I know you want to
work numbers now just to get it over
with, but even then, if the car get does
get delayed and delayed, we never know
what could possibly happen.
>> So then I'm giving you $1,000 for it to
get delayed and delayed and we won't
know what will happen. I'm giving you
good faith money and for the opportunity
to maybe get a deal on this car. If not,
I've wasted all this out in time because
now you're asking me to wait till
September 3rd. Well, yeah. Month plus to
wait to not have a pricing down in
writing. Like, I want It's not because I
I'm I'm I want to get it out of the way.
I want to know before I give you a
$1,000, I'm giving you $1,000 for I
don't want to give I'm not giving you
$1,000 for the right to negotiate.
>> So, basically, what you don't want to
give $1,000 to reserve the vehicle?
>> I would give you $1,000 if we agree to
numbers. I don't think that's a crazy
concept.
>> Yeah. I mean, I'll just get a manager
involved. He'll talk to you and go from
there.
>> Yeah. I mean, that's fine.
>> Yeah. Uh, again, Tommy, I don't want to
butcher your last name.
>> Mula.
>> Mula. Correct.
>> Yep.
>> And then I have all your basically what
you want to do with the deal and all
that. I'll have the manager talk to you.
Obviously, I'm at a standstill with the
information I'm given and maybe they can
help you a little bit further. Is that
okay?
>> Yeah, no problem.
>> All right, Tommy. So, I'll have one of
the managers reach out to you here
shortly in the next 5 to 10. Is that
cool?
>> Yeah, that'd be perfect.
>> All right. Thank you, Tommy. Bear with
us. Okay,
>> no problem. Bye.
>> This is Mitchell.
>> Hey, Mitchell. It's Tommy. Sorry, I
missed your messy call.
>> No, you're good. You're good. I know uh
you spoke with Brandon. You had some
questions on reserving a Highlander we
have coming in.
>> Yeah. Grand Highlander. Yes.
>> Yeah. What's going on?
>> Yeah. Um like I said, I'm super
interested in it. Uh it was really just
coming down to um trying to get the
pricing figured out and he said we
couldn't talk about price and we
couldn't talk about price, all that fun
stuff. And here we are just trying to
figure that out.
>> No, no problem. What I can do is um I
can have him or myself I can I can send
you over the breakdown of out the door.
We just need your address uh with a zip
code so we can figure out sales tax. Um
but on these cars we're just doing we're
not charging markup but we're doing MSRP
plus $7.99 for nan.
>> Okay. And you guys can't take that off.
>> No. No. Unfortunately.
>> Okay. So you guys are charging above
MSRP. It's just you guys are adding up
paint stuff on there.
>> Yeah. Paint protection.
>> Okay. So the idea Okay. I'm glad I
didn't put a I'm glad he called back.
Glad he put a deposit because he said it
he felt confident we'd be able to get
the price down once I came then. So
you're saying there's no moving on the
price at all?
>> No. No. Not at all. Now, once the car
gets here, it's just hard to say, right?
Cuz we don't get a whole lot of these,
but the last four that we got in, we
didn't The cars were sold before they
came in, and there was there was no
there's no discount on them.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Uh yeah, I'm looking for,
like I said, I already have a deal for
2K off. It's just not on the color we
want, so it's our second favorite color,
but we're more than willing to settle if
we have to. We're just calling to see if
we can get the blue.
>> No, no problem. I understand.
>> All right. Sounds good. Appreciate it.
>> All right. No problem.
>> Bye. So, I'm going to like give you guys
like the the secret. Sales managers
don't like selling cars, right? Like
their their main goal is to to have
their teams do stuff for them. So, when
you try to skip the process and just get
right to them, you have a big chance
that they're just going to hold firm on
the price and call it a day and then
maybe they make it easier, but there's
no like guarantee that happens. There's
no I have never seen and we've we've
tried every method. We negotiate
hundreds of cardios a monthly basis.
We've tried them all. We try them all
all the time. There is no magic wand by
calling a dealer or sales manager.
Normally, you actually move less
compared to somebody that's been working
five different phone calls with them and
he's like, "You know what? Call today."
It was good talking to you guys. I got
to go do a few things anyway. Peace out.
Bada boom, bada bing. Talk to you guys
later.
[Music]