Tommy, I am not a manager. Now you need
to tone down the enthusiasm. Okay, it's
Wednesday, Tommy.
>> Two door broco.
>> Jeez Louise, are you a mind reader? I
feel like I'm dating again and I'm
engaged. That's crazy. So, I'm sorry if
I said something wrong. Maybe we can
start over. Maybe we can just be
friends.
>> Can you step it up a little bit?
>> 77250. I'll do the same thing.
>> Stop it, Tommy.
>> What do you mean? Why would I stop it?
>> Hey, Tommy. Quick question. You sound
really familiar. I mean, I was the
Campbell Soup baby back in '92. Let's
just make sure this client is ready.
They want a 2024 Bronco Raptor. These
are the deals I've been looking at.
Almost the perfect spec. If it was blue
and orange, it had no graphics. It' be
the dream car. Like 24 grand off is kind
of my number in my head. Okay, so this
dealership is advertising their car at
$100,000.
Let's see.
>> I thank you for calling.
How may I help you? Hey, I just want to
see if you guys have a car available.
>> Yeah. What car are you looking at?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
Actually, maybe there is a stock number.
Am I going crazy? Yeah, I have a stock
number. Sorry.
>> Is it new or used by chance?
>> Brand new.
>> Okay, cool. Let me search it up. Okay,
ready whenever you are.
>> Stock number is B as in Bronco 33794.
>> Bronco Raptor. Yep, this one is
available still.
>> Awesome. Perfect. Well, I'm interested.
Love it. Want more of it. Living West
Coast. Really just trying to get the
best deal I can on the West Coast. You
guys already advertise it strong. I have
a slightly better deal. home. Hoping you
guys can just blow this other deal out
of the water and I can buy a car from
you today.
>> Yeah, of course. And could I go ahead
and ask for your name?
>> My name's Tommy.
>> Hi, Tommy. Nice to meet you. My name is
Zuriel. Um, let me go ahead and go ahead
and get that information. Could I go
ahead and ask for where you're from?
>> I'm from San Francisco, but I love I
love a good road trip.
>> Okay, cool. Sorry, you cut off right
there.
>> Sorry, I'm from San Francisco, but I
love a good road trip. And just so you
know, you're really quiet. I don't know
why. Maybe maybe
>> I've been hearing that issue right now,
but would it be easier if I just called
you on my personal phone?
>> Sure, I'm going back.
>> Because it seems not working. Give me
that number real quick.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> Thank you.
>> Your phone.
>> Hey, uh are you in new car sales?
>> Yes, I am. My name is help you.
>> Hey, uh I just want to see if you guys
have a car available.
>> Okay. Uh do you have a specific VIN or
what are you looking for?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Yeah. Give me a second information up.
I'm sorry. Uh what was your answer?
>> My name is Tommy.
>> Tommy?
>> Yeah.
>> All right. Cool. Uh what's the stock
number that you got? Stock number is
going to be R is in Ralph, L is in
Larry, A is in Alpha, 38571,
>> two door Bronco.
>> Jeez Louise, are you a mind readader?
>> That's been the popular vehicle of the
day specifically. I we've had three
other customers calling about that
vehicle today alone.
>> Long story. Crazy.
>> Yeah, I mean, we've had quite a few
people asking for that. Yeah. I mean,
that vehicle is right out here on my
lot. Uh we're going to help you out with
that, though.
>> Really just trying to get pricing. I've
already driven one already, you know, I
want it, but yeah, I'm just trying to
get some pricing on it.
>> I'm sorry.
>> I'm just trying to get some pricing on
it. pricing on it. Okay.
>> Pricing. Yeah.
>> All right. And then um
>> I know there's some crazy good deals.
Maybe that's why everybody's calling.
>> Yeah. Looks like I think we just have
listed as MSRP at the moment. I think
because all the pricing on that vehicle
has been fluctuating like crazy. Uh
Ford, let me take down your name and
number and I can I give you a call back
once I get a good answer.
>> Yeah.
>> Awesome. And then this is your the
number on the caller ID ending.
>> That's it.
>> Awesome. If the number looks good, how
soon you plan to purchase the vehicle?
>> Today.
>> Okay. And paying cash financing.
>> Open to cash. open to finance.
>> Nice. Give me a few minutes. I I'll give
you a call back once I get to talk to a
sales manager.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> So, one of the other things with
delivered, uh, one of the other
quoteunquote benefits is we do 200 deals
a month, right? So, we have a pretty
good understanding of what is a good
deal, what is a bad deal, uh, which
helps us tremendously. There's a thing
that I call delivered called chasing
ghost, right? What that means it
delivered is you have a good deal. You
don't really realize you have a good
deal, but you just keep calling
dealerships and then you start losing
the deals you had and then you realize
those deals were great and by the time
you go back to them, it doesn't work.
So, we're pretty good.
>> Hi, thank you for calling. How can I
help you?
>> Hey, can I speak to Zuri?
>> Who?
>> I think it's Zuri. Z. Maybe Israel.
Maybe. I'm just like I'm like trying to
go back memory. I'm sorry. I'm getting
old.
>> We don't have a Israel either. We have
James
>> Yurio. Like is it was a weird something.
>> Yurio. Yeah, we have a Yurio.
>> That must be him. Zuri. Yeah. I mean,
I'm just going crazy.
>> Okay. Yeah. Let me transfer over to him.
>> Okay.
>> Your call has been forwarded to an
automated voice messaging system. At the
tone, please record your message.
>> Man, I'm not going to lie. This is
Tommy. I I feel like I'm dating again
and I'm engaged. That's crazy. But like
maybe I said the wrong thing and you
just were like, "I'll call you." And
then you just never called me. I don't
know if I said something. But now this
is even worse cuz if we were in the
dating world and I called you back and I
I shouldn't be calling and leaving a
message. I should be cool and just
chilling. But I thought we had
something. I thought we were going to
get a deal together and I was going to
buy a Bronco Raptor and it'd be fun.
Again, I'm engaged. So, but I just feel
like I said something wrong. So, I'm
sorry if I said something wrong. Maybe
we can start over. Maybe we can just be
friends. But this is Tommy. I gave you
my number if you don't remember. We we
were talking. It was a good
conversation. You're a little quiet, but
that's okay. Anyway, if you can give me
a call back uh just so you have my and I
don't have like Snapchat or anything,
but you can call, text, email, fax, page
me, whatever makes the most sense for
you. Again, now it ended.
>> Thank you for calling.
It's Franklin. How may I help you?
>> Franklin, it's Tommy. Nice to meet you.
I just want to see if you guys have a
car available. Tommy, I am not a
manager. Now, you need to tone down the
enthusiasm. Okay. It's Wednesday, Tommy.
>> You know what? You're right. I'm so
sorry. I'm going to tone it down. Yes,
sir. Yes, sir.
>> Uh, Ali, is Ali on the phone? Hang on a
second.
>> You're good.
>> Ali,
>> future Tommy, how's it going?
>> What's up, bro?
>> Hey, what's up? I I heard you are the
one to talk to for numbers on a car.
>> How can I help, sir? Uh,
>> I have a stock number of the car I'm
looking for. If that helps.
>> Whenever you're ready. Yeah, it's F is
in future 300061.
>> What's your name, sir?
>> My name's Tommy.
>> Tommy, nice to meet you.
>> You're Ollie, right? Like Ollie. Ollie,
like a skateboard does an ollie?
>> Ollie. Yeah.
>> Dang, that's cool.
>> Bronco Raptor.
>> A raptor, as some people may call it.
>> Yeah,
>> I love it. That's the one.
>> Perfect. Let's simplify it. Tommy, how
can I uh how can I be of service or how
can I help?
>> Uh well, I'm looking for basically a
crazy deal on these 2024s. I hear some
there's some some insur absurd deals on
these old old age units. That's right.
There is. Yeah, there is. Yeah.
>> What are we thinking?
>> About 17 grand off sticker.
>> We're getting closer. We're getting
warm. We're getting warm.
>> Where you at?
>> Add 7,000.
>> Can't do, sir. How much all in 18 off
the sticker?
>> Oh, I There's There's deals for 20K all
day.
>> 20K all day, huh?
>> Yeah, there's one for 20k off right now.
>> What would you buy it for, Tommy? I
>> I told you I wanted to be at 24, but you
know, I'll be nice. I'll buy it at 23.
You came up. I'll come down.
>> 77.
>> 7 to 7. Sorry.
>> You're at 77 grand in the truck. 23
grand off would be 77. Yeah, he went 18
all in and now he's considering my
offer. I just muted him.
>> We're close. We're so so close. We're
super close.
>> Okay. I'm I I I feel like the magnetic
energy close to us. How close are we?
>> Very close. Very close.
>> You're at 229. You know what? I I'll
come down 100 bucks. You win. Jeez.
Tough negotiation.
>> I'm all in. 20 grand off sticker. Tommy,
I'm at 80. 20 grand off sticker. 80
grand for the vehicle. Are you
financing?
>> I'm open to financing. Yeah.
>> Okay,
>> man. I really really was hoping we could
do better than that.
>> I'll do 79750.
>> So no 250 bucks. See if we just keep
talking. Eventually we're going to get
to my number
>> eventually.
>> I'll just stay here like so. So So did
you grow up around here or you got Did
you move here?
>> No. No. I move. Where do you live?
>> I live pretty darn close about 30
minutes away from the dealership. So not
bad. But I will go up to if I need to.
>> I mean sure, brother. I mean if if you
if you're getting a better deal from
them, why not?
>> Like I said, I'm open to either or. But
again, they're 20k and I haven't even
called them yet. You know,
>> at 20k, that's pretty much net deal from
them.
>> Yeah,
>> that's net deal from us. At this point,
I just want to get rid of it. You're
financing, right?
>> I'm open to finance you.
>> Okay,
>> I'll I'll finance on the 77.
>> I can't do 77. That's three grand loser.
We can't We can't do that. We're We're
in the business of making money.
>> Yeah. Not a 2024 Bronco Raptor. You're
in the business of losing money on that
car.
>> We're right. I'm at 80. You're at 77.
Why don't we
>> 79 750?
>> Right. I'll close it at 79. Would that
Would that make a difference? I can't.
We keep talking. The number keeps going
down.
>> That is correct. I want to find out what
we do it for, but not 77.
>> 77 is my number.
>> I get it. Can you step it up a little
bit?
>> 77250. I'll do the same thing.
>> Stop it, Tommy.
>> What do you mean? Why would I stop it?
>> How 785 and then we'll close it. That's
that.
>> You're You're I get Man, you're making
this like easy. You just keep coming.
We're I don't
>> It's supposed to be easy. It's It's a
Bronco Raptor. It's been sitting in
here. We We want to get rid of it.
There's no reason for me to be a hard
bargain on it. I got a live one on it.
It's the right car for you. Let's make
the numbers right.
>> You got you got the hook on. You just
got to reel it in again. 77. Yo, come
up. 775. Send me the numbers. Let's rock
and roll. Let's close it.
>> 78 flat. Tommy, come down here today.
We'll close it out.
>> 775. And I just want to make sure
there's no dealer ads or anything crazy
where you guys are all losing all my
money back.
>> You're good, bro. 775. Come on down,
Tommy. 775. Look for me, I'll leave.
>> Okay. You want to send me those numbers
real quick and then we'll rock and roll?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Let me Let me do that
right now. Here.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You want to text him over?
>> Yeah. Yes, sir. I'll text it over to you
right now. Is this uh yourself?
>> Okay. I'll text it over to you.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> Thank you.
>> All right. Thank you. Bye.
>> Thanks. Bye-bye.
>> I don't know what to say. I need to call
the client. I did not expect that to
happen. That's a crazy deal. I need to
call my client. One second. I got to I'm
going to have to mute.
>> Nice.
This is Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. This is Kevin.
>> Hey, man. How's it going?
>> Hey, good day. Just quick call right
away. I got over to my manager, told him
the vehicle. He says that we can do
$20,000 off MSRP of that that vehicle.
>> We're close. We're so close. I'm trying
to be 24k off.
>> You had 24K off?
>> Yeah, I have an offer for 225 already.
>> Okay. Are you able to send that over to
me? Uh this is my cell phone. You can
text it over to me if you don't mind.
>> Yeah, I can take it over to you in just
a few minutes.
>> Yeah, I can double check and see. I
mean, I think he he told me we're trying
to be around like 18 to $20,000 off. I
don't like I'm just going to hit you
with a bigger number instead. Just
starting off that way if anything.
>> Absolutely. Once I get the like I said,
I just talked to the sales manager over
at the other dealership and they told me
they would do they they were $500 away
from my number. So, sorry, $1,500 away
from my number. I apologize. So,
>> Oh, cuz you were trying to get the
$24,000.
>> 24 and they said they could they would
do 225. And I said, "Okay, send me that
and I'll look at it and if I can't get
24, then I'll uh then I'll go back." So,
>> Okay. Yeah. Send that over to me and I
I'll I'll show them what the offer is
and see what they're willing to do for
you.
>> All right. Sounds good.
>> Yeah. Take care. Talk.
>> Bye.
>> This is Ocean.
>> Hey, Ocean. Hey, I was uh talking to
Zuriel earlier and he said he was going
to call me back in like 2 minutes and
that's been like an hour. So, I'm just
trying to get Sorry. Yeah,
>> possibly. Were you speaking to Yuriel
maybe? He is one of the newer sales
reps, so I might have to see.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I was saying and it took
forever. I just didn't want to wait. I'm
about to buy this other car. So, I'm
like, you know what? Let me call
somebody to see if you guys want to do
this deal or not. Otherwise, I'll buy
this other one.
>> Yeah, no problem. Let me go ahead and
see if he's available or maybe I can
even help you out. I know he is with a
customer right now. Who am I speaking
with?
>> My name's Tommy. I mean, what's a good
phone number for you?
>> Yeah. Uh,
>> what's that vehicle we're taking a look
at?
>> Uh, it is a Ford Bronco Raptor.
>> You got a stock number by any chance?
>> Uh, I did. Let have it still up. It's B
is in Bronco 33794.
>> The blue Raptor. Perfect. What kind of
information can I get you on this one?
>> So, I told him already, so I have I'm
really just trying to get $24,000 off. I
see you guys are offering 20K. I have an
offer for 23K. Just trying to be a 24K
off. If I can get that, I'll buy the car
today is what I told him. He said, I'll
go check. And that was like he's like,
I'll call you back in like 2 minutes.
And that was an hour ago. So now I'm
just kind of annoyed. And
>> can I possibly give you a call back in 2
minutes?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Dude, I don't care who I
work with. Like I said, I'm super easy.
You say yes to 24K, I'm buying a we're
buying a car. If you say no, then I'll
just go buy the other one. Like I'm I'm
I've been doing this enough today. I'm
at the I'm at my tipping point of I just
want to buy one of these two trucks.
>> Hey, Tommy, quick question. You sound
really familiar.
>> Well, I mean, I I I was the Campbell
Soup baby back in '92. I feel like I I
heard you. Um or I might have seen you
on social media. I don't know if I'm
just jumping the gun, but let me double
check on this one real quick. I know you
trying to get some information on this
car.
>> It It is me. Just so you know, it is
>> Man, that is crazy. That is absolutely
crazy. I'm glad I picked up the phone.
>> I know, right? Well, I'll tell you, man.
Like, this is like I said, this is this
is a done deal at 24K. Client's ready.
They're ready to travel up to see you.
They're the one that sent me this car.
So, if I can make that work, otherwise
they I have another deal. So, let's just
close the deal, man. make it easy.
>> Yes, sir. I'm here and I watch your
videos all the time. So, let me try to
make this a smooth process for you. I'm
going to give you a call back. I'm going
to make sure that it is in two minutes
and not if uh two hours. Just give me a
second. I'm put my hands on this car and
I'm going to just give the offer to my
car or to my uh used car manager, my new
car manager. See what we're able to do
on this one. Okay.
>> Okay. Bada boom, bada bing, man. Could
give me a call.
>> Sounds good. Thanks, Tommy. I'll talk to
you soon.
>> No problem. Bye.
>> All right.
[Music]
>> This is Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. This is How are you doing?
Hey man, doing well. Doing well. How
about yourself?
>> Doing good. You spoke with a salesman of
mine earlier?
>> Yeah, I did. He He was great.
>> Perfect. Happy to hear that. How can I
help you, man?
>> Man, I'm trying to get this Bronco
Raptor deal. I I was telling the
salesman. I have I have one that I'm
looking at here, but I like your guys a
little bit more. I'm hoping that you
guys can just give me the deal I want so
I can buy it. Otherwise, I'm buying this
other one.
>> Perfect. Straightforward enough. What
deal are you looking for?
>> I'm trying to be a 24K off. No ads.
>> 24K. So, an additional four on my
online.
>> Yeah, another four. No ads. Easy peasy
lemon squeezy. No protections, cash or
finance.
>> Open to cash, open to finance. Probably
finance, though, realistically.
>> Okay. I don't see why I can't do that.
Is he local?
>> He's not, but he's want to come to you.
So, like he's want to road trip up to
you. He's in San Fran, but he he's like,
I'm willing like he likes your car more,
so he's willing to drive drive up to
you.
>> Okay, perfect. And he's aware it's uh
24, not a 25. Correct.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. He's he even sent me
this exact He's He's literally watching
me right now, waiting for me to if he
says, "If you give me this deal, I will
buy the car right now. This would be a
done deal."
>> Perfect. Yeah, I'm I'm willing to do it.
>> Bada boom, bada bing. Just send me those
numbers real quick. I'll send it over to
him. We'll get it all rocked up.
>> Perfect. So, my proposal I want to send
over. That's why I asked Casher Finance.
What down payments would you like me to
show? I can three show you three
different options.
>> Yeah. 51015 is fine. And we'll
>> All right. Perfect. I'll get that sent
over to you. Let me just make sure I
have an email address. Or do you want to
text it?
>> You just text it. Just easier that way.
And this will be He's ready to go right
now. So, the second you send that, we're
good.
>> Perfect. And I have uh standard 8.9
interest rates on here. Is there
something else he wants to see? By no
means is that accurate.
>> Yeah. Yeah. No, no, I understand. I
mean, I imagine he'll qualify for top
tier. We I don't think he's
pre-approved, so we'll get that figured
out. But I imagine, you know, five to 6%
somewhere in that ballpark will be
somewhere. High fives, low sixes.
>> Perfect. Just let him know that 8.9 by
no means is that based off of his
credit. It's just your standard rate for
your ti.
>> Yeah. All right. I did just send it
over, texted. I'm sure you got a
breakdown with an out the door and
monthly breakdown with 510 and 15 down.
>> I love it. Let's rock and roll. Let's
get cardio down. Let's get 24 off your
lot.
>> Let's do it, Tommy. Appreciate it.
>> Appreciate it, man.
>> You have a good one.
>> Bye.
>> Bye-bye.
He still got it. He still got it. 24K.
Dang. 24K. Dang. New record. So, in this
deal, client actually sent me these
deals. Said they want to do. So, let's
get congratulations to Here's a
proposal. Let's just make sure the
proposal looks good before we give them
the congratulations. Boom. We got it.
Boom. Done. So, congratulations. Numbers
look good. $24,000
off. I don't want to bragious, but we've
negotiated two cars and we have saved a
total of $40,000.
There's no more markup in cars, Tommy.
There's no discounts. You can go to the
dealership and maybe get a hundred or
$200 off. The dealership is losing money
selling at an MSRP. That's a funny one.
I love that one.
[Music]