Justin, how's it going, man?
>> I can't complain. Nobody listens. So,
honestly, what I think you should do is
just keep shopping around. Make this
easier for me.
>> Just give me the deal. Call a day.
>> Yeah, that doesn't work like that, man.
I'm sorry. What do you have now? Do you
have an EV?
>> Uh, I have a Hyundai.
>> Uh, isn't an EV Hyundai?
>> It is not. No.
>> Okay, never mind then.
>> That's funny cuz our one sales manager,
his last name is Kula. K U L A.
>> What are the chances?
>> We are going to be negotiating on
night. that ready. I'm going to call his
dealership. I wanted people to see that
I'm more professional. So, I brought my
tie. Clearly tied it really well. And
then my my medal from the Royal
Caribbean, which obviously was given to
me cuz I was a professional. I'm not
like those other guys. I'm not like the
people they think I am. I really just
want to prove myself here. So, hopefully
you guys understand that this is a new
wave. This is a new me.
>> It's a kooky day at Destination Kia.
We're so happy you called. If you know
your party's extension number, you may
enter it at any time. For service, press
one. For sales, press two. For part,
press three.
>> Thank you for going to Sandra. How may I
assist you?
>> Hey, Sandra. It's a kooky day here at
Tommy's house. I just wanted to talk to
somebody in new car sales.
>> I can help you. What's going on?
>> Awesome. Perfect. I just want to see if
you guys have a car available.
>> Yeah. Which one are you looking at? New,
brand new?
>> Uh, it's a brand new car.
>> Okay. Which one?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Yep. Go ahead.
>> Awesome. Uh, it is K as in kind of 26, X
is in Xylophone. 0272.
>> Is this the only one that you're looking
at or any others I could check on for
you?
>> I mean, the EV9 is the one I want.
That's the dream. You know, that's the
dream in the driveway type stitch.
>> Okay. Yeah. Let me see if that one is
still available for you. What's your
name?
>> My name's Tommy.
>> All right. And is this a good contact
number for you in case you get
disconnected on hold, Tommy?
>> This is the best one.
>> All right. Perfect. Give me one moment.
All right. Thanks.
>> Meanwhile,
>> hi.
>> Hi. Thanks to your patience. So, good
news. It looks like that one actually
just landed here today and it is still
available. Did you have time to swing in
today before we close? We're here till
7:00.
>> Well, I've already driven it. Already
know I want it. Really just trying to
get some numbers on it. So, I can be
even quicker than that.
>> Okay.
>> Were you looking to lease or finance?
>> I'm looking to finance the 0%.
>> And were you trading anything in or
putting any money down?
>> I'm looking $30,000 down, but not really
too worried about the payment. Obvious.
But, uh, no, just looking to um get the
best possible deal. No trade. Just
trying to get one of those last second
EV deals.
>> Okay, totally understand. And what's
your home zip code for tax purposes?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. My zip code is
>> Yeah.
>> Going to have one of our product
specialists reach out to you to kind of
get everything going for you over the
phone. Um, but it shouldn't be a
problem. And what's your last name,
Tommy?
>> Makula. M I K U L O. U L A.
>> That's funny cuz our one sales manager,
his last name is Kula. K U L A.
>> What are the chances?
>> That's funny. He'll like that. Okay.
Well, let me get your information out to
one of our sales guys. Um, so you're
looking at finance. 30K down, no trade.
>> That's it.
>> All right. Perfect. I'll have somebody
reach out to you shortly here. Okay.
>> All right. Sounds good. thing, right?
>> So, she's not in new car sales, correct?
>> This is Justin speaking.
>> Justin, how's it going, man?
>> I can't complain. Nobody listens.
>> You know, I like that. You know, it took
me a minute to get there, but I get it
and I like it and I like your humor.
>> Thank you.
>> You know what? I think we're going to
get along real well. I I want to see if
you guys have a car available.
>> Let me get to my computer.
>> You know what? You're good. Take your
time.
>> So, um, what's the stock number?
>> It's 26. K is in kooky 6370.
>> Gotcha. White EV9.
>> That's it.
>> Gotcha. Let me go see if it's available.
Give me one second. So, it looks like
it's actually on our patio.
>> Oh, it's on your patio. Wow. It's having
lunch.
>> So, what's up? What can I do for you?
>> Hey, awesome. Well, I love it. Want more
of it. Uh really trying to get one of
those last second EV deals. I'm hoping
that you can help me out.
>> Gotcha. So, what could I do in terms of
to make a deal happen? What can I do?
>> You know, I'm trying. Everybody's trying
to confuse me with all the rebates and
all the fun things and tax credit 5,500
bucks. I'm going to tell you what I want
to do. I want to do 0%. You know, I want
I have the competitive I have the
Hyundai deal discount. I get the APR
discount. Here I get the $5,000 discount
and I'm looking to get like a a sizable
dealer discount.
>> Okay. So, what dealer discount were you
looking at?
>> You know, small, kind of big, depends on
you ask. 4,000 bucks is kind of what I
was hoping for.
>> Has a dealership done that for you yet?
>> Not yet. I've seen I've seen some offers
around 2500, 3K. Um, but 4K has been the
magic number, you So, usually there's a
reason why you haven't seen it yet,
maybe close to it, is because there's
not much room for the EV9 to go down
that low. There's not that much markup,
but what I can advise you made a few
phone calls. So, we only made like three
phone calls. So,
>> yeah. Yeah, no problem. So, what I can
advise you to do is I can grab your
phone number and then, like I said, you
sound like an intelligent guy. Seems
like you're shopping around. That's what
I did with my vehicles as well. It's a
smart thing to do. So, you're kind of
like me. What I can advise you to do is
keep shopping around and when you find
the number you think is the lowest, you
can always contact me and I can probably
beat it by a margin you'll be happy
with. Where are you calling from?
>> Uh New Hampshire.
>> New Hampshire. So, wow. You're still in
the same region technically, so it's
still competitive. Connecticut competes
with New York, Massachusetts, then
Maine, I believe, is in there, too. Then
the two little ones, New Hampshire,
Vermont, Rhode Island. So, honestly,
what I think you should do is just keep
shopping around. Make this easier for
me. And if you send me over a money
sheet, I can probably beat it by a wide
margin. Like I said, you would be happy
with like we're very competitive. We're
in the middle of nowhere. So, in order
to hit quotas, we just beat people's
prices. That's why we actually sell the
most cars in Connecticut being a
dealership in the middle of nowhere. So,
that's what I would suggest doing.
>> You know, I appreciate that. Why don't
we just, you know, cut all the BS and
you know, I'll get there. I'll get to I
mean, you said you'll beat it by a
sizable margin. I already have a
discount for 2K off. So, like just let's
just
Yeah. I mean, let's
>> Can you send that over to me?
>> Sure. Just call you, text you, email.
>> Uh, you can take my phone number. You
can take my phone number.
>> Okay. Well,
>> that would earn your business.
>> I mean, I'm trying to get to 4K off. I
told you that's the number that just
ends it,
>> you know. Yeah. So,
>> I'm telling you, I'm telling you, like I
don't want to play the games of calling
78 dealerships, calling one in
>> Kansas. We're not Yeah. I'm going to
save you time. We're not going to jump
from 2,000 off to 4,000 off. But if you
want to work your way up to that and
then get me a deal that's like $3500
off, I probably can't do it then. But we
have to have a reason to do that. And if
we're going to lose about $1,500 to sell
a vehicle, it has to make sense for us
to do it.
>> Yeah. No, I I get it. I get it. But like
I said, I I just don't like to we just
cut through all the noise, you know?
>> Yeah, I got you. But it's just it
doesn't make sense to sell a vehicle to
lose $1,500 on it. It's just I'm just
being honest with you. There's not not
that much markup on the EV9 to
>> Well, I mean, the idea behind it is in
five days, it becomes a paper weight.
So, if you don't sell it in five days,
then you know, then you lose the $7,500
bucks. And
>> well, technically, we don't lose the
$7,500. The person that chose not to buy
it loses it. It doesn't that $7,500.
>> We can all agree that people are buying
these EVs with the $7500 and people the
chances of everybody being, you know
what, I want to buy an EV now that
$7,500. I completely agree, but they
were selling before that federal tax
rebate came out. So, and maybe not as
much, but like I said, it doesn't make
sense for us to sell a vehicle to lose
$1,500 unless we absolutely have to. I
can beat whatever quote you give me, but
we have no reason to beat
>> that quote's $11,431
off. And that one has $7,500 off plus
the competitive bonus or the APR bonus.
>> I' actually never even heard of that
dealership. Well, I have your phone
number. I can see what my general sales
manager thinks, but I think he's going
to relay the same message. It just
doesn't make sense to jump in discounts
that much. So, you have the competitive,
you have the $7500, you have the $5,000
rebate, 0% down. So, I see the total
savings that's 11,431. You have the
breakdown on that.
>> No, it's the $7,500 plus $1,000
>> plus the what? I'm sorry.
>> Plus the plus the $1,000 rebate for the
competitive.
>> Gotcha. So, that would be $8,500.
Where's the other? So, is that the just
the dealership war or dealership um
discount the extra? Okay, gotcha.
>> See, just beat it. I told him 4K, too.
I'm telling everybody 4K. It's the
number.
>> Gotcha.
>> I'm easy peasy lemon squeezy, you know,
like
>> Yeah. I I just don't think we would do
it unless, you know, it made sense for
us to do it.
>> You said you'll beat you said you'd beat
the deal.
>> Yeah. But but not by like $1,100.
Maybe like $500 I can get, but not
$1,100. Like I said, it's got to make
sense for us, too. Well, I understand
you're trying to get the best deal, but
it just doesn't make sense for us. But I
can, like I said, I have your phone
number now. I can go ask for you and
then worst comes the worst, you can just
part away as friends. You can keep
continue shopping and then get a quote
that's better than that and see if I can
beat that.
>> Well, yeah. If that's how you guys want
to do it, I mean, that's totally fine. I
mean, I'd rather like I said, I feel
confident I'll get to this number. So, I
can keep calling to get to this number
and then you guys have to beat it. Don't
like why and but but here's the thing is
why why make me do all the work? Just
give me the deal. Call a day.
>> Yeah, that doesn't work like that, man.
I'm sorry. I wish it did because trust
me, I wish it did, but it just doesn't
just doesn't make sense to lose $1,500.
There comes a certain point where it
doesn't make sense to sell a vehicle
even if you have a quota to hit. And
usually we hit a quot. It's about the
you guys have seven EV9s and if you
don't sell them in 5 days, then you're
correct. You don't lose the 7500, but
clients lose the 7500. And the chances
of selling those cars exponentially goes
down. It's not impossible. You could
still sell them. people might pay more,
but the chances are lower after.
>> Yeah, but and then they'll sit and then
we'll sell them and we sell them. You
know, we have a lot of inventory, so
it's just doesn't make sense, man. But
>> well, like I said, that's where, like I
said, that's where the I mean, a lot of
people are losing money on EVs right
now, so it's not like they're not losing
money. Like the idea that people aren't
losing money on EVs, trying to get rid
of them.
>> Oh, yeah. The I'm sure the discount that
we have online is probably making no
money on the vehicle. Believe it or not,
there really isn't that much markup on
there, but if it makes sense to sell it,
it makes sense to sell it. Yeah. So,
I'll let you keep shopping around. You
have my phone number, and when you have
the best offer, please just give me a
shout, and I think I can beat anything
you get.
>> So, if I get, just to make sure I'm on
the same page, if I get $3,800 off, you
feel confident you'll be able to beat it
by 500 bucks to give me $4,300 off.
>> I wouldn't say I'm completely confident.
I'd have to still talk to my general
sales manager, but we're notorious for
beating any deal we get. And if it makes
sense, we'll do it.
>> Okay. So, do you want to start here? see
if you can beat this deal.
>> If it doesn't earn your business, then
why do it, you know? Cuz if I go into my
manager's office and be like, "Yeah, if
we beat this number, then he'll keep
chopping around." Then it just be like,
"Dude, you look like a bozo." So that's
why we don't usually say, "Hey, this
client has a deal. It's already pretty
strong. He's pretty determined." He said
if we get to 4K off, we get rid of one
of our most expensive EVs.
>> That's why I said said, "Let me go. Let
me go talk to him and see if I can do
that for you." But I don't think he
will, but I'll try, you know.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I mean, I know you guys have
three of the GT lines, which are the
least popular out of all of them.
>> So, you'd be shocked. We did sell two
recently in the past month, which isn't
a lot technically, but like you said,
they don't really sell much. So, we just
like having inventory because a lot of
dealerships around our area just don't
have the inventory. So, they leave their
dealerships to come over here cuz we
have them in stock.
>> Sure. Yeah. No, I understand. Yeah. I
mean, I guess we can also have this
conversation in in 5 days when it's the
30th and you guys still have six of them
and you guys are trying to get rid of
them. Yeah. Yeah. And then and then and
then those just stay on our lot, which
is fine.
>> I mean, you're saying that's fine, but
I'm betting your your owner is freaking
out about all the things that he has to
pay for those to stay on his lot.
>> I actually know my owner personally.
He's actually really good friends with
my dad. And he's actually he's loaded,
dude. So, I'm sure he'll be fine. But
like I said, let me go ask my general
sales manager cuz I want to get
something done for you.
>> Okay. Yeah. I mean, if he's lo you know
what? Here's the good news. Your owner,
the one that owns the building, the one
that's putting this deal together, he is
loaded. He will not mind losing 1,500
bucks. You I think you put the words
right in my mouth. So, why don't you go
to your manager, get this wrapped up,
and when he says no, I want you to
repeat the words, "Mr. is loaded, dude.
He won't miss the money."
>> Okay, that's fine.
>> All right, let me know how that goes.
>> Okay. All right. You got my phone
number, man.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> All right. I'll talk soon.
>> All right. Bye.
>> If you have an EV on your lot right now,
it's not, "Oh, we're not worried about
selling it. It's fine." There's a reason
why there is a fire sale on all EVs. And
the idea that he just said his owner is
loaded. He won't care if we lose money.
>> Hello, this is Jake.
>> Hey, Jake. It's Tommy. How's it going?
>> Hi, Tommy. How's it going, man?
>> Yeah, absolutely. Uh, hey, uh, I'm doing
well. Sorry the words are not coming my
mouth today. Uh,
>> it's good to me every day. I'll be
honest.
>> I know. Just It's the kooky day. So,
hey, I just wanted to check up and I was
trying to get numbers on the DV9.
>> Okay. Now, let me make sure first of
all, we're on the right one. Which trim
were you looking at? Did you have one
mind? Are you kind of open? The GT line
is what I was looking at.
>> The GT line. Okay. I've only got one of
them. I've got the Wolf Gray with the uh
brown black interior.
>> That's it.
>> Now, you are New Hampshire.
>> Yep. Correct.
>> All right. What is your um zip code?
>> My zip code is
>> What county are you in?
>> Oh, sorry. We just moved here. Let me
get you that. I apologize.
>> I know. I feel that. Where'd you move
from?
>> Uh I moved to North Carolina.
>> Oh, really? That's I'm moving down there
uh next month in November.
>> Where are you going to North Carolina?
>> Wilmington area. Uh, Loomington area is
nice. Uh, Hartford, sorry.
>> Hartford is that that's the county.
>> Yeah.
>> Nice. Okay. Good thing about New
Hampshire is there's no vehicle tax,
which is good. But I will say your
registration is awfully high, which is
not fun. But
>> I'm sure you did that research before
you went there, but I did.
>> Yeah. No. Uh, actually, myself, I've had
a couple New Hampshire people get cars,
and it's always funny seeing zero sales
tax, but then when their registration
comes back, it's like, oh, okay, that's
why there's no sales tax. Yeah. But uh
so GT Line financing I'm assuming.
>> Correct. Yeah, a 0% is ideally what I
was looking to do.
>> Okay. What I will say is usually Kia
does one or the other. So you either get
the 5 grand rebate or you get the 0%. In
my opinion, the 5 grand rebate's
probably better because it's still a
pretty low percentage. I don't know the
exact percent, but I can figure that
out. Otherwise, you're leaving five
grand on the table.
>> I know I know I've heard both ways. I
know I get the 7500 either way.
>> Let me see. Yeah, the 7500 thing that's
on your end, but Kia does put up a
rebate themselves as well. So, they put
up a 5,000 rebate plus there's
another,000 just for financing it. And
then I there's another,000 as well if
you own a competitive car. What do you
have now? Do you have an EV?
>> Uh, I have a Hyundai.
>> Uh, is it an EV, Hyundai?
>> It is not. No.
>> Okay, never mind. So, I think you are
able to take advantage of six grand
worth of rebates. And I'll double check
that with the manager, but I think
that's what you get. And then whatever
you do on your end with the federal,
that's up on you with the taxes when the
taxes come around in January or
February, whenever you decide to do
them. Okay. Financing, are you putting
money down?
>> Yeah, probably 10 to 20K.
>> Gotcha. And credit's good, I'm assuming.
>> That's great.
>> All right, perfect. No trade, no nothing
like that. All right. Financing, 10 to
20 grand down. I'll have them show you
both so you know what you're looking at.
And then uh I'll figure out with the
rates, too, what you're looking at with
those. But um we'll go from there. Is
this something you'd be able to uh get
here by Tuesday to pick up?
>> 100%. Yeah, I can come here uh today,
tomorrow. Probably tomorrow. Today's in
late, but today, tomorrow, whatever.
>> Yeah, a little late today, but yeah,
tomorrow could probably work. All right.
Yeah, give me a few. I'll go talk with
them, see what we're looking at
number-wise, and uh I'll give you a call
back. All right.
>> All right. Sounds good.
>> All right, my friend. Talk to you soon.
Bye.
>> So, the dealership texted me back and he
said, "My manager just said no." He
said, "Let me know when you get closer
to four grand down." Does it make sense
for him to do? I wish you luck. I don't
want to argue with him anymore. It's not
worth the time.
[Music]
This is Tommy.
>> Hey Tommy, it's Jake again.
>> Jake, he's back.
>> All right, so I got you a couple
numbers.
>> I'm excited.
>> Actually, it actually works out a little
bit better for you to do the 0% than the
six grand, which is surprising. The 0%
is only offered for 4 years, so 48
months. If you do, you still get a grand
rebate, luckily, cuz it's just an extra
rebate. They still give you one grand of
that. If you do 20 grand down, be like
$11.90, just about 1,200 to do that. You
do the 6 grand rebate, the rate actually
jumps quite a bit. I thought it was
better than this, but it's not. The
rate's 6 1/2. 20 grand down, you'd be
1240s. So, you save yourself like 50
bucks a month to take the 0%.
>> Great deal.
>> You could go up to 60 months on the low
APR. Low APR would go to 1 19. I don't
know what the numbers would look like
with that. I would assume it would get
you right around a,000, but
>> Okay. And what would u what's uh can you
break down the numbers for me? like
what's the I know you said there's a
rebate but what's like the price of the
car or what is there a discount?
>> So those numbers aren't doing any type
of discount. Obviously that's where it
comes into play. If you wanted to give
me a realistic offer I'll see what they
can do. But 77270 is the price. The one
with the 0% you get a,000 rebate
regardless. So you take the th000 off of
that. That's no taxes but he is figuring
your um w fees in there. Like I said, we
can't 100% estimate them until it's all
processed, but it generally works out to
about 1,500 bucks.
>> Okay.
>> And then 20 grand down, $1,1000 per
month. Sure. And then 77 Oh, yeah. Of
course. 77270 for the price. And then if
you take the 6 grand off, 20 grand down,
that's 1240. So you just it would
subtract that. There's no sales tax. So
it's easy there. Don't have to do too
much figuring, which is nice without
sales tax.
>> Okay. Yeah. Yeah. So, uh, like I said,
I'm trying to do a little bit. I mean,
I'm trying to get a discount on the car.
Obviously, I'm trying to buy it at the
end of the week tax credit. So, if I
paid MSRP, I think I'd get disowned. I
have a I have a deal for $11,431
off. They're adding the $7,500 rebate in
there as part of the discount though.
Acknowledge that. That's still with 0%
though with the rebates in there. So,
>> so they're showing up front. They're
showing you the 7500 that you are able
to get.
>> Correct. So, so it ends up being 3931
off, but with the $1,000 rebate you're
mentioning, it ends up being 2931 off.
>> So, what do I have to show you to make
it work?
>> I'm really trying to I mean, the dream
is 4K. Uh, that's that's where I'd love
to be at. If I did that, I'd sign it out
of line right now.
>> All right. And then I'm assuming you
want to go with the low APA or the low
interest.
>> So, 4K off, 0%, 20 grand down. All
right. Let me see. And that would be you
could give me a deposit over the phone.
Come pick it up. Uh well, tomorrow you
said or Saturday or whenever you can get
here.
>> Yeah, I'll ask him. I'll see see what he
thinks and uh we'll go from there. All
right,
>> sounds good.
>> All right, my friend. Bye.
>> Hey, talk to you later. Bye.
>> Just got I'm going to see what he says.
Just got 3500 off. Did you want to try
to beat it? I just want to see what he
says. He said, "Send it over."
>> Hello.
>> Hey, Nick. It's Tommy from Delivered.
How's it going?
>> Good. How are you?
>> Hey, man. I'm doing well. I see you guys
have an EV9 GT line. I was going to see
if you could work a deal on Yeah. Wolf
Grey.
>> Wolf Grey. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Let me I know it's here. I'm
looking at it right now. I think we have
a deposit on it. Where's your customer
located?
>> Uh New Hampshire.
>> Are they willing to come here or would
we have to ship it?
>> I mean, I can probably They'll probably
come there if the deal's right.
>> Okay. Yeah, I know for a fact my manager
is not really interested in shipping
cars. Can you uh I'm working a deal
right now. Do you mind texting me over
the details? Are they looking to lease
or buy or finance? Buy. Okay. Cash
>> 0%.
>> Okay. Yeah. Can you shoot me over some
of their details and I'll uh I'll work
it up with my manager. I'll shoot it
back to you.
>> Okay, perfect. I'll just send you over
the zip code right now and I'll see
>> All right, sounds good. The I'll just
link you the car so you have it.
>> Cool. Yeah, I'll get working on this as
soon as I'm done with this customer.
>> Yeah, of course. Yeah. Yeah. Take care
of the live body.
>> All right. Yep. See you soon. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> Calling.
This is Rebecca from South. How may I
help you?
>> Hey, I just want to see if you guys have
a car available.
>> And which one is it? Uh
>> I have a stock number. If that helps.
Yeah, if you have that, that's great.
>> Awesome. Uh, stock number is 26066.
>> And what year, make, and model?
>> It is a 20206
EV9 Kia GT line.
>> And it may actually take me around 10 to
15 minutes to see if we do have it. The
last thing I want to do is waste any of
your time. And what is the best contact
number?
>> Best contact number.
>> And how do you spell your last name?
>> Spell my last name is M I K U L A.
>> And first name
>> Tommy. You said Tommy. T O M Y. Yep.
>> Yeah. Let me check on this and as soon
as I get that information, Tommy, I'll
be more than happy to give you a call.
Okay.
>> Okay. Awesome.
>> Thank you so much. I'll speak with you
soon.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> Byebye.
>> This is Travis.
>> Travis, it's uh Thomas Love. How's it
going?
>> Oh, it's going.
>> Uh you know, I'm just trying, you know,
I'm trying to buy a car. Put a dream in
my driveway.
>> Uhhuh.
>> Uhhuh. So, I was transferred to you.
You're supposed to be the the the the
the man with the plan,
>> I guess. Uh you said you wanted numbers.
Uh you have a trade, no trade,
>> no trade. Easy peasy. Uh 0% finance.
>> Okay. And next amount down
>> the the amount down 10 to 20k.
>> And what county do you live in?
>> Uh I live in zip code zero.
>> Oh jeez. Do you know your sales tax?
>> Uh in New Hampshire.
>> I'll figure it out. I'll call you back
here.
>> There's no there's no sales tax in New
Hampshire.
>> Oh, really? That makes it easy. Cool.
Yeah, give me about 10 15 minutes. I'll
figure it out. Give you a call.
>> Okay, sounds good, Travis.
>> Thank you. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> Thank you for call.
>> Hi, this is Tommy. I just want to talk
to somebody in new car sales.
>> I'm in new car sales.
>> I love it. Well, I'm in the right place.
Uh, I want to first off see if you guys
have a car available.
>> Which car?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Oo, even better. Go ahead.
>> 010217.
>> I believe it's available, but give me
one second. Where are you calling from?
>> New Hampshire.
>> Okay.
>> Bada boom, bada bing. trying to buy a
car today or I guess tomorrow cuz it's
kind of late but
>> that's okay. Give me one second. No
problem.
>> I appreciate it.
>> If this deal is available and this is a
crazy deal. 4852. I mean this would be
insane that they're offering this crazy
of a discount. I want to see.
>> So it is still available.
>> Awesome. Perfect. Well, I'm super
interested in it. Want more of it.
Really just trying to get a breakdown of
the price with 0% and if it all lines
up, I'll buy it.
>> Sounds good. When you go 0% you forgo
rebates. I don't know if anybody's told
you that.
>> I know. I know. I lose some rebates.
Yeah.
>> Okay, perfect. Let me get a little info
from you. Sure.
>> What's your phone number?
>> Uh,
>> and what's your first name? I know you
said your first name. And your last
name?
>> Makula. M I K U L A.
>> And your zip code?
>> My zip code would be Z.
>> Perfect. Are you trading anything in or
just adding to the collection?
>> Just adding to my collection. Get one of
these deals near the end of the month.
>> I agree. Best time to do it. I'm glad
you did your research. You make my life
a little bit easier.
>> I love it. I try to make it as easy as
possible.
>> Any money down? Did you have a plan?
>> Uh 10 to $20,000 down. But yeah, you
know, in theory of 0%, we might just do
zero. But we're thinking 1020.
>> Yeah, that makes sense. What I'll do
when I quote it, I'll do 0, 10, and 20,
and you can kind of figure it out from
there.
>> Yeah,
>> I'm just putting the VIN in so I can get
rebates for you. Every time I think it's
going to slow down with the rain, it
just starts dumping on us again.
>> It's been crazy today.
>> I can't complain cuz we need it. I'm
worried my well's going to go dry, but
at the same time, like, holy.
>> So true. It's sunny as possible in North
Carolina.
>> So, you can go 0% up to 48 months.
>> Yep.
>> They do have a competitive rebate. I got
to make sure it still qualifies with the
0%. What do you currently drive?
>> I have a Hyundai.
>> I wonder if that's competitive.
>> I think it's competitive or loyalty. One
of the two. I think I'd get one or the
other.
>> Yeah. I will need the registration for
the Hyundai for that, but we can worry
about that later.
>> I mean, this dealership's
advertising,000.
>> All right. Military, first responder,
any of that fun stuff.
>> No military, no first responder.
>> Perfect. Give me a few minutes. I'm
going to get some stuff put together for
you. Is it okay if I call you back on
this number in about 10 minutes?
>> Yep. Perfect. I'll be here.
>> Awesome. I will call you shortly.
>> Okay, no problem. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> Sorry. Doing all the work first so you
don't have to look like a bozo to your
sales manager. May have just found 4852
off plus rebates. Hopefully your manager
is ready to lose some money.
[Music]
This is Tommy.
>> Hey Tommy. It's Heidi.
>> Hey Heidi. How's it going?
>> Good. So zero down 48 months. You be
1457 at 0%.
>> This says, "What what Hyundai do you
have?"
>> Yeah, I'm trying to figure out. I just I
just texted her. I asked her. I don't
even know what kind of model is. Just a
car, but I know we have a Chevy
Traverse. That helps, too.
>> Okay, I will find out. So on the rebate,
it says for EV, PHEV. So, we got to dig
a little deeper and make sure not only
if you have an
>> E. We'll figure we'll figure out the the
rebates are what the rebates are. We'll
qualify for them or not qualify for
them. What's the like what's the price
of the car? What's the discount?
>> So, we're discounting at 48.52. You have
a $1,000 rebate besides the competitive
and loyalty thing. Potentially $2,000 in
rebates there potentially.
>> So, we're just showing you with a,000
now.
>> Okay.
>> Our doc fee is $649.
>> New Hampshire title is 25.
>> Okay. And the total is 69902.
>> And then if I qualify then I'd get the
>> extra thousand which would make
>> extra thousand but then also the 7500
with the IRS tax credit.
>> Yes. So you would get that on your
taxes.
>> Okay. Can you send that breakdown so I
have it? Uh and then I think Yeah. And
then this is great. I mean this is super
easy. So yeah, this this sounds great.
>> Perfect.
>> Awesome. So I just pulled up the
incentives. It looks like it is only for
EVs and PHEVs. Ford Lightning, Maki,
Mustang, Hummer, Sierra, EV pickup.
>> Okay. I don't think ours is that. So,
we'll we'll double check, but I'll
double check the registration. We'll get
this I'll talk to her right now and then
we'll get this all locked up.
>> Perfect. Sounds good.
>> Sounds good. I appreciate it.
>> Of course.
>> All right. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> Hey, what's up, Tommy?
>> Hey, man. I was calling. I was just
seeing if we were able to do this.
>> Yeah, let's see. I was just in my
manager's office. I'll give you a call
back. Oh, I mean, as I say, I know we're
a little bit over the $4,000 now, but
they kind of blew it out of the water.
So,
>> yeah. No, that's fine. I'm actually
happy for you. I want you to get a great
deal. So, I'll give you a call back.
Okay.
>> Okay. Sounds good. Give me a call back.
>> Yep. All right.
>> Bye. This is why like it can backfire
about competition. Like, I want to hear
the last one. So, now if he actually
wants to beat this deal, he has to get
4852 off, right? So, if he would have
got 4K off, his deal would have been
done. I would have told my client, it's
a great deal. I would have meant it.
This deal is incredible. I mean, I I
don't think I've ever seen a deal for 5K
off. I'm going to let the client know.
We're testing this dealership and then
obviously it's my job to make sure I
give options to my clients, but this
dealership said they'd beat any offer.
He felt confident of that. When I asked
for 4K, his manager said no and said,
"If you can find 4K, maybe I'd do it."
And now we got over 4K. So now we're
testing to see what he would do. They're
both not too far. Doing it as we speak.
Beating it. Okay. Okay. Give me a call.
I'm waiting. Yes. Yes, it is. The
salesperson that's going to end up with
this deal has done a total 7 minutes on
the phone. That's it. Oh, wait. Guess
what? After my manager took a look at
it, he says, "You got the deal of the
day." He says, "You should take it." I
guess the owner doesn't have that deep
of pockets. So, if you guys don't know
who I am, right? A lot of people are
like, "Who is this? Who is this nerdy
little 5-year-old that's on the stream
telling people how to buy a car?" If you
guys don't know, my name's Tommy. I own
a company called Delivered. We negotiate
car deals for a living. My goal with all
this company is to save you time,
energy, and anxiety. We save you money,
but that's a byproduct of it all. You
can do this on your own. You don't have
to hire me to do this. You can literally
watch my tips, watch my videos, watch
these streams and learn how to do this.
I don't have a magic wand or a secret
sauce that saves you thousands of
dollars more than you can your own. I I
am very good at what I do. I know how to
have the conversations. I know the games
the dealerships play. And I'm just
willing to put up with a lot of the BS
because, you know, that's what we do.
The idea that you are working 45 hours
non-stop
and then the second I call it's like I'm
taking money. Like no. Like you there's
downtime in car sales. Let's just be
honest with people and be like yeah
there's downtime. And if I could say hey
you can get another five cars a month
and all you have to do is take these
spoons. So you don't think wasting their
time is valuable? What happens if you
get in an argument with some I'm trying
to buy a car? Man, this is where Zach
this is where you're like so determined
to like just hate me. It's not my fault
that the dealership didn't come to
terms. If the dealership said yes to my
deal in five minutes, the deal would be
done. If they say yes to my deal,
they're done in two seconds.
[Music]