You are the Toby guy. I know you are. He
charges 1,000 bucks.
>> He charges 1,000 bucks, but if he gives
me four grand off the car, you won't
give me anything off the car. It seems
like a win, right? I appreciate you
making it easy. This is great. I I might
be disappointed if I don't buy a car
from you cuz you've been straight
shooter. A lot of dealerships are crazy.
>> Yeah, know that's how I do business and
it uh makes my life a lot easier and I
sell more cars.
>> Bada boom, bada bing. If you're here
now, we're here to negotiate some car
deals. Enough. Enough with the yap. Time
to get back to the clap of negotiating
car deals. So, the first thing I want to
do is call on this Rav 4 Limited, baby.
Let's go. This particular client is
looking for a blue or a gray one.
Looking for a new one. And of course,
you got to go with the hybrid. This
client does live in the Northeast. Now,
it looks like there's a lot of these
cars here.
>> Hi there. Thank you for calling. This is
Owen speaking. Who do I have the
pleasure of talking to?
>> Hello, Owen. The pleasure is all mine.
My name is Tommy. Nice to meet you.
>> Nice to meet you, Tommy.
>> Hey, I just want to see if you guys have
a car available. Yeah. Tell me which one
you're looking for, Tommy.
>> Uh, I have the elastics of the van if
that helps.
>> Let me bring up my system here real
quick for you, Tommy, and I'll figure
out which one we're looking at. All
righty. And ready when you are, Tommy.
>> Uh, ready. Last six of the VIN is
091357.
He has said my name four times. That is
weird. He knows for sure.
>> Yes, I do have it. It is an allocation,
Tommy. So, we're I don't even have an
ETA on it yet. Give me one second.
Okay, there we go. So, it's expected to
be here anywhere between 10:31 2025 to
119 uh 2025. So, it will be coming and
it is available.
>> Awesome. Love it. Want more of it.
Already driven one. Been looking for it.
Really hoping that you can help me, you
know, put the dream in the driveway and,
you know, get a deal on this one if you
guys can and, you know, buy this one.
>> Yeah, absolutely. We try our best
always, Tommy. Now,
>> Parson can help you.
>> Uh, I was talking to somebody in sales
and then the phone just got put on hold
and now I'm here. So, I think I need to
go back to sales.
>> Oh, do you know who you're talking to?
>> I uh don't remember. I'm so sorry. It
was He was a nice guy.
>> Okay. Um
>> Owen, maybe. Owen.
>> Owen.
>> Owen. I think it was Owen. My brain says
Owen. We talking to anyone from Was it
at Nissan? Toyota.
>> Oh, it was Toyota. Toyota.
>> Okay, we're at Nissan right now. So,
>> oh my gosh, I got transferred to to the
moon.
>> Yeah. How am I going to transfer over
again? Let me see. Let me go and
transfer over to the cashier. I let her
know and then
>> Got it. Give me to the cashier and
she'll get me to the right direction.
>> Wait, she she's having lunch at the
moment. Uh, let me turn over to my my
sales manager. Okay.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> One second.
>> I can use
this is Tommy.
>> Hi there, Tommy. Sorry about that. A
call dropped.
>> Yeah, I I think you if you put me on
hold to the parts department. I don't
know if you like didn't like me or
>> Oh, no. No.
>> Parts. I was talking to somebody. I was
trying to figure out who you were.
>> No, no worries. No worries. I know.
That's what I was like, I need to get
the number back. But good, good. I got
you back here, Tommy. So, for this one,
like I said, you do have the option of
putting a deposit on it, but that's all
all depending on you if you want to
reserve it for you. Does it have does it
look like it have everything that you
were looking for?
>> It has everything I'm dreaming of. Uh I
just need to know I'm willing to put a
deposit on it. Bada boom. Um I just
really need to know what kind of numbers
you guys are going to be on it.
>> So right now MSRP 43499 Tommy that's
usually what we work off of. Well, not
usually most of the times. flop, you
know, can you go ahead and give me an
offer? If there's something out there
that you know that you're looking at
that's pretty close to this one, and if
we can maybe do something for you here
on our side, we'll go ahead and do it.
Tommy, are you looking at any other ones
beside ours?
>> Uh, I've looked at a few of them. Yeah.
Uh, I'll be I'll be honest. I have
looked at a few of them. Uh, you're just
uh looked out of state now. I'm looking
a little bit closer and um hoping that I
can get one more local to me than the
deals I found out of state.
>> Absolutely. That's what That's good.
Good that you called. We absolutely like
to sell for local people here as well.
And are you are you here from That phone
number is a little little unfamiliar.
>> I'm in Seattle.
>> Oh, over in Seattle.
>> Yeah, not too hot in a skip, you know.
>> Yeah, not too far. Yeah, we sell a lot
over there.
>> Yeah, cuz you make it easier than those
people in Seattle.
>> We usually can. I mean, the big benefit
with us is that you get a little bit
less charge on tax, you know, but
depending on which vehicles that you
see, right? Um, I could definitely get
you out the door number on that one
unless you want to try to go ahead and
make an offer and and I can see what I
can do for you, my friend.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I mean, yeah. So, so the
best deal that I've seen so far, um, is
$3,500 off is where I'm at on it.
>> It's $3,500 off,
>> correct?
>> All righty. H might be a at the end of
the day. I don't make that decision, but
looks a little steep. Let me see what I
can do. Tom, is this a good number to
call back?
>> Yep. Yep. You can call me back once, you
can call me back again.
>> All righty. Sweet. So, if I get to do
the $3,500, would that make you or
incentivize you to put a deposit on this
one?
>> Yeah. I mean, that that incentivize me
to put a deposit down. If you can get
$3,500 off, it won't even incentivize
me. It will 100% put a deposit down.
>> Okay, sounds good. Hey, Tommy, give me
about few minutes here. I'm going to
write everything up for you. talk to the
manager and give me about 5 10 minutes
and I'll give you this call back. Okay.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> Appreciate you, my friend. Talk to you
soon.
>> Bye.
>> No problem.
>> How many times did you say my name? Do
we have a number? So guys, so on this
deal, just so you guys know where I'm at
with this deal, right? And sometimes
everybody's different. Um, but I already
have I've already done all the work out
of state. I already know what kind of
deal I can get in state. So I'm just
going for that deal. I don't need to
play the back and forth game. I know
what's a fair market value on this deal.
go too high. We're going at 10% to go to
4,000, which would be incredible, right?
Like, I'd love it. Um, but the chances
of us getting that in Pacific Northwest
rather than just shutting down an offer
is slim to none. Uh, for people that are
wondering why we do this, so if you guys
don't know, my name's Tommy. I negotiate
car deals for a living. My goal is to
save you time, energy, and anxiety. We
save you money, but that's a byproduct.
The reason why we stream these and put
this all content out um is not only just
for us to do work, but also it teaches
you on how to do this and you get to see
our work ethic. You can say, "Oh, wow. I
would pay for that. That's an awesome
guy." You might say, "Tommy's so
unlikable. I would want to punch him in
the face." That's cool, too. I don't
mind. Whatever it is, you you would hire
us. We charge a flat fee of a,000 bucks.
We save you time, energy, anxiety. We do
175 to 215 deals on a monthly basis. We
have a waiting list for the service. We
Sorry, we have a waiting list for free
consults.
This is James, sales department. How can
I assist you?
>> I am I'm sorry you're so quiet. You're
like you're like a million miles away
from the phone.
>> I said this is James.
>> Okay. Thank you. Hey, I I just want to
see if you guys have a car available.
>> Yeah. Um what car are you looking for?
>> Uh I have the last six of the VIN if
that helps you.
>> Okay. Uh give me one second. Yeah, I'm
ready for you.
>> It's U is in uranium, 43 K is in
Kangaroo. 559.
>> Okay. the RAV 4 Hybrid Limited.
>> That's it.
>> So, this Rav 4 Hybrid Limited has
already been pre-sold to a customer, but
it's still um a couple months away, like
two two months and 13 days. Were you
looking specifically for that RAV 4
hybrid with the same color and spec and
everything like that?
>> I'm looking for gray, red, or blue.
>> Gray, red, or blue. Got to be a limited.
And are you uh what's like the time
frame that you kind of need this car
around?
>> I mean, I'm willing to put a deposit on
an allocation if that's what you're
asking. Yeah. You said, "Yeah, you
>> Yeah. Yeah. I totally I totally put a
deposit down on allocation."
>> There's a black one that's incoming. I
can send you a spec sheet of this one.
You kind of want every single thing on
there. How about
>> Yeah. I mean I mean ideally I mean as
much I mean I'm okay if it doesn't have
the tech package. If you have one
without the tech, it's not needed, but
it's appreciated. Um but we're looking
for gray, blue, or red. That's the
priority.
>> Okay. And Matthew. And your name is
Matthew? No, my name is Tommy.
>> Yes, Tommy.
>> You sound very familiar, Tommy.
>> Okay. Yeah. I mean, I don't know. Should
I sound familiar?
>> I don't know. There's like this guy that
I was watching like three days ago. I
was just going on TikTok or whatnot. He
does like um what is it? He buys cars
for customers or whatnot. I don't know
if that sounds familiar.
>> Oh, that's cool. Maybe I should call
him. Maybe it be easier than buying
cars.
>> Maybe. Maybe. Yeah, you got the same
cadence in your uh the way you speak.
Maybe.
>> I have to look him up. What's his name?
Uh, I think his name is Tommy.
>> Dude, no way.
>> Tommy or Toby? I don't know.
>> Toby. Oh, it's probably Toby.
>> Toby.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, I think I'm looking him up. Devered,
>> I think. So, it's he's late on TikTok
and he like buys cars for customers like
across the whole um uh United States and
then tries to get like a really good
deal for them.
>> Probably save me a lot of time, energy,
and anxiety from me myself. Huh.
>> But I think you got to pay him a little
bit. I'm not sure.
>> Oh, you got to pay him too. That's what
they're always trying to take.
>> Yeah. I don't know. So, there is
>> He's a good looking guy.
>> You You saw Does he have glasses on?
>> He does have glasses on. Yeah. He's
standing in front of a Harry Potter
sign. Kind of a nerd, I imagine.
>> Oh my god. Okay. Um let's get back to
the RAV 4 Limited.
>> Oh, yeah. Let's get back to the RA 4.
>> We do uh we do have a RAV 4 hybrid
limited available. Um it's same time
frame. Uh supposed to be here around uh
let me grab that number. anywhere from
November 19th to December 21st. And it
is in that um blueprint color with the
black soft text interior. And it's got
all your bells and whistles in here.
>> Okay. Um Okay. I mean, you said it's
blue.
>> Yeah. Is that something of interest to
you?
>> Yeah. Yeah, it's interesting. I'm
noticing this guy's negotiating the same
car I am, so I'm looking to see what
kind of discount he asked you for. M.
So, usually on like an A like an F or A
status ones, these vehicles aren't
currently on the ground right now. Um,
how dealerships work, especially like
ours is especially on these RAV 4
hybrids, um, there's not a big inventory
of them currently right now, especially
the limited. So, when you're talking
about discounts, uh, there's not really
too much of a discounts that we can help
you on. Plus, this car is currently not
here yet.
>> Oh, well, he he just I'm looking at the
notes on the the the comment. He just
said he got $4,000 off this one.
>> Oh wow.
>> Do I Toby? Tommy
>> the Toby guy. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Um usually I can give you if
you're interested in stock unit one, I
can get you somewhere around that price
range.
>> Do you got one in stock?
>> No, it's just we have a lot of RAV 4
hybrid XLEs. Like the XLE premiums, the
limited
>> XLE premium with all the packages and
blue gray.
>> No, that's where I was going. like those
those ones sell out super fast just
because they got the leather uh seats
interior and then you can upgrade them
to the JBL sound system with a bigger
infotainment screen up here in the
Pacific Northwest. Those specs are
really popular with our customers. So,
>> well, if this if this Toby guy can get
it, I feel like I should be able to get
that deal, too.
>> You don't understand. This car is not
currently on our inventory. It's like
this guy just did one. It was last week
he posted the video. He must have got
that soon.
>> Are you him? Like I might be
>> I'm just looking at this video guy you
told me. I don't know. No, I'm not him.
I don't Do you think I'm on TikTok,
dude?
>> Yeah.
>> I'm too nervous to be on TikTok. You're
scary out there.
>> Well, that's that's just the way it is
right now. Um so right now it's if
you're interested in the limited one, we
got that one. The XLE, it's the same
story. We still have to wait on these
vehicles to arrive. I don't currently
have any in like F status, which is um
on a delivery truck or on the railway to
us, but yeah, like reservations on them.
>> Yeah, we have some in a status, but
those are going to take about a month
and a half to two months to get to us.
>> Okay. Well, I mean, you know, I'm like I
said, I'm in Seattle, so I'd love to buy
a car from you, but you know, I guess if
I can't get four grand off, I mean, why
not just pay this other guy whatever his
fee is and he can give me four grand off
and then I don't do any of this. It
seems like a better idea. I mean I
>> Why are you going to give me a pay the
guy?
>> I mean I would love to earn your
business is the thing. But it's just
like on these vehicles like we don't
really have much leverage as of right
now. It's like like I told you the car's
not here. I can't really do too much
about it. I mean I can bring it up to my
sales manager. Um but he's going to tell
me the same old story.
>> Look at his website. He does free
consults, too. Maybe I could go talk to
him and ask him.
>> I mean I can transfer over to him.
Usually when it comes to pricing and
everything like that, I'm not
>> No, I meant I meant the the Toby guy.
This Toby guy.
>> Oh, you are you are the Toby guy. I know
you are.
>> No, not Toby. My name is not Toby.
>> Oh, same thing.
>> It's not the same thing, but yeah, he
does free consults. $1,000 for me to him
handle all of it. And he gave me four
grand off this car. That seems
incredible, man.
>> He charges a,000 bucks.
>> He charges a,000 bucks. But if he gives
me four grand off the car, you won't
give me anything off the car. It seems
like a win, right?
>> Yeah. Yes, it does seem like a win, but
those are like hard. I mean, just to get
it's a RA four hybrid. Like, if you I
mean,
>> this would turn the market.
>> Maybe May I send this footage?
>> I mean, if you're interested in used
one, we got great discounts on those,
too.
>> Nah, I I want I want a new car, not a
used car.
>> Okay. There's not much I can jeez.
You're You're a hard customer. I mean,
there's a
>> Whoa, I'm a hard customer. Jeez,
>> you're not. But I just don't have the
car that's on inventory for you to give
you a $4,000 discount like that.
>> This Toby guy even said slimy car
salesman tells you you're going to be
difficult. I'm just kidding. He didn't
say that.
>> Trust me, I've I've only been in the
business for about five and a half
months. So, I just got on the floor
three months ago. But
>> dude, yes,
>> you should do some work with Toby. I bet
he'll give you some good deals.
>> I don't need to buy a car, Tom. I mean,
we got great deals on RAV 4 hybrid XLEs.
That's like what we have right now,
>> but not not XLE premiums or limiteds.
>> There's Nav and XLE premium that we can
Well, there's a couple in a status, but
those, like I said, those are just like
the Rav 4 hybrid limited.
>> And you can't you just got to tell me
any deals on those?
>> They're in a status. So, there's, like I
said, they're about a month and a half
to two months away. So, if you want to
if you want to wait for them to hit our
inventory and sit for a couple days
because the dealership does pay interest
on these vehicles that do sit for a
little bit. Um, that's what drives us to
discount these cars is I mean that's
also another route you can take. But at
that point, it's just going to be a
gamble if you can get the car or not.
>> Yeah, but why not just give me the deal
on it before all that happens? Then you
get a customer locked in. I pay a
deposit.
>> Well, Tom, if so, Tom, we're we're a
business. Okay. And then these RAV 4
hybrids, limited especially or actually
premiums, they don't sit on inventory
for long. Um, if you just take a look at
the market, you know, we can from my
manager perspective and what you know
they see is they could probably sell
this car for MSRP and just be done with
that instead of trying to discount the
car and just trying to get a deal out.
But if it's at the end of the month or
something like that, it's a little bit
of a different story. If the vehicle
staying, we need to get a unit out.
>> I get it. I I understand. I'm just
saying I could I could I want to help Or
I could call Toby, you know.
>> I mean, yeah, I want to help you out,
but there's nothing like that I can do
right now.
>> Well, I mean, you could just you could
just be like, "Hey, I'm talking to this
guy. He knows this Tik Tok guy he's
going to hire and he's going to save
him. He's local. Just give him like four
grand off. Bada boom, bada bing, you
know, and you know, we have
>> Salem is not local. Salem is not local.
Seattle's not local dealership.
>> I mean, Seattle's
>> Well, we're we're up north. We're up
north. So, um, we're with like
>> all up north. We're all in we're we're
as north as we're going to we're not
Canadians yet.
>> You make a very good point. But yes, I
mean like talking like locally for
dealership wise it's like you know if
you can find a deal in Seattle as much
as I want to earn your business then
Seattle they're a one price store. So
>> I'm just a bunch of dealerships in this
Seattle area. There's Kirk.
>> No there is there is
>> there's a million. I want to buy it from
you though. I want to buy it from you.
You told me about this Toby guy.
>> I know Tom. I want I want to sell you
cars. That's like my frustration. I want
to sell you a car. I mean, I be happy to
sell you car.
>> You want to sell one? I want to buy one.
Let's just do it. Let's just get your
manager involved and let's just put a
metal. It's just metal. It's just metal.
>> How about I send you over to Jack? He's
my uncle. Um he's one of the desk
managers over here. You can have
>> your uncle. Dude, am I about to get into
a gang here? Like I think you talk to my
uncle. You know,
>> this dealership is familyowned. So, you
know, there's a lot of family that's
within this dealership. We try to help
out the community. If you want me to
talk if you want me to talk to Uncle
Jack, I'll talk to Uncle Jack.
>> Yes. All right. I'll transfer you to him
and then um we'll go from there. Okay.
If things work out, then we'll proceed.
Okay.
>> Sounds good. Let me let me talk to Uncle
Jack.
>> All right. All right.
>> A few moments later.
>> This Jack's account. Can I help you?
>> Hey, Uncle Jack. I made an offer that
you couldn't refuse and he refused it.
So, here I am.
>> Which one is that?
>> A RAF 4 Limited. You guys have an
allocation status. Apparently, we're
talking about family discounts cuz your
uncle Jack and your nephew was giving me
a hard time cuz he said he said he said
that the deals there's no deals to be
had on these cars.
>> Do you know which one refer it is?
>> It was I had a stock number. It was the
blue one. I think limited.
>> Is it gas or hybrid?
>> Hybrid.
>> Okay. Hold on a second.
>> No, you're good. Take your time. Sorry.
>> Blueprint limited one. Okay. It's an uh
allocations. I believe it's a blueprint
with a black interior.
>> Yeah, that's it. And we have it for
let's see the MSRP is 4689 and then
we're advertising it for 50,85 with
action package on there.
>> Oh, you guys have even more than MSRP.
He didn't even tell me that. He said you
guys are above. You guys said you had
MSRP.
>> Yeah, what we do is we we we do all that
stuff on there just you know see if the
customer wants it the protection but you
just recommend it. It's not like uh you
have to get it.
>> Okay.
>> So we recommend that. So it's 4689. So
what's the So what's going on anyways? I
was trying I was trying to get a deal on
one. He was telling me about this Toby
guy online that does negotiations and he
gets four grand off of them. So I wanted
to get four grand off of one.
>> Yeah. On the hybrid we don't we don't
really discount cuz our invoices on this
car is 4 to4,000 89. So we literally
have $2,000 markup on this car. So it's
selling you the car. We're actually
going to lose money on this car for
$4,000 discount.
>> So what can you do?
>> I typically just MSRP on these cars.
>> Okay. Well, I I've seen some deals at
other dealerships for about 3,500 off is
where I've been seeing it
>> for hybrid limited.
>> Hybrid limited. So, I'm trying to buy
from my local dealerships around that
same deal. And that's why he told me to
talk to Uncle Jack.
>> Let me see what I could do to help you
out. Well, it's typically um I usually
do like a normally I negotiate, you
know, not I don't like to do over the
phone, but um since you're on the phone,
I'll see if I could help you out with
that. Since you said my nephew was
friends and family,
>> I won't be mean. I'll be super nice. And
this vehicle, let me see when when this
vehicle is coming in. This will be here
probably like in the right before the
Christmas. It seems like the dates going
to be on this one should be here around
December 20th plus or minus few days.
Are you okay with that?
>> Yeah, totally fine.
>> Okay. So, what I could do is uh let me
see. How about if I just 500 over our
invoice?
>> So, that would be
>> 445.
>> So, it's like what? 2 grand off.
>> So, I'll give you about $1,500 off on
this car.
>> I've just seen all these deals for 3,500
off, but are just like
>> Yeah. Unfortunately. Yeah, I mean I
won't able to do that for you, sir. On
on a gas one though, however, cuz um
gas, you know, I have some in stock. I
might able to do a little bit better
than that. But up front with you, $4,000
is a little bit too hard for us to do
that.
>> I appreciate you trying. I mean, like I
said, I'm uh I said, I do have an offer
for $3,500 off already. So, doesn't make
>> But you have any trade or anything like
that?
>> I I might trade in, but I I was, you
know, I also was thinking about keeping
the second car or, you know, it's
nothing crazy. So,
>> Okay. How about financing? Are you
financing it? Yeah, I'm finance.
>> Okay. Well, what kind of budget are you
looking for on a monthly payment? How
how much down? Maybe I could help you
with that.
>> I can pay for the cash.
>> I can finance if I want, but I can pay
cash. That's like the payment's not
important. Um
>> Okay.
>> You know, we're just we have the payment
obviously as a payment thing, but if we
want, we can pay cash. So, more focused
on, you know, the price of the car and
what kind of deal we can get there.
>> Well, how about this? So, I want you to
stop by my dealership and I would give
you my number and um maybe we could hash
a little bit better, but I usually don't
like to do like a negotiation over the
phone like that, but I would like to see
you and come and see me and maybe drive
the car here.
>> Well, the car is not going to be there
till Christmas,
>> right? No, I'm talking about we have
other cars that maybe like pre-owned
that is drive similar. They maybe drive
the car.
>> I already driven one. I already know I
love it. Like, so I've already driven
this car. It's great.
>> Okay.
>> It's really just coming down to me
finding a deal, putting deposit on them.
You know, I'm like I said, I understand
you don't like negotiating over the
phone. I get it. But um for me, I like
staying here. Nobody has them in
inventory anyway. The idea of me
stopping at every dealership to go
through the rick and roll doesn't make
sense when I can be on the phone for 10
minutes and get some answers.
>> Totally understand. I I'll probably do
the same thing between your end too. So,
but unfortunately, I mean, like right
now, the car's invoice is $44,89
and we're selling for $46.89. And I have
actually no problem selling this vehicle
for MSRP. I just did, matter of fact, I
just did one just now. But since you're
local and I want to own your business
and I would love to own your business.
So I don't know if you have time to stop
by chat, but that's best I could do and
I'll see if I can get you a little bit
better.
>> You're scaring me with a little chat
thing. It's like you I was told I was
going to talk to an uncle Jack and now
you want to have a little chat with me.
I feel like I'm about to like get taken
out in the alley about.
>> Well, I want to know who I'm going to
give you a big discount to.
>> Well, you g a big discount to Tommy.
>> Yeah. Unfortunately, I need you to come
in. Like I said, I would love to earn
your business, but I just don't like to
go back and forth like that. I'm I don't
>> I'll give you my number. You just give
me my number $1,500 off. You don't have
to go back and forth at all.
>> Yeah. Well, I'm giving you $1,500 off
and I need to be close to my number.
>> Yeah. I mean I mean it just doesn't make
sense. I have an offer for $3,500 off.
Why would I mean I appreciate it, right?
I appreciate you coming down some.
Right. You guys came from $50,000 down
to $1,500 below MSRP. I appreciate that,
but I have an offer for 3500. So, uh it
doesn't make sense for me to take that
deal. Just like it doesn't make sense
for you to, you know, maybe not sell the
car. Somebody's want to sell it for 35.
Why are they willing to do it? I don't
know. Somebody's want I hope we
understand that part, too. That's great.
>> Yeah, I'm not I'm not mad at you. I'm
not disappointed. I mean, you're trying
to take me out in the alley out back,
which I'm a little concerned about, but
>> No, we don't do that. We like to take
care of our customer here and we'll do
actually really good service and I was
hoping that you come by and maybe look
at our staff, you know, and look at me
and and I'll give you a good service on
it when you're here. You just don't
you're not helping yourself by just
saying, "I hope you can come look at me
and look at my staff and you'll change
you'll change your mind. I promise you."
Um, just a kneecap or two. You'll change
your mind. Uh, no. Uh, I appreciate
that, but Oh, no problem. I appreciate
you giving the good service, all the fun
stuff, but um, Uncle Jack, you scared me
a little bit, so I think I'm going to
have to pass.
>> Okay. Well, if you change your mind,
give me a call. Okay.
>> Okay. Sounds good, Uncle Jack. I
appreciate you.
>> All right. Thank you, sir. Have a nice
day. Bye.
>> So, so just so you guys know, just so
we're out on this car, we have a deal
for $3500 off out of state. That deal's
already locked up. that deals already.
Client has said, "Yep, I'll buy that
one." Bada boom, bada bing. Now, my job
here is not just to get the client the
first car that I find, but try to find
something local. So, we're going through
our options locally. We're trying to
find something that makes sense for
them. Seeing if we can get something a
little bit local to save them on the
shipping. If not, we have that deal for
$1,500 off, right? I'm making more phone
calls. I I have other cars I got to call
on, too. I do want to call in this Golf
R. I'm going to take a break from this
Volkswagen. I want to call in this Golf
R cuz I want to make this other
dealership regret not doing a deal with
me. And to be fair, they won't regret.
They'll be happy they didn't do a deal
because I need a I need a Golf R without
a Euros. We'll only take a black
edition. I want two grand, $2,500 off
MSRP is what I'm looking for. This is
how many cars they say there are. Look
how many Look how many dots, right? This
is the exact color. Everything I want.
Let's see how these dealerships react
when I say that I'm looking for a car.
Uh, we are looking. I mean, I could zoom
into the exact city. There's 7 million
of these things. So, my client lives in
New Jersey. So, New Jersey is the state
right here. There's none in New Jersey.
I'll give them Actually, there's no,
there's plenty in New Jersey. What are
we talking about? So, the one thing this
car cannot have is the Euro style pack.
They do not want the Euro style pack.
So, we've got to kind of go through
these a little bit and see, does it have
the Euro style pack? Now, you might say,
Tommy, what is the Euro style pack? I
want a Euro style pack. Essentially what
the Euro style pack is makes it it takes
away options. You know what? I just
think more dealerships need to have
window stickers of their cars. Like I
shouldn't have to like sort through this
to find all of the cars and like I have
to go through and like look through
their options and it's kind of silly.
>> Sales department. This is Travis.
>> Hey Travis, I just want to see if you
guys have a car available.
>> Yeah, which one?
>> I have I have the last six of the VIN.
There's a stock number, but it's blank.
So, I think I need to give you the last
six of the VIN.
>> Yeah, that that works.
>> Uh, it is 2-604.
>> 260104.
Do you know what it is?
>> It's a Golf R. Golf R.
>> Okay. Is it a new one?
>> It is new.
>> Okay. Is it 25 or 26?
>> 25.
>> Okay. So, that one actually is already
sold. It hasn't gotten here yet.
Customers plan to purchase it. You put a
deposit, all that stuff. Um it just been
delayed for like a couple weeks
ironically was showing up. So once the
car gets here, customer is planning on
buying the car. I mean assuming you know
do you want me to take your information?
Say if it were to fall through I can
give you a call. But as of now he the
customer we had that pre-sold.
>> No no I'll keep looking around. You know
that's my goal to try to find one. So
I'll keep looking around. But I
appreciate it.
>> Okay. Yeah. No problem. Thanks for the
call.
>> No problem. Bye. All right. Bye.
>> Thank you for calling.
This is Monica speaking. How can I help
you?
>> Hey Monica, are you in new car sales?
>> I'm in internet sales. How can I help
you?
>> Hey, I just first off want to see if you
guys have a car available.
>> Okay. Do you happen to have the stock
number?
>> I do. Uh stock number is S is in Subaru.
W as in winner. 254594.
>> Okay. Give me just a second and I'll
look this vehicle up for you.
>> Of course. Thank you.
>> You're welcome. And also, while I'm
looking this up, may I have your first
and last name, please?
>> First name Tommy, last name Makula.
>> Okay, so I have the 2025 Volkswagen Golf
R Black Edition, and the color is Lapis
Blue Metallic.
>> That's correct.
>> So, that vehicle is actually on hold and
is not available at this time.
>> H Well, that's a bummer.
>> It is. I'm so sorry about that.
>> No, no worries. I get it. Okay, I guess
I'll call somebody else.
>> Okay, but were you also interested in
the Golf GTI or just the Golf R?
>> Just the G. I couldn't be caught dead in
a GTI.
>> Okay, I get it. I completely understand.
>> Well, I wish you luck. I wish you luck
on your journey and if you ever want to
contact us again about the Golf R,
please make sure to do that. Okay.
>> Okay. Thank you so much.
>> You're welcome. Have a good day.
>> You too. Bye.
>> Goodbye.
>> Good afternoon. This is Bo. How can I
help you? Hey Bo, this is Tommy. How's
it going?
>> Good. Pretty good. Tommy,
>> hey, I just want to see if you guys have
a vehicle available.
>> Yeah, what are you looking for?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Pardon?
>> Oh, that absolutely does. Yeah, what's
the stock number?
>> Yeah, it's 211072.
>> Um, you know what? Can I take your
number and give you a call back? I might
need I might I need to mess around the
computer for a couple minutes to find
this thing.
>> Sure. Yeah, you can get my number.
That's fine.
>> Sure. It's Tommy. I'll call right back.
All right. Awesome. Thank you.
>> Thanks. Bye.
>> Bye.
Good afternoon. John speaking. How can I
help you?
>> Hey, John. This is Tommy. I just want to
see if you guys have a a vehicle
available.
>> Sure. What are you looking for, sir?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Sorry. Could you repeat that, sir?
>> Oh, yeah. Go ahead, sir.
>> Uh, as V is in Volkswagen, W is in
wagon.
>> 2550492.
>> If I could put you briefly on hold for a
few minutes. Let me check on that for
you, sir.
>> Sure. Take all the time.
>> Okay. Thank you.
[Music]
sir, you still there?
>> I'm still here.
>> Yeah, very good, sir. Uh, yes, it is
available.
>> Awesome. Awesome. Love it. Want more of
it. Uh, really just trying to get some
pricing on it. Hope you help me out.
>> Okay. Um, just if I could have your
name, sir, again, just real quick.
>> Tommy.
>> Tommy. And you were looking for pricing
on it as far as looking for financing,
leasing.
>> Uh open financing. I'm paying cash. Um
I'm not looking leasing.
>> Gotcha. And just give me a second here.
Can you give me just a minute, sir? And
I'm going to check with the uh my
managers about that. Just a sec.
>> Right. I'll wait.
>> Okay. Thank you, sir.
>> No problem.
[Music]
So, you're doing this here or is I
notice it's a North Carolina number?
>> Oh, no. Sorry. I I live in Jersey.
>> Jersey. Okay.
>> Jersey.
>> All right. Gotcha. So, we'd have you'd
be registering it in Jersey then?
>> Yeah, I would register in Jersey. Yeah.
I've heard good things about your deal.
>> Give me a sec. Oh, good. Good to hear.
Give me a few minutes, sir. I'm going to
have to give you a call back cuz I need
him to run stuff for Jersey structure
down there as far as the payments and
the cost and stuff like that. and I can
give you a call right back with uh all
the information. Is this the what's a
good number to reach you at?
>> If you need anything else. Um and it's
Tommy. Last name, sir?
>> Mula. M I K U L A.
>> Okay. Very good. Yeah. Give me just a
few minutes. I'll be right back in touch
with you with stuff.
>> All right. Sounds good.
>> All right. Thank you, sir. All right.
>> No problem. Bye.
>> Byebye.
>> Bo called me back. The color makes
>> good afternoon. This is Bo.
>> Hey, Bo. This is Tommy. Hey, how's it
going?
>> Hey, Tommy. Okay, so I find out. All
right, so we so I have good news and bad
news. So I we have one coming in, but
it's already sold, right? There is a
small chance that this deal could fall
through. Uh there is 2026 is coming in
at some point, but we don't have a date
on when that'll be. So what I can do is
I can keep your information here and I
can ask every day. So my sales manager
Sam is not in today. He's off on
Thursdays. I can ask him, you know, when
and where this 2025 will come in and if
there's a possibility that might be like
fall through for whatever reason. Uh,
and I can certainly call you first and
then I can give you an update when I
know when the 2026ers come in.
>> I appreciate it. I'm I'm I'm looking
like a hawk on these things. So, um, I'm
hoping that I can just get one on my own
and u I don't have to wait anybody else.
But I appreciate it.
>> Yeah, no doubt. So, I'll keep you
information and I'll I'll definitely
give you Buzz when I get some more
information, but it sounds like the one
that we haven't coming in is gone just
to be honest with you. But, if it falls
through for whatever reason, you're the
first guy we're going to call.
>> Okay, sounds good. I appreciate it.
>> You got it, man. Take care.
>> No problem. Bye. You're no AMG. Okay.
Mikey. Mikey.
>> Thank you for calling Volkswagen sales.
For service, press one. For sales, press
two for parts.
>> Thank you for calling Volkswagen sales.
For service, press one.
>> Thank you for calling. How can I help
you?
>> Hey, are you in new car sales?
>> I'm sorry.
>> Are you in new car sales? I'm sorry. I
was laughing.
>> Oh, am I in sales?
>> New car sales. Yeah, new car sales. Like
like you sell new cars.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Awesome. Perfect. You're I'm in the
right department. I just wanted to see
if you guys have a car available.
>> Uh which vehicle are you looking at?
>> I have a stock number if that will help.
>> Uh what uh vehicle is it?
>> It is a Volkswagen Golf R.
>> The blue one, the white one or the black
edition white one?
>> It is the Leis Blue.
>> I believe this one we still have, but
let me just double check. Yes, this uh
the blue one is still available.
>> It is available. I'm so sorry. Sorry. My
lovely lady just brought me food in
front of me. I apologize. Sorry. You
said it was available or wasn't
available. I'm so sorry. I just didn't
hear you.
>> It is available.
>> Awesome. Perfect. Well, I love it. Want
more of it. Um I've already driven one.
Just trying to get some pricing. Um I'm
hoping you can help me out.
>> Yeah. What What uh what exactly are you
looking for?
>> The pricing of the car.
>> Got you. So the MSRP is 48,836.
>> And that's what you guys are selling it
for. That's that. And then of course the
um the standard New York State taxes and
fees, the registration, license plate,
and all that jazz, which we'll go
>> all that jazz. Okay. Um I'm more of a
blues guy myself, but do you guys have
any add-ons, fees, anything crazy?
>> No, just the just the original stuff
that that goes on it.
>> Okay. So, no add-ons, no fees. Uh are
you guys willing to take offers on the
car?
>> Like what what what are you thinking?
You know, um, like I said, I've I've
seen a few of these. I've been doing a
lot of research, doing a lot of work on
this. Um, you know, I've seen about two
grand off is kind of the going rate on
one of these bad boys. So, like 46 836.
>> We could we could possibly try uh just
cuz we uh want to be transparent with
you. We have had some customers um want
a,000 off, but it's just really
difficult on our end to get that down.
But we can we can always try to um try
to put the price down. I'm not too sure
if we can do two. We might be able to do
one, but that's just like that's very
slight. How does that sound?
>> Well, I'd love to I'd love to get two. I
know I know you say it's hard, but in
theory, it's just hitting the the backst
base button on one button and then
putting instead of an eight, putting a
six there. So, difficulty difficulty
levels probably not too hard, but
obviously you guys have to justify that
doing those two clicks.
>> Are you around the area? Yeah. Like, are
you going to be able to come in um
sometime this week so we can figure out
what we can do for you?
>> Well, I'm I'm in Jersey, so you know,
I'm not too far, but uh you know, if we
can create a numbers, I'll put a deposit
on it and then come in tomorrow or
today. I guess you guys close soon, but
tomorrow.
>> So, you So, you want the you want to
figure out how much it'll be before
>> Yeah. I mean, I'm like I've already
driven one. I already know I want it.
I'm willing to put a deposit on it. I'm
I'm ready to go. Like, I'm just a You
say yes to two grand off. Here is the
credit card. Let's rock and roll. Right.
Like, that's that's where I'm at.
Gotcha. Okay, let me let me get in
contact with somebody to see what we can
do. Is it okay if I put you on a brief
hold?
>> Of course.
>> A few moments later.
>> Hello.
>> Hi, this is John from How you doing
today?
>> Hi, this is Tommy from my house. I'm
doing well.
>> How you doing, Tommy from your house?
What can I help you with?
>> Um, I was talking to somebody about this
Golf R, hoping that we can come to an
arrangement on a deal.
>> The uh the Liz Blue one, correct?
>> The Liz Blue.
>> Yes. Okay. And are you're in New Jersey,
you said he told me, right?
>> I am in Jersey. Correct.
>> Make sure the car is still available.
All right. And where were you looking to
be in terms of make a deal?
>> Sorry. Um I was trying to be at um right
around two grand off the car.
>> Yeah, it's We really don't discount
them. They usually go over sticker to be
completely upfront with you.
>> Oh, well, he said he probably could do
$1,000, no problem. So,
>> who told you that?
>> The the person I was just talking to.
>> Yeah. No, we don't. They're not sales
people. Uh they kind of just deal with
the phone things. But yeah, we don't we
don't really discount VR. Again, they
really go over sticker most of the time.
>> Sorry, I didn't talk to a sales person.
I want to ask for sales. That's weird.
>> They they go to like a phone like a uh
phone sales, but they don't really deal
with like the numbers part of it. So,
you know, they don't know our programs
and what's we're exactly doing on the
floor and things like that. But yeah,
the R isn't really a part that we
discount.
>> So, you guys don't go and you guys are
normally over sticker.
>> Yeah, they usually sit around 3 to 5,000
over sticker depending on market at the
time, things like that. Okay. Um, yeah.
I mean, I was definitely hoping to get a
little bit better deal than MSRP.
>> Yeah. No, I'm sorry. They really I have
yet to see one. I've been here three
years. I've yet to see one even go any
go at MSRP.
>> Oh, okay. But you're willing to sell
this one at MSRP?
>> No, this this one again would be a few
thousand over sticker like the rest of
them.
>> Okay. So, what what is
>> Especially because there's very few of
these. I mean, I try to get you around
like 53,000 52,000 something in that
realm. So you'd be up 52 53,000.
Um and you go sticker. I mean sticker is
not I've called a few dealerships.
Plenty of people are sticker.
>> Um yeah
>> on a l blue one because I know there's
not a lot of these out there.
>> Yeah. I mean it's just a color though.
It's not like a rare color. It's not an
exclusive color. There's about 30 30%
like it's an equal more.
>> It is. But they they didn't make that
many of the Liz blue ones so far yet. So
that's kind of on Volkswagen, but most
people have the white, some will have
the black, but the OP's blue is not
super common right now. So that's just
what market um the market is showing
that there's 25 black ones and 21 white
ones on the market. So blue is the most
color currently available in new car
sales.
>> Internally, I'm seeing 30 white, 26
black, 19 blue.
>> Even with those numbers, you're you're
almost break even.
>> Yeah, but I but again, it's
>> not like there's like five blue ones and
48 white ones. There's 10 more white
ones and red ones.
>> Again, if the blue one is the ones that
people are paying more for, we're going
to ask, you know, more than sticker for
them. That's kind of just where they
sit. I'd be happy to kind of work with
you a little bit. That's no problem. But
a car that
>> Yeah. I mean, I'm all for want to work
on it. Just doesn't make sense. You said
they didn't make as many blue ones and
there's less blue ones available. All of
that adds up. It doesn't mean like
they're selling more, right? There's
only 19 left on the market and there's
30 white ones. They made more white
ones. It means they're selling about the
same rate. No, they I'm saying they make
the same amount, but if the blue ones
are selling more, then there's just a
higher market, you know, want for that
car, then that's what we're going to,
you know, we're going to ask based on
that.
>> Okay. So, if I get a white one, you'll
sell it to me below MSRP.
>> I'll go a little It's again, it's still
going to be over sticker, but it's not
going to be, you know, it's not going to
be as desirable as a blue one. So, maybe
I can work with you a little more on
that cuz I right now I have two white
ones.
>> Okay. Well, I I have multiple
dealerships around you that are at MSRP
on just normal ones and blue ones and
that's not this. So,
>> I understand.
>> Yeah. So, yeah. I mean, I don't want to
waste your time,
>> but yeah, the idea of going to MSRP on a
Volkswagen seems insane.
>> I mean, it's like any other performance
car right now, you know, like a Honda
Civic Type R is going to be over MSRP.
>> A Civic Type R.
>> Yeah, you can make two arguments. What
happened?
>> But I'm also But but I'm also paying the
same price for a white one or a blue one
there. Like I don't have to pay a
inflated price for a different color.
>> It's just depending on again market on
them. You know, if anything changes with
those dealerships, they might be telling
you MSRP over the phone and you come in
and they're going to tell you it's not
MSRP. The dealerships that do stuff like
that, I'm just going to be completely
upfront with you.
>> Yeah. I mean, I'm looking to just get
numbers over the phone and then buy the
car. So, well, good news that won't
happen to me because I'm going to pay
for it over the phone.
>> Okay. So, yeah, whatever whatever works
for you, but uh yeah, unfortunately, we
are going to go over sticker for any
golf bar in general.
>> Okay. Yeah, I will pass on that. But I
appreciate it.
>> No problem. Thank you for calling.
>> No problem. Bye. So, just so we're
clear, I understand that the guy didn't
say I will do $1,000 off, but he said
typically we can do maybe $1,000 off. I
don't think we can do two. So, that's
why I said he thought he probably do 1K,
right?
>> This is Cararissa. How can I help you?
>> Hey, are you in new car sales?
>> I am. I'm the internet sales manager
here. What can I help you with?
>> Hey, I just want to see if you guys have
a car available.
>> Okay, I can check on that for you. Which
car is it? I have a stock number
whenever you're ready.
>> I'm ready.
>> Uh V is in Victor. Either I or one.
258173.
I think it's an I.
>> Yeah, it's an I. Let me look here.
258173.
Correct.
>> Correct.
>> Golf R.
>> That's it.
>> I'm showing it is here. What questions
can I help help you on for it?
>> Well, I already already know I want it.
Already driven one. Fell in love with
it. Really just trying to get some
pricing and if I agree to pricing, I'll
buy the car. Are you local to us here in
Indianapolis?
>> No, I'm in Jersey.
>> Jersey. Okay. I can tell you they
actually just took the markup off this
cart. Is it MSRP? Um, so that would be
the sales price on it and then we would
just have to calculate the taxes for
you. Is it something you would be able
to come here to pick up and do paperwork
on should you decide to move forward on
it?
>> Yeah, I mean, if we agree to numbers,
then yeah, that's that that would be
fine. And so you guys took the markup
off. Um, I appreciate that. That's
awesome. Do you guys have any add-ons or
fees on there?
>> No, the only fees that we have are we
have a $250 uh dock fee and then it has
uh whatever titling fees are. I know for
the state of Indiana it's about $46 or
so. We'd have to look up and see what
the titling fees are for New Jersey
though if that's where you're going to
be titling it.
>> Okay. And you guys just throw the pulse
in for free then.
>> It's on there. Um I'd have to check the
pricing on that one. I'm not quite sure
exactly how much the pulse is.
>> Okay. Okay. So, the pulse would be
something. I just saw the stick around
there. So, figured that might be an
extra charge.
>> Correct. And I can get with my new car
manager to get the exact break um
pricing breakdown for you.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, that'd be
great. If you can give me the exact
pricing breakdown, that'd be awesome.
So, I know what I'm working with and we
can kind of go from there.
>> Okay. Are you just looking to pay cash
or is it something you would be
financing?
>> Yeah, I'm looking to pay cash. I'm open
to finance if that helps the deal out at
all. You know, obviously I'm looking for
the best deal on one of these and trying
to get one today or tomorrow. Hopefully
at least put a deposit on one and
obviously if I need to come in, we'll
make it work. But yeah.
>> Yeah. Unfortunately, we don't have any
type of electronic signing or anything.
So, we would have to do everything here,
but you can always ship it back or you
can drive it back as well. Um, what's a
good name and email for you?
>> My name's Tommy, last name Makula. But
can you just text me? I don't use email.
>> Yeah, I can text you. This number here.
>> Yeah, that'd be perfect.
That's it.
>> All right, Tommy, I'll get that for you
sent over. Okay.
>> Okay. Thank you so much.
>> You're welcome. Bye-bye.
>> Pulse. The reason why I caught the pulse
thing was if you saw on their car,
there's a little triangle that's
pictures. Um, and I know that's the
pulse sign. Basically, it's an add-on
that a lot of dealerships do. So, when
she said there's no add-ons like three
times, they paid to put the pulse on
there. So, I imagine that would cost
extra, and it does. So, that's why you
got to ask the questions. to know. My
goal is to find this car for my client.
My client again, we have deals on other
colors, right? I have $2,000 off on two
different colors. I just don't have the
blue.
>> This is Greg. I can help you.
>> Hey, Greg. This is Tommy. How's it
going?
>> Doing. How's it going, Tommy?
>> Hey, doing well. Doing well. I just want
to see if you guys have a car available.
>> I don't know. Let me transfer you over
to the manager.
>> Okay.
>> Are you looking for a dealer trade?
>> No, I'm looking to buy a car.
>> Oh, I am so sorry. I thought you were
asking about a car available for a
dealer trade. Yes.
>> No. No. I'm looking at just to buy one.
They'll buy, not trade.
>> Gotcha. No, I'll help you out.
>> Perfect.
>> And tell me, what's your last name?
>> Last name? Mula.
>> Bakula.
>> Makula. M I K U L A.
>> M I K U L A. Thank you. Again, my name's
Greg.
>> Y I'll never forget it. Uh stock number
V is in Volkswagen 25785.
>> That is the Golf R.
>> Golf R.
>> Yeah, that is sold.
>> It's sold. A bada. Boom. Bada. Not a
bang. Dang. Yeah, I know. They show up
on the they show up on the website right
before they roll in and just I want to
say got in yesterday or had the windows
tinted for the buyer and he is taking
delivery tomorrow afternoon.
>> Bummer. Okay, I will keep uh I will keep
uh looking around, but I appreciate your
time.
>> All right, I appreciate you. All right,
byebye.
>> All right, bye.
>> Jacob.
>> Hey, Jacob. I just want to see if you
have a car available.
>> Yeah, what car? I have a stock number if
that helps.
>> That helps a lot. What is that stock
number?
>> Uh it is V is in Volvo. W as in wagon.
1144.
>> The Oh, yeah. The Golf R. The the blue.
>> Yeah,
>> that is uh that is still available. I
just took it on a test drive the other
day.
>> Oh, awesome. Perfect. Do you know what
kind of pricing you guys are doing on
it?
>> As far as I know, the Golf Rs are going
at MSRP.
>> Okay. So, you guys don't have any
markup, no dealer ads, anything crazy.
Just MSRP. No, no markups, no dealer,
nothing like that. They're just MSRP.
>> Okay, awesome. Perfect. Um, just
curious, uh, are you guys willing to
take any offers on those?
>> Uh, below MSRP, I highly doubt it, but I
will, you know, I can see if I can swing
something.
>> Yeah, I was trying to be 2K off.
>> 2K off.
>> Super easy. Easy peasy. Learn squeezy.
>> Yeah. Yeah. If I get So, essentially,
this will help me a lot. I can give you
a straight up yes or no answer. So, I go
into my manager's office. I say, "Hey, I
got, you know, so and so here. Uh, you
want 2K off? Done deal right now."
>> Yep. Done deal right now.
>> Perfect. Let me get some information so
I can try that for you.
>> Okay.
>> I am uh, by the way, I'm rooting for
you. I don't I'm
>> appreciate you rooting for me.
Somebody's got to. My mom wasn't.
>> What's your uh, first and last name?
>> Uh, first name Tommy, last name Mula. M
I K U L.
>> Tommy. M I K U L A.
>> You got it.
>> Perfect. And then give me one second.
What is your zip code?
>> Oh, my zip code that I'd be registering
to her out.
>> All right. Uh, question for you. Is
there I assume there's no trade that
you're going to be doing on this?
>> No, no trade. Yeah, we're just adding
into this one here.
>> Perfect. And is this going to be a cash
deal? Financing?
>> Uh, I'm open to financing. Obviously, I
understand that helps you guys, but I
can get cash if I need to. Uh, but open
to cash, open to finance. I would say it
I would say the the financing will
definitely make it way more compelling
to take the 2K off. Um and also it makes
it a little bit easier for your end. So
I I I still have it all the time. If we
do the in-house financing um after like
2 or 3 months, depends who it's financed
through. Once they get the title, if you
want to just pay it off, there's no
penalty fees or anything like that. So
it's nice and easy. But but it enables
us to do all the uh uh titling and
licensing and everything so you don't
have to. I love it. Yeah, that's great.
I don't want to go there.
>> We also get that little bit of kickback,
so it makes the managers, you know, more
likely to take a little bit off.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I'm definitely down to do
that.
>> Assuming since I'm going to shoot this
uh proposal to him with financing, do
you want me to put anything down or no?
>> Um I mean, you can just put 510K down,
something like that.
>> Okay. Yeah, I will do that. Uh I will
let me shoot you a text message real
quick.
>> Sure. certainly got my number cuz in
here in a minute or two I'm going to
send you over the numbers, give you a
yes or no. It's nice and easy. Thank
you, by the way, for making this uh very
easy.
>> I appreciate you making it easy. This is
great. I might be disappointed if I
don't buy a car from you because you've
been straight shooter. A lot of
dealerships are crazy.
>> Yeah. Know, that's how I do business and
it uh makes my life a lot easier and I
sell more cars.
>> Hey man, that's it. There no no sense of
going back and forth. I like the the
question of what will make you say yes
and uh you know, I'm going to go ask
that question, you know. Um, that's
that's a good one.
>> Everybody did that. That would be I I
would never retire. I'll tell you that.
>> I love it. Good.
>> I got uh You should have just got my
text here in a second.
>> Just got it.
>> I'm going to go.
>> Yeah. I'll say yes. Just in case you
need Sometimes you need that. Okay.
Boom. Let's go ask him. Let's put it
together. I'll I'll wait by the phone.
>> All right. Sounds good. I'll be back in
a minute.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> Thank you.
>> Bye.
Somebody's calling me back. This is
Tommy.
>> Hey, it's Jake already. Well, I'm
guessing you got a yes and let's call it
a deal.
>> Uh, would you be able to finance with
just zero down? Make it easier.
>> Yeah, we can finance with zero down.
>> Then we've got a deal.
>> Okay, awesome. Just send that to me
right now. I'll get a deposit over and
let's do this all. We can do it all
remotely, right? No big deal there.
>> Yeah, I mean I could probably wrap this
up in the next I could pro I leave in
about two hours like we close down. I
could probably have it all finished on
my end uh well before that.
>> Okay. Yep. Awesome. Let's let's rock and
roll. Send me what you need from me and
uh I make sure I have the just so I feel
better. Make sure I have the numbers and
uh I'll send you whatever you need.
>> I am texting you. You should get it any
second. I'm texting you the link. Uh
fill that out. That's the the credit
application. Do you have a preference of
a bank that you'd want to send it to or
>> um no?
No preference on that side. So um
>> yeah, I'll just we'll just shoot for the
lowest APR we can get and uh I know
it'll only be for a few months, so it's
no problem.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Shoot. Obviously the
lower APR was the better, but yeah, if
you mind just sending me that just so I
have it in writing so I feel better
before I give you my social. Uh that'd
be great.
>> And then uh Yeah.
>> Yeah. And then could you send me a
picture of your driver's license? I'll
go print off numbers right now to show
you that you have it in writing, you
know, the 2000.
>> I appreciate that.
>> Off the MSRP and all that fun stuff. And
it won't have your APR on it yet cuz
just the general 9.99. Um,
>> if you send me your license, I should
have everything I need right now.
>> Okay, awesome. Perfect. Send that over.
I'm going to do that right now. We'll
I'll start getting working on this app.
>> All right. Thank you very much.
>> Hey, man. I appreciate you making it
easy.
>> Thank you. I'll talk to you here soon.
All right.
>> Hey, talk to you soon. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> Cool. Thanks, man. Um, I'll have a look
at that and if if you can send over once
you have the shipping and the the full
full numbers just to look at. But yeah,
>> awesome. Hey, thank you so much. I
appreciate you trusting us here and I'm
excited we got the color you wanted.
>> Thank you. And so just to confirm, it's
the non-year, right? It has the sunroof
and the the leather.
>> Correct. I sent I sent you over the uh
link if you want to look at it when
we're jump off the call.
>> Okay, cool. Cool. Thanks, man.
>> No problem. Bye. This is awesome. This
guy is great. Made it easy. And this is
why, you know, a lot of people, a lot of
car salesman say, "Dealing with Tommy is
the worst." Right? This person spent two
minutes on the phone with me the first
time, five minutes on me, so seven
minutes. He agreed to the deal. We
agreed to the deal. Now it's done.
client didn't have to make all the phone
calls dealing with the guy that said 5K
above MSRP. Nobody sells these below
sticker. That's crazy. That's insane.
Let's give a congratulations to our
client. Thank you guys. Seriously means
the world. I'm going to jump off. Uh you
guys have all been amazing. Uh peace
out. Bye-bye. Bye. Bye-bye.
[Music]