But if you're trying to buy a Raptor R
with the R ar arg maybe.
>> Sorry, but the user's mailbox can't
accept more messages.
>> All you got to do is pick up phone,
dude. I'm not going to I just muted him.
He sounds so high right now. We can all
agree.
>> Are you planning to put anybody down?
>> I'm sorry.
>> Bada bing, bada boom.
>> That's what my mom always said.
Jennifer, it's Tommy. How's it going?
>> Hello, Tommy. How are you?
>> Did you just pull out a British accent
all of a sudden? or dead.
>> I'm confused about it. My tools myself,
man.
>> Okay, let's do a raptor. He wants a moon
roof. He wants an 802A
package, which are going to pop up. Bray
in bed liner if possible. He wants a
black or shelter green. Let's talk about
the Raptor. If you guys don't know what
the Raptor is, uh there's multiple
different levels of a Raptor. There's a
Raptor and then there's a Raptor R and
then there's a Raptor 801 and a Raptor
802. Essentially, if you are trying to
buy anything but a Raptor R, you should
be able to get around $4,000 off of
MSRP. It's crazy cuz some dealerships
will say that you are 15 grand above
MSRP on this car or something crazy.
They're absurd. You don't do that. But
if you're trying to buy a Raptor R with
the R arg maybe that is above MSRP 10K
at least. So, we're doing a Raptor 802A.
So, the expected discount on this bad
boy is going to be about 4 to 5 grand.
>> Thank you for calling.
>> This is Mia. Can I help you find a car
or book a test drive?
>> Find a car.
>> Sure. What kind of car are you looking
for?
>> F150 Raptor.
>> Great choice. Could you tell me if
you're looking for a new or used F-150
Raptor?
>> New.
>> Awesome. Before we check availability,
could I get your first and last name,
please?
>> Tommy Mucula. Let me see what I can
find. We have a few new 2025 Ford F-150
Raptors available in colors like space
white metallic, agot black metallic, and
carbonized gray metallic. Would you like
to set up a test drive for one of these?
>> No.
>> No problem. When would you like to come
in for a test drive?
>> Never.
>> All right. Let me know if there's
anything else I can assist you with.
>> Pricing.
>> I'm not able to provide you with that
information, but a sales adviser can
help you with pricing. Would you like to
speak with someone from our team?
>> Yes.
>> Let me forward you to someone who can
help.
The person at extension 1 0 1 1 3 is
unavailable. Sorry, but the user's
mailbox can't accept more messages.
>> Honestly, guys, that was probably the
best car buying experience that I've
ever seen.
All you got to do is pick up the phone.
>> It's a great day. This is Terrence
Sales. I can assist you.
>> Hello, Terrence. This is Tommy from the
buying department. and I just wanted to
see if you have a car available.
>> Tommy, is that your name?
>> Yeah, my name is Tommy. Nice to meet
you.
>> Thank you for calling in. Do you have a
stock number associated with that?
>> Uh, you know what? Uh, let me see here.
Uh, I do. I I can give you a stock
number whenever you're ready.
>> Yes, sir. Give me a second. I want to
make sure. Thank you for calling in
first and foremost.
>> No, thank you for picking up. I
appreciate that.
>> Yeah, no worries. Stock number, sir.
>> Stock number S is in Sierra. F is in
Ford. B is in Bronco. 52247.
I also want to change my S to Shelby.
Let's go full. Gotcha.
>> The Ford fanboy there.
>> All right, Tom. Tom, is that the only
vehicle that you're interested in?
>> I'm open to another one similar to it,
but it would have to be in one or two
colors.
>> Okay, perfect. Uh, could I put you on a
brief hold just to check the
availability of this vehicle?
>> Of course, Derren. Hold away.
>> All right. Thank you. Yes, sir.
[Music]
>> Hey, that's copyrighted.
>> Tommy, thank you so much for holding,
sir. I just want to let you know that
that uh rap is available.
>> Awesome. You understand that your hold
music is a Rick Roll? Right. I don't
even know if I'm actually calling a
dealership right now. Is this all is it
all just just a is a is a meme? Is a
joke being made fun of? Am I on like
that one show Punked? Have you seen that
show Punked with Ashton Kutcher? Like is
there a secret cameras watching both of
us at all times? That'd be crazy. Uh
what are the chances? Okay. Hey. Uh
well, hey man, I've already driven this.
I already know I'm interested. Want it
out in Augusta. Looking for just a great
deal and you know, I heard good things
about your dealership. Is why I call?
Tommy, what's a good contact number,
sir?
Right. So, Tommy, this is what I'm going
to do for you. I'm glad you called in
about that particular vehicle. I am
going to text you my business card. And
if you could be so kind, Tommy, to text
me the address where you would title the
vehicle. Sure.
>> And I will give my manager, give you the
best price.
>> Do you mind if I just give you my zip
code though? Just privacy.
>> Yeah, that's fine.
>> Awesome. Text it away. Let's let's let's
buy a truck.
>> Okay, man. Sounds great. Sounds great.
>> I'll be texting shortly. And thank you.
Hopefully we'll put this thing together
for you. Appreciate you calling in, sir.
>> No problem. Bye.
>> Byebye.
>> That was crazy. He's a good guy. His
phone was insane. Their their dealership
phones are about a one on the scale of
efficient phones, but he was funny.
>> Hello to see.
How may I help you?
>> Hi. Uh, I'm sorry you're so quiet.
You're like the quietest person I've
ever met.
>> No, my fault.
>> Oh my god. There we go. I got you now.
You're loud and clear. I can hear you.
Uh, I just want to check to see if you
guys have a car available.
>> Yeah, I got you.
>> Nice. Okay. Uh, what makes the most
sense for you? Auto code VIN.
>> Stock number.
>> Stock number. Stock number. Stock
number. Stock number. You know what? I
don't even see a stock number on here.
Call me. Call me Willis. But I don't see
one. I don't think it exists.
>> Let's see. Let's see. What is it?
>> It is a Ford Raptor F-150.
>> What color is it?
>> Agitite blade black metallic.
>> What's the last for the VIN?
>> Last for the VIN is 5491.
>> All right. So, it's not this one.
>> You said it's not one.
Where does it say it's located at?
>> Ford South.
>> South. So, it says it's located in our
area.
>> I mean, I just clicked on our website.
Did I call the wrong one?
>> Nah, you're at the right one, but the
VIN number doesn't matches up to the one
that we have.
>> Let me make sure.
>> South.net.
>> Mhm.
>> Union plus city 2025 Ford F-150 Raptor.
Do you have like another Raptor? Maybe
this vin is tricking us or something.
>> Yeah. No, no, we have another We have a
couple black raptors. It's just the one
that you gave me with the vin doesn't
matches up. But we do have plenty black
raptors, but you're trying to get a
couple
>> black raptors. Okay. I'm just looking at
the one that doesn't actually exist.
Okay. Okay. Well, I'm interested in a
black raptor with the 802A package and
the moon roof.
>> 802A package. Let's see what package
this one is. 802A. Perfect. And it has a
moonroof.
>> Yes, it does. Has a twin panel moonroof.
>> Awesome. Well, I love it. Want more of
it. As long as it's the color I want,
then that's the car truck I'm looking
for. Really just trying to get some
pricing on it. Hoping you can help me
out.
>> Yeah, no problem. Um, this color is the
black is black.
>> Yeah, perfect. Yeah, black's the one I'm
looking for. So, we're we're on the same
page.
>> Perfect. Perfect.
>> If we agree numbers and everything, um,
when can we put you in this vehicle,
man?
>> I mean, I can come in today, tomorrow, 5
minutes. I mean, what if we numbers
immediately?
>> What's your first name?
>> My first name is Tommy.
>> Last name?
>> Makula. M I K U L A.
>> All right, perfect. What's a good uh zip
code for you?
>> Yeah. Yeah, the zip code. Sorry. Just
>> Are you going to be trading anything in?
>> Uh, nope. Not to trade anything in. Just
adding to the family
>> inventory. Yep. Yep. No problem.
>> It's for my 12-year-old. That's a joke.
That was a funsy
>> about
the best dad ever.
>> Yeah. I didn't even have a kid. And that
was the even funnier part.
>> I'll take it.
>> I don't even have a kid. All righty. Are
you planning to finance?
>> I'm open to finance if uh Yeah, the deal
makes sense. Dude, I'm not I just muted
him. He sounds so high right now. We can
all agree.
>> Are you planning to play anybody down?
I'm sorry.
>> So, are you planning to put any money
down?
>> Uh, you know, I'm open. 10, 15, 20
grand. Fine. I mean, I can pay cash,
too.
>> All right.
>> He is. This guy is blazed. I mean, like
high as a kite. It's not even 420 right
now.
>> Righty.
>> Smoked on his brake. He was smoking
literally right before he got the car.
>> Money on this vehicle. Are you military
first responder? Anything? College
graduate.
>> Okay. This actually is your address. Um,
street. You know what? I don't like to
give out my address to strangers, but
it's the zip codes. I mean, Gustoa just
if we grade ID, I'll give you I'll give
it to you. But
>> no, it's straight. We can leave it for
the zip code for now. Um, if you're a
greater numbers and all that stuff, I do
need that information. You know, just
take a photo of your ID or something.
>> I love it.
>> All righty, that's fine with me. Um, I'm
going work on it for you. Is there an
out the door you want to be at? Like,
you're not trying to spin over?
>> I'd love to be like, I don't know, like
five grand off the car plus tax license.
Seems great to me.
>> Okay. All right. All right, I'll give
you a call in a second. Okay, sounds
good for you. All right.
>> All right. Bye. Just for I guess just
for purposes of everything, I'm not
saying he was actually high or under
anything, but I'm saying his mannerisms
might want to increase his energy by
about 300%.
>> Thank you for choosing. This is
Jennifer. How can I help you?
>> Hey, Jennifer, this is Tommy. Can I
speak to somebody in new car sales?
>> Yeah, how can I help you?
>> Hey, awesome. I just want to first off
see if you guys have a car available.
>> Sure. and give you stock make stay stock
number make model VIN.
>> Give me one second here. Your day going
well so far?
>> It is going just the best day that I've
had in the last day.
>> Oh, in the last day. Oh,
>> 24hour recording. How about yourself?
>> Oh, you know, not bad. Not bad. All
right. What is the stock number?
>> Stock number is 1319.
>> A raptor. Let's see here. Big green.
>> The shelter green.
>> So pretty. This one I know I I know it's
on the way in. It might be spoken for.
One second.
>> You're good.
>> Give me one moment. I'm just going to
make sure someone cuz I know we were
just talking to someone else and I
thought they left a deposit, but let me
make sure. See if I actually have a
deposit for it. Okay. Can I
>> Is this a good number to call you back
on in case we get disconnected?
>> This is the best number.
>> Okay. One second. Okay.
[Music]
I'm getting a call from Terrence again.
One second again. Lol.
>> Much for holding. Uh, yes, this one is
still available. Were there any like
musthaves or features or anything you
were looking for?
>> This is it. This is the car. It's in the
driveway. I'm just hoping you can help
me with some pricing and we can bada
boom bada bing and buy a truck.
>> Bada bing, bada boom.
>> That's what my mom always said. Really?
>> No, she never once said that. That was a
lie.
>> Oh, okay. Well, I thought so. I could,
you know, I could tell from your tone.
Thought you were fibbing me. Um, let's
see here. So, yeah, I see our online
price. Give me one second.
>> You're good.
>> I'm trying to pull it up. What are you
driving now?
>> Uh, I drive another Ford, but not as
cool of a truck.
>> What kind of Ford?
>> Uh, just an F-150.
>> An F-150. Are you going to be selling it
or you're keeping? We're adding on to
your collection.
>> We're We're adding to the collection.
I'm trying to collect them all. That's
my goal. Like Pokmon.
>> Really? You have like 30 cars?
>> I have a holographic one already. So,
I'm really trying to get this raptor to
add to my collection.
>> Oh. Oh, okay. Okay. All right. Well,
usually, let me see. I know where you
have to Are you You want like your total
price out the door and everything?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I'm looking for just for the
best price on the car, obviously. Open
total out the door or I mean really just
a sales price. You don't have to add tax
in there if you don't really want, but
it's just a
>> Right. I wish. Right. Where are you
registering it?
>> Uh, in a so right on the border.
>> If you give me like your zip code that
we're registering, I'll be able to give
you the full breakdown.
>> I love it. Uh,
>> all right. Okay, Tommy, can I get all of
this and can I give you a call right
back? I just don't want you listening to
music for 20 minutes. It won't take
long.
>> Good idea. Give me a call back.
>> Okay. All right, Tommy. I will talk to
you in just a second.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> Okay. All right. Bye-bye.
>> Bye.
>> I'm going to call this dealership. Now,
this dealership I love cuz they say,
"Call for price." Terrence just texted
me saying he need my zip code. I gave
him my zip code. This dealership says,
"Call for price." And I love when
dealerships call for price cuz it means
it's such a great price.
>> Thank you for calling. If you know your
party's extension, you can dial it now.
Press one for sale.
>> One for sale.
>> Thanks for calling.
>> Hello. Can I speak to somebody in sales?
>> Have you already been speaking to
someone?
>> No, this is first time. First time
caller. Long time listener. Thank you.
The person at extension one one
is unavailable.
>> Hello extension 1111. Uh this is
actually extension or you can just call
me back. Hey. Uh I was just calling uh
cuz I was thinking of you. Not in any
weird way. I was really just trying to
buy a car. Uh and it's a call for price
and I love a good mystery. Um you know
me and my fiance like to go to mystery
dinners. So, you know, we're really
excited. As long as I am not the one
that, uh, you know, gets on alive
immediately, I'm excited. Uh, anyway,
uh, if you can give me a call back, you
have my number. Uh, don't use that
extension cuz that extension's fake. But
I appreciate you 1111. Have you in the
Squid Games? I bet you'd win. Thank you.
Have a good day.
>> Thank you for choosing the This is
Jennifer. How can I help you?
>> Jennifer, it's Tommy. How's it going?
>> Hello, Tommy. How are you?
>> Did you just pull out a British accent
all of a sudden?
>> I did. I'm not good at it, though. I
just sound like Jack the Ripper. An
Australian Jack the Ripper. I thought I
I just went to London recently and I I
thought I was back back there. It was
crazy,
>> right? Oh my gosh. So, I have all these
figures for you.
>> I got my pen and paper. Let's Let's rock
and roll.
>> All right. So, I'm making it very easy.
Lower than our online price. It's just
MSRP. I'm not doing any market
adjustment or anything like that. And
then we have our closing fee of $5.99.
Your state tax is atrocious. It's
6704.88.
And then the title registration fee
6250. So that brings your total to
102551 and 38.
>> Okay. So you guys are at MSRP.
That's what your website says. You said
you were doing better than website, but
you're saying it's
>> No, the website is 500 over.
>> Oh,
>> it says 95685 or I'm Yeah, that's 500.
500 over.
>> So I'm just MSRP.
>> Yeah, you're right. It does say $500
over. It didn't even say that. It just
said the deal. Yeah. Okay. Well, uh
Okay, awesome. Well, first off, I
appreciate you giving me the numbers.
That's great. I was hoping for a little
bit better of a deal than that. A little
bit of a bad view, Tommy. Come on.
>> I don't I don't have any accents to pull
out, but you know, I was I was You know,
I've heard there's a lot of inventory on
these bad boys all of a sudden, so
dealerships are just giving them away.
>> There's not You know that. That's You do
this for a living. You know that.
>> What do you mean I do this for a living?
>> You know, come on.
>> Okay. Well, well, now you know who I am.
But now, now you know that. Now I know
what I'm talking about. I do.
>> And you saved me. You said, "Oh, this is
mine. This is for me." No, this cuz we
have a few people looking at it. I mean,
and we have locators, too. So, I mean,
I'm trying to be as aggressive as I can
with just MSRP and no market adjustment.
>> I appreciate that, but I feel very
confident even close to you, I can get
about four grand off.
>> Four grand off?
>> Yeah, that's what I'm I'm normally four
to five grand off on these.
>> Okay. Yeah, I have I can't Yeah, I can't
do that.
>> I understand these Raptors are even
>> if it was something else. If it was
something else, but MSRP would be my
best.
>> No worries. I appreciate it. You were
You were fun at least to call cuz not
everybody is. So, uh I'll take that.
That's a win.
>> Okay. Well, if anything changes,
definitely let me know.
>> Okay, sounds good. Appreciate it,
Jennifer.
>> Mhm. Bye-bye.
>> All right. Bye.
>> Thank you for calling.
>> Director call.
>> Hello. Can I speak to new car Ford
sales?
>> One moment, please.
>> One moment.
>> Great day. How can I help you?
>> Hey, uh, my name's Tommy. I just want to
see if you guys have a car available.
>> Okay, sure. Uh, you got a stock number
handy?
>> I do. Whenever you're ready. Uh, it's F
is in Ferrari
2 or 5285.
>> Ready? And it's a 25 Raptor P37. That's
it.
>> Yep. Looks like it's available.
>> Awesome. Well, I've driven it already.
Know I want it. Want more of it. Really
just trying to get some pricing and I've
heard honestly there's nobody better to
call but the
>> Okay. Uh, have you worked with anybody
here previously?
>> No, I've just heard good things. You
guys have a good reputation.
>> Yeah, absolutely. I mean, we've been
around for a century plus. So, you'd
hear a few things. Awesome. All right.
Um, are you local to Savannah?
>> I mean, but honestly, I love Savannah.
There's some of the best food, some of
the best seafood in the in the country.
So, I'm always down to make a trip. If
you force me to come down, I'll do it.
>> Okay, sounds good. You said your name
was Tommy, right?
>> My name's Tommy.
>> Okay. And what's a good last name for
you?
>> A good one? Like, I'd really like to be
like Tommy John, Tommy Business, but the
the actual one is Makula. M I K U L A.
But a good one.
>> M I K U L.
>> And what's your zip code?
>> Uh zip code.
>> Ready? And then are you looking to just
purchase this outright by itself or do
you have a trade in?
>> I'm looking to just purchase it
outright.
>> Okay, sounds good. Um, I will go ahead
and get some numbers sent over your way.
And are you looking to finance or pay
cash? Not that it makes a difference in
the pricing. It's so I know what to send
you.
>> Open paying cash. Um, you know, I pay
cash, but open to finance, but just send
me the cash numbers. It's easier.
>> Okay, that works. Um, all right. I'll
make sure I get this sent over to you in
like the next 15 minutes. Is that okay
with you?
>> That works for me. I appreciate it.
>> Awesome. Thank you, man. Hey, I'll talk
to you soon. Okay.
>> Okay. Talk to you soon. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> Now, I want I want to get your guys'
thoughts. Over under, he knew who I was.
He either followed the process that I
want people to do to a T, even asking
for the zip code, or he knew who I was.
He knew. I don't know which one. I
wonder what I want to know in the
comments. What do you think? Does he
know who I was? Does he know who I is?
>> Thank you for calling.
>> One of our team members will be right
with you.
>> Connecting to an agent now.
>> Thank you for calling. This Lena, can I
help you?
>> Hi. Are you in new car sales?
>> I work in internet sales.
>> Is that is that is that question?
>> Yeah. My name's Tommy. Is that the right
department? I'm here for it.
>> Yes, sir. What you looking for, Mr.
Tommy?
>> Hey. Uh oh, you're being so proper. Uh,
I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Okay, I'm ready.
>> Stock number is 1 2 5 033 5T in tango.
>> That's going to be at my other store.
>> I was really hoping it was at your
store.
>> What kind of vehicle is it?
>> Uh, it is an F-150 Raptor four-wheel
drive
>> Raptor. Is it brand new?
>> It says new, so I'm trusting it's new.
All right. I can't get that pulled up,
so hold for one second, Mr. Tommy, and
I'm gonna get one of my salesman's on
the line for you. Okay,
>> sure, that's fine.
>> Thank you so much.
>> No problem. Thank you. Somebody said
Ford sent out an email. There's no way
that's actually true. Wouldn't that be
crazy? I muted. Just so you guys know,
when I talk to you guys, I'm
Hello. Hello. I had some really good
hold music and now nothing.
Oh, it's copyright. It's an A. I did ask
for it. I do feel like a Coco Melon
baby.
>> Mr. Tommy.
>> Yes.
>> Hello. Hey. How you doing, sir?
>> Hi. Oh my gosh. Are you Mr. Tommy, too?
>> No, sir. I'm not. My name is Dion.
>> Oh, Dion. Nice to meet you, man. Sorry.
Uh, okay. Awesome. Nice to meet you,
Dion. Uh, I'm hoping you can tell me if
this car is available.
>> Give me one second.
>> No, take all the time.
>> You got a stop number?
>> I do. Let me know when you're ready for
it.
>> What is it? It is one two five 033 five
T as in tango
>> 023
>> no one
>> two 023
>> 0335 T is in tango
>> that's a black
>> it is a black car
>> black
I'm looking at man raptor
>> that's it that's it that's the dream
that's the dream in the driveway
>> hold on hold one second sir okay
>> no you're good take your time oh you're
right in before says it's Sims music
that's 100% what that was Why? I
recognized it because my sisters used to
play Sims all the time. It's some Sims
music. I don't know. A lot of people
saying it's rude. I actually want to own
up to this one. Do you think that I was
rude on this one or do you think he was
rude? Like, am I crazy? I I know I cut
him off uh because I made the joke about
Tommy, but like I was a perception. I
thought it was a joke, but maybe he
didn't get the joke.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Awesome. Perfect. Well, I love it. Want
more of it. I'm super interested in it.
Uh really just trying to get some great
pricing and hoping you can help me out.
>> Quick question. Are you trading anything
or
>> No, I'm not trading anything. I'm just
adding to the family.
>> Adding to the family. That's what I'm
talking about, man. What's your phone
number?
>> Uh, my phone number.
>> What's your last name, sir?
>> My last name is Makula. M I K U L A.
>> And your zip code?
>> That's a Martinez.
>> A mucula.
>> Which one is it?
>> Wait, I'm sorry. It's Sorry, I can cut
off a little bit.
>> I was like, what?
>> Yeah, that's crazy. Yeah. No, just
Augusta. Good old Augusta. I know you
deliver anywhere in Georgia.
>> What street address you want to use?
Yeah. What street address do you want to
use? Oh. Uh, can I give you my street
address once we agree to the deal? I
just don't like to give it to strangers.
>> Yeah. Only reason only reason why we're
asking that because sometimes Fords does
like little special programs for people
that I just trying to get all the money
I can for you to help you out. So
sometimes Ford gives away certain money
certain
>> money. I don't think I get any.
>> Oh, you don't get any? Okay, that sounds
good. Give me less than 10 minutes. I'm
going to shoot you some numbers over.
Are you planning on putting 10, 15, or
20 grand down or no money down? I am
looking to put down I mean I'm looking
to pay cash if possible but if I finance
I'll put like 20 30,000 down.
>> Okay, that sounds good to me. Give me a
few minutes. I'm gonna shoot you over
with some numbers and we'll go from
there.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> All right, thank you sir.
>> Hey. No, thank you. Bye. True guys. Uh
if you guys don't know, my name's Tommy.
I negotiate car deals for a living. My
goal is to save you time, energy, and
anxiety. You you heard me not say money
there because I don't advertise this as
a money saving service because random
chatter is correct. You can do this on
your own. Very similar to you can cook
your own dinner. You don't have to go
out to eat on Saturday night, but you
probably do cuz you don't want to cook
dinner and buy the groceries and do the
research and watch the YouTube tutorial
on how to make something that they make
look so simple. But I'm telling you,
every single time I try to make the
banana bread, just doesn't come out the
same way. So, if you're like, "Hey, I
don't want to deal with that. I don't
want to make my own banana bread." Even
though that's one of the easiest
recipes, I digress. Links in the bio. I
charge a flat fee of a,000 bucks. It is
what it is. Timeline about 2 to 3 weeks.
>> I'm getting a phone call, so let's
answer. This is Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. Eli just Are you able to opt
in to texting so I can uh send you a
video? And
>> I can I can opt in. Here we go.
>> The number.
>> Boom. I opted in. I'm I'm in. I'm opted.
>> All right. Perfect. Perfect. Perfect.
So, that video should Let's see. It
doesn't say you're opt in on my side
yet.
>> Perfect. Great. I'm so excited.
>> Did you end up getting the text?
>> I did. I text I said yes.
>> I don't know. Maybe Maybe it's just
taking a little while long.
>> Yeah, I did say yes back. Maybe it's cuz
um I don't I don't know. I mean, I did I
did say yes. I promise.
>> All right, that's fine. What's your
email? Just in case it doesn't
>> I don't even I don't even use email. I
I'll text you my email. I'll do that.
But I don't use it. So if you email me,
I'll probably never check it ever again.
>> You're all good, man. All right. Yeah,
if you could text it to me, that'd be
great.
>> Yeah, I just texted called.
>> All right, perfect.
>> Thank you.
>> Yeah, no problem. Have a great day.
>> All right.
>> Uh this guy, this dealership is so
messed up. I said yes. I sent him my
email and they said, "Did you speak to
Dayon?" I'm like, "Yeah, that's the
person I'm responding back to."
>> Yes, sir. Mr. T.
>> Hey, I'm sorry. It looks like you're
calling me back on two different lines
here.
>> No, you're good, man.
>> Hey. Hey. So, I got your numbers here.
Uh, I'm going through them here. So,
MSRP is 95015. You're giving me a $215
discount to be at 93k. Uh, government
fee, dock fee plus a pro plus. What is
pro plus?
>> So, Ford is doing something now that if
something happens to your vehicle get
stolen or get misplaced or something
like that, they got some kind of program
or chip. Basically like a GPS type thing
that's involved into the price. is on
all cars now starting at 25 and it's
through Ford.
>> Okay. And that's a Ford.
>> It's sometime it's some kind of type of
some type of insurance they got going
on. Actually, I can take a picture and
send it to you all. So, it's called Hold
on. It'll be on your door when you
receive the vehicle. Let me see what
it's called.
>> Are they tracking me?
>> It's just a little tag. Sir,
>> hello. Yeah. Are they tracking?
>> It says on It says on the window I I was
asking the same thing. It says warning
bright line dealer advisor vehicle
traceable by law enforcement. Oh, so the
go the feds are going to be watching me.
The feds are watching me right now then.
>> Don't make me lie to you, Brett. I I'm
confused about it to myself, man. It's
on all the windows on your on every
vehicle. Every 25 vehicle that came in,
it's on all the windows.
>> Wow. Jeez. Okay.
>> I don't know if that's something you can
opt out of or something that you got to
opt into.
>> Well, I'll be honest. If I'm getting the
if I'm being tracked, I need a bigger
discount than that.
>> That's the government, not me.
Hey, I I understand that. But somebody's
got to pay and the government's shut
down right now, so it's it's you or
nobody. They can't afford to pay it.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, that was serious though. I really do
need a better discount than if you can
do that.
>> Hold on one second. Let me let me take a
look at something real quick.
>> A few moments later.
>> Hello.
>> Yes, sir. Talk to me. What you What you
talking What you saying now? You say you
need a bigger discount.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm I'm being
tracked. It's It's I'm looking for a
bigger discount than two grand off.
>> Another two grand off. Uh, you know, I'm
looking for another two grand off and no
tracking. Ideally,
>> I definitely cannot give you another two
grand off. Usually, we sell these
Raptors at stickers. You might get
roughly $1,000 off, but I went ahead and
g put my best foot forward. So, I gave
you my best number. Now, the 399
tracking thing that the Fords got going
on right now, that's probably going to
be through your Ford pass. You can turn
that. It's going to be optional to turn
it on and off. Once you log into your
Ford Pass, you going to have an option
of turning that stuff on and off. Opt
into, opt out. But I'm 496. I'm paying
for it, but it's $496. I know you said
it's 3.99, but you guys are charging me
$4.96 for it.
>> I knew I knew I'm not looking at the
paper. I don't have the paper in front
of me. I knew it was right around that
price point.
>> Okay. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, uh, yeah. Just
transparently, I've seen a few of these
out there. I know that that $4,000
number isn't crazy. I've I've seen
plenty of other people get it. Uh, I
know there's a lot of these Raptors that
all of a sudden kind of got released, so
it's not like they're impossible to get.
I get if you can't do it. I don't want
to, you know, I'm not gonna be or plead,
but uh I've seen a few dealerships that
are that are saying they can get pretty
darn close to that. So, I've told people
four grand is where I'm going to be at.
>> Four grand off.
>> Four grand off, no ad. And the
government gets all my data then watch
wherever I drive.
>> That's interesting.
>> I mean, they already listen to your
phone calls, you know. You heard all
that? They listen. They listen to
everything now. They can track me. It's
great.
>> That's very That's out of my hands.
Don't know where I can't track
you. I know that for a fact. I guess
it's supposedly for the customer.
supposedly is for the customer and also
when you report to the insurance that
you have, your insurance shouldn't be as
high also.
>> Yeah, but then they know if I'm speeding
>> that but that's what that's what being
said. I don't I don't know. You know,
everybody after if I speed with that
thing, then they're going to know I'm
speeding and my rates are going to go
right back up.
>> Realistic with me. Talk to me, man. What
we need to do to wrap this thing up,
man.
>> Dude, I'm I'm a straight shooter. I'm
straight shooter from day one. That's
what people like about me. $4,000 off is
where I need to be. No ads.
>> Let me take a look at Give me one.
>> Sure. I'll give you 10. He's probably
shocked because he hasn't heard anybody
say that the government shut down. So,
>> send me your driver license insurance,
sir. Wrap this thing up.
>> Send me Send me those numbers. Let's
rock and roll.
>> I'm sending to you as we speak.
>> Okay, perfect. I'll look at those over.
We'll get that sent over right now. Bada
boom, bada bing.
>> And and you guys will deliver it right
now.
>> You drive you drive a hard deal, man.
>> Wait, but you didn't take the pro pack
out. What are we saying? Is that no ad?
>> Say it again. Now,
>> you didn't take the pro pack out.
>> That's not I cannot control that, sir.
If I take it out for you, I have to take
it out for everybody that would have
sold a car to the whole year. I cannot
change I cannot change that.
>> We're so cold. I gave you the money. I
gave you the money.
>> I know, but I said 4K off, no ads.
>> 4K off, no ads.
>> I was ready to go. I was scared my
wallet. No ads. No Pro Plus.
>> So, basically So, basically, I
>> I'm not changing my mind. I I said that
that was the That was the offer I gave.
>> Hold on one sec. Let me go back and look
at my numbers again.
>> Okay. I did say that, right? Right. I
did say that. 4K no ads.
>> Sure. Hello.
>> Hello. Yep. Sorry,
>> Mr. Tom. You got any new numbers?
>> Uh, I haven't got them yet. Sorry, I
just looked away from um they're the
same numbers unless I'm crazy. Oh, okay.
Got it. Okay, cool. Yep. Rock and roll.
Uh, let me get off the phone. I'll send
this all over right now.
>> Send the application right this second.
Okay.
>> Yeah. Text it over to me right now.
>> Send it to you right this second.
>> Okay. Sound. Yep. Send that over to me
right now and I'll get me and my
business partner. We'll get this rock
and roll.
>> All right. Sounds good. Um, when do you
want this delivered? Today or tomorrow?
>> If you can do it today, let me let me
call my business partner right now and
uh we'll get the time that makes sense
and we'll get this all wrapping and
rolling.
>> All right. We'll figure it out.
>> Thank I appreciate you making it easy,
man. Thank you.
>> All right. Thank you.
>> Okay. Bye. Uh, boom. Got it. Done.
$4,500 off. Bada boom. Bada bing. All
you have to do is say the government's
tracking it. It's a strong offer. So,
and this is what happens, right? The
dealerships will go through and say the
deal is real unrealistic. Once they say
the deal is unrealistic, you hold firm.
You know, the offer we know we're giving
is fair. So, right now, I've texted to
my client. I call. So, a lot of people
don't know what's happening here, right?
So, I'm negotiating for somebody that
has paid me money. We do about 200ish
deals a month. Um, I have an entire
team. So, what will happen is we will
give this number to my client. He's
watching. We normally inform them. We'll
let them know anytime we're doing a deal
live that they know. We're going to give
that to him. he's going to give the
thumbs up. The other benefit to this
deal is that it's free shipping to his
house, so he doesn't ever have to leave
at all. It's very simple when you know
what a competitive offer is. I know
$4,000 on a 2025 is a really good deal
on this car. It's an aggressive deal on
this car. How our process works here at
Delivered is we go through and pull all
the data of every deal we negotiate. And
the requirement here at delivered is
every five deals we negotiate our client
or if a deal hasn't been negotiated in
30 days, we have to go through a full
audit of negotiating with 15 dealerships
to make sure we're still good on that
price. Right? So we we make sure that
market data is accurate because we go
through and we have a certain system in
our side to verify that that deal has
been verified as a good deal. But it's
every 15 days uh or every five deals we
go through. We do about 200 deals a
month. So the market uh so then we
connect the dealership and the client.
We say hey business partner business
partner now is getting a video from me
saying hey this is what's going on. He
also watched it live which is a win. So
we got a raptor done. Uh that's it. What
will happen now is they will schedule a
time to do paperwork. They'll let us
know what that is. I'll verify all the
paperwork. If he wants a warranty, I'll
negotiate warranty, maintenance, gap,
whatever he wants there. Uh he's he
doesn't probably need gap on this deal
for how he's paying. Bada boom, bada
bing. This has everything he wanted to.
So it's great.
[Music]