I don't expect to get $5,500 off an
all-wheel drive one. That'd be insert.
But 2 to3,000 I do expect to be able to
get off.
>> Good news is you're talking to a guy
that just missed a week. I just got
married. So, um, congratulations.
>> I literally just missed a week. This is
my Thank you, man. It's my first day
back.
>> Where are you located?
>> Uh, in Glenn Oaks, New York.
>> Where is that?
>> Not terribly far and it's kind of in the
middle of nowhere, but I can come to
your dealership. You're not that far. I
know a lot of dealerships going crazy on
them, so I'm not interested in paying
sticker. No, no big deal. If you guys
are at a sticker dealership and that's
where you guys are at, I know other
people will sell them for a discount, so
no big deal. Okay, so what we're going
to do is we're going to do a Camry XSE
all-wheel drive in the Northeast. Uh,
this person is looking for a premium
plus package, heavy metal with red
interior, but open to black. Uh, we've
been looking for this car. Allocation
just came out, so I'm hoping that gets
people a little bit more excited about
doing this Camry all-wheel drive deal.
Let's call this one right here.
>> Thank you for calling. This is Shelly.
>> Hey Shelly, are you a new car sales?
>> I am.
>> Awesome. Love it. Hey, I just want to
see if you guys have a car available.
>> Which vehicle?
>> I have the last six of the VIN if that
helps you.
>> Sure.
>> Um or or maybe I have the Sorry, you
guys have a whole different sometimes.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Last six of the VIN.
I'll just give you that is 541289.
>> Camry XSSE. Camry XSE with the cockpit
material or red interior.
>> All right, that one is on its way. It
should be here. It's in transit. Should
be here within the next 4 days.
>> Awesome. I'm so excited. I love it.
Awesome. So, really interested in it.
Just hoping to get some pricing and I
heard nobody's better to call but the
supertore.
>> Okay. Where are you calling from?
>> Uh, I'm calling from Queens.
>> What's your uh first name?
>> My first name is Tommy. Nice to meet
you. Yeah. And what's your last name,
Tommy?
>> Uh, Makula. M I K U L A.
>> Good email address for you.
>> I don't use email. Can you just text me?
Life's easier when I uh when I text.
>> Well, if I I will text you, but in order
to send you numbers, I have to get an
email address because it does not accept
it in our Toyota Smart Pass system.
>> Is there a way to send the numbers via
text message?
>> No, I can send it to you in the numbers,
but Toyota, we use Toyota Smart Pass and
it does not allow it with no email
address. I won't email you.
>> na na.com.
>> Nope. doesn't allow me to do that.
>> na1na.com.
>> No, I need
>> I really don't like my email. Like
that's just like if you text me, I'll
text you my email. It's just long and
obnoxious and I don't ever chat. I'll
never look at it.
>> Yeah, that's okay. Were you referred by
a customer?
>> Nope. I just heard good things about the
um supertore.
>> Oh, okay. I had a previous customer with
the same last name. That's why I asked.
>> Oh, wow. What are the Really?
>> Yeah.
>> Wow. Crazy. Makula. Wow. I don't even
know. Got some family in Pittsburgh, I
guess. But
>> no. Um they're in con lower Connecticut.
>> Oh, just must be happen chance.
>> What's your zip code?
>> My zip code that I'll be registering the
car is
>> Glen Oak.
>> Yes. Which basically Queens, but it say
Glenno. You get confused and then you
ask me where that is and then it's a
process.
>> So, did you see the um vehicle on our
website?
>> Yeah. Yeah, I saw it on your website.
Yeah. I'm looking for this exact model
and I saw it. I'm like, I got to call
you guys.
>> So, if you go on our website, so we
actually pay for a service through
Toyota called Toyota Smart Path. So, if
you look at this vehicle and you click
on vehicle maybe in transit, estimate
payments, it's going to give you the
exact and then you it's going to default
to a lease, but if you I don't know if
you're financing what you're doing. So,
if you click on finance and you don't
have to sign up for anything, is that
you'll get to pay?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I mean, I appreciate that.
I'd like to get something done in
writing. No, no offense. Uh I've I
trusted a dealership with this uh once
upon a time and uh they ended up having
a whole bunch of hidden fees that were
not on here when I tried to do the smart
path thing. So not a big fan of it. I
would prefer just the old fashion.
>> Yeah. 111. So this is exactly what I use
is Toyota Smart Path. So everything I'm
going to give you is everything.
>> So you guys don't have like a a sheet to
do. You guys just do it all.
>> We don't use No, we don't use like old
school floors square or anything like
that. We use Toyota Smart Pass. So it's
going to show you your taxes and fees,
price details. So, it's going to show
you the price, which is 4,2658.
>> Okay.
>> And then if you click on see price
details, it's going to give you the
special color, the premium plus package.
It's going to give you the smart path
price of 42658. It's going to show you
the breakdown of the tax and fees, which
you have a state tax of 1,738,
county tax, 1956. I don't know what SPDS
tax is. That's something you have in New
York. dock fee tell it's going to give
you everything completely broken down.
So that's what we pay for. We pay for
that service. We don't have any fees on
top of that.
>> Okay. And you guys don't you guys can't
do any better than the 42658.
>> Well, it looks like it is the one of two
excesses that we have. So if you know if
it came down to a couple hundred to make
a deal, absolutely. I don't know what
you're looking for in regards to
pricing, but we only have two all-wheel
drives and neither of them are here yet
out of the 26 Camry that we have.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I already have I
already have offers on frontwheel drive
options and they're really strong, which
is, you know, I'm considering taking,
but I really want an all-wheel drive,
so, you know, now I'm just doing my due
diligence to see, can I get a decent
deal on an all-wheel drive one? The
sticker wouldn't make sense. Um, so
>> there's a $4,000 price difference
between all-wheel drive and not
all-wheel drive. Between the all-wheel
drive and the front-wheel drive. So, we
don't have $4,000 in room on these
vehicles.
>> Yeah. We don't even have $4,000.
>> I have $5,500 off a all-wheel drive or
front-wheel drive one, right? Uh, but
I'm I'm not asking you to match the same
deal as a front-wheel drive one. That'd
be absurd. But, you know, if I can get a
competitive deal, that makes sense.
Maybe the extra few,000 then start to
add up. But, uh, you know, sticker
versus $50, $500 off. All-wheel drive is
not that important. Snow tires are
pretty advanced nowadays. So, that's why
I was calling you $5500 off
>> $5,500 on a frontwheel drive option.
>> Oh, okay. We honestly, I'm going to be
honest with you. We have this priced at
$2,000 over invoice what we own it for.
So, that's how much room we have. Can't
get you the $5,500 off.
>> Yeah. Oh, I'm not ask just just real
quick. I'm not asking for $5,500 off. I
I just to recap, I have $5,500 off on a
front-wheel drive one that's already
done. I'm not shopping for a frontwheel
drive anymore. I'm not going to beat
that deal. So, now I'm just trying to
get a few grand off an all-wheel drive
one to see, you know, if I can get $2 to
$3,000 off an all-wheel drive one. Now,
the price difference isn't too crazy,
right? The Delta is not insane. Um, but,
you know, if it's I don't expect to get
$5,500 off an all-wheel drive one.
That'd be insert. But 2 to3,000 I do
expect to be able to get off.
>> Yeah. I mean, I could give you $600 and
that would allow you to keep the
lifetime powertrain warranty that we
have, but with the shortage of inventory
and only having a couple right now.
>> What if I said no to the lifetime
powertrain warranty? I was I'm going to
risk it for a Toyota.
>> We honor that because that's what we I
mean, that's what we do. Still,
typically $500 off would be like the max
to earn somebody's business, but like I
said,
>> you can do $1,100 off without a power
train warranty. No, we don't even have
we don't we barely have that much profit
in in the vehicle and we're you know
having one within the next week. Not you
know and drying up like our local
inventory and stuff like that be very
hard.
>> So is it $500 off not $600 off? I'm just
>> I said I could do $600.
>> So 600 um 500 we're we're bypassing the
max. I like it. No, I said 500 is
typically, you know, the most that we
would do to earn somebody's business,
but make it down to an even 4258,
but before taxes and fees. But, okay,
>> you know,
>> I'm I appreciate I'm going to still make
a few more phone calls. Like I said, my
goal is to get $2 to $3,000 off. If I
can get that, I'll just buy an all-wheel
drive one. Otherwise, I'll buy the
front-wheel drive one. But, you know,
I'm I wrote this number down and, you
know, if it makes sense, then that's
great. I mean, I just said, you know,
obviously the frontwheel drive versus
allhe drive is important, but is it
thousands of dollars of important,
right?
>> Well, to, you know, when we're losing
money on it, then yeah, I mean, we don't
have 2,0002 to $3,000 in markup.
>> Well, I'm I'm not saying for you. Like,
obviously, as a business, you've got to
make decisions of what makes sense for
you to sell a car. I'm saying for me,
does it make sense for me to spend $4 to
$5,000 more on your car versus me just
taking a front-wheel drive one, putting
some snow tires on it, call it a day.
But I know I know some dealerships do
lose money on cars, but I know at $1,000
discount, you would still be making
a,000 bucks plus hold back. But I get
it. No worries. If you guys It's your
guys' choice. You guys you guys are the
ones selling the car, not me. Okay.
>> Okay. Awesome. Well, if you guys decide
you guys want to go a little bit more
aggressive on that car and maybe end of
month or something crazy, don't be
afraid to let me know. I'm trying to get
a deal done today. Want to buy a car
today, put a deposit on it today,
whatever it takes. Call a few other
dealerships in the area and hoping we
can, you know, wrap something up.
>> All right. Well, best of luck to you.
Um, thank you. Anything changes, we'll
let you know.
>> Yeah, absolutely.
>> Thanks. Bye.
>> All right, Tommy. Bye.
>> Service. How may I help you?
>> Hey, can I speak to somebody in sales?
>> Who in sales?
>> Any anybody that uh has a pulse? Smiley
face.
>> Okay, one second.
>> Meanwhile,
>> good afternoon. This is Trisha on sales.
How can I help you?
>> Hey, Trisha. I just wanted to see if you
guys have a car available.
>> All right. What's the car?
>> I have elastics to the VIN. If that
helps, that might be better.
>> Um, let's see. Is it Do you know if it's
used or if it's new?
>> It's brand new.
>> Okay, let's see. Let me get logged into
my new car website.
>> You're good. Take your time.
>> Let's see. You have a stock number.
>> Thought I had a stock number, but this
is why you should just call me a liar,
cuz I only have the last six of the VIN.
There's no stock number here.
>> No, it's fine. I'll take the last six.
>> Okay, last six is going to be U is in
uranium, 34, C is in Caterpillar 146.
>> Camry XSE allwheel drive.
>> That's it.
>> Let me find out about this one because
there's some notes on the comments here.
I don't know if it's already pending
sale or what the deal is with this one.
Okay.
>> So, let me go confirm and find out
what's the status on it. Can I just get
down your information and everything so
I can give you a call back?
>> Of course. What do you need?
>> I need name and phone number.
>> First name is Tommy. Uh, and my phone
number.
>> All right. Give me a couple minutes. Let
me go find out what the deal is with
this one and then I can give you a call
back. Okay.
>> Okay. Sounds good. Bye.
>> All right. Bye-bye.
>> This is Kim. How can I help you?
>> Hey, Kim. Are you in new car sales?
>> Yes, I am. How can I help?
>> Bada boom, bada bing. I love it. Hey, I
just want to see if you guys have a car
available.
>> Which one? I have a stock number if that
helps you. VIN, make, model, last
forfeit social. What do you want?
>> You said it's new, correct?
>> It's brand new. It's uh I don't even
know if it's at your dealership. I know
it says on the lot. It's on the lot.
>> All right. Hit me with that stock
number.
>> Hey, uh stock number is 251348.
>> Available. No deposits on it. What are
you looking to do?
>> Uh well, I'm really interested. I've
already driven one. I fell in love with
it. They're awesome. Really just trying
to get the best possible price and
looking to buy one today.
>> Are you local to us? Uh
>> you know, I'm in Queens, but you know,
I'm I'm willing to travel. I have family
all over the Northeast, so it's not a
big deal for me to, you know, hop in a
car and call it a day.
>> You're in Queens, New York.
>> Yeah, Queens, New York. Yeah. Great
area.
>> So, unfortunately, we do not sell
outside of New England.
>> I mean, some people could consider New
York New England in theory, right?
>> Some people, but not us.
>> Oh, okay. So, you guys wouldn't sell me
a car?
>> Unfortunately, not. We're just a smaller
dealership. Oh,
>> okay. No worries. I don't want to waste
any more of your time. I wish I could
convince you, but I'm not that crazy.
>> All right. Thank you so much.
>> No problem. Bye.
[Music]
Bye.
>> This is Tommy.
>> Hey Tommy, it's Trisha with How's it
going?
>> Hey, it's going well. But yourself?
>> Good. So, that car is still available.
>> Awesome. Love to hear it.
>> Now, I noticed the zip code. Where are
you located?
>> Uh, in Glenn Oaks, New York.
>> Where is that?
>> Not terribly far and it's kind of in the
middle of nowhere, but I can come to
your dealership. You're not that far.
>> Oh, okay. Perfect. Yeah, that's why I
call just cuz um it's not here
currently, but when it is. So, with new
cars, the process is a little bit
different with this one. So, it's still
in product confirmation. It's expected
to arrive here September 13th. Now, with
that being said, with new cars, a lot of
the times these vehicles sell before
they even arrive at our location.
>> Okay?
>> So, what I tell people when you're
looking at new cars, I can send over a
spec sheet so you can see like what
features it has, the interior, the
exterior, the whole nine. like
everything the whole inside and outside
of the car basically you can see on a
spec sheet so you know what what it is
we can also do like a breakdown and
everything the credit we can do the
entire process basically as if you were
sitting here at my desk and you wanted
to buy a car we could go through the
whole process remotely what I would tell
you though is in order to secure the
vehicle so that it's not on
advertisement or anything like that we
normally take a deposit which comes off
of the price as well and it's fully
refundable
>> that way it secures it in your names off
of our website like as an advertised
vehicle it's on hold it's on reserve
That's why I had to go find out about it
because it was marked as if it was on
reserve for somebody. Okay.
>> So, that's what that would do in order
to secure it before it arrives just
because we don't know like you could get
off the phone with me today and then
somebody else could come in or call and
do the same thing.
>> Yeah. Awesome. I mean, I just want to as
long as we can create a price, I'm fine
putting deposit down and all that fun
stuff. That's no big deal on my side.
>> Yeah. No, I can send over um the spec
sheet and everything like that. Is it
something you want to put the deposit
down now and just go forward with the
process?
>> Well, no. I'd want to know what what
price you guys are selling it at and all
the things you guys are doing before I
put deposit down.
>> Yeah. So, it's priced at 43,711.
>> Okay. That's what it's priced at. You
guys can't do any better than that?
>> No. With new cars, window sticker is
normally where it's at.
>> Oh, yeah. These these Camry deals, I
know a lot of dealerships are going
crazy on them. So, I'm not paying
sticker.
>> Yeah. New cars, it's tough because the
demand's so high for any of these
vehicles. Grand Highlanders, Camry, and
then Siennas actually are the other
ones, too.
>> Oh, I get the Grand Highlander and the
Sienna. Yeah. you know, preach or
preach. But, uh, when it comes down to
Camry's, it's a little bit a little bit
different.
>> Yeah. And this one too, this one's an
XSSE, so it's a higher trim model than
like the Ellie. So, are you set on the
XSSE, or is there another option you
would also look at?
>> Yeah. I like the XSSE. I like the I like
the one with the RAD with the premium
plus and all the fun stuff. All the all
the bells and whistles,
>> right? Okay. I know I have two other
ones that are Well, I actually have a
couple other ones that are coming in. I
have two LE's, an SE, and then two XSE
coming in. So, I don't know if you
wanted to see any of those ones or
>> No, I this is the car I want. Like, this
is the dream that would be in my
driveway, so to speak. It's it's more
just the price, you know? I don't want
to pay Sticker. It's No, no big deal.
And if you guys are at a sticker
dealership and that's where you guys are
at, I know other people will sell them
for a discount, so no big deal,
>> right? Okay. Well, like I said, that's
it is available. So, if you ever come
back and circle back around to us, just
know that currently is available now.
Okay.
>> Awesome. Perfect. I appreciate your
help.
>> All right. Not a problem.
>> Okay. Bye.
>> Bye-bye. If I go out. So, just so you
guys know like how dramatic of a
difference this is. I can get I just got
$5,500 off a front-wheel drive one
yesterday.
>> Toyota, may I help you?
>> Hey, Toyota. This is Tommy. I just want
to see if you guys have a car available.
>> Sure thing, Tommy. Um, was there a
pre-owned or a new one?
>> It's brand new.
>> Okay.
>> Picture shows it's in the factory still.
>> What vehicle was that?
>> Uh, I have the last six of the VIN if
that helps. It's a Camry.
>> Yeah, sure thing. Last six of the VIN is
U is in uranium 34 D is in dinosaur 887.
>> All right. Yeah, it looks like this
vehicle is currently getting built and
it should be arriving to our dealership
sometime within the next couple weeks.
>> Bada boom, bada bing. Super exciting.
Well, this is the one I want. This is
the dream in the driveway. I'm really
just trying to get some pricing. Hoping
that you can help me out.
>> Yeah, sure thing, Tommy. Are you looking
to lease or finance the vehicle?
>> Uh, looking to finance.
>> All right, so give me one moment. Let me
get you over to one of my sales
managers. Is this the best call back?
>> Yes, it is.
>> All right. Perfect. Give me one moment.
>> Okay.
>> Meanwhile,
>> hello.
>> Hello.
>> Hey, Tommy. How you doing?
>> Hey, man. I'm doing well. Hey, man. I
just want to see if you guys have a car
available.
>> Yeah, we have one car XSC. Probably you
can see also online. I can provide the
stock number also the VIN number.
Whatever is better for you. You can
check on our online website or you know
like any questions that you have for me,
I can help you right now, you know.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. No, no worries.
I know how to use the internet machine.
I already did that one. Found it online.
And you guys are saying so if it's on
the website, it's guaranteed to be
available.
>> Yeah. So I have the one that I want to
make sure is the same. The 7942 we have
available. That's not the one I'm
talking about.
>> Which one is it? The
>> It's U3 as in dinosaur 887.
>> Let me see. This is a car. Let me see.
This
>> AAR, which means allocation. Yes,
correct. That is that is correct. I
think so. I mean, the picture in the
thing shows that it's in a factory. So
>> yeah. So it's a factory and it's going
to be here around like August 27 to
September 10. So basically not not too
pretty soon though I guess. Yeah.
>> As I told the last gentleman also super
nice. Super excited to buy this car.
Super interested in it. Was just trying
to get some good old pricing.
>> Uh-huh. Okay.
>> Um yeah. And question. Have you checked
out the 7942 like the difference? So, do
you see something different from the one
that we have available now or the one
that you interest in the ECAT?
>> This one has the premium plus. This one
has I mean what what color interior is
this?
>> It's uh the same cockpit red.
>> Okay. Yeah. Sure. If you want to go with
this one instead. I mean I'm not I mean
if
>> Yeah. Yeah. That's why I would just want
you know like some customers they prefer
you know they have a special look or
they they have something specific that
they saw in the vehicle. So basically
but I was just checking is the basically
the same features. I don't see not much
difference especially color and yeah so
you can come take come take a look and
then you know test drive then you know
whatever decision you have then you know
at the end it's your decision you know
>> well good news is I already I already
drove one I already fell in love with it
dude the Camry it's just a hybrid motor
just vally excited to buy this car
really just as I said uh the first four
times uh just looking for some pricing
>> Mhm. Okay so you would like to have the
out of the door price right? Yeah, that
would be awesome. Yeah, just getting the
out the door price and if I agree to
that, I'll I'll put a deposit on right
now and I'll come on in, get this all
taken care of, you know, like I'm I'm
like the easy guy. Like, agree to
numbers. I'm putting money down. I got I
got money. I got money just waiting
right here.
>> No, no worries. So, you're going to be
paying cash, right?
>> Uh I'm open to cash. I'm open to
financing. You know, I'm open. I know
that the dealership gets a little bit of
a kickback, so I'm I'm wide open if that
makes more sense for you guys.
>> Okay. All right. Let me just give me one
Can you give me like 3 minutes? I'm just
going to go run with the manager and
then he can bring me out of out of the
door and then you're going to have it.
I'm going to send you a picture right
away. Sounds good.
>> Awesome. Perfect. I'm excited. Yeah.
I'll sit here and wait 3 minutes. No
worries.
>> All right. I'll be back here. All right.
>> Bless his soul. But this is part of the
reason why people do not like buying a
car, which is we talked to the first
person, which then got us to a second
person, which then said, "Oh, I don't do
the numbers. I'm going to go to the
third person." To the third person
switched the vehicle, which is fine.
This vehicle is probably here sooner. I
don't see anything wrong with it. It's
underground. Works. Uh, that's fine.
Thank you. But now it's like, okay, now
I got to go to the fourth person to get
numbers. Oh my goodness. Now I got to
hold again.
>> Okay, I'mma send you right now a
picture.
>> I'm excited to see them. I'm literally
just looking at my phone. I'm not doing
anything else.
>> I'm excited to send you. Let me know if
you receive it. So, thank you.
>> I'm looking here. It literally gave me a
notification that I got. I got
>> You got it.
>> I got it. Bada boom, bada bing. Okay.
So, MSRP 42317.
>> It's the sticker is 42317.
>> So, you guys are above MSRP.
>> Yeah, that's MSRP. Yeah, we doing MSRP
and uh we including the lowjack. We
including the all new vehicles is 599.
And then comes the taxes and yeah, the
duck fee 175.
>> Okay. And you can't take so just above
MSRP. I'm not looking to pay above MSRP
on the car. I'm just trying to see if
there's any way we can get a better
price than that.
>> Send me a number. So, I can ask the
manager. I have the manager. Like,
>> oh yeah,
>> I can ask him.
>> I was hoping be about 3,000 out the
door. How much?
>> $3,000 off that.
>> I don't think so. Let me ask. I don't,
you know, I don't I don't lose anything
asking the manager, you know.
>> Yeah. It doesn't hurt to ask the
manager.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Okay. One second.
>> Meanwhile,
>> Yep. Sorry.
>> Hello, Tommy.
>> Hey, I'm still here. Sorry. Mute. I
muted you.
>> Yeah. Can you hear me? Right.
>> I can hear you. I can hear you loud and
clear. So, sorry.
>> Yeah. I asked the man know he say that's
the final number that we can give you
the car.
>> Oh, so the final number is above MSRP on
a Camry.
>> Yeah.
>> Holy moly. Call me. That's crazy.
>> Yeah. We give you a sticker basically.
You know that
>> I mean you're above sticker. I mean you
got add-ons and fees.
>> You know taxes. We cannot do anything
with the tax.
>> I'm talking about the dealer installed
options. That those are the ones I'm
talking about.
>> What dealer?
>> It says total financed aftermarket $599.
Oh, the lowjack. Yeah, lowjack is 5.99.
Yeah. So, so you guys are above.
>> I can ask we can remove that. I mean,
you know, if you don't want Let me just
ask the manager so we can
>> No, I mean, that's I have I have 5500
off a front-wheel drive one out of
state, but I don't want frontwheel
drive. I want all-wheel drive. So, I'm
like, okay, well, you know, if I got a
$3,000 discount, you know, bada boom,
bada bing, I'd be happy. But otherwise,
I'll just put some snow tires on this
bad boy and call it a day. You know,
>> let me see if we can do something with a
lowjack. But that's pretty much it that
we can, you know, I can I speak with a
manager cuz you know all the well in our
in my dealership, all our vehicles comes
with a low jack with a 2-year low jack
for that.
>> I know. But I know I I know um the
original car, at least I was asking for
wasn't even there yet. But uh either
way, I I don't want to waste any time of
yours. I'm I'm looking for about a
$3,000 discount. That makes sense.
Otherwise, I'll just go buy the
front-wheel drive one.
>> Oh, yeah. And all right, let me just
speak with the manager. But yeah, he
definitely he say now there is no way
3,000. Yeah, if he wants to throw. So,
he's just staying at above MSRP. He's
not want to move a dime.
>> Yeah. I mean, it's included at taxes and
two. So, you know that basically the
price by by above MSRP. I'm talking
about the 599. You guys are above MSRP
even at MSRP. So, he's not willing to
move a dime off of MSRP plus lowjack.
>> Okay. So, let me let me speak to our
manager if we can do something with uh
Lowjack. We can include in the MSRP.
Okay.
>> Yeah. Just just so we're clear. I don't
want to waste any time for your manager
in this. Like I said, I'm trying to get
$3,000 off. If you wanted to offer
$2,000 off a nojack, I'd consider it.
Right? Like I'm I'm open to the
negotiation part of the deal, but I'm
not willing to do it at MSRP. So, if
that's all you can do is throw lowjack
in. I've got 12 other dealerships that
are willing to do that. You know, that's
not exciting. It's
>> really exciting. I understand that. So,
let me just speak with the see what he
says. Okay.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> All right. Just give me five minutes.
>> Bye.
>> Thank you for calling Toyota. Chris in
sales. Am I direct to call?
>> Hey, Chris. Can I speak to somebody new
car sales?
>> That would be me. Hey, how are you, sir?
>> Man, I am living a dream. How about
yourself?
>> I am doing great. Now, I'm going to act
like I don't know who you are because I
know how this is about to go.
>> What do you mean? Did Did you see I was
I was on Channel 3 Charlotte News. Did
you see that?
>> Yeah, man. That was insane what you had
done over there.
>> Oh my gosh.
>> Big things, dude. Big things. You're
changing the world,
>> dude. I appreciate it. Let's change the
world one car deal at a time and let's
see. You have a car and I think it's on
the lot.
>> All right. Let me see what I can do for
you. It's a new one, right?
>> Brand new. I got a stock number if that
helps.
>> Sweet. I actually just got logged out of
my new car system, so give me just a
second. Let me see what I got.
>> Oh, I got to warn you. You are being
streamed in front of millions of people.
>> No, you're good. My heart's racing a
little bit, but in a good way.
>> It's racing a Don't make a mistake. No,
they're good.
>> Not going to mess this up for you, man.
We going to put this together,
>> dude. Let's get this deal. Let's get
this deal rocking.
>> Manager ain't going to know who I'm
talking to either.
>> Oh, the manager is going to think you're
crazy. Oh, there's some guy on TikTok,
man. I tell you, he's he's he live
streams the negotiation.
That's hilarious. All right, man. Let's
see here. What car is it?
>> Okay, it's U034691.
>> Uh, what car is it?
>> It's a Camry white with cockpit XSSE
with premium plus.
>> Heck yeah. You got the red interior on
it.
>> Yeah.
>> Woo. That's a good pick. Yeah, this
one's sitting on the ground right now.
Get you in the system real quick. What
name do you want to use?
>> Put Tommy. You can put delivered if you
want, but
>> Tommy, we're just going to do
>> Davis.
>> Perfect. You know what? That's That's
the name I always wanted. That's a
powerful name right there. Yeah. Let me
put your phone in. Is it 98?
>> Why Davis? Now I'm curious. Why'd you
pick Davis?
>> Tommy. I just sound I don't know. It
sound We actually had a dude here that
worked here. His name was Tommy Davis.
So it kind of just rang a bell. Starts
with a D. Delivered. It works.
>> It works. And you know what? It makes
sense. It's a secret. So nobody knows
when you Tommy Davis starts buying all
these cars. You're going to be like,
"Wait, what?"
>> Yeah. Well, it's funny because you had
caught up here and worked with Chris uh
guy. He sits right behind me.
had a great conversation with like just
phenomenal.
>> Yeah. No, he he's a great dude. He is he
is awesome, bro. I just got married. He
uh
>> did one of the people to reach out and
let me know. It was funny because I was
just scrolling through your channel and
I heard his voice and I was like, "No
shot. No way." So, I had to give him
some uh some some crap over a little
bit.
>> But uh but no, I could tell he did a
good job with you. But I think he he
told my manager who you were and my
manager, "Oh, no, no." But
>> he's an old school. He's an old school
guy. He's not here right now. So,
>> okay. He's not here. So, let's get this
deal wrapped up and we'll show him how
easy it is to work with delivered.
>> Yeah. All right. Let's see here. I got
this VIN number put in here. We'll we'll
just make it really easy. Is there a
certain number that you're trying to get
on it?
>> I'm trying to get 4,000 off.
>> Can I be honest?
>> Yeah.
>> On these cameras, especially being an
XSSE, I know you call around a lot, so
you you know, you do it a lot. We don't
have any special add-ons or anything,
which is great. The way we do business,
it's just the number and then our doc
fee and taxes and tax time and license.
So, I I can always ask, but four grand
off on the XSSE is going to be very hard
to do cuz I can't even really hardly get
that on an Ellie most of the time.
>> What about
>> Are you familiar with like are you are
>> Dude, I would totally go in there and
say, "Hey, do this right now." I I do
know the answer would be no on that. Do
you do you know how the invoice works? I
know you know how it works, but do you
know what the invoice kind of is around
these cars? uh it's right around 2200
off something around that ballpark.
>> It would be something like that. And
that's the thing is we have a uh we have
a competitive dealership down the road
that's a little bit newer than us and so
they just get cars and cars and cars and
cars. We don't get too many of them. Uh
they take away from our share pretty
greatly. But I will definitely work on
getting you a good discount on it. The
only problem is again I will not have
you know four, you know, I won't have
38. I think we're probably gonna be in
the ballpark if I was able to get it
down.
>> 3,000. Let's just
>> If I was If I was able to get it down,
you know, somewhere around invoice, I
think I'd be able to do it for you. I
just have to uh I just have to ask. Good
news is you're talking to a guy that
just missed a week. I just got married.
So, um congratulations.
>> I literally just missed a week. This is
my Thank you, man. It's my first day
back. So, I'm wondering if my manager is
going to help me get a deal here.
>> Yeah. Just And we'll do this. Is this
the nice manager?
>> Yeah. You know, it's very out of
character. very out of character for
your last call because you know I'm very
happy to be where I'm at. They take good
care of me here. So
>> Oh, are you were you watching the stream
right now?
>> I think. No, not at all. No, sir. I'll
go back to watch it. Hopefully I'll be
posting. Hopefully it'll be one of those
good experiences that you have. Say,
"Hey, this is the best experience I ever
had."
>> And I got I got like 15 Toyota deals I
can do right now, too. So, we got this
one done. We got a few others wrapped
up. We'll start stealing away from that.
>> I do have an idea. I do have an idea.
And again, it's not me trying.
Obviously, you know, I do get paid
gross. I get paid on the profit on the
vehicle. And whenever we do this,
there's not going to be any profit. So,
I'm just going to get my mini. With that
being said, do you have a like a number
that I need to try to beat? Like, what's
the best offer that you've got? Maybe I
can go in there. You're not going to
like that.
>> Oh gosh. Really? Did somebody really get
you 4 grand?
>> No. Well, somebody got me 5,500 on a
front-wheel drive, but he wants
all-wheel drive. So, dude, I'm telling
you, some dealerships are crazy. That's
why for that's why I'm trying to get
this one at a slightly less discount at
all-wheel drive because he really wants
the allhe drive.
>> Yeah, I'll try my best. I can I can see
if I can get you down uh at least the
invoice, you know. Hopefully we can have
a good experience together. Yeah. I Man,
I hate that. Uh where was that at? I'm
going to go buy a car from them.
>> I don't even get 5500 get my seat for
the day. Really? So yeah, if it's
already that's at least pretty close to
invoicing.
>> Yeah.
>> Let me see if I can do this.
>> We put this together. We're ready to
We're ready to wrap and roll on this one
here. So, we can wrap and roll.
>> I'll go to bat for you.
>> Awesome.
>> So, we're at 3,300 off right now. If I
was able to make it, you know, like 37
38 go in there.
>> See, now we're talking.
>> Okay. Give me just a minute, man. I'll
do what I can do for you. And then Yeah.
Is this a good number to call yet?
>> Yeah. This is the best number here. I'm
going to unmute this line.
>> And no email.
>> Devil's work.
>> All right. I got you, brother. You give
me just a minute. All right.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> All right. I'll talk to you soon. Oh,
wait. Hey, real quick. I'm sorry. Hey, I
skipped a step. Give me your uh give me
a good zip code I can factor in your
taxi.
>> Uh oh, it's it's out of state.
>> Is that uh is that
>> that's Queens? It's Glenn Oaks.
>> Okay, that's perfect. All right,
brother. You give me just a minute. I
will call you right back.
>> All right, sounds good.
>> All right, I'll talk to you soon.
>> All right, bye.
>> Hello, this is Nate. How can I help you?
>> Hello, Nate. This is Tommy. I just want
to see if you guys have a car available.
>> Okay, what uh car are you looking for?
>> I have the last of the van if that
helps.
>> Okay. Yep. Is it uh new or used?
>> It's brand new. Okay. Yeah. Go ahead.
>> Okay. Stock or sorry, Vin. Vin. U is in
uranium. 34. A is in apricot 027. It's
>> a Camry XSSE.
>> Oh, yep. With the windchill midnight
black roof in the cockpit, red interior.
>> Yep. Got that. Okay. Let me check
something real quick cuz there's some
sort of comment on it. Let me just check
with the manager real quick. One second.
>> No problem. Meanwhile,
>> hey Tommy, you still there?
>> I'm still here. I'm just chilling.
>> Awesome. Yeah, that's uh still
available. So,
>> awesome. Uh super super excited. I love
this car. It's awesome. It's great.
Really just trying to get some great
pricing on it and hoping to buy a car
from you.
>> Yeah. So, this is scheduled to arrive
probably end of the month, maybe early
September. We can't really lower the
price any further if that's what you're
asking. We don't have a whole lot of the
Camry available right now. They sell
very quickly. If it was on our lot and
sitting for like more than 2 weeks, then
we'd probably be able to discount it.
There's no need for us to discount it at
the moment cuz it's not even at our
store yet. But you can definitely uh
reserve it and see it when it comes in
if you want to do that.
>> I appreciate that. Um, you know, I'm
definitely looking to just get a good
deal on this car. And I understand that
uh some of them are have not hit the lot
yet, but I know there's a lot of them
that have. I have a deal on a
front-wheel drive one. I'm trying not to
take that. I have a pretty aggressive
deal there. So, I prefer not to, but in
>> You prefer the all-wheel drive or
>> I prefer the all-wheel drive, but I
don't want to pay MSRP because the
frontwheel drive one I have is too good
of a deal. So,
>> this is I'm looking here, too, and this
is the only It's the only all-wheel
drive one we have coming in for the next
3 months.
>> I get it.
>> Out of all the uh Camry. Yeah. I mean,
you can wait for it to come into our
store and then uh take a shot then, but
we don't we don't really discount our uh
vehicles, especially if they're not
arrived to our store yet. Maybe if it
was sitting here for a couple weeks,
then we could probably discount the
price a bit. But just check the price
every now and then cuz actually
sometimes our pricing does change.
Sometimes our uh GM will, you know, set
the pricing like $500 below MSRP for
certain vehicles like the Camry. So,
>> okay. Yeah. I mean, that's that's great.
Uh I mean, that'd be awesome.
>> The You said you reserved the
front-wheel drive one.
>> Uh yeah, I already I haven't reserved
it. I just talked to a dealership that
was willing to do a deal on it, but
again, I don't want a front-wheel drive.
I don't have to. But I'll put snow tires
on it if I if push comes to the shelf.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I mean I can let you
know if we uh lower the price, but we're
not able to right now. So,
>> yeah, no, no worries. You don't even
have to let me know. I I'm going to keep
looking around. That seems like the best
route for me. And like I said, if I
can't find one, I'll just go with the
frontwheel drive one.
>> Okay, gotcha. Yeah, just call us back.
You can ask for me. My name's Nate. I
can help you out.
>> Awesome, Nate. You're a delight. And if
you need anything, uh you I will call
you back.
>> All right. Take care, man.
>> All right. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> Uh but like I'm not going to fight
somebody if they don't negotiate. If
they don't negotiate, it's a move on,
call it a day, which is what I do most
of the time, but normally I can tell if
a dealership says they don't negotiate,
but they do. And we got to play around
with that a little bit. So,
>> this is Tommy.
>> Tommy, my man.
>> Okay. I'm hoping you have good news.
>> No, I've got great news, man. I talked
to my uh sales manager. I talked to my
owner. Well, the owner. I I don't have
an owner, but I talked to the owner and
and everything is good. So, I am able to
kind of set this up for you as long as
you know he looked up your website and
everything. It's fine. I eventually had
to spill the beans a little bit just
because I had to make it look
comfortable to him. So, I'm about to
shoot you this picture, this worksheet
over again. I've got the got the sales
price down to 41 and and then of course
you've got the taxes and everything
which I can't can't do anything about
there. But, let me shoot this over to
you real quick. You just text it to your
phone, right?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Just text it to my phone
right now. I got to send it to the
client. Client's texting me. So,
>> you're good. I'm texting this right now.
Take a look at this. I think it's I
think it's pretty aggressive.
>> And then as far as Maverick goes, you're
familiar that Maverick is absolutely
they they take their time with it. So,
it can take it can take a couple weeks,
but as long as your customer Yeah. As
long as your customer is not in a hurry
thinking he's going to get it right this
second, then we should be good. But I
know you'll explain that to him and
everything. I will, too. Yeah. Just go
ahead and take a peek at that that
worksheet. Absolutely. The best I can do
for you. And we can kind of start lining
this up for you.
>> Okay. Perfect. Awesome. Send that over
to me right now. I'll get this wrapped
up and call it a day. One of many.
>> Are you going to call me back today or
what should I do?
>> I will I will text you back to solidify
this. I don't like do that on tech. I
just don't want to steam my customer's
information on stream.
>> No, you're good. Just text me whenever
you can. So, I need to go out there and
throw a soul sign in ASAP. So,
>> I mean, if you give me Yeah, he's he's
going to agree to this for sure. So, uh
give me Yeah. Yeah. Give me a second.
I'll just send it over to him and uh
we'll go from And then real quick, are
you familiar with bot do? Have you
worked with bot doc at all?
>> What?
>> So botto is like a secure it's just a
secure link that I send and what you're
what I'll have your customer do is he
can send me a $1,000 deposit just to
make sure that the vehicle is you keep
the thousand until you know the Maverick
paperwork comes back and as soon as that
paperwork gets back then we can have the
uh we can have the car sent over to you.
We are going to have to kind of figure
out a shipping solution because I don't
have my own. Oh yeah, we we'll get that
figured out.
>> Okay, sweet, man. You just call me or
text me here in a minute and then let me
know and I'll I'll text your customer
and and get that card info from them.
>> I love it. Awesome. I appreciate you
making it easy, man. And let's get this
wrapped up and we'll we'll do a few more
here.
>> Absolutely. Sounds good, brother. Well,
good luck.
>> Hey, thank you. Bye.
>> All right. Talk to you soon.
>> Bye. Okay, I just sent that over to my
client. I want to get this deal wrapped
up. Client's just texting me. So, now
we're just waiting on the dealer. We're
waiting on the client to text us back.
For everybody that says this is all fake
and not real, we can confirm where this
car sales has been. This is an all
all-wheel drive spec. It's just a
dealership that's given a crazy deal on
it. I'm not going to be mad about it.
They made it really easy. I want to say
this dealership. Last time I called them
had $2,000 of ads, so they're not doing
anymore either. Wait, lock it. Lock it
on it. Lock it. Lock it. Lock it. One
second. We got the camera done. I'm
trying to trying to lock it. Okay. Boom.
Okay. Sorry. I got I got to get this
camera in the system properly for
Dakota. Dakota, if you guys don't know,
we have an entire team dedicated to
making sure people have the best car
buying experience of their life. I don't
have this dealership. That's crazy. This
dealership knows who I am, but they
never sign up for my list. So, let's go.
Toyota 3.5K off a Camry. Boom. Okay, we
did it. We did it. We did it. We did it.
Okay.
[Music]