He's beating me up, Rick.
>> Beating him up, punching him left, right
side.
>> All right, Tommy. I I like you, by the
way. I just want you to know that.
>> I know. And no add-ons, no fees, just
tax title license. And honestly, I want
I want the notebook ending. I'm going to
look at what we're building here. We had
the perfect car before. It was just the
wrong color. So, this client is looking
for a F-150 Lariat. So, let's go build
it in Invisor. They're looking for a new
Lariat. They are looking for the Blue
Cruise. They are looking for the
off-road package. Oh, and they're also
looking for the 3.5 L EcoBoost. And they
are not looking for a hybrid. They are
looking for a gas. And they want every
color but white. They're open to
anything but white and ideally not
silver. So, we're going to get rid of
the whites and the silvers. Make their
life easy. So, uh there's 500 of these
trucks nationwide. Uh, my client lives
in,
which I don't even know where it is, but
it's in Washington.
>> Hi, this is Alex. How can I help you?
>> Hey, uh, I just want to see if you guys
have a car available.
>> Sure. What was the car you're looking
for?
>> Uh, I I would give you the stock number,
but it's just like a blank slot. So, I
can give you the last six of the VIN if
that helps.
>> Sure. Yeah. What was the last six of the
VIN?
>> Yeah. Uh, it's C as in Chrysler 25809.
And this is a new car, I'm assuming.
>> Yeah, a brand new car.
>> Is it a Ford, Jeep, Dodge, Ram?
>> Ford.
>> Ford. Gotcha.
>> See,
>> I wish I could whistle. I can't figure
it out.
>> Oh, no. You're all good. I I barely do.
So, I just have to uh
>> Yeah, I just
>> I mean, yeah. I mean, it's not as it's
not as high pitched as my dad, that's
for sure. I'm still trying to work my
way up there.
>> Y
>> um
Is this a uh a truck or is this a
certain
>> Yep, it's a truck.
It's a truck.
>> Gotcha. It doesn't seem to pop up with
my system. What truck was it? Just so I
can see if my managers can uh find
locate that
>> F-150 Laria.
>> All right, cool. I'm going go ahead and
check in with them. Could I put you on
the brief board for just a little bit?
>> Yep. You can put me on a hold as long as
you need.
>> Awesome. What was your name, man?
>> My name's Tommy.
>> Tommy?
>> Mhm.
>> All right. All right. Let me go ahead
and check back in with him. I'll I'll be
right back with you.
>> Sounds good. We can all just agree that
it just didn't happen, right? Yeah. I
just
>> I mean, yeah. I mean, it's not as it's
not as high pitched as mine does. That's
>> Thanks. Thanks. Well, this is Joe, one
of the sales managers. I'm having a hard
time finding that truck. So, I'm going
to confirm the uh stock number you got
there. The last view of the bin. Is it
C25809?
>> Correct. Yeah.
>> Okay. And that's a new 2025.
>> Yeah. 2025 Ford F-150 Lariat Super Crew
4x4. We don't have any more free consult
spots uh right now. Uh we're booked out
for a little bit, but you guys can send
an email in and a question. We can help
you out. So, we're not booked out for
the month for deals, but we are booked
out for consults right now. We're trying
to add up more spots. We're just not
there yet. This is Marsh Gray. Marsh
Gray is fine with He just doesn't want
white. Also, when I'm when I'm talking
like this, I have it muted. So,
>> all right. That's why I wasn't able to
find it on my website. It looks like
it's uh inbound. It's not here yet.
>> Let me take a look.
>> You have an inbound 25. That's crazy.
>> Yeah. Yeah. It looks like it was ordered
103 of 2024. So, we didn't expect that
one to take that long to get here.
>> Oh, wow. 103 to 20 24. Oh my goodness.
>> Yeah.
You know, they're probably like one
piece at a time.
>> I know. See, and that that that that's
what makes this one special for you. Uh
let me take a look and I'll tell you
exactly where it's at. It looks like
it's been uh inbound for a while, but uh
I'm going to double check.
>> Maybe they got lost that.
>> It could have been. It could be on a
rail somewhere, you know, just went the
wrong direction. Maybe maybe I flew over
the uh what's it called? The the place
in the Caribbean, you know, where
everything goes.
>> Exactly.
That's it.
>> There you go. About a year and a half
ago, there was a uh a bunch of imports
coming like Mercedes and Audi's that
were coming across on the boat. The boat
sunk.
>> Wow.
>> That was pretty crazy. Yeah, the whole
boat sunk.
>> $4 million worth of vehicles.
>> That's insane.
>> Oh, so yeah, that one that one's due
here any second now. Um, it's actually
it's actually literally on a semi-truck
coming from the port in Kent to here.
So, we should see it sometime today or
early tomorrow morning.
>> Well, I'm definitely interested in it.
I've already driven one. I already know
I want it. I'm just looking for this
exact truck. So, you know, we can read a
numbers. I can sell it as your oldest
truck that's been built even though it's
not your oldest truck on your inventory.
>> Absolutely. Absolutely. Let me I'll get
you back over to uh Alex. That way we he
can get your information. I'll tell you
exactly when it's here. All right.
>> I love it. I am curious about the
condition of the car, but the car is not
shipped over the Bermuda Triangle
either. I don't know why I'm still on
hold.
>> Tom, you still there?
>> I'm still here.
>> Awesome. I was just uh It looks like my
manager was able to locate that for you
and he I believe he even mentioned it
over to you that we're going to be able
to see any day now. Yeah. When we were
looking to stop by and checking it out
or I can also uh uh if you want to stop
by today so we can kind of go over the
uh the window sticker with you too, just
so you know where you're exactly what
you're getting, we can also do that as
Well, the good news is I went to I went
to college to read window stickers, so I
really don't need help doing that, but
this is the car I want. So, this is
great. This is awesome. This is the one
I'm looking for. So, uh, as the the last
person, if if we can agree to numbers,
I'll come buy it.
>> Okay, sounds good. Um, all right. Let me
just get a little some information here.
This is a good number to contact you on.
>> Yep. This is the best number.
>> Awesome. And what was your last name?
>> Last name is Makula. M I K U L A.
>> Awesome. And are you available to come
come in today? and uh has um all the
facts and figures or
>> you know even better uh I can I can do
it all at home. So you send those over
to me right now and I'll look at them
and if I agree to them and you give me
an awesome deal I'll put a deposit on it
today over the phone and you don't have
to see my face.
>> Oh wow. I always want to shake your
hand. But in any case if that's what the
method you prefer I'm not a problem on
that. What's a good email for you? Or do
you prefer text?
>> Texting is better.
>> Texting is better for now. Okay. Not a
problem on that.
All right. Just getting you loaded all
into the system here. What I'm going to
go ahead and do is just let my manager
know kind of get you uh uh some numbers.
Did you want me to send you over a link
to the credit app as well if you're
going to be financing or would this be
cash?
>> You know, I'm open to cash, open to
finance, but let's let's make sure we
create a numbers for first before we get
to a credit app.
>> Not a problem. Not a problem at all.
I'll go ahead and uh get back with my
manager, see what we can do for you,
man.
>> Thank you. Appreciate it.
>> Yeah, absolutely. We'll keep in touch
soon. All right.
>> All right. Sounds good.
>> Not a problem. Bye.
>> If you guys don't know who I am, my
name's Tommy. I negotiate car deals for
a living. My goal save you time, energy,
anxiety. Do we save money? Sure. But
that's a byproduct. Don't hire me to do
that. Hire me because you don't want to
deal with it. What if you're like, "Hey,
Tommy, I just want to learn. Follow my
tips. Follow my tricks. You're going to
do it." Great.
>> This is Hunter in Sales. How can I help
you?
>> Hello, Hunter and Sales. It's Tommy from
Buying. I just wanted to see if you guys
have a car available.
>> Of course. What are you looking for?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Uh, give me one second to get to the
website. Looking at new or used, Brian?
>> Tommy, but uh, new.
>> Tommy. Tommy from buying. I'm sorry.
>> Tommy from buying. That's okay. That's
right. That's right.
>> I made a funny mish heard it.
>> Go ahead. Fire away.
>> Yeah. Yeah. C is in cat. 30710.
>> C30710.
Lariat F-150.
>> Yeah, that's it.
>> Nope.
>> All right. Let me double check my other
source. That's not pictures at our
dealership. So sometimes that means the
vehicle could still be in transit.
>> Maybe it showed up this week. Let's
check.
>> Yeah, no worries. Take your time. I have
nowhere to be.
Almond. All in.
>> So, car is not currently here. The ETA
I'm seeing is 107 to 10:13. So, it's
literally any day that thing's going to
show up.
>> I love it. Well, I'm definitely
interested in it. I already driven one.
I already know I want it. I'm just
looking for this exact spec. Um, if we
can go to numbers, I'm all for buying
it.
>> Perfect. Let me get your information
down. We'll move forward. Are you guys
looking to trade something in, pay cash,
finance?
>> Uh, looking to pay cash or finance.
Either way, uh, we're open to financing
if the deal makes sense. Otherwise,
we'll just pay cash.
>> Cool. Yeah, I think there's some
incentivized rates. So they do 0.9 for
36, 1.9 for 48, 29 for 60, 39 for 72,
and 49 for 84.
>> Yeah. Okay. Well, we're definitely open
on that as well. So
>> cool. Do you want to see the longer
terms or shorter terms?
>> Shorter terms.
>> All right. Cool. So I'll show you 36
through 60. Sound good with those
advertised rates?
>> Yeah, sounds great to me. More focused
on the out the door, just so you know,
but definitely want to see those rates
as well.
>> Cool. No problem. Um, and then I got
Tommy. Tommy, what's your real last
name?
>> My real last name? Do I have a fake last
>> Well, I know it's not from buying, so
>> Oh, it's from your m UA.
>> Say it again.
>> M I K U L A.
>> M I K L U buying though.
>> And then what's your address so we can
get title taxes and fees?
>> You know what? I don't love giving my
address, but I can definitely give you
>> How about zip code?
>> Yeah.
>> Got to love taxes in Washington.
>> Yeah. Right.
>> And then is this a good cell phone for
you?
>> Yep. This is the best one. Cool.
So, one of my sales reps is going to
send you over a text message to opt you
in. You can always end it by replying
stop, but that means we can't text you.
So, make sure you reply yes at first and
then we'll shoot those numbers over to
you on the truck. All right.
>> Correct.
>> All right. Cool. All right. Coming your
way.
>> Sounds good. Appreciate it.
>> All right. Cheers.
>> Bye.
One second. I'm getting a phone call
back. This is Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. Alex here.
>> Oh, hey. How's it going?
>> Good, man. So, I just got done with my
meeting with my manager and it looks
like we're able to sell it over to you
for 69281.
>> 69281 you said?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Okay. So, sorry. Let me pull that back
up. So, you guys are at 73980 and now
you guys are at 69. So, you're about
three grand four grand off
>> from the original MSRP. We're
discounting it for that uh for that
price. Yeah. For 69281.
>> 69281 is And that's not out the door.
That's just the sales price, right?
>> That is just the sales price. Yep.
>> And then what's what's above and beyond
that? Is it tax title license? Is there
any dealer add-ons, fees, anything
crazy?
>> Um, let me see if we're able to get you
an actual pencil, but it looks like from
for our dealer discount already gives
you 46.99
for that dealer discount there. And
yeah, in terms of out the door, are you
local to you living in a different area?
>> I live in I I live in Washington but
close to Seattle. Seattle. Yeah.
>> And do you have an RTA tax on where you
live?
>> Oh, I have no idea. I mean, I can give
you my zip code, but that's fine. Exact
out the door. But the zip code,
>> we're running those um figures for you
now.
>> Of course.
>> Yeah. We want to get you We want to get
you accurate licensing and everything
like that for you, man.
>> Thank you.
>> Absolutely. Yep. So, it looks like out
the door price would be $769.90.
That's tactile licensing, everything
included.
>> Okay. And you said you could send me
that pencil.
>> Um yeah, we'll we'll go ahead and get
that worked on to for you right now. Is
it okay if I can send this? Yeah, I'm
also sending you this invoice too as
well, just so you can see where the
numbers are.
>> And just for transparency, you know,
obviously I've been trying to find this.
I I I do have one for about six grand
off already on a white one. Um I'm
trying to get a little better color. I
already have a deal for six grand off.
It's just a white one and I'm trying to
get a different color other than the
white.
>> So we're we're we're currently $46.99
off. So we just need to come up uh what
1,200 bucks, 1,400 bucks.
>> I mean, you get to 6K off is where
you're trying to be. Yeah, correct.
>> All right. We We'll do 60 out plus tax
license.
>> Okay, cool. Let's send that a call
today.
>> All right, I'll get it sent over to you.
>> Okay, sounds good. I appreciate it.
>> All right, thank you.
>> This is the dealership that we thought
knew who I was. What's What's the over
under they know cuz he folded so
quickly.
>> This is Tommy.
>> Hello, Tommy. This is Christian with
>> Hey, how's it going?
>> Good. So, I was talking to my manager
said that you're interested in our F-150
Lariat that we have coming in.
>> Yes, correct.
>> Awesome. Do you have any questions about
it?
>> Well, I already driven one. Already know
I want it. Really? Just trying to get
the best price and I'm hoping we can get
that done with you.
>> Okay, perfect. Let's see here. Where did
you see our truck by any chance?
>> My CR truck? I'm sorry. What?
>> Where did you see our truck? Did you see
like on Autotrader on, I don't know,
Ford? Curtis.
>> Oh, okay. Through our website. Okay. Not
sure if it like you came through a
different spot. So, we have it right now
advertised for $69944.
I'm going to see if there's any more we
can do for you.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I have a I have a deal off
for 6K already. I was hoping try to get
it to close to 10% is what I was trying
to be at.
>> You want to be at 60 grand?
>> No. So, I already have six grand off.
I'm trying I told the last deal I'm
trying to be at 10% off is where I'm
trying to be.
>> Okay. Okay. Okay. So, we need to be at
672.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. What's your zip code?
>> My zip code is
>> Okay. And then I think my manager had
mentioned you're open to either
financing or paying cash. There is some
decently nice interest rates on those
right now. Um but that won't affect the
price or anything. I'm just letting you
know.
>> No, it's good. Okay. I'm more than want
to compare contrasting
>> for sure. All right.
Okay. Okay. So, there's no rebates on
those. Just a second. So, Tommy, let me
give you a call back cuz I said we
already at 4,800 bucks off. So, mean
that means since there is no rebates
from Ford that are going to help us, I
need to get be able to get that extra
2500 from my boss. So, let me see if I
can get you the extra 2500 bucks for
you. Okay.
>> Okay, sounds great.
>> Awesome. Thank you, Tommy. I'll give you
call right back.
>> Okay, sounds good. I'll be here.
>> Bye.
Um, one second. This is Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. It's Christian with
>> Hey, how's it going?
>> Good. All right. So, I talked to the big
boss, too, cuz the the other guy who
answered the phone, he was not
available, so I had to go straight to
the general manager on this one.
>> Okay.
>> And unfortunately, I can't do 68 672,
but I can do 68,500.
That would be my best price on that
unit.
>> 685. So, how much of a discount is that
>> from MSRP? That is exactly $6,170.
>> See, I have one at 67980 plus tax title
license is where I'm at right now. So, I
have one $500 lower. That's why I was
trying to get to that 10%.
>> Okay.
>> G Willickers. I like you, too. You're a
good guy,
>> buddy. I know I am, but it's just that
it's hard. Um, so 500 bucks and you'll
buy it is what is what I think I heard
you say, Tom.
>> Well, I'm already at I'm already at
67980 with the other dealership. So,
that's that's where I'm at with them.
That's where they came. I didn't even
talk about your numbers. I haven't even
seen they they that's where they put it
at. So I obviously I told them 10% as
well and this is where they came at.
>> Okay.
>> So they're like again I'll ask again
talking.
>> I'm here. I'm not doing anything for
another about hour or two. So you got a
little bit of breathing room, but I'd
like to if I can make a decision and get
this all wrapping and rolling, I'm good.
>> Okay. 500 $500 and you won't even call
that other dealership. Or is it 750 and
you won't even call the other?
>> I If you give me 10% off, I'll I'll
ignore I'll put the dealership on red.
I'll ignore them. Hang up. Call it a
day.
>> Oh shoot, man.
>> That's That's not I don't ever call this
dealership back and they're wondering
what happened. They got ghosted is what
happens.
>> Hey,
>> you want me to ghost somebody? That's
for real, dude. Have you ever been
ghosted in real life? Dude, that hurts,
man. When a girl goes,
>> you know how many girls have ghosted me
in my lifetime? A lot.
>> Dude, that's it's it's happened.
Luckily, I'm engaged now and I have a
woman that uh does not ghost me. It's
great. But I I do not I do not miss
those days.
>> See, me, too. I'm engaged now. Happily
going to be married next year, you know.
And even she ignores my calls sometimes,
you know.
>> She's just trying. She's good. I get it,
man. That's good.
>> So, okay. So, let me give it one more. I
think I'm able to get you like 500,
maybe 750 more. I don't know if I can
get you another 1300, but I'm going to
see if I can how close I can get to that
$1,300.
>> Okay, let's see what you can do. I
appreciate you trying, man. I appreciate
$300 away, man.
>> I know. I get it.
>> $300.
>> I get it. Yeah. There's 67.980 plus tax
title license though. So
>> I don't know about the taxes and all
that. I can tell you if I can sell you
the truck for 68 even, you know, then
tax licensing, you know, that's on Uncle
Sam.
>> That's $20 more expensive than this one.
>> Yeah. So Okay. $520. Okay.
>> Yeah. Like I said, you're you're $520
more expens. So I'm trying to I'm trying
to be you're trying to you're trying to
beat that. You told me what it was going
to take for me to never call this
dealership ever again. I'm going to go
somebody. We're going to put the pain
through this dealership. They're gonna
be thinking about Tommy for the rest of
their life. It's got to be 10%.
>> Okay. Okay. Let me see what this
truck's even gonna be here. Let's see.
>> I think he said like any day now.
>> Let's see. Let's do that first. I can't
mess this up. My manager's like, "Hey,
Christian. I got this customer for you.
He's ready to go. He's going to buy it
right now. Don't don't mess it up." And
I come back and Tomy's like, "Christian,
we're like $2,500 away from a deal. What
are you talking about?" Okay. Oh, yeah.
This thing's going to be here like any
day now. It's sitting at the Port of
Portland. So, that means this should be
at my dealership probably. Yeah. End of
the week. Okay. All right, Tommy. Let's
say I get you the money. You're like,
"Yep, let's do it." Can you be here this
weekend or what are we thinking?
>> Yeah, we can come. Yeah, I can put a
deposit on it tonight and put it um come
in tomorrow.
>> Okay.
>> If you're off tomorrow, the next day, I
mean, I'm I'm flex,
Thursday. So, I'm here the whole
weekend, Friday, Saturday, Sunday,
whatever. Uh we we can make it work.
Like I said, it should be here like any
day now. So I don't but so but that that
that's that's a mood point anyways. I
can go grab it whenever since that's
it's at the port. But let me see if I
can get you $13 more $100. We can forget
about the other dealership and we we can
make you drive all the way to beautiful
Portland, Oregon. Okay.
>> I love it. It's beautiful down there.
>> Oh, especially right now.
>> I love it, dude. I I don't have any
reason to go.
>> Yeah. You you want to check out the the
madness that the news says that's going
on.
>> Oh. Oh jeez. I didn't think about that.
Ah, it's fine. We'll we'll be fine.
All right, Tommy, let me give you a call
back. All right, give me like five
minutes.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> All right, thank you. Bye.
>> No problem. I want to talk about this,
guys. Competition drives the price down.
That's it. It's not rocket science. It's
nothing crazy. Competition. Putting two
dealerships against each other. Given
the numbers, call it a day.
>> Christian,
>> call me. I thought you I thought I was
going to be the one who's going to get
ignored though, but when I missed your
call,
>> I I called you cuz I'm trying to figure
out these guys are calling me left and
right. It's like the girl is like,
"Dude, come on. Come on." I'm like,
"Dude, I'm trying to ghost him right
now.
>> I I'm still working on it, man." Um, so
he he put me on ice for a second. Some
customers showed up. So he's like,
"Christian, give me a minute." He's
like, "I think we can put a deal
together, but like just give me a
minute." So I that's why I didn't call
you back right away. And that's and
that's on me. So hopefully longer do you
think otherwise I'm going to just go buy
this other one.
>> With that one close to you,
>> they're both I'm Dude, I'm down to go to
If you give me this deal, I'm down to go
to Portland. Like we don't care. We like
Portland.
>> All right, give me one second. I'm going
to Here, stay on the phone.
>> This is two going to call a day. Come
on.
>> I got Tommy on the phone. He's beating
me up. He's beating me up. Rick,
>> beating him up. Punching him left,
right,
>> he's still at 672. I can't get him to
budge. I know you told me 685. No,
>> 68.
>> Another 500 bucks.
>> See, tell about get fired because of
you. I just want you to know that.
>> Yeah, I have 67. I already have 67980.
You telling that? Thought we're trying
to ghost somebody here. That's what
we're trying to do. We're trying to
ghost somebody.
>> No, no. I'm trying I'm trying to get you
to buy a car from from here.
>> That's what I'm trying to do.
>> You know what's crazy, too? You'll get
your first oil change for free.
>> That's worth like 50 bucks. Okay, fine.
You can give me,
>> you know, 50 bucks less. You win. Good.
Good negotiation skills.
>> What was the number again? Sorry.
>> I see what you're doing. Uh 68,000 plus
>> 68,000 even. So, $20 more expensive than
the deal I have.
>> You in there? Don't bring
>> $20. Are we Are we gonna Are we going to
do this for 20 bucks? All right. $21.
>> I told you the number. I needed to ghost
a man. Dang, man. This sucks. I really
like you, Christian.
>> Man, call me. Oh, he's looking at me
like it's my last day here. Come on.
>> What do you mean it's not your last day
here? You're about to sell a car.
>> Tell me it's only the seventh of the
month. Come on.
>> So what? You're going to wait till the
30th of the month and then tell me
you're going to do the deal and I
already bought a car. So now you know
I'm buying a car. I'm buying a car. Like
I said, I have this other deal. It's a
strong deal. I don't have to drive to
Portland for it. So, I'm willing to
drive Portland. I like Portland. I don't
mind Portland, but I'm not willing to
drive Portland for a dollar, you know?
It doesn't make any sense.
>> Oh my goodness. See what I can do for
you.
>> No. $20. I'll buy you lunch. You You'll
get home with a nice cool pick of gas.
Should I'm all in. That's the problem,
Tommy. I'm all in.
>> So, the best deal you have is 67979
and a free lunch.
>> Yes. So, I can beat that other deal.
I'll beat the other deal by a dollar.
>> So, what's the total discounts right
now? It's like 65 something. 6600.
>> 66.91 is the total discount.
>> 66.91. Okay. Well, I can't I can't ghost
the dealership for that. Give me like 5
minutes. I'm going to decide if it's
worth it. I'm going to talk to my
partner and we'll make a decision. I'll
call you right back.
>> All right, Tommy. I I like you, by the
way. I just want you to know that.
>> I know. And no add-ons, no fees, just
tax title license.
>> Yeah.
>> You hesitated for a minute. Don't scare
me. Don't scare me. The other dealership
is going to charge you some crazy stuff,
just so you know.
>> No, they gave me they gave me an out the
door number. I have the out the door. I
have this right in front of me.
>> Okay. So, if you call me back and if if
you like that number, then I'll give you
an out the door number. I I have to I'll
figure out the taxes and stuff.
>> Well, I'm imagine this other dealership
is probably going to call me and give me
give me the number to ghost you and then
you're going to get ghosted, man. And
then it's going to remind you when you
were dating. Remember those good old
days?
>> Yeah, those were not fun. That's why
>> I don't want to I don't want to get
ghosted by you. You don't want to get
ghosted by me. I wish you just give me
the deal and then we don't we don't have
to ghost each other, you know? I can't I
can't give you that deal. I just can't.
>> This would be like better this would be
a better movie than The Notebook.
Imagine it being a better movie than The
Notebook. People would be talking about
day Christian and Tommy came to a
Cardial.
>> Tommy, what do you do for a living?
>> I talk to people.
>> You talk to people. I see that you're
very good at talking to people. Okay.
Okay. And what what? Give me a little
bit more. I need I need I need I need an
analogy.
>> Call a day. 7K call a day.
>> You what? What' you say?
>> 7K call a day. It rhymes. 7K calls.
>> 7K call it a day. 7K600
7K call it a day. I'm coming down. I'm
being nice cuz I like you and honestly I
want the notebook ending and I
understand sometimes.
>> 7K if if if you finance I'll do 7K.
>> But I'm financing at the low rate.
>> That's fine.
>> Fine. Send me the numbers. Lock it up
right now.
>> Okay. Perfect.
>> Okay. Send me those numbers right now.
We're going to We'll put a deposit on it
and we will lock this deal up.
>> All right. When you want to come in,
>> I'm talking to my business partner right
now. Give me five minutes. Send me those
numbers and we'll talk. I'm calling them
right now.
>> Are you going to put in your personal
name or a business?
>> I'm going to talk to him right now about
which one we're going to do. We'll get
that. But we can put in personal if that
if that that's what we need for the
rate.
>> We're open.
>> Okay. Shoot me your address for your
taxes. Okay. The complete address.
>> Okay, that's fine.
>> Okay.
>> Okay. Sounds good. Um, is this the
number to text?
>> Yeah, that's fine.
>> All right, cool. Give me Yep. I will
send that right now.
>> All right. Thank you, Tommy.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> Bye.
>> Bye. I'm debating if he knows. I don't
know if he knows, right? I don't know if
he knows. I got to get the client
verified. Client, I think, likes this
car a little bit more, but 7K, call it a
day. And this is this is what, right?
Like, I could have just gone through, he
would have gone through. We're going
back and forth, back and forth, back and
forth. And again, I'm pushing him to his
limit. And and I think this is where
people make a mistake, right? Like I
make a lot of jokes and a lot of funny.
I do it in a way that pushes the deal
forward. Like in this one here where
we're talking about the notebook and
making jokes. A lot of people are like
Tommy I don't I don't know. I don't
know. Like that that seems
condescending. Like it's funny. It's in
the moment. It's like let's dude let's
figure this out. It's a joke. It's good.
Let's lighten the mode. Call it a day.
7K. Call it a day. Client is in chat.
Client is saying, "Dude, I'm not even
kidding. My client just said, "By the
way, these two dealerships are the same
distance for me." He said, "I'm watching
live hoping for the Portland deal. Any
way I can get VIN on there. I found the
VIN. I like the car. The distance is the
same. I like I want to work with
Christian. Boom. Okay. So, I'm going to
give the address. This is the only time
where we start giving some personal
information. This looks like a done
deal. So, we're going to give this
address to the person. We got this deal
done. We got two deals done on the
stream. Just a recap. Mazda CX50 Hybrid.
We're able to get a lot of different
offers. I'm going to compare them with
my client, but local and out of state
13% off plus rebates. Remember, we
learned today when we talk about
discounts, we want to make sure it's
discount without any rebates. That's how
we do that, right? Discount plus
rebates. On the second deal, we got just
under 10%, like 9.7%
off of an F-150. There's three in the
state that matched the client's spec.
They had very particular options. We had
an offer for 6K. Bump that all the way
up to 7,400. The original offer we got
was 4K off. So, we ended up getting
$3,000 more. and the perfect car for the
client. Big win there. Done. Got it.
Sending to business partner now. I
appreciate each and every single one of
you. Thank you for dealing with all the
fun things. Thank you for the good.
Thank you for the bad. Tell your friends
and family. Tell your mom, your uncle,
your brother-in-law about us. I
appreciate all of you guys. Dead
serious. That means a lot.
[Music]