We officially are EV free. What that
means is we've gotten all EVs out of
delivered before the timeline. Bada
boom, bada bing. That is exciting cuz
that was nerve-wracking. We're locked
and loaded. Congrats on the EV closeout.
Thank you.
Okay. Ooh, that's not good. Yeah, I'll
jump. I'll I'll I'll pivot. I'll pivot.
Do we need to do Do we need to do a deal
in Texas? That's going to be crazy. Oh
jeez. Fire. Fire. First off, if you work
at GMC and you have a Hummer EV lease
deal on a demo, let me know right now.
We'll get a deal done. We had a client
that they just sold their EV last
second. Happens. It's life. We're going
to pivot. All hands on deck. If you work
at GMC and you can sell this Hummer, do
not tell me just somebody has the car.
If you have it, let me know. I'll call
you right now. Why are we pivoting? We
have a client's deal that fell through,
which is part of life, right? People
always say, "We're just making phone
calls. Call it a day." Sometimes deals
fall through and this is the last second
of the last month. We should have some
deal shell in my first a to call on
people that were trying to do Hummer
deals with me yesterday that I we got
this deal done. So, um unfortunately
life happens. Oh, wait. John, wait one
second. Okay, Matty V has one in
Michigan. But okay, where that's fine.
Wait, where am I calling? Somebody give
me a call Hummer GMC in Florida. They
they are present on TikTok. No, I'm not
doing guys. Only if you work at the
dealership. Call what dealership am I
calling? Discord. Okay, got it. Calling
them right now.
>> Thank you for calling
TMC. If you know your party's extension
number, please dial it at any time. We
are sorry we were not able to answer
your call. Please press zero to try our
receptionist skin.
>> Please hold a moment.
>> He didn't answer either.
Are you guys just giving me names? Am I
just getting trolled? So guys, just so
you guys know what happened. We had a
deal done on a Hummer. We finished all
of our EV deals yesterday. We got a
crazy good deal on this Hummer. Long
story short, the dealership sold the car
from under us. Not ideal. It happens. It
does qualify for it. Tax credits via
lease is how it works. So, you get lease
credits that are built into it. Uh,
which is why that exists. Those lease
credits can go away as of tomorrow. So,
that's it. Yes, it doesn't qualify for
the finance. It qualifies for the lease.
So, dealerships sold it from under us.
So, we're now trying to find a different
one. The current deal we have right now
is it was a $100,000 MSRP. We got a
$15,000 dealer discount on there plus
another $4,250 of incentives. It made
the payment $756 a month without tax
with 756 do it signing.
>> Thank you for calling out. This is
Danny. How can I direct your call?
>> Hey Danny, can I speak to somebody new
car sales?
>> Uh, yes you can. Um, I'll get you over
to a new car sales associate. But first,
can I have your first name to transfer?
>> Yeah, Tommy.
>> Tommy. All right, Tommy. And I see the
phone numbers. I'll transfer you right
over right now to New
>> Awesome. Thank you.
>> Thanks calling. So, this is Ryan. Hey,
Ryan. Uh, I just wanted to see uh if you
guys have a car available.
>> What car are you looking at?
>> Uh, I'm looking for like a demo 2025
Hummer EV. Kind of getting like a last
second crazy lease deal before the
credit ends today. Willing to sign it
all today. Understand you guys closed
soon, but
>> yeah, we closed in about 5 minutes.
Let's see.
>> I'll sign it all remotely so you don't
have to stay late.
>> Um, see
>> I have a deal and then unfortunately the
dealership just kind of screwed us over.
So, uh, we uh they sold us from under
us. So, now we're uh trying to find a
different one.
>> Oh, wow. Where are you uh where are you
located?
>> Uh yeah. So, uh I am in Texas, but I'm
willing to do everything remotely,
deliver the car, whatever it is. I'm
just kind of calling dealerships here at
this point, trying to get us all rocking
and rolling.
>> And we don't have a single one left. I
know we had a couple and they all went
today. They kind of blew them out, which
I'm sure you've heard.
>> Yeah, that's kind of the thing that I
saw. No, no worries. No worries at all.
So, uh I'll keep Thank you so much.
Thank you.
>> Thank you. Byebye.
>> So, if you guys don't know, my name's
Tommy. I negotiate car deals for a
living. My goal is to save you time,
energy, and anxiety. We save you money,
but that's a byproduct. There's a flat
fee you have a,000 bucks. We handle
everything for you. Just so we know what
happened on this deal, so you guys have
a full recap. EV credit ends today. Our
goal was to have everything done by
yesterday for all of our EV deals just
to make sure we were safe. So, if
something like this happened, we would
be good.
>> Thank you for calling. This is Miles.
>> Hey, Miles. Uh, I just want to see if
you guys have a car available.
>> Yeah, absolutely. What uh what vehicle
were you looking for? Hey, so we're
looking for a demo or loner Hummer EV2
pickup. Cheapest one you have for lease
deal. Trying to buy one last second.
Hoping that you can help us out.
>> Yeah, let me see here. It looks like
we've got You said pickup?
>> Yeah, we're looking for a pickup.
>> Yep. We've got a 2025 Hummer EV pickup.
Um it it looks like it just got out of
our our loan car fleet.
>> Awesome. Uh well, I know it's the last
day for the credit. Uh I'll be super
transparent. I have another I had
another deal locked up. They just sold
the car from under me, so I'm trying to
get one. Just similar deal that I have
there and I'll buy it right now.
>> All right. Yeah, absolutely. Let me Is
this a good number to contact you at?
>> Yeah, you can call, text, whatever. I'll
be working here. I'm just trying to get
one of these locked up before the credit
ends.
>> Absolutely. Let me go ahead and get with
my team cuz it's for some reason it's
not pulling up. It says it's here. Um
it's just not pulling up on the website.
So, I want to see what's going on there
so I don't tell you the wrong thing. And
your name was
>> My name is Tommy.
>> Tommy.
>> Yeah. All right, Tommy, let me go ahead
and just see. Yeah, we we have one on.
It's at our offsite location, but it is
here. Is there a time that works for you
to come in?
>> Uh, if we get agreed to numbers, we'll
come in ASAP. We can do the deal
remotely, sign it, whatever makes most
sense for you. But agreed to numbers,
we'll do everything signed right now.
>> Okay. Yeah, absolutely. Let me get with
my manager, get you kind of what we've
got it at, and then we can figure out a
time for you to come in. Does that work?
>> Yeah, that sounds great.
>> All right. And I've got you here in the
system, so I'll send you a message and
get back to you here shortly.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> All right. Thank you.
>> Bye-bye. Guys, I wasn't planning on
working late, but I'm we're going to be
working late to get this deal done for
the client. That's absolutely ridiculous
that a client would fly to you and you
do that. The reason I have a flipping
job, but
>> thank you for call this Richard. How may
I help?
>> Hey, uh, can I are you in new car sales?
>> Yes.
>> Awesome. Hey, perfect, man. I am looking
for a 2025 GMC Hummer EV pickup lease
deal last day of the month. Hoping that
you can help me out.
>> Okay. Did you see a particular stock
number that you're interested in?
>> I think I see one on the website. Yeah,
stock number. I can give it to you
whenever you're ready.
>> I'm ready.
>> Uh 25 L as in lion, T as in tango, 6575.
I think this is Let me switch to my
other Let me switch to my other phone.
Let me switch to my phone. I'm going
transferred you. Okay,
>> you're good. Take your time.
>> A few moments later.
>> Hello.
Hola.
>> Okay. I'm sorry about that.
>> No, you're good. You're good.
>> Okay. I just had it pulled up. 25 LT.
What was the last four again?
>> Yeah. Uh last four is 6575. Okay, got
it. Okay. Yeah, I have 10 grand off of
that one.
>> Okay. Is this a demo unit by chance?
>> Let me see cuz it looked like it has
miles on it.
>> Yeah. I'm looking for Yeah. kind of see
if it's demo cuz I know demos give an
extra rebate.
>> Let me pull it and see what's what's a
good call back number for
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> And give me your name again.
>> My name's Tommy.
>> Tommy.
>> Yeah.
>> All right. Tommy, give me give me five
minutes. I'm going to give you a call
back. Let me pull this vehicle. Make
sure I still have it here. And then let
me make sure get some information on it
for you. Okay.
>> Okay. Sounds good. Take your time.
>> And you're interested in a lease,
correct?
>> I am interested in a lease. Yeah,
correct.
>> Okay. All right. All right. Hang tight.
Let me let me pull the key and make sure
I still have it first.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> All right. I'll call you back.
>> Okay. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> This is Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. This is Miles. We just
spoke. Could I get a little bit more
information from you? So, I looked that
the vehicle is available, the uh 25
Hummer EV pickup, and it's got the two
motors. I'm getting with my manager to
to get a deal sent over to you right
now. Could I just get uh your first
name, Tommy, and then what was your last
name?
>> Makula. M I K U L A.
>> All right. And then this is a good phone
number.
>> Yep. The one you just call me back on
you.
>> Perfect. And what's a good email?
>> I don't email. Can you just text me?
It's easier.
>> Yep, that works. Uh and then a good
address.
>> I can give you my zip code, which is
>> that in
>> um
>> All right. Let me let me go ahead and
send that over to you.
>> Okay, sounds good. Yeah, like I said, I
already had another deal wrapped up.
Unfortunately, this sold it from under
me. So, if I can get a similar deal,
we'll end up just buy that.
>> All right, sounds good.
>> Okay,
over. Thank you. I'll see you. Bye.
>> This is Tommy.
>> Hey, Tom. This is Travis calling you
back.
>> Oh, hey. How's it going?
>> All right. This is my sale. Hey, um I do
have this vehicle available. However, I
do have a customer that's on a test
drive with it right now.
>> Okay. Yeah. You know, obviously I
understand they have first dibs on it.
Is there you going to work a backup deal
on it so they don't buy it?
>> I mean I mean they should be back here
in the next 10 minutes.
>> I'm I'm call Like I said to give you the
long story short, I I have a deal that I
already had wrapped up. They just sold
it from under me. So uh I'm trying to
find one again before the end of the
month. So I'm I'm calling a few
dealerships. Anybody who can give me the
same deal I have, I'm just going to buy
their car. So I'm more than want to do a
backup deal.
>> What deal did you have? Uh they gave me
15 grand off with uh $4,250 of
incentives uh for the reed demo. So 19
$19,250 off.
>> Okay. Oh, now are you local?
>> Uh I'm in Plano.
>> Okay.
>> I'm just calling dealerships at anybody.
>> Sending me Do you mind um sending me
what you have?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I mean I Is this the number
text you?
>> Yeah, you can text it to me here.
>> Yeah, I'll just text you the sheet I
have here. Okay, perfect. Just text you
over the numbers that we have. If you
guys can match that deal, we'll buy
yours.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah. Whatever. remote sign, whatever,
so we can get the deal wrapped up today
or so it's the end of the month.
>> Okay, perfect. All right, let me give
you a call back.
>> All right, sounds good.
>> Thanks for calling, GMC. This is
Malcolm. We had the pleasure of speaking
with you.
>> Hey, Malcolm. My name is Tommy. How's it
going?
>> Going well, Tommy. How's it going?
>> Hey, doing well. Doing well. Hey, I'm
seeing if you guys have a car available.
>> Let's take a look here. This
availability for you.
>> Oh, yeah. I'm ready to buy it. If the
car is available and we can get to the
numbers, it makes sense. Rock and roll.
>> Do you have a particular stock number in
mind? Uh, I I think this one um,
actually this is a One second. I have a
pickup here. I'm looking for a demo 2025
GMC Hummer pickup is what I'm looking
for. Actually,
>> again, do you have a particular stock
number?
>> I thought I had one, but it's actually a
I just realized is an SUV. So, I'm now
looking to see if I can get one that is
not the SUV. So, I don't have the stock
number right in front of me anymore. I
can give me two seconds. I'll get it
pulled up. But, if you can also look for
the one that would be just splendid.
I'm sorry I'm going through all your
inventory, but I'm completely open on
literally everything as long as it is a
Hummer demo lease su or pickup. Um, you
have some 3Xs, 2X's. I'm looking for
your 3xes. I can do I can
>> Where are you calling from, Tommy?
>> Uh, from Dallas.
>> Okay. Are you available to come in today
or
>> if we come on in? Yep.
>> All right. So, what are you trying to
accomplish on the price for the deal?
>> Yeah. Yeah. So, I had another dealership
that I had a deal wrapped up with. Long
story short, they sold the car from
under me. So, um, I'm now trying to find
a replacement. I have 15 grand off of
that dealership plus rebate. Why' they
sell it? Great question. You want to
call them and ask? I have no idea. Like,
great question. I'm uh if I knew that, I
wouldn't.
>> Did you leave them a deposit or was it
just
credited? Everything was on the way to
the dealership and
>> Yep. So, we're now trying to find a
different one.
>> So, what was the vehicle that you were
looking at over there and see if EV
pickup? Um 2X
>> 2X Hummer. I do not have a 2X. I can
tell you that. 3X is just different
colors.
>> Okay. What colors are you open to?
>> Open to any color. Would take a 3X if
the deal made sense.
>> All right. So, how much more are you
willing to pay for a 3X, I would say,
cuz they're going to be about $15,000
difference.
>> 15 They're about a $7,000 difference.
>> I'm sorry.
>> Sorry. I thought it was about a $7,000
difference, not a 15 grand difference.
MSRP is about 100K on a 2X, 107K on a
3x.
>> Yeah, my residual and the money factor
is a lot different on a 3X. So, I guess
I'm I guess at the end of the day, the
payment that you worked out on the 2X
was how much and and how much more are
you comfortable paying for a 3X?
>> 750 a month first payment 750 a month.
Can't do it. No big deal. If you guys
don't have the car, no worries.
>> First payment down on a 3x loaner.
>> Mhm.
>> All right. So, I am selling one here in
the next 45 minutes and that payment is
probably not obtainable on a loaner uh
with just
>> have it from another dealership. So, if
you can't do it, no big deal. I'll call
somebody else. But um but I I have a
deal right here. It's just unfortunately
they just sold it from under me.
>> But on a 2X, correct?
>> Correct. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So, you don't
have a 2X? No big deal. I don't want to
waste your time. It's the last day of
the month. So,
>> yeah. Unfortunately, we've we've sold
out of our 2X's. I've got um looks like
three 3Xs available.
>> Worry about it. You go take care of live
bodies that are there right now. I
appreciate your time.
>> Hello.
>> Hey. Sorry. I was on the other line.
>> Hey. Hey, Tommy. My Hummer is not a
certified I mean a service, so I don't
have an extra discount. Okay. So, you
guys don't have a demo unit?
>> No.
>> Okay. Where I mean, can you guys be
competitive with a non-demo?
>> I mean, my price is my price. I don't
have dealer ads or anything. I'm selling
mine for 86. I can work you up a lease
payment based off that.
>> I mean, if you I
>> I mean, 89. I'm sorry.
>> 89. So, it's more expensive. Um, I mean,
I'm trying to be, like I said, I'm
trying to keep pretty close to the
payment I have now. So,
>> you put money down.
>> Um, nope. Probably had first payment
down 756. I'm trying to get a similar
deal to that.
>> Okay. I can work up my payment. I mean,
but I mean, I can't compete with a car
that's sold.
>> No, I I understand. I I understand. I
can find this deal again. Like I said, I
was we're on our way to buy it today.
So, I understand the car sold. Uh but
that doesn't mean like I can't find
another one of these. Just because one
dealership sold it doesn't mean somebody
else will match. So, no big deal if you
can't or if you can be competitive with
it. Good.
>> Yeah, I'll send you over my very best.
How about that?
>> Okay. Sounds great.
>> Okay.
>> All right. Bye.
>> I'm being as straightforward as I can.
Yeah. I'm just trying to be honest with
people. Being honest, I've figured out
is sometimes the best way to do it. I
could lie and go through the whole game.
I just need people to either give me a
deal or move on, right? Like I don't
need the the back and forth game right
now. This is exactly why you don't tell
the dealership everything. I'm trying to
get no BS fast results, which is not the
best for negotiation. You see, every
time I say a dealership sold the car
from under me, rather than them being
sympathetic and be like, "Oh my god, let
me get you taken care of." They said,
"Well, that car is already sold, so I
can't compete with a car that's sold."
See, this is Nico here. Oh,
>> this I'm sorry. Who is this?
>> This is Nico.
>> Nico, sorry. It was just a whole bunch
of couldn't even understand. Awesome.
Hey, uh, are you a new car sales?
>> Yes, sir. How can help you out?
>> Awesome. Love it. Hey, I just want to
see if you guys have a car available.
>> Yes, sir. What's your name?
>> My name's Tommy.
>> Okay, Tommy. Nice to meet you. What
vehicle you looking at?
>> Uh, I'm looking for a Hummer EV pickup
uh 2X. I'm looking for hopefully a demo
unit.
>> Hey, Tommy, give me one second here.
Where are you calling from?
>> Uh, Dallas.
>> Dallas. Okay. Are you looking for that
lease special everyone's calling about?
Uh
>> I I don't know if it's a particular
lease special. I mean, long story short,
I'll give you the the long story short,
I had a deal, wrapped up, did the credit
app, did all this, ready to go on our
way to the dealership. It looks like
they sold it from under us and just
called us to let us know they sold it to
somebody else even though we had a
deposit on it. So, they gave us our
money back, but now we're trying to find
another one in the grand scheme of time.
So, uh just so we're clear, just trying
to find I already have a deal. If you're
willing to match that deal, I will buy
that car today.
>> Okay, tell me, hold on one second.
What's the What's the lease payment they
told you at? I have a 75645
payment. First payment down, 15 grand
dealer discount. Uh $4,250 other
incentive for the lease money or for the
demo money. We're also Costco members I
can send you this too.
>> Okay. But no uh no supplier or GME V
code.
>> No, no, nothing on those.
>> Okay. No. So I don't have any loaners. I
have some 26 models. Um so I don't have
anything that would get you down to that
payment. Let let me ask you this quick
question and you tell me if I'm right or
way off. You you sound like the guy who
negotiates deals online.
>> Yes. Yeah, that's me.
>> True or not true?
>> This is true.
>> That is you.
>> No, I love it.
>> Long story short, yeah, you're looking
for a one-off car. I don't know how many
CTPs you'll find around the market out
here.
>> There's one that your competitor that
your competitor that story is true. We
lit the client was flying to Dallas back
from their trip and long story short.
They just sold it from under him. So, if
you don't have one, no big deal. I got
to find one before the deadline ends.
Have you got any word that they're
extending the credit? Like does GM said
anything?
>> No, they it could be a thing where they
try to with GM we we residualize the
credit. I'm sure you know that if if you
work deals with people all the time. So
really it's just going to come down to
buying the car. Um that payment is not
entertainment. I mean that's a that's a
payment you can get to if you get a car
that has that credit. Yeah.
>> So you just got you just got to find
someone who has a car.
>> Can you give me any insight to anybody
that might have it?
>> Uh yeah. Hold on.
>> Appreciate you.
>> Yeah. Do do you do a lot of GM deals out
here in the DFW area or No,
>> I do. I do a bucket load. It's one of
the biggest brands.
>> Here, if you want to take my number
down, I'll give you my sell number, but
you normally aggressive.
>> I normally don't miss deals. If there's
a crazy stupid one out there, I normally
won't match it, but like the the number
you're giving me is a pretty reasonable
one. And where we used to be able to
sell them if we had one.
>> Yeah. No.
>> Um, you want a SU or SUV?
>> Uh, we're looking for a pickup. Uh 2x
MSRP should be right around 100K. 99K.
>> Yeah, they're all going to be the same.
Yes, sir. Give me one second.
>> You're good. Take your time.
>> Oh, I don't see one local that I could
help you out with.
>> Dang. Okay. So So none in Dallas, so I
should be looking outside Dallas.
>> No. Yeah, I would I would probably go
outside of Dallas. Where was the store
that you were talking to at before?
>> Um I can get the exact one as my one of
my teammates that had it. They were I
thought they were in Dallas, but um give
me two seconds. I'm also live so I don't
want to give the location even though
they're they did that.
>> Oh, you're good.
>> It's okay.
>> No, I don't see that one.
>> Yeah, I don't see anything that's local
around here. Best of luck with it and I
know I have that one listed online. It's
it's being long gone, but yeah, if you
need anything in the future, um you have
my personal number and then again, my
name's Nico. Reach out to me, brother.
And then I'll be happy to help you out
or um make things easy for you on the GM
world.
>> All right, appreciate it, man.
Appreciate it.
>> No problem, brother. Best of luck.
>> Hey, no problem. Bye.
>> All right. Bye.
>> Bye.
I'm sorry. The number you have dialed is
not in service.
>> What? Okay, fine. I won't call you. This
dealership is a 10,ou I'll call him.
I'll call him. I don't like it. Do not
like it, Sam. I do not like this
dealership that has 10 grand of ads.
>> Thank you for calling. This is Buen
speaking. How can I help you?
>> Hey, um my name's Tommy. I just want to
see if you guys have a car available.
>> Yeah, absolutely. Tommy, what's uh is it
a new vehicle or a pre-own? Uh, I think
it's a demo, but new demo.
>> Okay. Do you have the stock number by
any chance?
>> Uh, yeah, I think I have the stock
number of the one that would work here.
It's S is in SAM. U is in uh uranium 110
912.
>> That's a GMC, right?
>> Correct. Got it.
>> It's a Hummer EV.
>> Hummer EV. Also, that one is pickup. I
guess
>> that one's what?
>> It's a pickup.
>> It's a pickup. Yeah, pickup.
>> Yes, Tommy, we do have it.
>> Okay. And is that a demo as well? Yes,
this one is uh this one is a demo, but
this one has additional accessories on
it.
>> Okay. What are I guess um do you guys
have one without accessories on it? What
are the accessories?
>> So, it has a different wheels. Uh bigger
wheels, bigger tires.
>> Okay. And those wheels are 10 grand.
>> Yeah, it's already discounted it. U so
10 grand. So, basically it cancels out
kind of thing.
>> Yeah. No, I get that. But dealerships
are giving 15 20 grand off these cars.
So, give me 10 grand. Give me 10 grand
wheels. Appreciate it. wheels must be
super nice to be 10 grand wheels, but do
you guys have one without the 10 grand
wheels?
>> Are you planning on leasing this vehicle
or buying it?
>> Look, looking to lease it, ready to do
it all today.
>> Okay. Yeah, I can actually tell you
numbers on this one.
>> Yeah. Uh I mean, long story short, I
already have numbers from another
dealership. I thought I was going to go
buy that one. They sold it from under
me. If your wheels are 10 grand, I don't
think we're going to be anywhere close
to those numbers. But if you have one
without the wheels, or you can match the
deal they have with those wheels, I'm
all for hearing it out.
>> Okay. What's the What's the deal that
they give you? Uh, I have a 756 payment,
first payment down, plus taxes. I'm a
Costco member. I don't have supplier.
And it ends up being a 15 grand discount
plus a $4,250 rebate to get me to 756.
>> 756 and zero down.
>> Uh, first payment. Yeah. And plus and
then 756 plus tax.
>> 756 plus tax.
>> Correct.
>> Okay. And the the first payment like the
do at signing is like around 23 grand.
>> No, first payment would be 756.
>> Oh, just like that. Okay.
>> Yeah. Yeah. first pay down.
>> What What was the term?
>> Um, give me one second. Let me pull that
up. It is 36 months. 36 months, 12,000
mi a year, $100,000 MSRP, $15,000
discount, $4,250
incentive. Payment without tax is
$756.45 with do at signing $7,585645.
>> Okay. So, is this your good number?
>> That is my number.
>> Okay. Amazing. Let me just get some
information from you really quick so I
can send you a text message. Please opt
in and send me that. If you can just
send me a screenshot of that and I will
see what if if we can match it right
away.
>> Yep. I will send that right now.
>> If we can match it, are you going to be
okay with the accessories for this
vehicle?
>> If you match the deal, sure. I mean, I
don't see why not. Why wouldn't I?
>> Okay. Spell your name for me, please,
Tommy.
>> Uh, spell my name is Tommy. T O M Y.
>> Okay. And last name?
>> Mucula. M I K U L A.
>> Got it. And what's your email address?
>> I don't use email. Can you just text me?
>> Sure, absolutely.
>> Thank you.
>> No problem. Give me one second. I'm
going to need your zip code.
>> Yeah, you need the zip code that I'm
going to be registering the car in. Is
going to
>> Okay. So, I'm sending you a text right
now. I just did. And uh please opt in.
Send me the send me the the the deal
sheet that you you have from the other
dealer and let me start working on this.
>> Just send it to you. Should be in your
box.
>> I'll give you a call back.
>> Yep. Let's rock and roll.
>> All right. Cool. Thank you. I'll call
you back in a in a few minutes. Okay,
sounds good.
>> Thank you, sir.
>> Puts $10,000 wheels on an EV that isn't
going to sell. Stupid.
>> Thank you for calling.
Noel, who the you speak to?
>> Hey, Noel. My name is Tommy. Are you in
new car sales?
>> I'm sorry.
>> Hey, my name's Tommy. Are you in new car
sales?
>> I'm one of the BC managers uh that looks
over the car inventory. Is there
something you inquire about there?
>> Uh, yeah. Um, I'm looking for a
particular car, but I'm also open to
cars as well. I haven't I can give you a
stock number, though.
>> Yeah. What's the stock number? Uh yeah,
it's uh G is in golf 01522.
>> G01522.
>> Yep.
>> Okay. And then what was your name again,
sir? I'm sorry.
>> My name's Tommy.
>> Tommy.
>> Yep. GMC guy. If you
>> last name for you, Mr. Tommy.
>> My last name is Makula.
>> And how do you spell that?
>> M I K U L A.
>> This is going to be the new the Hummer E
pickup wax. Is that correct?
>> Yeah. The courtesy demo. Yeah.
>> Yes, sir. It's still available in a lot.
So, will you come out today to check it
out?
>> Uh well, I already uh long story short,
I already have a deal that I know I
like. dealership sold it from under me.
So, I have numbers on a car. If you guys
can match that car, I'll come buy it
today. If you guys can't match that
deal, no big deal. Call somewhere else.
Super easy.
>> Gotcha. I mean, yeah, we help match
match that deal for you. By chance on a
deal you were working on where you're
looking to trade in a vehicle, put any
money down?
>> Nope. No trade. Uh just first payment
down on the lease.
>> Gotcha. Okay. If you like, let me see if
I get one my one of my sales
professionals or one of my EV
specialists on the line for you so that
way we can help get this process started
for you.
>> I love it.
>> All right. Give me one quick moment.
Also, people can wonder why I'm so short
with people because like this is the
most inefficient way to buy a car. Why
did you need all that information just
to transfer me to somebody when I said I
want numbers on a car? It's cuz it's
their job in order to get that
information so they can get paid because
they paid on appointments. It's just a
silly process. This whole thing is dumb.
Make it easier to buy a car. Make this
There's so much inefficiency. So, now
I'm going to How long do I hold? BDC is
a joke. I wish there was better BDC. I
wish BDC had actual purpose, but right
now does not make sense. Yeah, correct
Legend. You're right. I'm going to get
transferred to somebody who has no idea
who I am. I'm gonna give it like another
30 seconds and I'm probably gonna hang
up and call the dealership that's spam
calling me. Do I really want to hold?
How long do I want to go on hold? I'm
gonna call this other dealership just in
case they have a deal.
>> Is this Tommy?
>> This is Tommy.
>> Hey Tommy, I apologize for that wait.
Um,
>> you're fine.
>> I just got the numbers here.
>> Okay.
>> So, it looks like out the door on this,
this is the 2025 Hummer EV pickup. We've
got it at 108335.
Um, and then with our ads, which is
going to be a door or door edge guards
and then uh window cup guards, uh, it's
$4.95 and then tax total licensing,
we've got you at 8167.
Uh, that brings your 36 if you're
leasing for 36 months or 36. Yeah, 36
months. Uh, it'll be 142894.
>> Yeah, there's no way. I have a payment
for 756 right now. Okay.
>> Payment down. Yeah, that's crazy. That's
crazy talk. You're literally twice as
much payment on the same car.
>> Yeah. I apologize. That's just kind of
where we're at with our with our Hummers
right now.
>> Yeah. I mean, I know. Last last day of
the month, last day of the EV credit and
you guys are twice the payment. That's
crazy. It is. It is. Uh if your manager
wants to sell the car before the last
day of the month and I have a payment
for 756, if he can match that deal, I'm
willing to buy it.
>> All right. Let me go see. Willing to
have a conversation with him. I don't
know. I mean, that's almost double, but
I'll absolutely see what I can do.
>> Yeah, that's crazy. Um, like I said,
that's a crazy payment, but if it's a
demo, you should be able to get there.
It's 15 grand off plus $4,250
rebate for it being a demo plus Costco.
And then it's buy rate. So, I imagine
two points and not doing any discount
and adding ads to it.
>> I've got you with that Costco. So,
that's the 12 1250. And then, do you
have a GMC executive referral?
>> Nope. Don't have referral. Don't have
supplier. Didn't need it.
>> Okay. So, just that Costco then?
>> Yep. Just the Costco. But it's 15k
dealer discount is what they would have
to do. They'd have to give me buy rate
and they'd have to give me the $4,250 in
rebates for it being a courtesy.
>> Let me see. I'm I'm happy to have a
conversation with him.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Like I said, we're willing
to wrap this up whenever it makes most
sense.
>> All right. I'll call you back, Tommy.
Thank you.
>> A lot of people say dealerships. There's
only 800 bucks of markup in a car. That
dealership, if it would have just
blindly said yes to the car, would have
been $700 a month more. 700* 36 is
somebody can do the math. But that
dealership is attempting to try. Like
that's insane. Like what in the world?
>> This is Tommy.
>> Hey Tommy, how you doing? This is Asel
from
>> Hey, how's it going?
>> Good. Good. How are you?
>> Hey, doing well. Doing well.
>> Awesome. Yeah. My internet engine let me
know that you were in contact with them
about a Hummer lease. Just wanted to
follow up with you, see what I can help
you with.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So, like I said, uh I
already know this is the car I want. Uh
looking just for a Hummer EV2 lease
deal. I had another deal. It just
unfortunately fell through. So, trying
to just match this deal and I'm want to
buy it today.
>> Gotcha. It's the black on my right. 2x
the one that I see here on my system.
>> Yeah. Yeah. 2x is totally fine. Black is
fine. Open on any color. Just looking
for a demo lease deal. That's great.
>> Last day of the month.
>> No, that that's the way to do it, man.
That's
>> Yeah, thank you.
>> Gotcha. But yeah, let me check on this
one. I mean, do you have um your deal
that fell through? Is there anything
they're offering you? Anything I need to
I need to get to your business?
>> Yeah, it's a So, I have a 756 payment,
first payment down plus tax is where I'm
at right now. So, if you guys can match
that deal, I'm willing to buy it today.
>> Can I repeat? Sorry, the land was
cutting off a little bit.
>> Yeah. No, you're fine. 7.56 a month
first payment down. Um, plus tax.
>> And for the term, was it 36 months,
$10,000? What What type of term are you
looking at?
>> 3612.
>> All right. Are you local here, by the
way?
>> Uh, I mean, uh, Dallas.
>> Oh, okay. Gotcha. All right. Well, let
me get to work on this one. I need to
see which one is um out of loner status.
We're just getting them out of loner
status this week. So, let me check on
this one. We're They're available to
sell, so let me see what we can do for
you. Okay, awesome. Let me know. Call me
back.
>> Sounds good. Bye. Bye.
Thank you for calling.
>> Please tell me what department you're
trying to reach.
>> You can say sales.
>> Sales.
>> Welcome to the GMC parts department.
Please have your VIN or vehicle
identification number ready so we can
verify the correct parts information.
Please continue to hold and the next
available part specialist will be with
you momentarily.
>> I'm going to just call back because I'm
just going to get to parts and I don't
want to talk to parts. The deal wasn't a
mistake. that has made more more money
on a different customer.
>> Thank you for calling.
Please tell me what department you're
trying to reach today. You can say sales
service.
>> Sales department
>> finance operator. Welcome to the
parts department. Please have your vin
or
>> thank you for calling.
Please tell me what department you're
trying to reach today. You can say sales
service
>> sales
>> part finance.
If your AI can't get sales from sales
department, you need a different AI. You
clearly said parts. I said sales
department. You're asking me what
department am I calling.
>> Sorry, we are unable to complete your
>> This is Todd Sales. How may I help you?
>> Hey, Ty. This is Tommy. I just want to
see if you guys have a car available.
>> Okay. What car would it be?
>> Uh, I have a stock number if it helps.
>> Yeah, go ahead.
>> Uh, stock number is 118522.
the uh white Hummer.
>> Uh yeah, that's it. As as long as it's a
courtesy demo is kind of what I'm
looking for.
>> Yes, sir. That's what it was. It
>> was or is.
>> No, it it is uh it's available right
now.
>> Oh, awesome. Well, I'm super interested
in buying one. Uh long story short, I
have a deal that I already had.
Unfortunately, the dealership just sold
it from under me. So, if you guys can
match this deal, I'm more than willing
to buy yours instead.
>> Okay, let me get some information from
you. Uh what kind of what kind of deal
are you looking for? Uh, so the deal
that I have right now, I can give you
all the exact numbers that I break down
to get there, but it's 756 a month,
first payment down. I have Costco. Uh, I
can give you the exact breakdown of the
numbers, but that's the least payment.
>> Okay. Yes, sir. Hold on one second. I
think my manager who handles that just
left. Give me one second. I'm going to
see if he's still here. Okay.
>> Sure. Take time.
>> Okay.
>> If you know anything for anybody that
says that this deal is fake, it's not
fake. It's actually not even that super
aggressive of a deal. There's been way
more aggressive Hummer deals. We've
talked to somebody in this that works at
GMC that says as long as you can find a
demo deal, that deal is not
unreasonable. The I the Costco gets you
$1,000 rebate. Yes, it does. So, the
idea that it's a fake deal is not true.
We already have deals around $800 a
month. We do need an aggressive deal,
but that being said, it's not
impossible. He's also muted. What's a
demo deal? Meaning the car is in demo.
Costco does mean something. You get a
rebate for being at Costco on a Hummer
lease deal.
>> Okay. So, my manager that handles leases
is already gone for the day. I can get
Yeah, I can get all your information and
try to work on it tomorrow if that's
something you're interested in. I mean,
the problem is is the UV deal ends
tomorrow. So,
>> Yes, sir.
>> Yeah. So, I appreciate that. But, uh,
I'm hoping to found one before that
happens. So, yeah, I appreciate it, but
thank you.
>> Yes, sir.
>> So, we have a $799 payment right now is
the closest we have. Uh, which is what
Dakota's found. Obviously, I'm trying to
do better than that. We don't have any
guarantee to the client, but we're
obviously going to keep working as hard
as we can to try to find this deal.
>> This is Amy.
>> Hey, Amy. Uh, I just wanted to talk to
somebody in new car sales.
>> Yes, I can help you.
>> Yeah, awesome. Hey, I just want to see
first off you guys have a car available.
>> Okay. And go. What is the vehicle?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Sure.
>> It's S as in Sierra Uranium 113834.
>> GMC Hummer EV pickup 2X.
>> Correct. As long as it's a courtesy,
then I'm interested.
>> Okay. And you said what?
>> As long as it's a courtesy demo would be
what I'm looking for. I think it's a
courtesy, but I verify.
>> Yeah, absolutely. Can you hold for just
one moment? Take your time.
>> All right. Thank you.
>> I'm being very short with the
dealerships cuz I don't have time to
waste. Like this is just they either
Yes, I could do user. If you can get me
that same a similar lease deal, I'd
consider it. But like I there's no
reason to waste. They either can do the
deal or don't do the deal. And that's
where I'm at. So we already have a $799
deal. I don't I'm not going to have
anything else. We're going to do
everything we can to get this deal taken
care of. And the client's going to know
that we took care of them. This isn't
their fault. It's not our fault. It's
nobody's fault. I mean, it's the
dealership's fault, but like our goal is
not to complain. This dealership's
calling me. $1,071 payment. We're not
even close. A $1,000 discount.
>> Hello, sir.
>> Hey, how's it going?
>> No, no, no. You're fine. Uh, so this
vehicle is here and available, but it is
not a courtesy demo.
>> Okay. Do you have a courtesy demo?
>> Uh, we do. Um, let me see. Hang on. Let
me go back to the other ones. Okay. So,
courtesy demos that we have currently.
See both of these. Are you you're
specifically looking for the truck or
the
>> correct? Yeah, I'm looking for the
pickup of
>> Okay. And a 2X truck. Okay. So, one.
Okay. So, we have one that is currently
courtesy demo pickup truck. It is the
GMC Hummer EV pickup 2X and that one is
Interstellar White.
>> Awesome. I'm interested in it. If we can
get to the payment I'm looking for on a
lease, I'm willing to lock it up today.
>> Okay. And where are you trying to be at
on a lease?
>> So, 756 a month first payment down plus
tax. Um, I do qualify for Costco. I do
not have supplier.
>> Okay. Which Costco is it? The gold or
the executive?
>> The executive.
>> Executive Costco. Okay.
>> Got to get that 250 bucks. No trade.
>> Okay. You said 7 756 a month, right?
>> 756 a month. 756 down. Yep. Correct.
>> All right. So, not a supplier. Let me
look over a couple others.
>> All right. And what is your name?
>> My name is Tommy.
>> You said Tommy.
>> Yeah, that is correct. Correct.
>> Okay. And your best contact number?
>> Yep. Um, my zip code is set.
>> What range of uh lease are you looking
at?
>> 3612.
>> Got it. Okay. All right. Let me get with
my manager and my name is Amy. I'll be
your contact person and I'll give you a
call back. Okay.
>> Okay. Sounds good. Thank you. Bye.
>> All right. Thank you, sir. Bye.
>> Hello there, Adam. Who do I have the
pleasure of speaking with today?
>> Hey, my name is Tommy. How's it going?
>> Going all right. How you doing?
>> Hey, I'm doing well. I just want to see
if you guys have a car available.
>> Yes. And then if you don't mind me
asking real quick, what was your last
name? Makula. M I K E U L A. I think
this guy knows who I am.
>> EU L.
>> Correct. I think so. Just the way it
Yes, sir. You said you were looking for
a specific vehicle.
>> Yeah, I have a I have a stock number
whenever you're ready.
>> Oh, you got a stock number. You came
prepared.
>> I love it. Yeah. Uh it's H is in Hummer,
S is in Sierra 3133.
>> Alrighty. So, correct me if I'm wrong.
HS 3133.
>> That's it.
>> Yes, sir. All righty. I've got it pulled
up.
>> Okay. And it's available.
>> Yes, sir. It is available.
>> Awesome. Well, I already know this is
exactly what I want. I'm really just
trying to get to a certain lease deal.
Last day of the month, last day of the
EV credit, witching hour. Just trying to
get this deal done. If you can do this
deal, I'll buy it today.
>> All righty. If if you don't mind me
coming out and being point blank period,
I mean, where are you trying to be?
>> Super easy. Uh 756 a month, 756 down,
3612 lease. Qualify for Costco. I don't
qualify for supplier.
>> You said 76 a month.
>> 756. 756 a month. 7656
down.
>> Yep.
>> And then what terms did you say?
>> 3612.
>> All righty. And then you say you qualify
for Costco.
>> Costco executive but not supplier.
>> All righty. And then what is your
current address just for titling
purposes as well as incentives?
>> Yeah. Uh zip code.
>> Allrighty. I tell you what, let me build
your profile here real quick. Nobody
said that I was smart. People just
understand that I know what I'm talking
about when it comes down to this exact
subject.
>> And then you said it was Tommy, correct?
T O M Y.
>> Sure, that's fine. I spell. So, it
doesn't matter either way.
>> Oh, it it does for my system. How do you
spell it?
>> T O M I.
>> T U M I.
>> That's it.
>> All righty.
>> Doesn't matter in the system.
>> All righty. I'm probably going to shoot
you a text here in a second. If you
could send over a picture of your
driver's license, that would help me out
exponentially.
>> I don't like this private information if
I don't have to. I mean, like I said, I
can give you everything you need in
order to make this deal happen. Like I
said, I'm willing to do it just plus
tax. 756 plus tax is what I'm looking
for. So, you don't have to calculate the
tax.
>> So, 7
>> 756 plus tax, you know, I don't want to
go through down the rabbit hole. I know
exactly what I'm looking for. I know
it's an aggressive deal. If you guys can
do it, that's great. If not, no big
deal. No hard feelings, but it's going
to require a $15,000 dealer discount
plus a $4,250 in rebate. So, if you're
willing to do that, that's great. I'll
get everything over. We'll sign it all
tonight, but I don't want to give you my
driver's license just to say that you
can't give the deal. So,
>> that's okay. But, I mean, it's credit
dependent is part of it. So, we would
have to do a credit application.
>> That's fine. I have perfect credit. I'm
not worried about that.
>> Okay. That's what I was trying to make
sure is that we were going to qualify.
>> Yeah. Yeah. That I don't I have great
credit, perfect credit, best credit,
something.
>> Okay. So, over 800
>> over 800 high score. All alighty. Well,
tell you what. Let me take this to my
manager. I can probably get back with
you. We'll say 10 minutes.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> All righty. Bye-bye.
>> Okay, sounds good. Bye.
>> How may I help you?
>> Hey, I just want to see if you guys have
a car available.
>> I'm sorry, sir. Can you say that one
more time, please?
>> Hey, I just want to see if you guys have
a car available.
>> Yeah, absolutely. What are you looking
for?
>> Oh, I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Sure, let's hear it.
>> Uh S is in Sierra, U is in uranium.
120112.
Sometimes it doesn't pop up on my end
and unfortunately this is one of those
times. Uh would you be able to just give
me some vehicle specifics if you don't
mind?
>> It is a Hummer EV2 courtesy demo. Pickup
2X.
>> Okay, perfect. That makes it easy. Sure.
Easy peasy. I'll
>> pull that up for you. I'm so sorry, sir.
Did you say the SUV or was it the truck
you were looking at?
>> The pickup.
>> The pickup. And which color was that?
>> It was gray. But I'm open to any color
that you have. That's a demo. That's
>> gray.
>> Yep. But open to any color in theory.
>> Okay. The only other one we have is
going to be a graphite blue metallic.
So, it's going to be a much darker blue.
>> Completely open to either one, whichever
one.
>> They're going to be just almost No,
absolutely. We're here to give you a
deal. Well, we do have both in stock.
Both are sitting on the lot right next
to each other. Is there a time this week
you'd like to come in, test drive it,
and check it out?
>> Neither one of us want to wait this week
because the EV credit ends today.
>> Oh, that's right. Yes, sir. Were you
looking at coming in today then? I'm
looking to get the numbers over the
phone today and if we can do that, I'll
I'll remotely sign it and come in and
buy the car. Super easy.
>> Okay, I completely understand, sir.
Unfortunately, I just wouldn't be able
to give you numbers over the phone.
Something we'd rather do in person.
Otherwise, you might not sell the last
two Hummer EVs you have 3 hours before
the end of the credit. And I mean, your
manager might not want to sell the car.
It's fine. But like, you guys have what,
an hour before you guys close and the EV
credit ends and you guys are going to be
stuck with us, too. So, if not, no big
deal. I'll call somebody else. Like I
said, I'm super easy, super simple. I
have a deal in mind. You can do it.
That's great. If not, no big deal. But
the chances of you selling this to
Hummers in the next hour are slim to
none. So, I understand you'd prefer me
to come in store, but chances are you're
probably not going to sell them.
>> Sure thing. Let me go talk to my sales
manager and see if he has something he
can write up for you.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> Give me just a moment.
>> This is this is where this is why I I'm
frustrated with uh the lack of
understanding your job. You should know
the EV credits ending today. This should
be an all like right now we have an all
hands on deck for a client that has an
EV deal. That should be every car
salesman's responsibility right now. I
had to tell him the EV credit was done.
And the idea that he's like, "Oh, I'm
sorry. Just do you want to come in this
week? I guess we wouldn't do it." Like,
dude, if you're a sales manager, it
should be I don't care if you don't
normally do deals. Every live body
that's on a Hummer right now, I want to
see them. I want to talk to them. I want
to speak to them because the idea behind
it is the credit's going to be gone
tomorrow. If the credit's gone tomorrow,
then like there's no getting this deal.
It's absurd. So yeah, I'm gonna be mean
to the guy, but like I'm not I don't
have time to play games because uh sir
text. Hello.
>> I'm gonna transfer you over to another
salesman that's more available right now
and he'll be more than happy to help you
out with this deal.
>> Sure. Sounds good. Aka more experienced
salesperson. I muted him, but yeah.
Thank you.
>> Yeah.
>> Hey, this is Jacob. How can I help you?
>> Hey, Jacob. Um just looking for this EV
deal. Hoping you can help me out.
>> Okay. What can I do for you?
>> Do you Did he give you the stock number,
all the information, or do you need to
give you that again?
>> No, sir. just told me that uh there was
somebody looking to buy a Hummer. That's
all I know.
>> Okay, I can give you the stock number. I
think I can go pull it up again. I can
give you the stock or it's a Hummer EV2.
I don't I think I might have closed out
of it. Actually, I think I have it.
Stock I can give you a stock number.
It's a meteorite gray.
>> I'll tell you what. Give me one.
>> Give me just a moment here, sir. I need
to get you entered into my system. Hold
on just a second.
>> Sure.
>> I got you a number.
>> That is correct.
>> Okay. Give me just a moment here. And
your first name?
>> My name is Tommy.
>> What's your first name? Tommy.
>> Tommy.
>> Yeah.
>> Is that your legal first name or is
Thomas your legal first name?
>> My My legal name is Thomas Slav, but I
go by Tommy.
>> Last name is Love. L O V E.
>> It's not. But if you want to call me
Love, that's fine. Is that correct? I
mean, my girlfriend would be a little
mad with you, but that's fine.
>> I'm sorry. I must have misunderstood.
What's that last name?
>> Yeah, last name Makula. M I K U L A.
>> Yeah, man. Samsonite. I was way way off.
>> No. Oh yeah, my first name is Thomas
Slav. Like it's inspiration. That's
first.
>> Oh, okay. That's what Okay, so Thomas t
h o m a s. How do I spell the rest of
that?
>> S L A V. Just add that to the end.
>> I only ask because if we come to an
agreement and you everything works out,
I have to have everything on here
exactly the way it is on your ID. That's
why I'm going through all this. What's a
good email for you, Thomas?
>> I don't use your email. Can you text it?
>> I can. They just typically want us to
have one. I'm not worried about I don't
have to have it right now, though.
>> Perfect. Hey, what's the stock number
you're interested in?
>> Stock number is S is in Sierra. U is in
uranium 12112.
[Music]
>> Okay, sir. Uh so what are we trying I
mean I know you said you're trying to
buy this. I I'm assuming you're want to
get this before the tax credits in.
>> Correct.
>> Okay. And is there a particular number
you're hoping to get on this?
>> $756 a month plus tax. 756 down 3612
lease. 756 down, 756 a month.
>> Yep. 3612.
>> Okay. I tell you what, give me I've got
your phone number here. Give me a few
minutes and I'll let you know if that's
going to be possible.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> Give him about 5 minutes. I'll call you
back.
>> Okay. Sounds good. Bye.
>> All right. Thank you, sir.
>> Bye.
>> Thank you for calling
Myin. Hello.
>> Hey, can I speak to I think I thought I
was talking to you and then I think I'm
talking to Sony now.
>> Oh, yes. Give you one second.
>> I'm sorry. The number you have dialed is
not in service.
>> Dude, some sales people, they are
starting to fr frustrate me.
>> Enjoy your food. That looks good.
>> This is Tommy.
>> Hi. How you doing?
>> Hey. Uh, yes. Um, I think we're texting
back and forth on this uh Hummer.
>> Yes, sir. So, the vehicle's here.
>> Yes.
>> Yeah. So, so I guess uh what I'm asking
for is some a little bit of creativity
there. Uh, I'm not you you don't want me
driving all the way from Dallas tonight
to Houston, which is going to take me
what 3 4 hours for you to stay late. So,
that means you're going to be staying
till 10:00 tonight in order to make this
deal happen. Uh, if you want to stay
that late and you can guarantee the
deal, I'm more than willing to have the
conversation, but this is the last day
of the Hummer EV credit. The chances of
you guys selling this in the next hour
and a half is probably slim. I'm willing
to buy it. So, I'm asking for like a
creative solution. So, you guys can lock
in that we can all lock in the deal
today and then we can figure out picking
up tomorrow. I understand you guys don't
normally do remote deals, but like it's
like a unique situation.
>> Yeah. I just talked with my finance
manager. He said that we needed to be
contracted by the end of the day.
>> I'm willing to sign everything remotely.
>> Correct. But we can't e sign a lease. It
needs to be wet signatures.
>> You you don't have any capability doing
any I mean there has to be some type of
solution.
>> Yes, sense.
>> And I believe so. Um I'll just have to
go to the GM general manager to see what
what we can do outside the box. So, just
give me a few minutes and and I'll make
some calls and see what we can do for
you.
>> Okay, perfect.
>> Yes, sir. Thanks for working for me.
>> No, no problem. Thank you. Hopefully, we
understand.
>> Thank you, sir.
>> Okay, bye.
>> This is this is the problem that I have
right now. And like this is where like
the frustration gets in and like for me,
I'm like trying to get a deal done, but
like why am I the only one with urgency
to try to figure this out? That's
absurd. Like, do better your job. This
is Tommy.
>> Hey Tommy, it's Jacob over here.
>> Hey man, just for me.
>> Well, uh, I've got news. I'm not sure
how you're going to receive it, but
we're going to be pretty far apart here,
bud. A lease on a $100,000 vehicle is
definitely going to be over $1,000 a
month. I mean, there's just no getting
around that.
>> No on a Hummer EV lease, but if you get
a $15,000 discount, $4,000 in rebates,
you get there all day.
>> Yeah, I understand what you're saying,
sir, but unfortunately, the math doesn't
work out. And we're we're going to be
over $1,000 a month on a lease.
>> Yeah. I mean, again, if you're charging
above, which is fine if you guys are
above or you're not giving that kind of
discount, but $15,000 discount gets you
there all day.
>> Yes, sir. Fortunately, we don't have
those kind of rebates and we're not
discounting our vehicles that heavily.
>> Great. That's fine. No worries. I'll
find somebody who is.
>> Okay. Have a good day.
>> Bye.
>> This is Tommy.
>> Hey, Mr. Tommy. How you doing?
>> Hey. I'm doing well. How about yourself?
>> Doing all right. This is Adam.
>> Oh, hey. How's it going?
>> It's going all right. I just talked to
my manager. Uh, we came real real real
close. We got 772
a month and that's 36 months, 12k a
year.
>> Okay. So, like $18 or $14 over where you
wanted to be. Uh $16. That's what it
was.
>> And just first payment.
>> Yes.
>> Send that to me. Rock and roll. Just
send that to me. We'll rock and roll
right now.
>> All righty. I will get all the paperwork
started. Uh if you could send me your
driver's license so I can get all that
and then we'll do a credit application.
>> Um and I won't I'm not even making this
up. Um because I would not do this to
you cuz I'm willing to I just had a
dealership send me a number at 762. I
don't know if this is real. They just
texted it to me. They they quoted me at
1,400 or 1,200 bucks before and I said
no. I said I need this number and they
just sent me 762. So, I can't tell if
that's real or not, but I do have to
call this one too cuz this one's also
local to me. I mean, if you can do 762,
you made it easy. So, I don't want I
feel bad, but but this dealership just
text me that as well.
>> Okay. Well, I mean, we have another
offer 747 for 36 months, but it would be
10,000 a year. That may have been what
they did. I don't know if they
see this is why you there. So, can you
send me that deal? Let's rock and roll.
Sorry, I'm I'm dumb. This is why you're
smart.
>> You're good. I I You probably been doing
this for a couple hours, huh?
>> Yeah, I'm I'm uh glad to be done. Okay,
send over to me right now. Text that to
me. We'll get it rock and roll and get
this all taken care of.
>> All righty. I will send over a picture
of a blank credit application. If you
could either print it out and fill it
out and email it back to me or whatever
is easiest for you. Uh I know you might
not want to text that over the phone.
>> Yeah. No. Yeah. Or I can take one over
the phone.
>> Yeah. This is a This is a phone call.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Let's just make sure I have
the I just want to have everything down
in writing before we do everything. And
then once I have that, we'll rock and
roll and call it a day.
>> Yeah. I'll get a uh like an official
offer all printed out and labeled out
the right way. I'll send it over to you.
I'll have my manager sign at the bottom.
But yeah, and then we'll just submit it
and get it all done.
>> Okay, sounds good. I I love it, man.
Appreciate you guys making it easy.
Let's get this deal done um at the at
the witching hour.
>> All righty.
>> Hey, man. I appreciate you.
>> Yes, sir. No problem. Byebye. Bye.
Oh my god.
Okay, I just need to get this deal down
in writing. Oh, that feels that feels
good. H how many calls is that? Holy
dude, the amount of calls I made. Okay,
I think I think I got one of two options
here.
>> All right, what you got?
>> Okay. Uh so I have this one dealership.
Uh, seems like they're going to do 772.
I I do I won't lie. They said, but this
is all Texas, so I just don't know which
one. He's super nice. I'm getting blown
up here. Uh, the second one I have is
another deal. This one is at 762, but
it's 10,000 m a year. So, I have either
one. So, I have two deals that we can go
through that are both in Texas. Holy
moly, I'm getting blown up. Boom. So, I
I have two 7 I have a 770 and a 7. If he
wants 747, we can, but it's 10,000 mi a
year. But I think you want a 12, right?
>> Uh, yeah, 12 12K. I thought that was 762
with the 10K.
>> It's 776 for 12K or 747 with this
dealership with 10K. Or I have another
offer that I just got as well, which is
10K for 762, which would be like a 780
with 780 with a Yeah. 12K. Yeah. So, e
either one works. Uh, you can let the
I'll tag I have the one offer right now.
I'm going to tag you. Do you have access
to primary ending in
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. I'm going to tag you in this one.
This is the worst offer. Is cl both
these can be e signed.
>> Okay.
>> Is client good to do that? Are they are
these going to I don't know if you beat
this or anything.
>> Uh client should be good to e- sign. I
do not have better than this. Is this
this is 10k? The one
>> the one I just tagged you in 10k. I just
got the phone with the other guy that
said he would do uh the 12k. I'm just
waiting on those official numbers.
>> Okay. Okay. Cool. Yeah. And then I've
got Yeah, I don't have anything better.
There's one in Arizona that has 15K
listed on the website. I'm waiting on a
call back to see where they're at.
>> Let's uh I'll have you verify the
numbers.
>> I'll have you verify the numbers, but
good job uh catching this early enough
that we are able to fix it. Obviously, I
know I appreciate you staying late. I
understand that's not your job and not
your responsibility, but I appreciate
you staying late to get that done. Let's
let's get this rocking and rolling so we
can get you off and hang out with
family.
>> Okay, cool. I'll send this over to them
and let you know.
>> Okay, sounds good. I'll uh once I have
this the better offer, I'll let you know
in a second.
>> Okay, thanks.
>> Right. Bye. Oh, okay. Uh you guys make
sure you guys like, follow, subscribe.
I'm still making sure this deal is done.
I've gotten like three calls. I do want
to call this one dealership just while
I'm waiting cuz I don't want to just sit
around and do nothing.
>> Chris, how can I help you?
>> Hey Chris, I missed your phone call.
This is Tommy.
>> Hey Tommy, I was trying to see I was
talking to one of my guys who said that
you might be interested in doing a lease
on it because I know that the today's
the last day for that 7500 toward the
residual. Now, if I can get get it done,
you'd have to e- sign tonight if they'll
allow us to do it. Are you okay with
that?
>> Yeah. Yeah, we're find we're fine. We're
fine sign to e sign as long as the
numbers make sense.
>> Okay. Let me see if I'm going to go
straight to my GM and try to go over his
head like go over their head and see if
I can just get him to approve it cuz he
can approve what he can approve. So, I'm
going to call him right now and then
I'll uh do you have are you a first
responder, educator, prior military?
>> No, but I am a Costco executive member.
Okay, let me put everything in here so I
have all the contacts. Uh, Costco, are
you on a current lease now?
>> Uh, no. I don't have uh any GMC lease or
anything like that.
>> Do you own a GMC?
>> Uh, I do not.
>> What competitor vehicles you got? 2015
newer.
>> I wouldn't qualify for any other rebate
other than the Costco.
>> No supplier either.
>> No company. Okay. All right. Let me uh
let me call him right now and see if
he'll let us do the e sign cuz I know
that uh that'll be great for you cuz we
can do that.
>> Yeah. Yeah. get that done.
>> All right, brother. All right, let me
see what I can do. I'll call you right
back.
>> Hey, sounds good. Bye.
>> All right, bye.
>> This is the dealership that I had to
like beg to e sign. This is uh like you
can see once the manager got on the
phone, he's like, "Okay, let's work this
out." Cuz people want to work out deals
in the last day of the month.
>> Oh my gosh. Okay, we're getting blown up
here. This is Tommy.
>> Hi Tom. This is Buen with
>> Hey, how's it going?
>> Good. Good. Did you saw the updated
numbers? Sorry about that, man. It was
just a lot of going on and
>> Okay, so you guys are now going to just
make sure that I'm on the same page.
This is 762 a month. Uh where you guys
at? Um 10,000 mi year lease, not a
12,000 mi year lease. We're trying to be
at 12 is where we were trying to be at
with that payment.
>> Uh let me let me make it 12 to to see
what the payment might vary though. It
might not be the same payment.
>> Okay.
>> Maybe a little more.
>> Okay. And then
>> do you want
>> is the ancillary? Is that just taxes in
there?
>> Yes. So, because you're leasing the
vehicle, uh the the taxes the the the
tax credit is is going to reflect into
the residual.
>> Yep. So, that's So, this has everything
all in the
>> everything. Yes. Yes. Yes. So, let me
update it to 12,000 mi and then we'll
we'll we'll see if that works for you.
>> Okay. Perfect.
>> This is the this is definitely the the
the best. So, I I I was not going to
heaggle back and forth.
>> I I No. Yeah. Let's Let's keep it
simple.
>> Yeah. It's close to to closing time, so
I just wanted to know if we can make a
deal or not.
>> Yeah. And we can do this all remote
signing, all that fun stuff, right?
>> Yes. Yes, sir.
>> Okay, perfect. Let's just get the 12K
updated right now. We'll get it all
rocking and roll and I'll text you right
now.
>> Okay, amazing. Thank you so much.
>> Okay, sounds good. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> No, the both of them are real. I have
the deal. The one thing I need to know
is that I've been saying that there's no
tax on these. This other dealership just
gave me the 762 with tax included. So,
it actually is a better deal. So, I want
to make sure that I know we had this
deal done, wrapped up, ready to go.
Client lives in Texas, but they are
currently on a trip. They made a flight
to back in order to sign this deal as
the dealership said they had to be done
in person. We locked up this deal, had a
deposit, had a credit app, had
everything rocking and rolling. We also
agreed to sign the deal remotely. Said,
"No need, just come on in." We then had
the client fly out. While the client is
in the air, the dealership calls and
says, "Sorry, we sold the car to
somebody else." My only assumption is
that they found somebody that would pay
more money because this is not a deal
you're making money on. So, we have a
team of really 10 people, but
realistically, we had five people all
drop everything they're doing to
negotiate this deal. I dropped what I
was doing. We all had a plan. Uh, I'm
not going to blast the dealership.
That's not what I do. You don't have a
signed purchase agreement or something
like that. We have a signed p or we have
a credit app and a and a deposit done on
the car. The dealership knew that the
client had fly to them and the dealer
client is local to that area. it just
didn't make sense. Like they had to fly
back early. So that's what happened. So
for the last I don't know like two hours
I've been calling dealerships across
Texas trying to find a deal that makes
sense and we ended up getting it. Like
our business philosophy is really simple
which is we do whatever we can to make
the customer's experience as amazing as
possible and as long as we take care of
the client like number one rule is take
care of the client. Money will continue
to come into the company. Employees will
be taken care of. Everything will roll.
Our number one value here at delivered
is do whatever it takes to take care of
the customer. You do that and you solve
their problems, money will come in. We
don't we don't talk about this is
delivered is how do we make more money?
How do we do this? We say how do we
solve more problems? If we solve more
problems, we all of these problems
everything else becomes solved. So
that's what we did. We dropped all hands
on decks. This also has tax built in.
Both of them t I'm going to call Dakota
on this. Sorry, I guess call Dakota. I
don't know if he's talking to the
dealer. He might Oh, he's talking. Oh
yeah, both have tax. Both have tax. I'm
going to text him. We we say like one
out of every like 500 deals we end up
having like something weird happen like
this. It sucks, right? But imagine this
person negotiated this deal on their
own, right? Just like like think this is
part of the value point of delivered.
Negotiate the point of their own. They
went to go fly to go do the deal cuz
again this is their local dealership.
They just came home early to do it and
then the deal gets canceled midair and
you have what 3 hours. He lands at 7:20
so he hasn't even landed. He's still in
the air. He would have lost his EV deal
and it would have been done. This is
this is great. I'm so glad we got this
done.
>> Hey, you're live. What's up,
>> Howdy?
>> Hey, Howdtie. I got So, both both deals
involve tax.
>> Both deals involve tax. Okay, cool.
>> Yeah. So, so it just depends on which
one the client wants to take. The other
one guys
>> the numbers on the other one.
>> I'm waiting for the other I did get the
other ones. I tagged you. It's 762 or
it's actually 772.
Um, so you did change that. I don't know
if he's maybe I'm crazy. 772 on this
one. I'm waiting on the other one to
have 12,000 mi a year, but whatever one
the client wants to take. Uh, both are
ready to do. It just depends on what
they want to do. One, the one that I
just tagged you in, they would have to
credit it up over the phone.
>> Okay. So, okay. Yeah,
>> I know the client I didn't think the
client Are they still flying?
>> Uh, they touched down in 30 minutes.
>> Hopefully, they understand. We did
everything we can to make up and just
apologize tremendously. So, sorry this
is acceptable. Uh, we'll talk about more
about what happened. Obviously, I want
to learn more, but not while I'm live.
>> Yeah. Yeah. No, 100%. I did I do too uh
have one in Arizona. They're double
checking taxes, but I'm at I'm at the
750 with Costco.
>> Oh, you're at 750, but that's in
Arizona. Do we want to do a deal out of
state?
>> They wanted they prefer to stay in
Texas, but I can still give them the
option that they'll obviously have to
ship it, so it may just be better to go
with the instate ones. But
>> yeah, let's let's just go through and
give client all the whatever client
wants to do, we'll make it work.
>> Yep. 100%. I'm on it.
>> Okay, sounds good. Let me know. Keep me
up to date. Thank you again for working
late.
>> Yeah, no worries.
>> Bye.
>> Okay, we did wrap up the deal. Uh we
wrapped it up with the
deal. appreciate each and every one of
you guys for being here. It really means
a lot. I'll be here. Um, thank you guys
so much. You guys are all awesome.
Seriously, you're the best. All of you.
[Music]