Is this the Tommy?
>> Which I don't know which Tommy you're
referring to
>> from Tik Tok.
>> Thank you, my friend. Yes, it is.
>> I'm genuinely in shock. Like, I'm a huge
I'm a huge fan of your video. So, I
cannot be the person to screw this up.
>> That' be $4,584
off and60.
>> Copy,
>> dude. They called me the mathematician
in high school.
>> Give me a second.
>> I want you back because because I I like
I like the Cinderella happy story.
>> The one that you were asking about has a
deposit on it already.
>> Okay. Oh, Diana's watching. The client
is watching on this. She wants a
Forester. A Forester.
>> Thank you for calling. So,
>> hey. Uh, hey. I just want to see if you
guys have a car available.
>> Okay. Which one is it?
>> Uh, I have the last six of the VIN. I
don't have Would that help?
>> See, what type of vehicle is it?
>> It is a 2025 Toyota 4Runner SCUV TRD
off-road premium PT4W.
>> What color?
>> Uh, what color? That is heritage blue.
>> Okay. So, that one is is priced at
58,388.
>> Oh, but what's the sales price?
>> We haven't took it in yet. So, um the
only price we're going to have is the
TSRP. That one looks like it's not going
to be available till the 27th. That's
when it's expected to arrive.
>> Okay. Sorry. It just says, "Please call
for the sales price."
>> Are you only interested in it because of
the color or
>> I mean, I'll take an underground too if
you have one in the same underground
with a moon roof as well. Yeah.
>> Okay. Let me see. The only one that I am
going to have that's here and available
is going to be a red exterior, black
interior.
>> No, I mean I'm fine waiting on the car.
I was just more interested in the sales
price. So,
>> okay. All right. Are you local to us
here in area?
>> Uh, no. I'm in uh
>> Okay. I mean, I can work on getting you
an estimate like an out the door pricing
and if you do agree on numbers like in
most cases, you know, placing a deposit
on the vehicle is recommended. Is that
the route you want to go or?
>> Yeah. I mean, if I agree to numbers,
that's fine. Yeah. I mean, as long as I
agree to the sales price.
>> Perfect. What is your first name? First
name is Tommy.
>> Tommy. Last name Tommy.
>> Uh, Makula. M I K U L A.
>> All righty. And then the 980 number.
>> That's my phone number.
>> All righty. And then what's your zip
code?
>> The My zip code is 61.
>> All righty. Let me go ahead and give
your information over to my sales
manager and he'll be following up um
with you shortly to go over pricing.
>> No problem. Sounds great.
>> All right. Thank you.
>> No problem. Bye.
>> This is Brandon.
>> Hey Brandon, how's it going?
>> It's going well. And yourself?
>> Hey, I'm doing well. Doing well. Hey,
before we get into this, do you mind
just do me a huge favor? Can you pick a
number between 1 and three? It's
completely random.
>> Okay, I can do that for you. Who do I
have the pleasure of speaking with?
>> My name is Tommy.
>> Tommy? Uh, I'm going to pick number one.
>> Number one. Awesome. Perfect. I just
want to see if you guys have a car
available.
>> Is this the Tommy?
>> Which I don't know which Tommy you're
referring to
>> from Tik Tok.
>> Thank you, my friend. Yes, it is.
>> No way, dude. That's I was just watching
your video.
>> Oh, that's that's sick. You're on stream
right now with in front of like 5,000
people. I am looking for a car for a
client though, so this is all good. But
yes, you are you are live on Tik Tok,
YouTube, Instagram, all the fun stuff.
>> No. Well, I got to pull it up now. Just
>> Yeah, you got to verify this is just
imagine it's some fake person acting
like
>> Oh, now I can see. Do you want me to
help you get get your uh
>> Now, now you're going to get fill your
board in.
>> Now we're going to get a deal done. The
whole world is I don't know how many
people watching.
>> Well, hit me with the stock number.
>> Stock number S is in Sam 251067.
>> In the uh in the making, model.
>> Make model Subaru Forester Touring
Hybrid.
>> Perfect. Let me get it pulled up for
you. I'm now I'm trying to check out
your board. I'm trying to see if I can
help you. Uh I can't find the stock
number. So, if you want to go ahead and
>> That's No, it's I won't I won't let them
cheat. I You can't Once you Once you
know the stream's happening, I it won't
happen. Oh, wait. Okay, here you go.
Pick Never mind. Pick a number between
one and three.
>> So, I'm going to go one again.
>> One again. Okay, cool. Okay, continue.
>> Okay. Uh and you said it was uh Hit me
with that stock number one more time.
>> S is in Subaru 25167.
>> 067. Okay, sorry. Thank you for the
gifted gift for hybrid. Correct.
>> Hybrid. Yeah.
>> All righty. Sorry, my co-workers just
walked in. I was just telling what was
what was going on.
>> Oh, wow. That's Dude, that's
>> crazy. I was I was think we can get to a
million likes with this deal. Let's get
to a million likes with these deals. I
think we have, like I said, I think we
have over We have 1500 people watching
on YouTube and Twitch and then whatever
we got on TikTok. So,
>> that's insane. Well, okay. So, tell me
what you need. Let me see what I can do
for you.
>> Um, you know, I really get pretty close
to 10% off of these right now. Like 9%
off. There's 2,000 people on TikTok. So,
boom. That's 4,000 people ready ready to
see this deal go down for for a nice
lady that's not too far away from you
guys.
>> Awesome. Well, I mean, now that uh I'm
going to be honest with you. I'm screen
recording it and it would be really cool
exposure. So, I do not see a reason that
they're not going to go ahead and do the
a deal for you. So, you're wanting it
for what? You said around 9% off.
>> Yeah. 9% off.
>> About about 4 grand off.
>> Yeah, about four grand off.
>> Okay. So, you want it for 426?
>> Yep.
>> And I can't believe I'm doing this a
third time. Pick a number between one
and two.
>> One and two, dude. Third times I'm I'm a
consistent I like I like consistency.
I'm going to go number one.
>> Okay, thanks for that, buddy. Uh yeah,
let's get a deal done at the very least.
So you got somehow three of my spaces
knocked out because people were going
crazy. But they're telling you genuinely
in shock. Like I'm a huge I'm a huge fan
of your video. So I cannot be the person
to screw this up.
>> Let me run in here and just holler at my
manager and tell them the situation.
Everybody here watches you. So
>> I'll just be like, "Dude, I'm on live
right now. I got to say yes." Right?
Like I have
>> I say I got a few of these deals sitting
around here. A few Subaru deals. We can
put a few together. I love it. Let's
Let's put this together. You got my
number here. Don't say it out loud.
>> Perfect. Okay. Yeah. Give me the the
call back number.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> On mute on the thing.
>> Yeah. You got it.
>> All righty. I'll give you a call back
here in five minutes, my man.
>> Okay. Sounds good, man. Appreciate it.
>> All right. Thank you. See you.
>> Bye.
>> Hey.
>> Hello. Hello. Are you there?
>> Yes, I'm here. How's it going?
>> Hey, Austin. Hey, I'm doing well. Hey,
before we get started, completely
random. Can Can you pick a number
between one and two?
>> Number between one and two?
>> Yeah,
>> sure. Two.
>> Okay, cool. Can you Can you let me know
if there's a car available?
>> Sure. What do you have?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Yeah. Hold on one sec. Let me get to my
desk.
>> No, you're good. Take your time.
>> What's your name, by the way?
>> My name's Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. I'm Don. Nice to meet you,
man.
>> Nice to meet you.
>> What are you looking for? Something new,
something?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Stock number S is in Subaru
17451.
>> One second. I'm just getting back to my
desk here.
>> Take your time.
>> Thank you so much, man. technology never
cooperates. All right. So, S17451,
you said
>> S17451.
>> Uh, Outback.
>> No, Forester Hybrid Touring.
>> For sure. Okay. Why the heck did it do
that? And what color is it?
>> Uh, it is white with the Java interior.
Yeah. Oh, you could find You couldn't
find the stock number. That's okay.
Perfect.
>> No, I found a stock number. Just how the
system does is it's been worked on. So,
everything is just mumbled right now.
>> Oh, okay. So, the exact car the stock
number.
>> Yeah. S174. Yeah. 451 VIN number ending
in 11:04.
>> That's 11:01.
>> I'm saying 1101. My apologies. That's
That was Yeah. 11:01. Sorry.
>> No, that's okay. It's okay. We I would
have been okay if you made a mistake,
too. I would have been kind of happy,
but that's okay. I Yeah. So, is that car
available?
>> Yes, sir. When are you looking at us and
take a look at it?
>> Awesome. Well, you know, I already
driven one. I already fell in love with
it. Really? Just trying to get numbers
and I'm hoping that you can just give me
the best numbers in the world and I come
buy it today.
>> Okay. So, let's get straight to it. What
What's the number to get you to buy it
today?
>> Uh 10% off. 10% off of what? MSRP.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. Hold on a second. Let me do this
math here.
>> That' be $4,584
off and60.
>> Copy.
>> Dude, they called me the mathematician
in high school.
>> Give me a second. Give me a second,
buddy. Let me go ahead and let me go
ahead and ask my boss. I'll be right
back. Let me put you on a quick hold.
All right, bro.
>> That sounds good.
>> Meanwhile,
>> hey, Tommy.
>> Yep.
>> Hey, buddy. I'm still here just waiting
for my boss to get off get off a call
and I'll get I'll get either a thumbs up
or thumbs down based off of that offer.
Just hold on a second. All right.
>> Yep. That's fine. You I I'll hold as
long as you need me to. There's no rush.
>> All right, buddy. Thanks so much, man.
>> No problem. 10% off a Forester hybrid.
That I mean, that's a really strong deal
on a on a Forester hybrid. Oh, wait.
Brandon's calling me. One second. Hi,
Brandon. Wait, I put you on speaker. I'm
on also on the phone with the
dealership.
>> Okay, no problem.
>> You were just watching the stream. You
You know that I was
>> Hey, Tommy, are you here in the Georgia
area? Uh,
>> I'm in North Carolina, so I'll hop in a
skip.
>> Okay. What's your What's your zip code?
>> Yeah. Yeah, you know the zip code.
registering the car on a beach.
>> All right. Thank you so much, man. Hold
on a sec.
>> No problem.
>> Hey, bud. Hello.
>> How's it going?
>> How's it going? Yeah, man. We got a
deal, man. Can you you call the right
time at the right at the right moment?
10% off the MSRP. You ready to do this?
>> Yeah, just send send it over to me and
as long as it looks good, I'll put a
deposit on right now.
>> Okay. Uh, let me go ahead and get that
printed out here a second again. Hold on
one second.
>> Yeah, just text it over to me right now.
>> Okay. Yeah, I'll go ahead and text that
over to you. Hold on one second, buddy.
One second. The way he's talking to me,
I just muted him. The way he's talking
to me, it does make it seem like he
knows who I am. Sometimes I just have
like a weird suspicion like the way
somebody's addressing me.
>> All right, Tommy, I'm I'm sending that
over to you now.
>> Give me a second here. Hold on a second.
What's your phone number, buddy?
>> Yeah, phone number is
>> I just went ahead and sent that over to
you. You'll notice MSRP is 45846
selling price of 41226
which is that $4,500 discount until the
door is 43479.
We should get there any second there.
>> Okay. What's the do is the delivery
service charge the
>> the doc fee.
>> Do fee?
>> Yep. That's to get all the stuff done
for you. Everything done in house.
>> Okay. I'm looking it over right now.
Then um you said the car is on the
ground, correct?
>> Yeah, it's here. It has a stock.
Definitely yours. Yeah.
>> Perfect. Yeah. Let me just show this
over. Let me give me five minutes and
I'll give you a call right back.
>> All right, buddy. Um Yeah. Can you call
the number that text you? That's my
cell.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Perfect. That's your
cell. Okay. Sounds good.
>> All right, buddy. Talk to you then.
>> All right. Bye. Okay. I do want to give
Brandon a shot here. I always try to
give dealerships to know who I am a
shot. So, I'm going to give him a shot.
But that is They did just do 10% off.
>> This is Brandon.
>> Brandon. I I didn't expect that to
happen. I made one more phone call and I
don't know if he recognized me, too, but
he just gave me 10% off. So,
you back because because I I like I like
the Cinderella happy story.
>> Well, it's actually bad news. I'm glad
she was able to get a good deal. The one
that you were asking about has u a
deposit on it already.
>> Okay. Bummer. Okay.
>> Yeah. But I am happy she was able to get
the deal that she was wanting.
>> Oh, okay. Awesome, man. Well, uh save my
number. I'll we'll do we'll do another
deal another time. That's That's sad,
but it's okay. We'll do another one.
Have you signed up before my first to
call list?
>> Oh, say what now?
>> Have you signed up for my first time?
No, I have not. How do I go about that?
Uh, I'll text you over the website to go
to right now. Uh, sign up to this and
then anytime I have a deal in your area,
you'll be the first one we call.
>> Awesome. I appreciate that. Thank you.
>> I appreciate the support. Really do.
>> No problem. You have a good one.
>> Hey, you too.
>> See you.
>> Bye. So, we're glad we made that extra
phone call. So, I need to I need to
throw this over to the client. That's a
deal. 10% off the car is a deal, guys.
And it's in a It's not too far away.
It's not super close. We'll have to ship
it, but there's nothing local. So, just
you guys know, the MSRP of the car is
55.846. They gave me 10% off which is
$4,500 off $7.95 dock fee, $1,200 in
tax, license fee, registration of $20,
$35 out the door, $43479. And this is
why we call every dealership every time.
So, I just had that over to the client.
That's a great deal. So, if you guys
don't know real quick while we're here,
if you guys don't know, my name's Tommy.
I negotiate car deals for a living. My
goal is to save you time, energy, and
anxiety. We save money, but that's a
byproduct of it all. I charge a flat fee
of a,000 bucks. Every call we're making
today is for a client. Okay, we're going
to move at Michael at Dakota. Who can
jump on this? This seems like a closed
deal to me potentially. Okay, I'm going
to get them to shoot that over to So,
right now we have $4,000
off MSRP. Let's just do this.
[Music]