So, the one that we're talking about,
the one that's on your website is not
actually available.
>> No, it's not updated. I think that one's
sold through the weekend.
>> I see a few on your website, but you're
saying I It's just a crapshoot if any of
these are actually available or not.
>> All right. So, anybody in particular in
sales?
>> No, I'm open. Unless your name is parts
and you're in sales. That would be crazy
though. But, I mean, if you prefer, I'll
call my local dealership if you don't
want to sell me a car. It's just like a
weird question you keep like drilling on
like, am I not allowed to call you?
>> No, just a lot of customers call in
sometimes.
>> Oh, yeah.
Open to 10. Open to 12.
>> I just got to mark it in just to get
>> Let's just say 10. I was singing to your
hold music. That is some good hold
music.
Okay. Client lives on the West Coast.
So, we're going to start on the West
Coast. Let's go through and we're going
to make a phone call. Okay. So, this
MSRP of this GV70 is $71,640.
They are doing some a lot of rebates on
this car.
It's a wonderful day. Michael speak in
the sales department. How can I help
you?
>> Hey, Mike. Uh, this is Tommy from the
buying department. I just wanted to see
if you guys have a car available.
>> Uh, sure. Which vehicles? What vehicle
are you looking for?
>> Uh, I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Is it for a Hyundai for a Genesis?
>> It's a Genesis.
>> What is the stock number you're
>> Let me give that to you here. Oh, let me
get my score real quick.
>> You ready?
>> Mhm. It's S is in Sierra. X is in X-ray.
>> GV70 electrified.
>> That's it. I'm coming in at the at the
end of the wire.
>> Here we go. All right. So, just to
confirm, we're looking at the white
advanced trim. Seems to me like it is
the Obsidian black interior. Correct.
>> That's it.
>> And I'm sorry, your name one more time.
>> My name is Tommy.
>> Tommy. Nice to meet you, sir.
>> No, nice to meet you.
>> All righty. Cool. And uh it I confirming
that the vehicle is here and uh just
wanted to see if you had some time to
come on down and take a look at it.
>> Well, you know what? I'm like the
easiest guy in the world. I've already
driven it already know I love it. Really
just trying to get some numbers on a
lease on it.
>> All right, perfect. And what kind of uh
what kind of lease are you looking for?
>> You know, there's always a sweet spot on
leases, I've learned. Um but you know,
open to 36 months, 10,000 mi a year.
>> 3610.
Okay, perfect. Let me do this. Luckily,
the head honcho of the Genesis
department is here, so I'd like to uh
consult with him real fast. see if we
can put together a deal for you and uh
get you down here quickly.
>> Yeah, call me, text me, beat me,
whatever makes the most sense.
>> All right, sounds good. We will reach
out to
>> at least maybe 5 minutes.
>> Okay, awesome. Thank you so much. All
right, bye-bye.
>> One of the things we're we're going to
you're going to run into right now like
uh is going to be availability. If
you're trying to buy like an EV right
now, opening up your options is going to
be pretty key. client ideally doesn't
want a black interior, but if we were to
skip black interior, right? Alto
together and just remove it, like I
don't want any black interior, that
actually removes. So, nationwide on a
car like this, there's only 16 total
options in the entire nation. Now, he's
willing to do red on black. We can see
if that one would fit.
>> Thank you for calling Genesis. This is
you speaking.
>> Hey, this is Tommy speaking. I just want
to see if you guys have a car available.
>> Okay. Uh, what is this in regards to?
>> Yeah, sir. You're really quiet. I'm
trying to turn you up here.
>> What is this in regards to?
>> Uh, it's I'm trying to buy a car. My
car.
>> Okay. Which vehicle are you asking for?
New or pre-owned?
>> It's a brand new car.
>> Which vehicle are you inquiring about?
>> Stock number T is in Tyrannosaurus. H is
in Harry. 06990.
[Music]
>> The SEC blue.
>> The Sice Blue in the frozen gray
interior. That's a must. Fortunately, no
one in the California area has a series
blue at the moment. We only had silver,
black, or white available.
>> Silver, black. Okay, so the one that
we're talking about, the one that's on
your website is not actually available.
>> No, it's not updated. I think that one
sold through the weekend.
>> What color interior is the white one?
I'm I can look on your website, too. But
I know your website, you said wasn't
maybe the most updated.
>> Yeah, the the ones that we have
available be with the frozen gray urban
ground interior black no more.
>> Okay. So, I'm I'm looking on your
website here. I don't see a white one,
but you said there's a white one
available.
>> There might be. Like I said, I have I
have
>> No, I'm willing I'm willing to do any
color option other than black that does
have a light interior. Like, I'm looking
at your inventory, but you're telling me
your website's not accurate. So, like I
I try to help you out so this you don't
have to like go through all this weird
back and forth. Um I see a few on your
website, but you're saying it's just a
crapshoot of any
>> Yeah, it's just that they don't update
quickly and we've been selling these
honestly. Um, we very quick because
everybody's taking advantage of the EV
rebate. What's your last name? Tell me.
>> Last name is Makula.
>> How do you spell that?
>> M I K U L A.
>> M. Okay. What's Where are you calling
from?
>> I'm calling from Sacramento. Carmichael.
>> Sacramento. Oh, wow.
>> Yeah. I mean, I like to come down south
in California anytime I can.
>> Uh, wow. There's there's not a lot out
there, huh?
>> No, I just like to go down south anytime
I can. If I have an excuse to take a $70
plane ticket to go to LA and go down
somewhere down there, I'd try to call me
wellraveled.
>> All right, give me one sec. Let me just
see if I could have my manager pull it
up right now.
>> Sure, that'd be great.
[Music]
Want me to pull out our flashlights?
>> Meanwhile,
>> sorry,
>> I was singing I was singing to your old
music. That is some good old music.
So, right now, I just confirmed with my
manager, we have three advanced trims
available. We have two in silver and one
in black.
>> Two in silver, one in black. Okay. What
are the interior colors?
>> It's frozen gray with every brown.
>> Okay. So, they're all frozen. Okay. Bada
boom. Bada bing. We're in business. I'm
willing to entertain, right? As long as
we can get some numbers. That makes
sense. I'm all for it.
>> Okay. What are you trying to do?
>> I'm trying to lease one. I'm doing what
everybody else is doing. And I'm waiting
till the wire to buy one of these EVs.
>> And how long do you want to lease for?
>> Uh, you know, I'm open to 36 months. Um,
you know, I I just know that the tax
credit's there. It's pretty strong. So,
>> I wouldn't I wouldn't want the black
exterior, though. Just, you know, the
silver ones would be the ones I'd be
looking at.
>> Silver. Okay.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. Give me one second.
>> Sure.
>> How are How much money are you putting
down for the lease?
>> Just the minimum that you'd put down in
a lease. You know, I understand tax
license norless.
>> Yeah. Drive off, you know. As long as I
get the drive off with the new car, you
know. You know.
>> So, you're going to play just your drive
off. So, we do have a better lease
special on 33 months. Are you okay with
that?
>> Yeah. You know, I'm all good. You know,
whatever's the better way.
>> How much miles per year you going to
drive?
>> Open to 10. Open to 12.
>> I just got to mark it in just to give
you
>> Let's just say 10.
>> Okay.
>> Don't worry. I'm getting I'm I'm I'm in
business mode now. This is This is worse
than my open mic.
>> Okay. So, 10,000 miles, drive offs, and
where are you trying to be at in a
monthly payment wise, if you don't mind
me asking?
>> You know, I'm really worried about the
out the door number more than anything
else.
>> Yeah. Out the door number. I mean,
you're going to be paying a certain
percentage. I'm just asking for I could
go ahead with my manager to see what we
could work for you.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You know, the monthly
payment I'm I'm more trying to focus on
an out the door number. I understand the
monthly payment will be what the monthly
payment is.
>> Okay. Yeah. Just give me a few minutes
and I'll get back to you.
>> Okay. My credit's great. Better.
Probably record high. Oh, sorry. I mean
like normal 825
>> out the door. All right. We'll get back
to you.
>> Bada boom. Bada bing. Excited.
>> All right. Thank you.
>> Genesis parts.
>> Oh, sorry. I'm trying to speak to sales.
>> All right. Anybody in particular in
sales?
>> No, I'm open. Unless your name is parts
and you're in sales. That would be crazy
though.
>> Yeah, our phones are all out of whack.
So, let me see.
>> Just just to whoever you think is the
the coolest person.
>> Oh, man. You're speaking to him. No, I'm
just kidding. I'll go ahead and transfer
you over a car. Let's go.
>> Not that cool. Just kidding. Have a good
one, brother.
>> Oh, you too.
>> Sorry. Is not available. Record your
message at the tone.
>> Hey, Simon. This is Tommy Mucula. I am
calling because honestly there's talk
around town that you are the second
coolest person that works at Genesis.
Now, that isn't my word. I've been
hearing it. I'm looking to buy a car.
You know, I asked for the coolest person
and uh parts sent me to you and said
that they're the coolest, but we have
the second coolest. So, I like the name,
Simon. I think we're on a good starting
relationship here. Uh you guys have a
car available. I've already driven it
already know I love it. Really just
trying to buy it. So, hoping that you
can put a dream in my driveway and you
know, bada boom, bada bing. My phone
number is I'd prefer not to get punked
and you can give me a call back. That'd
be great. Thanks. Bye.
This is Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. This is you.
>> Hey, man. How's it going?
>> Yeah, of course, man. It's good to hear
from you. I missed you.
>> Unfortunate news, Tommy. Looks like
those two silvers that we had available
actually no longer in stock. Last one I
would have would be the black one with
the frozen gray interior.
>> So, you don't have you just have the
black is all you got left, huh?
>> Yeah, the black one is still available.
>> Awesome. Perfect. Bada boom, bada bing.
You know what? Those little may maybe
you'll convince me cuz your deals must
be so crazy cuz everybody's buying them.
Maybe maybe I would do the black.
There's uh you know you got me
intrigued. You got me you got me
entertained.
>> Okay. Can I ask you is this? You live in
Sacramento. Is there any dealerships buy
you?
>> I mean there are. Yeah.
>> What has stopped you from buying closer?
>> As I told you four times now I I do like
to go to LA. So I have a good excuse. I
try to. You guys have inventory as well.
So there's a few dealerships in LA.
>> But I mean if you prefer I'll call my
local dealership if you don't want to
sell me a car.
>> I'm just ask I'm like a weird question
you keep like drilling on like am I not
allowed to call you?
>> No, it's just No, it's just a lot of
customers call in. I know they call.
>> That's good. That means people are
trying to buy a car from you. That's
exciting. A lot of people are calling
in.
>> Yeah. No, cuz they don't have the
inventory close by.
>> But do do you want me I mean there
there's there's enough of these cars in
the West Coast. There's three of them
local to me. Like I said, if I if I have
a reason to go down to LA, I will. It's
a it's like a $60 flight. I don't know
if you ever been to Sacramento. Like
flying between here and LA is like four
pennies.
>> Okay. Yeah. Cheaper than dinner. You're
open to the black one. So, you're the
you're open to a black one?
>> Yeah, I'm open to the black one cuz it
seems like your guys' deals are so
incredible. I mean, clearly everybody's
calling in for him to the point they're
selling before faster than you can
remove them from the website. So,
>> of course. All right, let me get back to
you.
>> Okay, cool. I'll be here.
>> All right.
>> There is not one car salesman in the
world that's trained to try to convince
somebody not to buy. Like, what if I had
it? Maybe if I had family, maybe I was
going to go visit. There is no car
salesman's trained to ask, well, why
haven't you called your local
dealerships? Like, what what do you gain
from that? Like, you already know. So,
fun fact, if you're selling cars, you
already know if somebody's calling you
from Sacramento, you have that in what
we call your back pocket. Somebody's
calling you from Sacramento, which means
they probably don't have inventory. You
save that in your back pocket. Finance
managers are really good at what they do
because they're really good at having
conversation with you and using the
information you use to save in the back
pocket. So when they need an objection,
they can pull it back because not only
does that show that you're listening,
but it makes a personalized objection.
This is why I was really good at finance
because people would I talk, have
conversation, learn what people do, and
then utilize that later in the
conversation. So yeah, he should take
note of it. He should put it in his back
pocket and when I say, "Hey, I want five
grand off the car." He should be like,
"Come on, man. You're calling me from
Sacramento. We both know you don't have
much inventory out here, but you know
that that's where that conversation
goes. You use it as ammunition, but you
don't like shoot before anybody shot
back at you. Come on.
>> Hello.
>> Hello. Hey, Simon. I missed a phone call
from you.
>> Yes. Hi. Yes. Hi, Tommy. I was returning
your call.
>> Yeah, absolutely, man. I I heard I heard
you're the bee's knees.
>> I don't know who told you that, but
thank you.
>> Hey, it was somebody in parts, but uh I
just wanted to see if you guys have a
car available.
>> Sure. Uh what is it? Is it a new car?
>> I I have a stock number if that helps
you. It's a new car. Sure. Uh, one
second left. What is it?
>> Uh, stock number 852608100.
>> Is it the white the frozen gray?
>> That's it.
>> Uh, GV70 electrified advanced.
>> Um, yeah, that is it. Correct.
>> Okay. And you're trying to purchase it?
>> I'm looking to leasing. I hear that's
the better way to do it.
>> Okay. Looking to lease. What are the
terms? Like how much down? How many
miles a year do you need?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I heard 33 months is kind of
the sweet spot. 10,000 mi a year. Yep.
>> Um, you know, really just want to put
drive off down. That's it. Okay. Drive
off. Okay. And if um you were to
purchase from us, would you come pick it
up or would we have to ship it to you?
>> Yeah, I'm open to picking it up. Uh is
it's like $5 flight to get down there.
Uh but you know, I can shipping as well.
I mean, whatever whatever you guys
dealership to NorCal, I think it's
probably around it might be around 500
bucks. So, you might have to pay a
little extra.
>> Yeah.
>> So, if you can pick it up, I mean
that'll probably Yeah. Okay. But, uh for
now, uh can I get a zip code?
>> Yeah. Yeah. It is.
>> All right. Give me a few minutes and
then I will give you a call back. Okay.
>> I love it. Can't wait to hear.
>> All right. All right. Thank you.
>> Hey, no problem. Bye. Bye.
>> Thank you for calling. Jenn is not
speaking his cells.
>> Hey, uh this is Tommy. I literally
dropped everything I was doing. I missed
your call. I'm so sorry. I cannot wait
to hear these numbers.
>> So, your minimum drive off for 33 months
on a lease. It's going to be 721 plus
tax.
>> I really like that out the door number.
Like, what's the price of the car?
What's the discount? What's the rebate?
Like, can we go through those lines?
>> Okay. So, the price of the car is
71,740.
Okay. Your discount is 4200 off the car.
Your rebate all you qualify to that has
a special for 33 months is $11,250.
The adjusted price is $56,90.
With your documentation fee, tax and
non- tax fees, you're looking at 58,789
with 22.
>> Okay. So, you are stuck at 15,400. Even
if I want another 500 bucks off, you'd
say no. Go my migo.
>> What kind of payment monthly payment
were you trying to be at?
>> You know what? Uh, realistically, I
mean, if you want to play monthly
payment, we certainly can. I'd much
rather be closer to a $600 payment,
which is where that's calculating out
to.
>> Yeah. Wouldn't be able to do that, sir.
>> Yeah. But again, the payment's not as
more concerned. It's more the out the
door number.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. And we had a few other dealerships
even locally that were uh above 16 grand
off. So, I mean that's, you know, I was
hoping LA would be a little bit better
than that.
>> This is the last car we have as well,
but you know, like I said, this is this
what we're able to do.
>> No, I get it. Yeah. But, I mean, I'm
also settling for the color, too.
>> Yeah. I mean, you're calling us from
Sacramento, too. There's not much colors
out there options
>> just because I mean, there's a few white
ones called, but
>> Yeah, I completely understand.
>> Okay, no problem. So, $15,450 is the max
she'll do on a black one,
>> of course.
>> Awesome. Appreciate it.
>> All right. Let me know if you want to
take the trip. Okay, that sounds good.
Bye. Going. We're getting a phone call
from Simon. This is Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. Uh, this Simon again.
>> Nice Simon. How's it going?
>> So, hey, we have one hiccup. My manager
traded that car away today.
>> Callie G will my mother told
>> I know out of out of all the all the
cars. Um, so
>> love you. You you will never be any
>> I can
>> sorry just reliving my childhood. So,
what I can Sorry. So, what I can do for
you is there is um Did you specifically
want the ultra white?
>> You know, I'm open to white, open to
red, open to blue, but it has to be the
gray interior.
>> Has to be the frozen gray. Okay. So,
what we have in stock right now is a
silver with frozen gray. Or I can get a
uni white, the metallic white for you
with the frozen gray interior.
>> That's That's Now we're talking the uni
white.
>> You want the uni white? Okay. With the
frozen gray, right?
>> Yeah.
>> That one I can probably get for you. So,
I'll run the numbers for you on that one
and then I will call you back. Okay.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> Okay. All right. Thank you.
>> All right. Sounds good. Bye.
>> Great.
This is Sandra. How can I help you?
>> Hey, Sandra. Are you in sales?
>> Yes, I'm in the internet sales. How can
I help you?
>> I love it. I just want to see if you
guys have a car available.
>> Okay, great. What kind of vehicle is it?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> I'm ready.
>> Uh, it's G as in Genesis 60030.
and with who I have the pleasure to
speak with.
>> My name is Tommy
>> 26 uh Genesis Electrify GV70.
>> That's it.
>> Okay, perfect. Let me just double check
to see if it's available. Is this a good
phone number in case we get
disconnected?
>> This is the best number.
>> Okay, thank you. Please hold.
[Music]
>> Meanwhile,
>> thank you for holding. Yes, great news.
That vehicle it is available. Do you
have any questions?
>> Really, I've already driven it. Already
know I love it. It's awesome car. Really
just trying to get some pricing and
hopefully just buy one today.
>> Okay, perfect. Did you get to see the
the MSRP and the incentives that we
have? Uh
>> I see the MSRP on the website. You know,
obviously uh you know, I'm looking at
lease, so I know all you know those
additional rebates, offers, you know,
obviously.
>> Oh, you're looking to lease.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I know there's a lot
of deals on these cars, so I just want
to make sure that I get my ducks in a
row.
>> Okay. Well, let me work on that lease
and then I will be sending it to you.
And uh can I have your last name?
>> Oh, last name is Makula. M I K U L A.
>> Okay, thank you. Yeah, just give me a
few minutes. I will work on that and
then I will send you that information.
>> Okay, sounds great.
>> Hey, Tommy.
>> Hey, what's up, man? So sorry. I was uh
you know, I was just uh away from my
phone.
>> Yeah, so I ran the numbers for you. So,
with uh 1,500 total out of pocket,
you're looking at um $799. That's what
tax included.
>> Okay. How do the numbers break down so I
know that?
>> So, um MSRP is 71,920. Uh the lease cash
is uh $11,250.
>> Yep.
>> And then we're discounting the car at
5600.
>> Okay.
>> And then uh we have uh two add-ons on
there. One is called clear shield which
is a door edge guard and then we have a
paint paint and fabric protection which
is $9.95.
>> How much is the clear shield?
>> 3.95 I'm sorry$3.95. Yeah.
>> All right. So $9.95 and 3.95
>> and then you're so for 33 months 10k
miles. That's what it looks like.
>> $7.99. Okay. So you guys are $5,600 off.
You guys have about $1,400 $1,500 in
addons
and then $5,600 off the price of the
car. Nothing else. Nothing crazy that I
should be worried about. Uh yeah, that's
that's it. That's pretty much the
breakdowns.
>> Okay. Well, I will say you are pretty
cool. These are this is not a bad deal.
Um you know, I was hoping to be just a
little bit better. You know, obviously I
went down to the wire for a reason
because I was hoping just get a little
bit better. And first I say no to those
add-ons first off the clear shield and
the the
>> 395. And then ideally wanted to be at
$6,500 off plus the add-ons removed and
we'd have a done deal.
>> 6,500 off without the add-ons. $6,500
off without the add-on. So, yeah.
>> What uh monthly payment were you
thinking of?
>> You know, I lease a lot of cars. I'm
really not worried about the monthly
payment. You know, obviously I like the
car. You know, try trying to, you know,
being under 700 is an exciting number
for me, but you know, I understand the
payment is what the payment is.
>> Uh-huh. Okay. Let me see what I can do
and then I will call you back. Okay.
>> All right. Sounds good.
>> Okay. All right. Thank you. Bye.
>> It's a great day here at This is Brandy
in sales. How may I assist you?
>> Hey, Brandy. I missed a phone call from
this number. I must have been talking to
somebody. I just don't remember their
name. I'm so sorry.
>> No, that's okay. Let me go ahead and
take a look. And this is the phone
number that they had reached you to,
sir.
>> Correct. Do
>> you happen to have a vehicle in our
service department?
>> No, I'd be in the sales department. I
mean, I think I was talking to sales.
>> I'm actually not seeing anything in
here. Was it a new or a pre-owned
vehicle? You were looking
>> It was a Genesis if that helps.
>> Yeah. Do you Was it a male or female?
>> You know, I it it was a male if I
remember correctly. It was a person I
was talking to.
>> We don't sell new Genesis here at our
location, sir.
>> Oh, I don't know. I mean, I missed a
phone call. That's what I was trying to
buy. So, I mean, I guess maybe a random
Hyundai just dealership called me. I
guess that's crazy.
>> Yeah, I do apologize. Yeah. For any
confusion. Unfortunately, we don't sell
any um I'm sorry, Genesis here. Um we do
have a Genesis sister store I can get
you over to. Um
>> don't don't worry about it. I don't even
know who's calling me at this point. So,
I'll just uh I'll just um Wait, was it
was it a Maybe it was a female. It was
Sandra. Is it Sandra?
>> We do have a Sandra. Um I can get you
over to her line and she can assist.
>> Yeah, I'll just make sure. Maybe my my
you know my mind just Sandra hits a the
ring. But you said she doesn't sell
Genesis.
>> We do have a Sandra. Um so she does work
with our Genesis story. Yes, sir.
>> Ah that all. See we're we're a figure in
it. See this is what it's like it's like
a chat that sometimes goes through my
mind and I just get the memory back, you
know.
>> No, you're okay. No worries. And then um
can I get your name before I get you
over to her?
>> Yeah. My name's Tommy.
>> Tommy. All righty. Let me go ahead and
place you on a brief hold while I get
her on the line. One second.
>> Yeah.
[Music]
>> Oh yeah.
Hi, Tommy. This is Sandra with uh
Genesis.
>> Hey, I'm so sorry. I totally forgot your
name. I apologize.
>> Oh, no problem. I did speak to my
manager and so he told me because it is
a new vehicle, you would have to
register the vehicle here in Texas and
then once you go back home, then you can
you would be registering the vehicle in
California. Well, how do I register in
Texas? I don't live in Texas unless like
unless I'm going to move in with your
manager for a day. Is you okay with
that? I mean, he probably has an extra
room.
>> That's our policy. Like, you would have
to register when it's a new card. You
would have to register the vehicle here.
>> So, you guys have just never sold new
cars out of state.
>> Unless they register the vehicle here in
Texas.
>> Well, then that would be an out of state
purchase. That'd be an instate. I mean,
unless unless your manager has a crazy
way for me to register the car in Texas.
I'd love to avoid tax. I just don't know
how I would register the car in Texas if
I don't live there.
>> Yeah. No, no, I understand. It's just
that we were having so many issues with
the license plate. Like I mentioned it
before, so they completely stopped doing
it.
>> Okay. Yeah, that's totally fine.
>> Okay. All right. Thank you.
>> Okay. No problem. Bye. Oh my gosh. This
is like the worst. Is this just like the
worst lease? 8 grand. Oh. Oh, this deal
isn't good at all. Oh no. Oh no. This
dealership is trying to have me to put
eight. I was like, "Oh, the payment's
even less. That's weird. That's odd.
That's that's crazy." $8,000
down. And this is why you don't
negotiate off monthly payment. Cuz for a
minute, I even fell for it. I'm like,
"Oh, even I fell for it for about a
second." Look, the last two years I was
there.
>> Thanks for calling, Genesis.
>> Thank you for calling or me answering my
phone. Sorry, I just Genesis. Got it. I
don't know why my mind just blinked.
Hey, I just want to see if you guys have
a car available.
>> Yeah. Who is this?
>> This is Tommy. Sorry, I literally forgot
how a phone call works. You ever do
that? No worries. And where you go to
the grocery store and you got to check
out and you're like, I don't even know
what's happening. That just happened to
me. Sorry.
>> Yeah. What store are you from?
>> No, I'm buying a car. I'm buying a car.
I I' I've messed up. Let's start from
Let's start from all over. Hey, thank
you for calling Genesis. Hey, my name's
Tommy. I'm trying to buy a car.
>> Cool. What car are you looking at,
Tommy?
>> Hey, uh, I have a stock number if that
helps.
>> Yeah,
>> G is in Genesis 26040.
>> It's the 2026 electrified GV70 Advanced.
>> That's it, man. I'm just, you know, I'm
trying to snack one of these last minute
EV deals, you know? I'm trying to jump
on. I know. That's my last one to be
honest with you. Well, my last advance.
Everything else is going to be a
standard.
>> I know. I want the advance. Let's just
put a bow on it. Call it a day.
>> I know. Let's do it. Let's wrap this up.
>> Did you want to come by and check it
out? Do you want me to send you some
numbers or where are you at?
>> Uh I I'm in Sacramento. Um you know,
I've been looking just around. There's a
few in LA, a few in Washington. So, I
figured let's just look at both and see
which one I can get and lock up a deal
today.
>> Easy. Um do you want me to Are you
leasing?
>> Yeah, I'm leasing. Yeah. Yeah. Maximize
the credit.
>> Cool. And then uh 3 year, 2 year.
>> 3 year, 2 year, whatever. Whatever's the
sweet spot.
>> Yeah. And then kind of the sweet spot
I've noticed is 33 months, 10K a year.
But I'll work it out for you and send it
over. And your first name is Tommy.
>> Tommy. Yeah. And then zip code if you
need it is 95608.
>> What's the last name? Tommy.
>> Hula. M I K U L A.
>> Over. And we'll see if we can make
something work.
>> Bada boom. Bada bing. I love it.
>> Easy. Are you coming up to pick up the
car? Would you ship it?
>> Uh, you know, I'm open to coming in.
Open to shipping it. I mean, whatever
makes the most sense.
>> Cool. Let me work this up. I'll get it
over to you right now. We'll go from
there.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> Thanks. Mhm.
>> Bye.
[Music]
Hopefully you got good news for me,
Simon.
>> Uh, I have good news. So, um, I was able
to take the pain and fabric protection
off of you, $9.95, and then get the
discount up to 6,000 and we're at 747
with,500 down.
>> We're so close.
>> Yeah, I mean, that's the best we can do
since we have to get the car, too.
>> If it was an in stock model, we can
probably do a little bit better, but
because we do have to get the car.
>> Okay. And then which what was the color
again? Just so I remember,
>> it's a Yuni white, the metallic white
with the frozen gray interior.
>> And you guys feel like is this one
you're actually able to trade for or is
this one you're trying to trade for?
>> From what I can tell, we should be able
to because we do have a good
relationship with them and they have two
of these.
>> So, I'm sure there wouldn't be they
wouldn't mind giving one up.
>> Okay. And this would be this is on the
ground, so it's here by the end of the
month.
>> Yeah, it'll be Yeah. I mean, if if all I
need from you is a deposit and a credit
application and then we can call the
dealership and get it here probably by
tomorrow.
>> Okay. Uh, perfect. Look, can we do this
just to make sure before I give you a
deposit cuz the 2 a.m., can you just
send me the numbers real quick? I'll
look them over with my partner and we'll
uh put a deposit down.
>> Sure. I will give me a sec. Give me a
second. I'll print that out. I'll send
the p I'll take picture of it and send
it to you. Okay.
>> Okay. Awesome. Perfect. Give me just a
minute.
>> All right. Okay. Bye.
>> Okay. Thank you. Bye.
>> That's good. But as long as you think
that's the best deal. Client said yes to
the deal. So that's a positive. So I
know a lot of people I know a lot of
people say like, "Oh my god, this is
super private and crazy how this ends up
happening." So I'm going to teach you
guys how we p we I I call a transfer of
trust, which funny enough, if you were
in car sales, you understand what a
transfer of trust is. Transfer of trust
is the same thing you call from sales to
finance. So when the sales manager,
normally a salesperson will go over and
say something along the lines of, "Hey,
this is my finance manager, blah blah
blah blah. He's great. He does this.
He's going to be awesome. He takes care
of all of my clients. You probably heard
that when you bought a car. Um, we do
the same thing. We just call it a
transfer of trust cuz vocabulary is hard
for me to come up with new things. I can
give you number. Okay. So, how we do
this is a few different things. Step
one, I'm going to give them phone
number. This CRM, I need to upload this
deal into the system. We're going to put
this deal into the CRM. We couldn't get
a hold of this dealership. And this is
like like a small thing that most client
people talk about the value right like
and maybe this isn't value for a lot of
people but like this one we couldn't get
a hold of sales every time we try to
call sales it wasn't working so we
actually got transferred to parts and
did the connection there still didn't
get a hold of somebody left a voicemail
that was kind of funny kind of
entertaining and that ended up starting
that dialogue so I know a lot of people
say oh those voicemails don't work maybe
I didn't need them maybe if I just said
hey my name's Tommy call me back but
maybe he called me back because the
phone call was interesting and it was
great and he was like you know what I
like this guy I'll call him back or it
could have been that he didn't care But
we got $17,250
off the car. The client does actually
qualify for the military. So look at
another $500. We're going to close this
deal. I'm going to put it in the system.
So we track all the deals we close.
Done. So we sent everything over. Good.
Congratulations in chat. So everybody,
let's give a nice little
congratulations. Round of applause for
for using delivered and using the
experience. And this is rock and roll.
So if you guys don't know who I am,
right? A lot of people are like, who is
this? Who is this nerdy little
5-year-old that's on the stream telling
people how to buy a car? If you guys
don't know, my name is Tommy. I own a
company called Delivered. We negotiate
car deals for a living. My goal with all
this company is to save you time,
energy, and anxiety. We save you money,
but that's a byproduct of it all. You
can do this on your own. You don't have
to hire me to do this. You can literally
watch my tips, watch my videos, watch
these streams, and learn how to do this.
I don't have a magic wand or a secret
sauce that saves you thousands of
dollars more than you can your own. I I
am very good at what I do. I know how to
have the conversations. I know the games
the dealerships play and I'm just
willing to put up with a lot of the BS
because, you know, that's what we do.
[Music]