credit score is uh new high score level.
Like they look at me at the bank and
they're like, "Oh my gosh, 88 plus 800
plus." Okay. Well, that's that's okay.
I'm not Now I'm not crying. I'm just I'm
just upset. Like I'm not upset with you.
I'm just upset with life. I really want
to do a deal with you. Dang managers. We
can blame Let's just blame the manager.
He's the worst.
>> Uh tax we can figure out. We don't know
your zip code.
>> Well, my zip code is a But you can just
put plus tax on the sheet. Like plus
whatever. I'm good.
>> But we we don't know what your taxes
are. We're looking for an ES300
luxury ES 3K off, 4K off, 3500 off. I
think 4K off is going to be our goal.
Let's go 3500 off cuz there's only like
nine of these in the country. So, we are
looking for an ES. They want a new car.
They want a 300. So, they want a 300
hybrid luxury. And she wants this green
color. Now, this green color is sunlit
green. There's only 13 of these in the
country. She wants macadamia or acorn.
Macadamia. I I think I have to look for
the Palamino as well just to give some
ideas because otherwise we're going to
be not negotiating for long. Client is
in Arizona. Oh, this car shows on their
lot.
>> This is Mo. How can I help you?
>> Hello Mo. This is buying department.
How's it going?
>> Good. How you doing? That's a good one.
>> Hey man, I'm doing well. Doing well. I
just want to see if you guys have a car
available.
>> Sure.
>> I have a
>> And your name, sir? Tony?
>> My name's Tommy.
>> Tommy. Okay. Tommy, which one you
looking for? I have a stock number if
that helps.
>> Sure.
>> Let me know when you're ready for it.
>> Yeah. Go ahead.
>> Stock number is S is in Subaru, U is in
uranium, 075
648.
>> Tell me, what model is this one?
>> I'm sorry.
>> What model is this?
>> It is an ES300H
luxury
>> green.
>> Sunlit green.
>> Yes. As of right now, Tommy, it's still
in a stock.
>> I love it. One more of it. Um really uh
I'm interested in it. I've been looking
around for one. This is the car I want.
hoping that you can give me some great
pricing on it so I can come buy it
today.
>> That's fine. Yeah, go ahead. Do you live
around here?
>> Not not exactly, but I live close enough
that I can make a quick drive over
there.
>> Okay. So, just let me know what you have
in mind and I can check with my
managers.
>> Easy. 4K off call a day. Bada boom, bada
bing.
>> 4K off. MSRP 56.
>> Yeah, just a good 52.
>> All right. And you paying cash? Are you
going to finance or anything?
>> I'm open to finance. Open to pay cash if
uh it makes sense.
>> Yeah, that's fine.
All right, Tommy, let me check and the
best number I can reach you.
>> Yeah, my
>> Okay, Tommy, let me check with my
manager and I'll call you right back.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> And and my name's Mo M O.
>> Mo M O. I won't forget it for the rest
of my life.
>> Easy one. Easy one. All right. Thank
you.
>> Talk to you soon.
>> And I'll call you. Sure, I will. All
right. Bye.
>> Byebye.
>> Thank you for calling. This is L
speaking in the sales department. Hey.
Uh, I just want to see if you guys have
a car available.
>> Okay. Yeah, let me check for you. What
was your name, sir?
>> My name's Tommy.
>> Tommy. All right. Which car are you
looking at?
>> I have a model code. VIN. What makes
more sense for you?
>> All of the above. No, I'm just kidding.
Just the stock number.
>> Stock. You know what? Normally, I would
say, "Yep, this is your stock number,
but I just don't see one." Call me blind
or call me crazy.
>> All right. What What car are you looking
at then?
>> I have the last six of the VIN, but it
is a ES300H
luxury.
>> Is it the red one?
>> No, it's a sunlit green one. We just get
this one in. Oh, is it new?
>> It is new. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Okay. That's why. All right. Give me one
second here. I have to check our new car
inventory, which is different.
>> No, you're good. Check away. I'm here. I
have nowhere to be.
>> All right. How's your day going, Tommy?
>> You know what? My day is just going
swell. You know, uh, how about yourself?
>> Good. Uh, it's not too bad. It's just
raining, so you know, that's never the
most fun.
>> Rain is, you know, rain is the worst.
I'm not one to dance in the rain, you
know. I'm like one to run through the
rain as fast as I can and get out of it.
>> That's fair. That is That is very fair.
>> Do you like to dance in the rain or do
you prefer to get out of it?
>> Oh gosh. Yeah, that's a very good
question. I think it depends on my mood.
I think mood changes a lot there for me.
>> I mean, I guess that's fair. I mean, if
you're in love with somebody and you're
in rain with them, maybe that's more
romantic than like you're trying to get
to a important business meeting in your
suit,
>> right? Like your brand new suit that you
just got. It looks like we don't have
any new ES300h's in sunlink green. Was
that the only color you're looking for?
>> I'm only looking for the sunlight green.
It says it's like going to be your
dealership today or tomorrow is what the
the interwebs say.
>> Oh, you know what that might be? Um,
>> my car.
>> Where are you calling in from?
>> Uh, Arizona.
>> Okay. So, that might be our store. What
we are able to do is possibly trade for
that. But if you're from Arizona, the
only way we'd be able to do like, you
know, sell you the vehicle, I believe,
is through cash deal.
>> It's fine. I can pick cash.
>> Okay. But I will say it does say it's go
I mean it maybe but I'm on the Lexus of
website and it does say visit our store
and it gives their address.
>> We we share with so our inventory we
share with so some people will call in.
It's actually at our location like you
know Northern California that is
something we're able to get. So we trade
with them like all the time for a bunch
of vehicles. So we are able to get that
vehicle. Tommy, what was your last name?
>> Last name Makula. M I K U L A.
>> Gotcha. We do trade with them all the
time though. So, I don't think it'd be a
problem getting the Sunlike Green ES300H
for you if that's the one you're looking
for. Or we can possibly get you one from
another dealership if that is, you know,
unavailable.
>> Yeah, I know they're a little harder.
The color is um, you know, they're
starting to make more of them. So,
>> so let's say we had the car and
everything was, you know, perfect. What
What was your next step in this? Were
you Did you want to purchase the
vehicle?
>> Is there is there another next step if
it's on What else would somebody do?
Like be like, "Okay, have a nice life."
>> Uh, no. more so just like you know
sometimes uh people from out of state
fly in to see the vehicle. I'm just a
little bit more confused by your call in
California for a specific vehicle. Is it
cuz Arizona doesn't have the Sunlight
Green one?
>> I've just heard there's really good
deals in LA and the flight is like $76
to fly there. So
>> Okay, gotcha.
>> I mean that's I mean that's
>> So what type of deal were you looking
for then?
>> I'm trying to get $4,000 off.
>> Okay. $4,000 off. And I'm assuming
that's off MSRP, right?
>> Yes. Correct. Or TSRP as it is.
>> Yeah. So then let's say are you you're
paying cash. Would you be interested in
any warranties or anything like that at
all?
>> Uh I mean I could be. I haven't got that
far like but sure. I mean in theory I
might be interested. Is that does that
help me? I say yes to that.
>> It honestly it doesn't it doesn't really
matter. Maybe it's just it's just really
up to you if you wanted a warranty or
not. It's just my I just like to get
knowledge up front so then I can you
know better help you out.
>> No, you're totally fine. I think we're
maybe jumping a little bit ahead, but um
you know, we we haven't even gone to
dinner yet. You know, we're still caught
in the rain.
>> That's fair. That's fair. Let's see
here. All right. So, $4,000 off and it
was I'm assuming on our website, which I
will be able to find right here.
>> Mhm. Yep. It is on your website.com.
Perfect. It's not. And it's all spelled
correctly. So, it's not a spam or fake
website.
>> Awesome. It is a.com.
>> Is a.com, notet. Anybody who has a net,
I don't trust them.
>> That's fair. That's fair. I don't really
understand why people donet over.com.
>> Honestly, I think they want to be
different just like Microsoft was trying
to be different than Google, but we all
saw how that turned out.
>> Yeah. I mean, they're not doing too bad,
but they didn't turn out to be, you
know, Google. So,
>> I I meant more like the search. But you
are correct. The company Microsoft is
doing well compared to Google as the
company also doing well. But I was
talking more the grand scheme of their
search engine. Bing. Bing. You know,
Bing Bing.
>> Mhm. Yes. Yes, I do. All right. So, it
was the luxury one, right? With the uh
acorn interior.
>> Yeah. A beautiful acorn. Sunlit green
with the acorn. It's just such a unique
color.
>> Yeah. So, I believe that one is going to
our store.
>> Okay, cool. I mean, I guess you guide me
on what to do. Should I call the store?
Can you handle it? I'm the
>> We'll get the car for you. So, to get
the $4,000 off, all I have to do is just
talk to my manager. But let's say
everything goes perfect and you know, we
get everything moving. We will require a
deposit on the vehicle for us to trade
for it. And then, you know, that's after
confirmation that we can get the vehicle
and then we go ahead and get the deposit
and then we'll trade. And then once we
get the trade in, we'll let you know
what time or like how soon. And then,
you know, assuming everything goes
perfect. And then what we'll do from
there is then we'll set it up to where
you can get the vehicle by the end of
the month. And then as soon as the car
gets here, I'll give you a call. You can
get a ticket over here and then we'll
hold it for you until it arrives or
until you arrive.
>> Yeah. I mean, as long as we agree to
numbers, then bada boom, bada bing, you
know, I'm good. Or bada boom, bada
Google, you know.
>> All right. So then never mind.
>> Yeah. Bada boom, bada bing. Yes, I got
it. Sorry.
>> All right. Microsoft though. All right.
Let's see here. What was your zip code?
>> My zip code is
>> Now that I'm thinking of it, I think
when you buy cash, no, cuz you'd be you
unless you wanted to ship it. No, that
wouldn't make sense. You'd be paying our
sales tax, which is actually quite low.
Fortunately for you, it's like I think
it's like 8% or something.
>> I understand that's low in California
terms, but I don't think that's low like
in general. But if I ship the car, as
long as I don't drive it off your lot
and I ship the car, even if I fly in, I
wouldn't pay. If you ship the car, then
you'll pay your tax wherever you dropped
>> off, which is possible. We'll figure
Obviously, like I said, let's get out of
the rain and figure out we can go read
the numbers and if we do that, then
>> All right, so cash 4,000 off MSRP. All
right, let me see if I can get this for
you. Then I will be right back and I'll
give you a call.
>> Okay, sounds good. Give me a call right
back.
>> All right, sounds good. Bye.
>> Okay, bye. Just so you guys know, in
California and other states like it, if
you buy a car in California and drive
the car off the lot, California will
charge you California sales tax. That is
how that works. In California, it's not
every state, but in California, they
will charge you that. Now, you can bring
that receipt to your current state and
say, "I paid tax here." And then you
don't have to pay or you'd pay the
difference, but you wouldn't get
reimbursed 90% of the time. So, what
that means is if you pay 9% sales tax in
your state, it's 5%. You're not going to
get that 4% back. It just gets thrown
away. If you guys don't know, as I'm
looking for the next car, my name is
Tommy. I negotiate car deals. Uh my goal
is to save you time, energy, and
anxiety. We save you money, but that's a
byproduct. I try to fly off you a,000
bucks to handle literally everything for
you. Price a car, trade, add-ons,
accessories. Again, the entire idea,
save you time, energy, and anxiety. I
don't advertise this as a money-saving
service because guess what? You can do
it on your own. You don't need me. I
just show you how to do it. So, if you
sit back, relax, you'll learn how to do
it. But if you're like Tommy, I don't
want to deal with any of this nonsense.
Link is in my bio to hire me or right
there there's a website somewhere you
can go and figure it out.
>> Hello, this is Ben. How may I assist
you? This is
>> Hey Ben, I think I'm looking for Mo.
>> You're looking for Mo?
>> Yeah, Mo called me from his number.
>> Just give me a second.
>> Okay.
>> Hey Mo Hey, this is Mo. This is Tommy.
>> Hey Tommy. Yeah, I called you back.
Yeah.
>> Yeah. I'm so sorry. I was busy.
>> No, no, it's all good. Uh, he said, uh,
rainy day, come on in. You can have it.
>> Okay. Yeah, just send me the numbers
real quick and let's bada boom. Let's
bada bing it.
>> Sure.
>> Yeah, send me those numbers and make
sure they all line up. And if so, yeah,
we can put Is it Is it officially on the
ground right as of right now?
>> Uh, I can double check. Is it showing on
ground? It is here, but let me touch
again. And what time can you stop by?
>> Well, I'm out of state, so I might have
to put a deposit on it first, but yeah,
that's totally fine.
>> But you do you have local address
though? I don't. No, I live in Arizona.
>> No. Oh, Arizona. Okay. So, let me see.
And you financing or paying cash?
>> I'm open to financing. Open to paying
cash. And I'm open to doing the whole
deal remotely if that's easier for us,
too.
>> Okay. Okay. Let me check with my
manager, Tony, and I'll call you back,
sir.
>> Okay. I'll be here.
>> Okay. Sure. Okay.
>> Right. Bye.
>> My name is Spel. What can I help you?
>> Hello. Are you a new car sales?
>> Yes, I'm a new car sales. My name is
Spel. What can I help you today?
>> Hey, I just want to see if you guys have
a car available. Okay. Which one was it?
Is it a new or pre-owned one?
>> It's It's brand new. I have a stock
number if that helps.
>> Okay. So, I'm ready. What model was it?
>> Uh, it is a 300HES.
>> Okay. So, I'm ready.
>> Stock number is 53481.
>> Mm- I didn't see it. What color is it?
>> It's sunlit green.
>> That's why I didn't see it. Okay, I'm
going to look. I have a different one,
but I'm going to tell you right now.
Give me one second. I just click in.
>> Oh gosh,
I sneezed so hard I fell over. Oh my
goodness.
>> So, this one is a sunlight green with
acorn brown, right?
>> Yep. That's it.
>> Okay, that's the one. Looks like it's in
here.
>> It is here.
>> Yeah, it looks like it does here. This
one is a luxury package. The MSRP is
56729.
Is the correct one? Sun green in a corn
seal line.
>> Yeah, that's that's the one I'm looking
for.
>> Okay. So, when uh would you when would
you like to come in and take a look at
this car?
>> Well, I've already driven it. Already
know I love it. Want more of it. I'm
really just trying to get the best
pricing. I'm hoping you can help me out.
>> Okay. So, what price are you looking for
right now?
>> Well, I have an offer for $4,000 off.
So, I'm trying to get like, you know,
4,500 5 grand off, you know, bada boom,
bada bing.
>> So, let's go. I'm going to talk to my
manager right now. What's your name?
>> My name is Tommy. Nice to meet you.
>> Nice to meet you, Tony. Okay, Tony. This
is the phone number. Can I call you
back?
>> Yep. This is my best number.
grand. Let's round up. Let's round up
for the funds. You know,
>> are you going to be financing or leasing
or what was the purchase?
>> Open to financing, open to paying cash.
>> Okay. Finance. If you want to finance,
how much do you want to put that?
>> Yeah, you know, 10 20,000, but more
focused on that out the door obviously.
>> Okay. So, sure. I can show you all. I
can show you out the door and also
financing rate. How is your credit
score? credit score is new high score
level like they look at me at the bank
and they're like 800 8 plus 800 plus
>> say 800 plus okay got it okay what is
your zip code I need your zip code okay
what uh city is it
>> Arizona Phoenix
>> okay I want to talk to my manager I'll
call you back shortly okay
>> okay awesome bada boom bada bing
>> okay awesome you're welcome thank you
>> all right bye this is edge Mickey a
hater time so hi Adam first off we don't
want going to put all of our eggs in one
basket because some dealerships will
advertise or say they will do a certain
discount. But lo and behold, when I ask
them for the out the door numbers,
conveniently, they just never come. So,
I could sit here and wait for 10, 20,
30, 40 minutes. It's been 10 minutes and
I still haven't got those numbers yet.
Or I could keep doing the work and
seeing if there's a better deal out
there. Secondly, why is it a bad thing
for the consumer to want to pay the
lowest price possible? How many times
have you been like, I want to buy a new
TV? I honestly want to pay the highest
price, so I'm going to go just to the
highest price. No, you go and look to
see what Amazon's offering, what Best
Buy is offering, what Walmart's
offering, what Target's offering, and
then figure out the best price, and you
pay that. Every single item in the
consumerism of America, consumers want
to pay the lowest price. Why is it a big
deal that the dealership should have to
make a competitive price that people
actually want to pay? Why are you so
offended by that? Now, the only negative
side is we have to go all the way across
the US to find any other example of the
car. I don't think I don't think you
guys understand our mission statement.
We have a mission statement here at
Delivered, which is all about putting
ourselves out of business. Like, that's
our goal. Like, that's the company's
goal. Just so we're clear, anybody can
do this on their own. If you can find
any clip of me saying you can't do this
on your own, you need to hire me to
charge a,000 bucks, otherwise you're
screwed. I will pay you 5,000 bucks.
Other than this time, I just said it
right now or saying it as an example to
get you to find that clip. You will not
find a clip on the internet of me not
saying that you can't do this. I think I
want to almost look for ultra luxuries.
I want to see if she'll take an ultra
luxury. Please hold. I don't want to
call on them without asking, but there's
we're out of options here. It doesn't
need to be a hybrid necessarily. Open to
the trim lux or ultralux. Okay, they're
open to ultralux. Okay, I found the
notes. If that opens up and you want to
go down that rabbit hole. Okay, let's
look at ultralux. Okay, that's
interesting. So, all of the ultralux are
in the Midwest. Like there's nothing on
So here. So, right here. Boom. This is
where the Ultralux in this color is just
chilling. So, we could look at these,
right? This one's been sitting on the
lot for 67 days. I like that. I like
that. Ooh, they're even saying they're
giving a $3,000 discount. Let's see what
happens to this Ultralux. It's $57,000
MSRP. Boom. Boom. Boom. Let's call this
dealership. Just kidding. Wait, wait.
Redo the redo the thing.
>> To provide the very best service, this
call may be recorded.
>> Thank you for calling Lexus. Please wait
while we connect you with a
representative. You can press one for
sales, two for service, and three for
parts at any time during this message.
>> Go.
>> A few moments later. Alexa, help me
direct your call.
>> Hey, Alexis. Uh, can I just talk to the
new car sales department?
>> Yes, just one moment.
Please leave your message after the
tone. When done, hang up or press the
pound key.
>> Hello, Lexus of this is Tommy from
Tommy's house. I just wanted to see if
you guys had a car available. It is the
2025 Lexus EX HY ES hybrid ultra luxury.
Stock number is X's and X-ray 38221.
I've already driven it. Already know I
want it. Really just trying to get some
numbers and if I agree to the numbers,
I'll buy it today. Bada boom, bada bing
is what they say in my country. So, if
you can just do me just the biggest of
favors and call me back. I was supposed
to go to somebody in sales. I listened
to some really good hold music with a
piano that really got me soothed and now
I'm ready just to, you know, bada boom,
bada bing, buy a car. So, anyway, if you
can call me back my phone, please call
me.
>> This is Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. This is Mo again.
>> I know.
>> Just going to How you doing sir? Just
going to give you a heads up. The person
who do out of state uh so she going to
call you right now. Her name is Summer.
>> Summer. summer like the season.
>> So anyways, so just just to let you know
and uh she'll handle everything online
with you.
>> Am I gonna get like numbers or
>> numbers of 4,000 off and she'll call and
give you all the info the way you want
it. If you're paying cash, you can let
her know if you financing. I don't know
how out of state works, but I'm giving
her all the information about the car
and we got the okay $4,000 off from the
from manager.
>> Okay. I mean, that's awesome. Yeah. I
just want to see that. So, she's going
to send me those numbers then?
>> Yeah, she going to call you.
>> Yeah, but is she going to like send them
so I can see them, right?
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. I just didn't know what's going to
happen. I don't want to sign any
paperwork until I see it, you know. Not
say I don't trust you, but you know.
>> No, no, no. That's fine. That's fine.
And you can give me your email, too, if
you want to.
>> You just text him. It's easier to text.
>> Yeah, you can text whatever.
>> Okay.
>> Okay. Tommy.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, yeah. Summer, you want to talk to
Tommy's on the line.
>> Hey. Hi, Tommy. My name is Summer.
>> Hi, Summer.
>> Here.
>> Good. Thank you. Okay. So,
>> I see we're going to do an ES luxury.
We're going to do 4,000 off. Well, okay.
So, we're going to sell it to you for
52354.
I just need uh your address so I can put
it into the computer to get the proper
pricing. Not pricing, your sales tax and
license.
>> Yeah, I'm fine uh texting all that over
here. I just wanted to make sure that I
can get like something in writing to
verify before I start giving you private
information that the price is what it
is. Not saying I don't trust you, but
there's a lot of crazy things going on
right now.
>> Right. So, I can't give you I I mean I I
can tell you this is the price, but I
can't give you tax and license and all
of that until I put it in my computer so
it tells me what all that is. So, I just
need your address.
>> Yeah. If you can just send me something
with I just, you know, I'm just a
private guy, so I don't like to give my
address out to random people. Can you
just send me something with plus tax and
I'll feel good about that. I just want
to make sure that the pricing is then
I'll give you my address. We'll get all
the licensing and all the fun stuff.
Call me crazy.
>> Okay, perfect. Okay, no worries. Um, I
will have him get you a square over that
just says this plus tax and license and
we will go from there.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> Okay. Um, are you going to come in and
pick it up or are we trucking it?
>> It might be trucking just so I can avoid
your guys' tax, but let me We're talking
I'm talking that over with my business
partner right now.
>> Okay, perfect. Because I can give it to
you both ways. It just said there's fees
associated with one way and fees
associated with a different way. So, I
just need to know which way. So, let me
get this over to you.
>> Yeah.
>> Can I set up my own shipping for uh we
don't let you do your own shipping.
We'll let you pay them directly. So, you
know that we're not making any money off
of it. However, we've had quite a few
problems where people have contracted
trucking companies. There's a big
trucking scheme going right now where
people actually steal the vehicles.
>> So, that that's been a big problem.
>> Okay. Yeah.
But let me get this over to you and
we'll go from there.
>> Okay, sounds great.
>> Okay, thank you so much.
>> Okay, thank you.
>> Bye-bye.
>> So, still haven't got the numbers down
in writing. It's the one thing I asked
for. We're probably going to get it, but
they're trying to There's a little bit
of hesitancy there. There's a little bit
of hesitancy there. We just want to make
sure it's good. Bada boom, bada bing.
>> This is Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. This is Thor. How's it
going?
>> I'm doing well. Thor, how's it going?
>> Good. So, I was not able to get that
sunlit green from the one place, but we
do have another sunlit green that we're
able to grab. It's the sunlit green
exterior with the um acorn interior. And
this one is the luxury with the
panoramic view monitor, the 18-in alloy
wheels, the heads-up display, triple
beam LED headlamps, smart access key
card, 12.3 in touchscreen display, and
it's got the Mark Levenson premium audio
system, power trunk with kick sensor,
illuminated door seals, the trunk mat,
cargo net, wheel locks, and key gloves.
And the MSRP on that is 56354.
Is that something you're interested in?
>> I'm interested in as long as we can get
to a better price than 56354.
>> So, I did ask my manager and for this
vehicle, we were going to ask uh our
MSRP plus our ads, which is a $24.90
add-on.
>> You're you're making me go to to the
frowny face, the sad face. I'm in tears
right now.
>> Uh it doesn't sound like you're in
tears. I mean, we got you a car. Have
you got Well, I mean, I already found a
car and I got four grand off the car by
the time it took you to do all that.
>> Oh, really?
>> Yeah. I got I got um another dealership
that's willing to do four grand off
theirs. Funny enough, same MSRP. I'm
wondering if it's a one you're trying to
trade with store.
>> Honestly, I'm not sure.
>> There's only like four in the area, so
>> Well, I gave it a shot. Can always try.
>> Okay. Well, that's that's okay. I'm not
Now I'm not crying. I'm just I'm just
upset. Like I'm not upset with you. I'm
just upset with life. I really want to
do a deal with you.
>> I appreciate that. It's just my manager
want wouldn't do that. I I do apologize.
>> Dang managers. We can blame Let's just
blame the manager. He's the worst.
>> Yeah, we can just blame the manager.
It's all good.
>> Okay. Thank you.
>> I just wanted to work with you. Yep.
Absolutely.
>> Take care, Tommy.
>> Bye.
>> This is Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. It's Thor again.
>> What up, Thor? You got you got you're
going to be you're going to be the
superhero here.
So, I uh went back to my manager and I
asked him, you know, he's just going to
get it from somewhere else if we don't
give him, you know, what he's asking
for. And so, he's like, "This is what
we'll be able to do." And it's nothing
more than that. It's ouruh 4 grand off,
right? Plus our ads, which is $24.90.
And that's just me being straight up.
That's what we're able to do. If you're
able to do that, then we're we got a
deal.
>> You did you did come in a little bit. I
mean, they told me I haven't got their
numbers yet. I haven't been in writing
yet. I'm still waiting on it, but they
told me they would do four grand no ads,
but they haven't sent it to me. It's
been 10 minutes. So,
>> well, uh, yeah, honestly, I I'm not
sure. I mean,
>> this is like $1,500 off with the ads.
What are the ads, so I know
>> it's a clear shield max shield. So, it's
a sealer jet on the outside and inside
of the car, giving you a 72-month
corrosion warranty. So, you know, in the
hot Arizona heat where, you know,
sometimes the paint chips and stuff a
little bit more easy than most, it does
come with the 6-year paint protection.
That's not scratches or anything. It's
just Yeah, the seal a jet, so it'll just
be for, you know, acid rain or uh sun
damage, things like that.
>> Yeah. No, I'll pass and all that, but I
appreciate it.
>> Yeah, I thank you.
>> No, thank you. I appreciate you going
for Bat one more time for me.
>> Absolutely. Bye.
>> All right. Bye.
>> I could just be going crazy. I'm calling
this dealership back cuz I'm annoyed
they're taking so long. Won't let me
call a dealership. I still have not got
the numbers from Mo. Mrs. Delivered
here. Hi, Mrs. Del.
>> Thank you for choosing. This is Patty.
How can I help you? Hey, I just wanted
to talk to somebody in new car sales.
>> I can help you with that. And which
vehicle were you interested in?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Absolutely. I'm ready.
>> 251395.
>> All right. ES300h Ultra Luxury. That
vehicle is available.
>> Awesome. Perfect. So, I want it. Want
more of it. Really just trying to get
some great numbers on it. I know these
cars are kind of been sitting around.
So, hoping that you can just give me
just a phenomenal deal and I can buy
your car today.
>> Bear with me one second. Let me do a
little math.
>> Do the math. Do a little math. Give me a
good deal. Buy a car tonight. Buy a car
tonight. It's a good song.
>> All right. So, 2,800 off. We're at
53839.
>> So, you're doing $2800
off.
>> Mhm.
>> Well, I appreci I was hoping to do a
little bit better than that if possible.
>> What were you thinking? I can always
talk.
>> Off, you know, a little bit more.
>> Yeah, that um Are you in Illinois?
>> I'm not in Illinois. I'm out of state,
but I just seriously see there's a lot
in your guys' area, which is why I'm
calling.
>> Hold on with me one second. Yeah.
>> For your peace of mind, we're taking all
necessary precautions to keep our
customers safe during this challenging
time. Thank you for your patience and
continued support.
>> What's the challenging time?
>> I'm getting a phone call
>> for Alexis. If you visited,
>> do I hang up or do I answer? It's Bobby.
I don't know who Bobby is.
>> A few moments later. All right. Sorry. I
did talk to my boss and just because the
hybrids are in demand, we're um not
selling out of state. That was a big
question I had.
>> Oh, so even though under goes a lot for
over a month.
>> Yeah, it's we want to keep them, you
know, keep the business here and then
that way people come back for service
and yeah, our markets, you know, I don't
know how different it is from where you
are, but we're keeping the the hybrids
definitely are our end.
>> Yeah, I get I get the NX or the RX. I
guess I'm a little surprised on the ES
cuz you guys have been sitting on this
one for like 30 days and you guys it's
not like you guys ES are different, but
I mean it's your choice.
>> Yeah, sorry about that.
>> Okay, no problem.
>> All right, appreciate your time. Thank
you.
>> I appreciate yours. Bye.
>> Thank you for calling Lexus of Please
wait while we connect you with a
representative.
>> This is Tommy.
>> I called him. He literally just hung up
with me. Oh my gosh. Okay. Thank you for
calling Lexus. Please wait while we
connect you with a representative. This
is Tommy.
>> Hey Tommy, this is Woody. Alexis, how
are you?
>> Woody, I'm doing well. How about
yourself?
>> Doing good. Watching you live over here.
>> Oh jeez. You know who I am. Oh, so you
called my voice. Did you like my
voicemail?
>> It came through. I recognized the voice
and hopped over and pulled you up here
to see how it was going with everybody
else.
>> It' be it would be it would be even
better if you just give me this deal and
then we can buy this car from you and
bada boom. Bada bing. Are you looking
for the 3500 off you've got in the
corner there?
>> No. So, the discount code is 3500, but I
already have a dealership at 4K. They
just haven't put it down in writing. So,
I'm trying to get 4500.
>> Give me the stock number you want.
>> Please hold one second. Let me stock
number S is in SAM 77671.
>> Our stock numbers start with an X. Can
you
>> Wait, did I pick the wrong I might have
picked the wrong dealership. Don't be
Don't be mad at me. Wasn't my fault.
>> That's all right. I'm a fan. We'll let
it go.
>> Nope. I just did some random dealership
voice. Lexus of
>> ultra luxury, right? Hybrid.
>> Ultra luxury hybrid. U076 761.
>> What color combo were you looking at?
>> Sunlight green.
>> Green Palamino 38221.
>> That's That's the one. That's it. Yeah.
Sorry, I'm looking. Sorry. I got to put
this as a happy face cuz you recognize
me. We can do so many Lexus deals. I
have so many Lexus deals. How have I not
called you? Have I not called you
before?
>> Not that we've spoke before. I didn't
get a hit from your phone number at
least, but distinct.
>> I mean, to be fair, I do use a new phone
number all the time because it gets
leaked. My client said yes to this other
deal, but they still haven't put me down
in writing, which is sad. So, if you put
it down in writing, get it faster. I'll
just rather give it to somebody who's
actually willing to put it down in
writing.
>> What puts a car deal on it? 4500 off.
>> 4500 cuz yours is farther for shipping.
They live in Arizona. So, that's LA.
You're in halfway through the country.
So, it'll be $500 more to ship.
>> Do4,500 off one of those.
>> Yeah. Send me the numbers on that. We'll
put those together
>> on a Nightfall mic when I'll do the same
deal on that, too.
>> Okay. If you can send me both of those,
then I'll pitch it to the client. I'm
just seeing. And you said you don't have
any premium pluses for GX's. You said
you have overtrails.
>> Luxury plus, Overtrail, Overtrail Plus.
They're not. We've had premium and
premium.
>> And I've got to ask you, I know you're
going to say, "No, you don't have any TX
550 Hybrid Pluses. Just chilling around.
>> Short on those.
>> These are such a hard car to get.
They're I think they're harder than
GX's."
>> Yeah. email or something you want me to
reach out to you from. So, I'd like
>> is the number you're calling me at the
number I can text you my email, but I
like to text. It's easier, but that's my
>> text to this number.
>> Well, you can't text this number. Tech.
If you have my number, text me and I
will or actually I'll make sure you have
that text.
>> Waiting on it to come through here
>> and then I'll text you my email.
>> Got it here.
>> Okay. Boom. Let's send these numbers
here. Let's get these ra rocking and
rolling and make it work. Now, do you
want proposals on both the blue and the
green ES? You've got different people
looking for those.
>> So, give me one on the green and then
give me one on the blue. Yeah. Yeah.
Give me two different proposals. You can
just do plus tax on them so you don't
have to calculate tax and
>> then, you know, it'll change based on
exactly where they live with sales tax.
We use a third party company to get our
out ofstate title and registration done,
but it's not um much. I've just got to
get that buttoned up whenever we figure
out exactly where we're getting this
title and registered. But I can send you
over both of those. And then by all
means, we're an extremely aggressive
dealer. If you've got anybody looking
for any Lexus, I think you're going to
be hardressed to find somebody easier to
work with than us.
>> Hey, I like it, man. You're making
yourself look good on live, too. But
like I said, we probably do 30 to 50
Lexus deals a month. So, uh, I'm going
to give my team your number so we can
start trying to put some of these
together.
>> All right, that's awesome. Let me uh
I'll put some quick quotes together on
those two ES options. Just let me know
what else you need from me. Okay,
awesome, man. I appreciate making it
easy. Thank you for calling me back and
listening to my voicemail.
>> Yes, sir. Thank you. Bye.
>> Okay, bye. That's a happy face. That's a
happy face. That's a really happy face
because as long as he gives me the deal.
Let's verify that he actually gives me
the deal. I really like what's up with
Mo. Is Mo about to drop the ball?
Remember when that one guy said, "Just
stop calling dealerships. Stop calling
dealerships." If you guys don't know, my
name's Tommy. I negotiate car deals. My
goal is to save you time, energy, and
anxiety. We save money, but that's a
byproduct of it all. If you want me to
negotiate a car deal because you feel
like you can on your own. I'm sorry
that's not true. You can 100% do this if
you're willing to put the time, the
energy, the anxiety in, that's the
thing. You have to make some phone
calls. You got to do some dealerships.
This is something that anybody can do if
they're willing to put that time in. We
can definitely do some deals together. I
don't know where you're from, but let's
boom, bada bing. Okay, I'm going to call
Mo one more time because this is the
perfect color combo. I have to double
check for the client one last time. I
know this dealership wants to get this
deal done, but I have to double check.
It's it's perfect color combo versus the
third color option.
Hello, this is Rafael.
>> Hello, I'm looking to speak to Mo again
or summer again.
>> Mo or Summer?
>> Summer. Okay, let me trans.
>> I'm sorry.
>> Perfect.
>> We are sorry there is no one available
to take your call. Please record your
message after the tone. Press star to
discard the recording or press any digit
to end the recording.
>> Hello, Mo or Summer. This is Tommy. We
were working. Thought I was buying a
car. I've been just sitting here
twiddling my thumbs for, you know, the
last like hour just wishing for, you
know, it's fall, but I was hoping for
summer to call me back or at least text
me to let me know or Mo to come in and
be the savior of my life. Uh, really,
I'm just trying to get these numbers. If
I get these numbers, I am buying a car.
I just want to verify before I give you
my address. If it's that important, I
can text you my address. Um, but like
I've been waiting for like an hour. I'm
like twiddling my thumbs. I cannot wait
much longer. Uh, so please call me, text
me, beat me, page me, fax me. You have
my number. Okay. Bye.
>> A few moments later.
>> We're in a phone call. This is Tommy.
>> Hey Tommy, I just got your message. What
happened? So when I ask you something,
someone was asking me. So you just need
the pricing and what we selling you for,
right? That's the only thing you need.
>> Something to confirm. I just need
something to confirm before I give you
all my private information.
>> Okay. Okay. Damon, I can text you.
>> Yeah, that's what I'm waiting for.
That's what I'm waiting for this whole
time.
>> Yeah. Okay. Okay. I'll text you from my
direct line.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> Because she was asking about the tax and
license because she don't know the
county and I can just confirm the
pricing with you. Okay, I'll do that.
>> Confirm the pricing with me that I'm
willing to give all the information you
guys need to finalize this and get my
business partner and we can all buy the
car.
>> Okay. Is tax not going to be included or
license or anything? Just selling price.
>> Just selling price plus t and you put
plus tax. That's fine.
>> Uh tax we can figure out. We don't know
your zip code. Well, my zip code is a
but you can just put plus tax on the
sheet like plus whatever the tax is. I'm
good.
>> But we we don't know what your taxes
are.
>> Yep. Just
>> DMV and official fees. Summer will
figure out but I can confirm you the
selling price for now. What do you
think?
>> Yep. Yeah, that's fine.
>> Okay. So, you have something in writing?
>> Yeah, that sounds great.
>> Okay, I'll do that.
>> Okay. Awesome.
>> Okay. Okay, Tony. Bye.
>> Thank you, Bo. Bye.
>> Okay.
>> Thank you for calling.
Unfortunately, our car wash is closed
today.
>> Dang it.
>> For sales, please press one. For
service, please.
>> Okay, we're going to see if we can put
any of this together.
>> Family adventures or weekend escapes
these
>> purch.
>> Hey, can I speak to Caitlyn?
>> Yeah, my pleasure to connect you. Hi,
this is Caitlyn.
>> Hey, Caitlyn. I was just checking to see
if your car wash was open.
>> It is not open, unfortunately.
>> Okay, awesome. Okay, so you're trying to
do some of these deals.
>> Yeah, let's take a look at inventory.
Which we what are we looking for?
>> Okay, let's go with this. You said you
wanted both these ES's. So, I have two
ES300H
ultra luxuries that I need.
>> Okay,
>> one is fully loaded with Nightfall
Cloudburst and then the least preferred
Caviar with the Palamino interior.
>> Got it. Would we be open to Nightfall
Palo out of curiosity?
>> Yeah, Nightfall Palo is the number one.
>> Okay, sounds good. I got that one
readily available on the ground right
now.
>> What can you do on that one? that one.
If you're looking for You're looking for
45, right?
>> Yeah, 4500 is what I'm getting on these.
>> Is that a finance or a cash deal? Out of
curiosity.
>> Uh finance.
>> Finance. Uh if you give me 30 seconds,
let me give my manager a call. I think
he'll take it.
>> Okay, cool.
>> Awesome. Let me put you on a brief hold.
Give me a hold.
>> Awesome. Thank you.
>> Safety and technology innovation coupled
with unmatched customer service.
>> No car wash. Unacceptable. Hello.
>> Yeah, I know. The car wash is
unacceptable. It closes at 4,
unfortunately. Oh jeez. Oh, it made it
seem like it was shut down forever.
>> No, no, no, no. They just closed at 4
during the week.
>> Um, yeah, he'll take the deal.
>> Okay. Boom. Send it to me. Let's Ba
boom, bada bing. Okay, let's go. You
ready for the next one?
>> Yep. Ready for the next one?
>> Boom. Let's sell some business. Uh, what
about an RX 350H luxury all-wheel drive
with convenience tech and advanced park
in silver black with black interior.
>> Gotcha. Let's take a look. We want
Aridium, correct?
>> Wait, say that again. Sorry.
>> Aridium.
>> Uh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Aridium or caviar.
Black. We're going fancy. The fancy
Lexus terms.
>> Black interior.
>> Black interior would be preferred in
this one.
>> Gotcha. It looks like I have an Aridium
with black interior. Luxury package.
It's currently an allocation at the
moment.
>> That's fine. My clients are willing to
wait for the deals.
And Convenience Tech and Advanced Park
has all three.
>> Yeah. With that luxury package here in
the Midwest, they pretty much come fully
loaded.
>> I like that. Okay. Boom. Boom.
Literally. Okay. We have so many deals
here. We're going to be having fun here
for a second. RX, this is my second
biggest brand. So, uh, what can you do
on that one?
>> Right now, all of our RX hybrids are
selling at MSRP plus taxes and fees.
>> Oh,
>> yeah.
>> Okay. We're not Okay, we're not doing
fun deals on that one. Okay, we'll skip
that one cuz I'm getting like three
grand off this. What about IS- 350 F
Sport all drive?
>> Let's take a look. Let me see if I got
anything. I need blue with caramel or
caramel, but would accept other
interiors. But once
>> it looks like both of the blue ones are
spoken for already. Those are held with
a deposit. Only F Sport I have available
is incognito with white interior.
>> No, they said the only one blue is open
to interior. So, we will not do that
one. Do this. This other ES is one I'm
doing right now, but I I don't think you
have the green.
>> No, I do not. I only have white, gray,
black, blue, and red right now.
>> Okay. And Okay. So, I have another RX
350 hybrid. You won't do premium plus.
You get all of them the same way for
you. You won't give deals.
>> Yeah, those are staying at MSRP plus
taxes and fees just due to the crazy
demand here over in the Midwest.
>> No, no, no. I get it. I get it. I
understand there certain cars you're
going to be hotter on. What about the
GXs or TXs?
>> GX's
the one I believe is available still. I
just have to get the confirmation is an
atomic silver luxury plus with dapp gray
interior.
>> Uh, okay. Captain shares
>> bench in the second row.
>> Okay. And then what is your guys's How
are you guys doing on those?
>> MSRP plus taxes and fees.
>> Okay. Send me that one cuz I might have
a home for that. Um, do you And you
don't have a premium. You said premium
plus.
>> Say that one more time for me.
>> You don't have a premium plus at all?
>> No, I do not unfortunately.
>> Okay. And you don't have a TX at all?
500 hybrid.
>> The 550, the plug-in hybrid.
>> Uh, they want a TX500 hybrid F-S Sport
performance luxury.
>> Got it. The luxury package I don't have,
unfortunately. Those are a limited
production run. I'm not sure what
they're doing right now. We only have
two of them and that's on a wait list.
>> Okay, cool. Let's do the send me the GX
and send me the ES.
>> ES sounds good. Do you want me to text
that over to this number?
>> Uh, yeah. text this over to this number
and then I'll give you the other number
that dealerships have that know who I am
so it's easier to contact me because I
get rid of these numbers every week. So
I'll text you on the number I don't get
rid of. So then you have that I'll give
my team your number so you can contact
you as well.
>> Awesome. Sounds good. I'll send this
over momentarily.
>> Awesome. Sounds good. Talk to you later.
>> Absolutely. Have a good one.
>> You too. Bye.
>> I still have not got a number. Wait, did
they send it to me? I think they got
Okay, thank you. Finally sent it to me.
Copy image. Okay. One second. Okay.
Okay. He says Okay, we'll undo the is I
want to make sure his numbers are right.
One second. Oh my gosh, everything's
going crazy. Boom. Boom. Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait one second. Okay, I got
4,000 Wait. Okay, so this the actual
discount was $3,500 off. I changed it
for that person. We got $4,000 off.
Yay. It's fireworks.
See? Oh, there's confetti. You guys You
guys see that? You guys see that? Wasn't
that fun? And no, I didn't just change
that for funs. I changed that for the
dealership that was watching that I was
trying to get a better deal on. So much
fun. Yay. I just joined. What happened?
Oh, what happened? I'll show you again.
Ready? Yay! We did it. We got fireworks.
You deserve a raise. Now, the problem is
is one dock fee is $85. The other dock
fee is $7.99. So, even though the 44500
looks nicer, it actually ends up being a
more expensive option, and it's the
customer's third favorite interior
option versus the first in color. So,
the deal, even though they've been a
more difficult dealership, is a better
one for our client. But what we do in
this situation is we just let our client
know, our client's watching right now. I
think they told me they're going to
watch. So, if they're watching, that's
great. If they're not, we're going to
give both to the client and say, "Which
one do you want to do?" Uh, and then
they'll make a decision based on that.
If you guys don't know what my name is,
my name's Tommy. I negotiate car deals
for a living. My goal, save you time,
save you energy, save you anxiety. We
save you money, but that's a byproduct.
I charge a flat fee of a,000 bucks. I
handle everything for you. Price a car,
trade, add-ons, accessories. Our main
goal is to make caring fun and make it a
great experience. We have a staff of
nine people. You get three people
dedicated to your deal at all times to
make sure you truly have the world's
best buying experience. That is what
we're trying to do. Our main goal uh
from the day you hire us to getting a
deal done. Right now our timeline's
about 2 weeks from the day you pay to
getting a deal done. We had a little bit
of a lag. We were closer to 3 weeks. I
think we're finally getting caught up
back to that twoe period. Been working
overtime to make sure that happens. Bada
boom, bada bing. That's what it is. Link
is in the bio to hire us. If you have
questions about the service, you can go
link in my bio, ask any questions. I
respond to basically every email every
night.
Yay. Confetti.