I do watch your Tik Tok videos all the
time.
>> You got to answer the phone better than
me.
>> Yeah.
>> No, it's okay. Yeah. I'd hate to, you
know, call a dealership and not have it
and waste time. That's not the fun
thing, but I get it.
>> So, that vehicle actually is available.
>> You got my attention.
>> We do put a full clear bra on the front
part of the car. We'll sell it for 2500,
though. So, we're not we're making 500
bucks on it.
>> Oh,
>> yeah.
>> I know you're off. I just I don't want
to bother you in your days off, but I
also don't want to lose the car. They
want me to do this car cuz it's hard to
do is what they want me to do. They want
me to do a TX 550 hybrid. I don't even
know how many there are of these. What
the fudge are we doing? There's none of
these cars. This is a trap. There's zero
in the country. He wants a red, which
isn't out yet. I can't negotiate a car
that doesn't exist. Daddy's open a
color. We're back in this. The only one
we got in here. This is a weird car.
There's so little of these cars. I'll
start with the brown interiors. Let's
try to get him the color he wants in the
interior color he wants.
It's a beautiful day. This is Christian
Sales. Who do I have the pleasure of
speaking with?
>> Hello, Christian Sales. It's also a
beautiful day at my house. This is Tommy
from the buying house my house. I just
wanted to see if you guys have a car
available.
>> Yeah. Is it pre-owned or new?
>> It is brand new.
>> Okay. Do you have the stock number or
the year making model?
>> I do. Whenever you're ready. Yep.
>> It's F as in factory 25342.
>> F25342.
That's it.
>> Sorry, my computer's a little slow.
What's the year, make model? I think
that would
>> Sure. Uh, it is a 2025 Lexus TX.
>> TX.
>> E S E
>> TX. T is in Tommy Todd Tyrannosaurus
Rex.
>> Okay. And is it a 350H, 500, 550 H+?
>> Oh, okay. That specific trim, that's the
plug-in hybrid, I believe. That would
Yeah, the 50 plus.
>> Yeah, they're super hard to come by. I
see the 26 Winchill Pearl Peppercorn.
>> Yeah, that one's fine, too.
>> Okay. It's a different stock number than
the one. Are you local to us in or
website?
>> Okay. Are you out of state?
>> I am.
>> Okay. Because I'm not at the store. So,
I'll get your information over to our
out of state team and they could go over
if this one's available or not cuz I I
know that they're super hard to come by.
You said your name was Bobby. Is that
correct?
>> Tommy.
>> Okay. I will
>> Tommy Hilfiger.
>> Yeah. I'll forward your information.
This is the best phone number for them
to reach you at.
>> Okay.
>> Where are you located?
>> I'm I'm in North Carolina.
>> What's the zip code over there?
>> Yeah, my zip code is
>> Okay. Will you have a trade?
>> No, I won't have a trade.
>> Okay. And if everything works out, do
you plan to make the trip here or would
you need shipping?
>> I mean, I'm open to either one. Whatever
makes the most sense.
>> Okay. And do you know if it's cash or
finance? Or do you want to discuss that
with them?
>> I'm open to cash, open to finance,
whatever makes the most sense. Will to
finance if the deal makes sense.
>> All right. Okay. And then can I have
your last name, Tommy?
>> Yeah. Last name, Mula. M I K U L A.
>> All right. My name is Christie. I'm
going to forward your information. I'll
also send you a text message where you
can communicate with the store. So,
someone will reach out to you shortly.
>> That'd be great. Thank you.
>> Thank you. No problem. Bye. Bye. Okay. I
hate dealerships that I cannot just
click their number. Like I'm clicking
the phone button right now. I'm kicking
the phone number. Okay. I guess I'll
call this one.
>> Tommy from my house.
>> Hello.
>> Yes. Who is this?
>> This is Tommy from my house. Who is
this?
>> Uh Jake.
>> Oh, Jake. Okay, that's your name. Oh,
nice to meet you, Jake. Hey, I just want
to see if you guys have a car available.
>> Yes. Give me a moment. Let me just
transfer you over to my phone because uh
I answered at the reception desk.
>> Sure, no problem.
>> I apologize about that.
>> No, you're good.
>> Okay. How can I help you?
>> Uh I just want to see if you guys have a
car available.
>> All right. And what's your name?
>> My name's Tommy from my house.
>> Tommy. Okay. And are we looking at a
pre-owned or a new?
>> Brand new.
>> Brand new. All right. What kind of
vehicle is it?
>> I have a stock number if that helps you.
>> Uh, yes it does.
>> Let me know when you're ready for it.
>> I'm ready.
>> Uh, F is in Vinance 26676.
>> TX 550H+ luxury.
>> That's it.
>> Uh, Celestial Silver and Peppercorn
interior. As of right now, I do have uh
somebody that has a deposit on it.
Bummer. I've always been late in life.
Okay. I'm assuming you don't have
another one of these just chilling
around.
>> Let me just see. Give me one second.
>> You never know.
>> Yeah, as of right now, I don't. Um,
unfortunately. By the way, I do watch
your TikTok videos all the time.
>> You got to answer the phone better than
me.
>> Ah, you caught me off guard.
>> I know. You answered at the receptionist
test. I get it. But no, it's good.
You're live right now. Um, so you don't
have any of the 550s? No, I I've
honestly gotten like over the course of
the last year, I'd probably say we've
seen about four in total.
>> Oh, really? Dang.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> I'm trying to see if I can put something
else together cuz you're on the phone.
I'm assuming you don't have any GX 550
Premium Pluses just sitting around in
your back lot chilling.
>> Not sitting around, but we do have some.
Let me see. I have like allocated ones
that are incoming, but nothing on the
ground. I have one that's close and then
a bunch that are about a month away.
>> Do you have any white or black exterior?
Black interior.
>> Um, yeah.
>> Premium with a third row. Must be a
third row.
>> Premium plus or premium?
>> Premium plus with a third row.
>> Yeah, I got two white with black that
are available.
>> Make sure there's one. What What can you
do on it?
>> All right. Is it going to be a finance
lease?
>> I'll finance for you.
>> Finance? Okay. Yeah. I mean, I could see
what they're willing to do. I mean,
honestly, as of right now, it's kind of
just been like an MSRP thing. Not going
over, but just kind of keeping it at
what it is.
>> I appreciate that. I was trying to think
like nothing crazy, like 500 bucks off.
I also need another one with a second
row bench, too. I need two of them if
that helps you at all.
>> Second row bench.
>> I need one with a second row, same color
combo, but one wants white and gray. The
other one wants white and black.
>> Yeah. So, the white with I don't have a
white with gray, but the white with
black I could do. All right. Let me uh
What would be the state that does
matter, though? What would be the state?
>> I mean, like, states are just like, you
know, I think in life we should stop
thinking about where people live, but
like where you feel you are. They're in
Texas.
>> All right. I think I think we could get
that done. All right. Let me do this.
Could I um get like a contact
information?
>> Yeah. Let me give you a better number
than this one cuz this is my number for
when I don't want people to have it. I'm
going to give you the number for that I
use more often. Okay.
>> No problem. Ready? Would you prefer if I
text that number? Call.
>> Yeah, just text. Just text me. But if
you get if you get a deal, call me.
That's cooler.
>> All right, sounds good. All right, I'll
get back in touch to you shortly.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> Thank you.
>> No, thank you, man. Talk to you later.
>> Anytime. Bye.
>> Bye. Just want to point out that I was
mean to him and he still might get us a
deal. Remember, people say that my
meanness would have people hang up. And
just so you guys know, MSRP on a GX550
is a good deal, but I'm hoping to get
$500 off because doesn't hurt to ask.
Apparently, it's impossible to call this
dealership. I wish dealerships didn't
realize how bad it is to call them. I'm
I don't want to call myself dumb. Like
this is the website right now. Right.
I'm on the website. I'm chilling. Lexus
of It's a company. The phone numbers.
Right. Right. It's not up here. Not up
here. I scroll down. Not here. Not any
here. I don't want to allow the cookies.
Maybe that's why I I found their
Instagram really quick. Maybe that that
takes me to the Auto Mall. But now I'm
not on the page with the stock number.
And this is the car I want. Which maybe
it's under the 500s. So now what I have
to do is I still have to call this
dealership. Where is their number?
People go back. I found their number. So
now I'm going to call them. Really
listen to me.
>> Good afternoon. This is Sam in the sales
department at Lexus of How. May I assist
you?
>> Hello. This is Tommy Mula. I would like
to see if you guys have a car available.
>> Sure. Which vehicle are you uh
interested in?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Is it a a new car or pre-owned?
>> I think it's a new car.
>> And what which model is it? It is a TX
all-wheel drive.
>> Just filtering down in our new cars to
TX's. And what was the stock number,
sir?
>> It's C as in cat 016356.
>> That doesn't show in our inventory
anymore as available.
>> Okay. I see it on the website, but I
know it's from the pen.
>> Was it Lexus of website?
>> It's the website.
>> The auto trade the automal site. Yeah,
possibly. Was it a a premium all-wheel
drive or a luxury all-wheel drive? No,
it was a 550.
>> Okay. So, yeah, the the plug-in hybrids.
Uh, there it is. Yeah, that one. Oh, so
our our internal website's showing it.
So, we that one was pre-sold um some
probably two months ago. So, you won't
see it anymore on our Lexus of website,
the specific one for the dealership.
But, uh, it's disheartening to hear the
Penske one still shows it cuz we have
that problem with Autotrader
Carus. They're not pulling the cars off
our site that we pre-ell cuz we're
trying to, you know, make sure people
don't call on something that isn't
available to talk about.
>> Yeah, that's no fun when that happens. I
agree.
>> No. So, you know, I had a customer get a
get one just a couple weeks ago. So, the
26 version, it looks like they've added
in the panoramic glass roof option, but
they've taken away the ability to add a
hitch to it.
>> That's the worst.
>> I find Yeah, it is. I I am like, "Okay,
our only V6 SUV short of a GXLX and
you're not letting us add a hitch to
it." But that kind of a discussion we're
not privy to when they uh they're
planning the next year's model. So, you
know, that was disheartening to read in
their latest update on the car.
>> Yeah. That's it's unfortunate when
manufacturers are taking things away
rather than adding them, you know.
>> Yeah. And I'm like, you added a glass
roof that we here in Arizona don't open
that often. It's too dang hot. It's too
bright.
>> Yeah. you know, seats will melt and then
they took away, you know, they took away
a a utility. I'm, you know, I'm a big
fan of, you know, if it can tow, don't
don't lose that ability. And that, you
know, until this new version, all the
models come with tow prep as standard.
So, you know, if you want to share your
info, I can let you know. I can try to
offer future allocations of the hybrid
plugin, but um, unfortunately, it looks
like that's going to be how the 26s are
coming. Oh, I don't even need to I don't
I don't tell anything. So, that's
perfect.
>> Okay. Did you want to share your info?
Because what we basically do with the
problem up to recent legislation was the
zero emission states gobbled up a a lot
of the plug-in hybrids and electric
vehicles, but now they're starting to
allow us to have more of them.
Theoretically,
they don't have to reach a much higher
MPG average in 13 states of the country.
>> Yeah. No, I understand. No, I'm uh No, I
mean, don't worry about I'm going to
keep calling around. If I can't find
one, I'll call back. But I'm going to
try to find one somewhere in the
country.
>> Oh, yeah. Are you here in Arizona or or
>> I'm not I'm out of state. I'm just
looking around for one.
>> Okay. Yeah, it you know, definitely a
challenge these days with low production
on on many models and we're, you know,
our store doesn't mark do a market
adjustment for a rare model and
unfortunately that's, you know, not
across the board. You know, we see some
It's basically price gouging going on on
the our GXs in the valley where they're
>> Yeah.
>> they're deciding to add Yeah. make 10 or
30,000 of modifications to the car that
doesn't require not great behavior by
these dealers. That's for sure.
>> Yeah. I agree.
>> I appreciate the call and I'll pass on
to my managers. Which site did you use?
The the nationwide one.
>> I don't go on there often.
>> The mall.com.
>> Okay. All right, I'll take a peek myself
and I'll let them know if it's staying
on there when it shouldn't. Dang it.
>> Yeah. No, it's okay. Yeah, I'd hate to,
you know, call a dealership and not have
it and waste time. That's not the fun
thing, but I get it.
>> Yep, definitely. All right, sir. So, um,
certainly wish you luck on your search.
>> Thank you. I wish you luck in your
sales. I will talk to you maybe next
time. I need a car.
>> You got it. Not a problem. Thanks.
>> No problem. Bye-bye.
>> Bye-bye. People particularly say Tommy,
you're just wasting people's time. To be
fair, he was a nice gentleman.
>> This is Charelle and Sales. How may I
assist you today?
>> Hello. I just want to see if you guys
have a car available.
>> Of course. Who do you have the pleasure
of speaking to?
>> My name is Tommy.
>> Okay. How you doing, Tommy?
>> I'm doing I'm doing well. Doing well.
How about yourself?
>> I'm doing fine, thanks for asking. Are
we looking for a pre-owned vehicle? I'm
actually looking for a brand new one.
>> Okay. What vehicle is that?
>> I have a stock number if that helps you
out.
>> Sure. Go ahead.
>> N is in Nali. L is in Lexus. S is in
Smyrna. 268583.
>> And what kind of vehicle is that?
>> Is a Lexus TX550
Hybrid Plus.
>> And what color? White.
>> So, that one has been pre-sold. We don't
get those in often. One every six
months. And that one has been pre-sold.
And right now they have a pause on
making those vehicles because of the
parts.
>> Bum bum bum. That's a bummer.
>> Yeah, we've had several clients and we
have a list. I think we have five people
on the list that's waiting, but we only
get one every 6 months or so.
>> I get it. No worries. I will keep
looking around, but I appreciate uh your
time.
>> Of course. You have a great day.
>> You too. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> If you guys don't know, my name's Tommy.
I negotiate car deals for a living. My
goal is to save you time, energy, and
anxiety. We save you money, but that's a
byproduct of it all. I charge a flat fee
of a thousand bucks. I handle the
literally the entire process. We have an
entire team of nine people dedicated to
making sure you have the best buying
experience possible.
>> Lexus sales, this is Brian. How can I
help you?
>> Hello. I just wanted to see if you guys
have a car available.
>> Oh, what vehicle assessor?
>> The stock number is blank, but I can
give you like the last six of the VIN,
make, model. What makes the most sense
for you?
>> Is it new or pre-owned?
>> It's brand new.
>> Okay, perfect. Uh, can I have the last
four at the end?
>> Of course, it is 1360.
>> Was that the RX 350 Premium Plus?
>> That is the TX 550 Hybrid Plus. Yes.
>> So, that vehicle is already Somebody
actually already um reserved that
vehicle.
>> A That's a bummer. That's okay.
>> A dollar too late.
>> Apparently, we don't Yeah, I mean, I can
keep you updated if we if I have any
more coming in.
>> No worries. I will keep calling around
until I find one.
>> Okay, perfect. You have a great day.
>> Thank you. You too. Bye.
>> Hi, thanks for call. This is Tracy. How
can I help you?
>> Hey, Tracy. Uh, is Zach available?
>> Zach is off today. Can I give it give
you his voicemail? I think he's going to
be off for a few days.
>> I just thought maybe he was ignoring me
cuz he didn't like me, but it's probably
cuz he's off that makes more sense.
>> Yeah, he'll be off for I think the whole
weekend. Can anybody else help you or
you want to
>> Yeah, you just have somebody else help
me. That's fine.
>> Okay, hold on. Please just let him know
you're, you know, dealing with Zach.
>> Yeah. Yeah, that's fine.
>> Okay, thank you. Hold on.
>> Meanwhile,
>> hi, this is Henry with How can I help
you?
>> Hello. I just want to see if you guys
have a car available.
>> Sure.
>> I don't have the stock number cuz it's
blank, but I have the last like four of
the VIN if that helps.
>> Sure. Give me one second. Let me gra get
into my uh inventory system and I'll be
able to help you out. What's your name?
I don't believe they grabbed it.
>> No worries. My name's Tommy.
>> Tommy. Pleasure to speak with you. I'm
Henry.
>> A pleasure is all mine.
>> All right. Okay. So, what are you taking
a look at today?
>> The last for the VIN is J is in Japan
032.
>> So, that vehicle actually is available.
>> You got my attention. Let's make sure
we're in the same vehicle. TX 550.
>> Yep. TX 550 H+ luxury all-wheel drive.
It is in allocated status, so it's not
quite on our ground yet, but it'll be
here between November 4th and November
21st.
>> Well, I'm interested in it. Uh, what's
the price?
>> Okay, price is going to be 85295.
No add-ons or markups.
>> And you can't do any better than that?
>> Absolutely not.
>> And what's your doc fee?
>> A doc fee is going to be 477.
>> Okay. And that car will be what date
what will be here?
>> It'll be here between November 4th and
November 21st.
>> Okay. And what would it take to hold the
car if we want to hold the car?
>> Thousand.
>> $1,000. $1,000. Hold the car and fully
refundable. That's completely fine. We
we sell out of our PMA all the time. No
issue on that whatsoever. Where you
located at, if you don't mind me asking.
We're We're in North Carolina.
>> Awesome. I've sold uh sold many North
Carolina cars this year. So
>> I love it. Awesome. Let me let me just
let me give a What time do you guys
close? I'm going to call my business
partner real quick. We'll probably put a
call you right back.
>> So we close at 8. I'm I leave here at 6,
but I can stay a little bit later if you
guys uh you guys want to make a
decision.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Give me five. Give me five
minutes.
>> Sure. Sure. Can I give you a return
number for me?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Last name is Makula. M
I K U L A.
>> Okay. And what I'm going to do, I'm
going to get you in our system here. I'm
going to send you what's called a text
optin. Whenever you get that, just reply
yes. That'll open up another line of
communication by text between me and
you. Okay.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> All right, Tommy. Well, I will do that
now. And uh just uh I'll I'll be
expecting a call from you here shortly.
Okay.
>> All right. Sounds good.
>> Thanks, Tommy.
>> No problem. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> Hey. No, you're good. Hey, I'm live.
Just so you know, uh red alert. I've
called every TX on the every color with
brown interior. No go, but I just found
one in Pennsylvania. We want to jump on
it quick cuz I'm live. Uh, but it's a
TX550 hybrid. It's MSRP. It's
Cloudburst, black interior. It's in PA,
so shipping won't be bad at all. It'll
be here in 30 days.
>> Bam.
>> What did you say? What' you say?
>> It just It's just MSRP, which is what's
we need to jump on this car ASAP. The
guy's going to be there for another He's
staying late for us for another five
minutes. So, we need to call the client
uh and see what he says.
>> All right, I'll call him right now.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> Bye. Two seconds.
>> This is Tommy.
>> Tommy, it's Henry with Lexus. How's it
going?
>> Hey, you doing well? I'm just talking to
my business partner. If you need to go
leave, I I can text you the deposit.
What it is, we're going to take it. I'm
just We're just talking everything over.
We're we're we're going to be good to
go.
>> Okay, cool. So, one thing I did did
forget to mention to you. So, I mean,
again, we're not over sticker here
whatsoever. But any out ofate vehicle
that's extremely popular, we do put a
full clear bra on the front part of the
car. We'll sell it for 2500 though. So,
we're not we're making 500 bucks on it.
>> Yeah. So, it protects the car and
there's a 10-year warranty on that as
well that you can use at any Expel
dealer. There's over 10,000 of them in
the country.
>> We were so close.
>> I hear you, man. I hear you. But other
than that, nothing's over MSRP. You
know, we don't have any hidden fees,
nothing like that. But that's the one
thing that we do do. You know, if you
want to think about it for a day or so,
but I can send you some info on expel if
you uh if you opt in to text.
>> I'm just not a fan of it.
>> Okay, I got you, man. Well, I apologize.
Let me know if anything changes. Okay.
>> Yeah. And you can't do anything else
like a warranty or something?
>> Yeah. I mean, if you wanted to take a
warranty, I mean, I mean, I could see
what that looks like for you.
>> Yeah. I mean, I'm I'm I'm fine with like
buying a warrant. I just want to put
something on the car I don't want to
have, but you know, I'm willing to do
like a warrant. I'm willing to consider
something. I understand what you guys
are going for. So, like, if that would
work,
>> I mean, we our rationale behind that. I
mean, I hope this is acceptable. I mean,
you know, it's a high market car that
doesn't have much markup that we can
sell here and get repeat business from,
you know, with service and that kind of
thing. I mean, we'd love to earn your
business, but again, we'll never see you
in a service department. You know, I
know it'll be it'll be really I can tell
my friends and family about you if that
helps. I got a few friends and family.
>> Sure. Absolutely. I mean, how about, you
know, something like, you know, would
you be interested in tire and wheel or
extending the warranty itself?
>> I mean, maybe extending the warranty
itself would be the thing I'd consider.
Uh, we were just talking it over here,
but
>> sure,
>> if you send me the deposit form, we'll
talk about it right now. And if we will
pay the deposit or decide not to or go
from there, we're talking about it right
now, though. I mean,
>> sure. I mean, what what I can do for the
deposit? I mean, I can take a credit
card over the phone, you know, if you
want me to do it that way. That's really
our only way to do remote deposits.
>> Okay. Um, well, can I text you to say
we're good to go? I know we wouldn't
want the clear bar, but like a warranty
would be something that we might
consider.
>> Sure. Issue is I'm not here tomorrow and
that vehicle just hit our inventory. So,
uh, just want to make sure it's secured,
you know.
>> Yeah. I mean, if I if I text you
tonight, is there any way we can get it
done tonight? Well, I know you're off. I
just I don't want to bother you in your
days off, but I also don't want to lose
the car. Sure. We don't typically do it
over text just because it's pretty
>> What if we call you? I just don't want
like I don't know. Are you going to have
the capability of doing it while you're
not at work?
>> Not necessarily, unfortunately.
>> So, what would be the best way to put a
deposit if we decide to move forward
with this?
>> You know, I mean, you guys you guys have
a time frame, you know, is is it hours
or, you know, couple more minutes?
>> Probably in the next 20 minutes, we'll
have an answer. And I just need to know
on the warranty side versus the clear
bar bar.
>> Sure. Well, let me let me run upstairs.
I'll get a warranty cost for you, but it
also and I'll get it on paper, too. Is
there going to be a trade involved?
>> Not that I think of. No, I don't think
we're going to trade.
>> Okay. No trade. What is the address that
you would title the vehicle at?
>> I can give you I don't like to give my
address out. Just do I have to I'm fill
out the app here. Um I can give you my
zip code if that makes more sense, which
is
>> and I can give you my address here in a
minute, but let me just make sure we're
going to do the deal first before we do
that. As long as we do the deal, then
we'll give you our address.
>> Okay. All right. Warranty wise though,
you know, how many miles a year do you
think you'll put on the car?
>> Uh, probably 10 to 15 or 10 to 12,000
year year.
>> Okay. So, I'll I'll shoot for 12 cuz you
can get a pro-rated refund if you sell
the car or anything like that. So, 12K.
How long do you want to keep it for?
>> Probably 7 years.
>> 7 years. Perfect. All right, man. Well,
I will get a true warranty cost for you.
I'll get with finance and then uh by the
time you know I get done with that,
we'll hopefully we'll we'll have an
answer. Okay.
>> Okay. Sounds good. Uh let me know on
that and we'll hopefully I'll have an
answer here soon.
>> Awesome. Thank you.
>> No problem. Bye.
>> All right. Bye.
>> He is going to call you right now. Right
now. Said Tommy is your business
partner. Boom. Sorry. One second. Let me
get this done. Boom. Done. I'm going to
peace out. Talk to you guys all later.
Bye-bye.
[Music]