I get the the the Tommy Makula I'm super
cool discount. Does that count?
>> Who do you work for?
>> This might be the best deal I got. This
might be I might be crazy for saying let
me think about it for a minute, but 76K
puts us in the moment where we're like,
let's do it.
>> All kinds of stuff like that. I'm I know
you're private guy, but I mean this
thing gets I'm going to be all up in
your business here in a little while,
Tommy.
>> You know, just trying to get some
pricing on it. Hoping you can help me
out and greet you some awesome
phenomenal best friend pricing for
friends and Yeah. We'll go. I said Jim
for a minute. I was like, who's Jim?
Maybe I 835 before. Isn't the truck like
85? Wait, what? What? Especially once I
start to stand up. They're like, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Let me go get my
Hey, you wait. You wait right there. We
are going to do a 2500. Uh, they want
blue or dark gray. 2500 heavy duty. They
want a new one. They want an LTZ. They
want gray or blue. Now, they do want
some packages. And they want a diesel.
They want the technology package and the
flex tailgate. Okay. What else? They
want the Z71 convenience package. They
want the goose neck prep package.
>> Thank you for calling. This is Sean and
sales.
>> Hey Sean and sales. This is Tommy from
buying. How's it going?
>> I'm doing all right. Myself?
>> I'm doing well. Doing well. I just want
to see if you guys have a car available.
>> Yeah, definitely check for you. Which
one you got your eye on?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> I'm ready for it.
>> Okay. It's nine. C is in capital 26439.
>> Silverado 2500 LTZ Trail Boss
>> that I mean Silverado LTZ. Yeah, with a
Trail Boss package. Correct.
>> Uh actual delivery date 87. Looks like
it's still available.
>> Awesome. Bada boom. Bada bing. Well,
this is the car I want. We're looking
for it. Uh really just hoping you can
give me some like knock dead crazy good
pricing and I can buy it.
>> Gotcha. Okay. I generally I mean the
these trucks are about 10% over what you
see online just when you factor in taxes
and whatnot. Probably a little less for
this one since it does come equipped
with everything that we're going to add.
>> You said it was 10% over. I'm sorry.
>> Generally speaking, yeah, once you
factor in taxes and all that. Like I
said, a little less on this one though
cuz you know, most of the things we add
like running boards, things like that
already on the truck.
>> Oh, you guys added like what do you guys
add? So I know.
>> So we do running boards on trucks, bed
liners if it doesn't have it. This is
the LTZ, so it's probably got the
Chevrolet one, but I'll I'll verify. And
then we do paint protection, you know,
things that just make sure these are
holding their value while they're on our
lot. Make sure no one spills coffee on
them and whatnot. As well as interior
protection. All that's backed by a
warranty.
>> And how much is all that?
>> Say anywhere from two to four kind of
depending on what you get. Now, I mean,
those packages while you I'm not trying
to sell you lowjack, anything like that.
It's not something you find value in.
Don't really expect you to pay for them.
So, that's something we can always look
into.
>> Okay. So, $2 to $4,000 in extra stuff.
And then what is the discount on the
car?
>> General Motors has customer cash for
500. We have a much larger dealer
discount of 43. So 4,35.
>> So it's 4305 and then you guys have a $2
to $4,000 add-on package. Can I just say
no to that add-on package?
>> Like I said, if it's not something you
see value in, uh, I'm sure it's
something we can get taken care of. I
can't really give you a definite, you
know, yes or no here. That's something
that has to be kind of done in person.
>> Okay. Uh, do I have to come in person? I
already know this is the truck I want.
Like I already driven one.
>> For a new vehicle, we have to have you
here at least once to verify identity.
>> Can can Sure. I mean, once we agree to
numbers and everything is good and I'm
more than want to come in and sign the
paperwork.
>> Yeah.
>> I don't want to waste my time coming in
there doing the back and forth and then
>> Yeah, I get you. Are you in the like
area? Are you somewhere?
>> So, so I live I we live in Pennsylvania
now, but we go down North Carolina all
the time. So, we have a a second home in
Charlotte, North Carolina. So, we we
drive through all the time.
>> All right. What's a good number to
contact you at?
>> Yeah,
>> my memory serves. His name was Tommy.
>> Tommy, you got it. Good memory.
>> What about email address when email?
Man, that's devil's work.
>> We'll use a text then.
>> Text is better.
>> Okay. All right. Well, let me uh let me
get someone on this and see what we can
get you kind of everything. Do you plan
on registering the vehicle, North
Carolina or Pennsylvania?
>> Uh, probably Pennsylvania.
>> You know what the zip code is for that?
>> The zip code I'd be registering the car
in would be
>> Gotcha. Okay. Uh, let me get these
details over. Let me get my someone on
my desk to work on this and then uh
yeah, I'll send you a text here in just
a second. We'll kind of go from there.
>> All right, sounds good.
>> Let me help you.
>> Hey, can I speak to somebody in new car
sales?
>> Sure. One moment.
>> Is this some Bo Burnham?
>> So, can help you?
>> Is your hold music Bo Burnham?
>> I don't know who Bo Burham is to be
honest either.
>> Oh my goodness. Okay. Uh, that's a whole
different conversation. Anyway, I just
they just dropped my jaw. Anyway, I just
need to see you guys have a car
available.
>> Which one are you looking at, buddy?
>> Okay. I got a stock number whenever
you're ready.
>> Uh, new or used?
>> Uh, and brand new.
>> What you got?
>> Uh, 2278.
>> Oh, where'd you see that at?
>> On the website.
>> So, that vehicle did sell. However,
>> it's always been
>> I think I have I think I have one
comparable. You're just looking for a
3/4 ton LTZ.
>> Uh, I mean, there's a lot. I mean,
there's a few packages we're looking
for, like the tech package, safety
package, trail boss, Z71.
>> You know, just like all the packages
that that one one man could desire on a
truck.
>> I think I have two or three other ones.
Give me one second. Oh, really? All
right. This one.
>> Yeah, they got to be a diesel. Yeah.
Could have technology package, safety
package, trail boss, Z71, convenience
package, and if possible, the gooseeneck
prep package is, you know, chef's kiss.
Yeah, that'd be mint there. Let me look
here. Pull this up.
>> There's one I was giving up. It would be
the goose
>> because I don't need to go on a goose
chase.
>> Dang. Doesn't have the tech package, but
we can always locate one. Luckily for
you, one of my many jobs here is uh
dealer trading as well. So, if I don't
have it, I can go find it. Not a big
deal here. But let me look cuz I do have
like six stores to pull stock from. So,
>> yeah. Makes life a little easier, you
know.
>> Mhm. And you know what? Goose neck
convenience package safety package. I'm
just missing the tech package. It really
is what it looks like. I have another
one in that same gray with the
gooseeneck convenience package two and
one power sunroof. What about the tech
package you like? What What was in that
that you wanted?
>> You know, honestly, this is for our
business and I was told to find one of
our tech package. So, I'll be
transparent. Great question. Glad you
asked. I was told get the I was told the
needs and the must. Okay. I say because
the tech pack is it has the it only it's
really only two things. Um it's the rear
camera mirror. So the backup mirror is
like
>> He's a horrible driver though.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And then heads up display
which is just projecting crap on the
windshield to distract you while you're
driving. But to each their own. Um
>> I mean I do like to we do like
>> find Yeah, that's fine. Let me look here
because I might have something coming
in. I don't have one exactly to that
spec in stock. Now, are we pref do we
prefer that sterling gray exterior?
>> You know what? Sterling gray is like the
preferred, but I would go slate gray. I
would go lake the lake the lake shore
blue. And if it was a steep enough deal,
I would consider white or black, but it
would have to be the steepest of deals.
>> Sorry, I'm just plugging into my locator
here. What uh what company you guys work
for?
>> Oh, we work for a construction company
out in Pennsylvania.
>> Oh, gotcha. Gotcha.
>> Yeah. So, I'm just buying a few trucks
for us.
>> Are you local to us or are you over in
PA, too?
>> No, I'm in PA. Yeah. Ser.
>> Gotcha. Gotcha.
>> Inventory isn't as great as it is over
there. So,
>> we deal a lot with people from PA. To be
honest with you, it's surprising,
>> but we also are right next to the
border.
>> Yeah. I say you're hoping a skip, you
know.
>> Yeah. It ain't nothing crazy. Yeah,
there's a couple out there. I think I
could snag I got a couple cuz what I do
is is um I've been doing this long
enough. I got a bunch of guys that work
at other dealerships and we just swap
inventory with each other to help each
other out. So, all I do is drop one of
these guys in line and say, "Hey, I got
this truck sold. What do you want back?"
Blah blah blah. And they'll take back a
truck or a Tahoe or whatever the heck
they think they could sell instead. cuz
yeah, there's a couple out there that
have been on a lot for, you know, 70
plus days. So, I usually start with
those guys just because, hey, you're not
moving the stock. Let me have a crack at
it here. Try and get that thing moving
for you. So, that'
>> be great. If you want to see one down
and then
>> Oh, yeah. It usually takes me a day or
two. I can get it cuz Yeah, I'm staring
at one right now. They've had for 76
days. Uh, turbo diesel LTZ convenience
tech package. Goo goo goo goo goo goo
goo goo goo goo goo goo goo goo goo goo
goo goo goo goo goos neck fifth wheel
prep convenience package two safety
package. Safety package. Yeah. So, say
that hits all the marks. So, the big
things are just tech package, safety
package, convenience, 2, gooseeneck,
fifth wheels, a plus,
>> correct?
>> Okay, cool. Yeah, I say I could probably
locate one for you. That ain't a big
deal. I think we can
>> Yeah, if you want to take down my
number, you can locate one and we can
talk the details and see if we can make
it make sense.
>> And I'm sorry. What was your name,
buddy?
>> My name's Tommy.
>> Mula.
>> Makula. That's crazy. You know my last
name. We go to high school together.
>> No, no, no. I watch you on TikTok.
Delivered.
>> I'm still trying to figure out. I'm not
I'm not lying. I'm I'm so distracted by
your old music or I'm still trying to
figure out if your old music is Bo
Burnham. Dude, I was saying I heard your
voice. Like I always wondered if there
was ever going to be a day one time
where I just hear talk to you. I don't
know. I see you all the time. It's
crazy.
>> I I love it, man. Well, let's put this
deal together. I have a client. I mean,
this is all real.
>> Yeah, for sure.
>> Bada boom, bada bing.
>> All right, Tommy Coola. What was a good
number for you?
>> And then I mean, you know the game here.
Are they going to be paying cash or we
like how are we working that is a
finance deal? Trying to locate one for
you at all. Like I said, I do a lot of
our dealer trades here and I see a
handful of them around and yeah, I mean,
I'm happy to try and locate one. Not a
big deal. All right, cool. Yeah. Um, let
me reach out to a couple guys before I
let you go. I'm not going to keep you
any longer. Um, was there any other info
or questions you want me digging into or
that you had for me here?
>> Uh, no. Nothing else I need here. I have
a whole if this works, then we have a
whole bunch of other deals we can make
work.
>> All right, cool. Yeah, I'll get to
cracking on this. Um, let me give me
like an hour. I'm going to start texting
some of my buddies here and see what
they got. And um yeah, I'll get cracking
on this.
>> Awesome. Perfect. Thank you, man. I
appreciate you.
>> Yeah, no problem. Have a good day.
>> Right. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> Sales. How may I help you?
>> Hey, I just wanted to see if you guys
have a car available.
>> You got a stock number?
>> I do.
>> New or used?
>> It's brand new.
>> Go ahead and give me a stock number,
please.
>> Stock number 25706.
>> 2025 Chevrolet Silverado.
>> 25 Chevy Silverado. Silverado 2500. So,
sorry.
>> 2500 LT.
>> The heavy duty. The heavy duty. Correct.
>> Yeah, it's heavy duty. Yeah, I'll tell
you what. Let me get your name and
number. Let me go touch it and then I'll
call you right back.
>> That's totally fine. Go touch it. Uh,
yeah. My name is Tommy. Last name
Makula. M I K U L A. And my phone
number?
>> My name is Jim.
>> Jim. Okay, I got it.
>> All right. Thanks. Bye.
>> No problem. Bye.
>> Thank you for calling. How may I direct
your call?
>> Hey, can I speak to new car sales?
>> Sure. I can help you out. Was there a
vehicle you found online that you're
looking at?
>> You are reading my mind. Yes, I have a
stock number even. No problem.
>> And what was that stock number?
>> Stock number is C as in crew. S is in
Santa 192704.
>> All right. That looks like it is a 2500
LTZ in the Lakeshore blue.
>> You got it.
>> All right. Let me just get some
information from you here real quick if
you don't mind.
>> Sure.
>> Is this the best number you're calling
me on? The
>> That is the best number.
>> And your name, sir?
>> My name is Tommy. Tommy and a last name.
>> Makula. M I K U L A.
>> Unfortunately, it doesn't let me tell
you. I mean, we had a heck of a Labor
Day sale. Moved a lot of cars yesterday.
So, in order for me to find out if this
is actually still on the lot, not sold
because our website hasn't caught up in
real time yet, I have to put this
information in. So, I do apologize.
>> No, you're good. I appreciate you giving
me all the information. Heck yeah. I'm
having a good Labor Day, you know.
>> Yeah. Oh, yeah. It was great. um just
you know unfortunately without putting
everything in and then putting the stock
number in our system. It won't tell me.
So the way to do that is to create a new
profile and it's a whole thing. I
apologize.
>> You're good. Take your time. I'm good. I
got nowhere to be.
>> And are we looking at trading anything
in?
>> Uh you know what? Not trading anything
in today. I'm just uh just buying.
>> All right. Perfect. This one is
available and still on the lot.
>> Yes. I love it. Okay. Cool. Lucky lucky
duck. Okay. Well, I'm super interested
in buying it. I've been calling around
trying to get the best deal and I know
you guys have had this one for, you
know, a little bit. First thing I want
to know, I saw a little disclaimer. It
said, "Is this a courtesy vehicle?"
>> Let me double check.
>> It just there was a disclaimer saying,
"Oh, courtesy transportation have more
mileage than normal units." I just don't
It doesn't say it's that, but just
asking.
>> Yeah, let me double check on that for
you. I don't see that this one. I mean,
this one it looks like it has 10 miles
on it from what I'm seeing, unless it
was used somewhere else. So, I'll
definitely get Yeah, I mean, let me
double check. I mean, it could have been
test driven, so it may have a few more
miles on it since then, but I don't
believe it was a courtesy transport
vehicle. I don't believe so.
>> Well, this is the one I'm interested in.
So, really just I'm ready to buy it
today. Um, you know, just trying to get
some pricing on it. Hoping you can help
me out and greet you some awesome,
phenomenal best friend pricing. So,
friends, and yeah, we'll go.
>> You got it. Well, let me ask you this.
if we can get you that awesome best
friends pricing. Uh, what time do you
think you could come in and pick it up?
>> Well, I I ideally do everything
remotely. I'm out of state, but like I
said, I heard really good things about
your dealership. Um, and that's why, you
know, that's why I called. I just heard
really good things. So,
>> okay, you got it. Let me uh let me get
this in the hands of my sales managers.
We'll put some numbers together for you.
I'll give you a call back just to
verify. I have
>> That's my phone number.
>> Perfect. Uh, give me 10 15 minutes and
I'll be right back with you.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> Thanks, Tommy. Take care.
>> No problem. You too, friend. Hi,
>> Jim.
>> Jim Tommy Mcula.
>> Yeah, I have it. It's here.
>> Bada boom, bada bing. I love it, man.
Right down to business. Okay, cool. So,
I already know I want this truck. This
is the one I'm looking for. Really
hoping you can just give me some pricing
so I can, you know, buy this thing. Call
it a day, you know.
>> Okay. Where where you located at first?
>> I'm in I'm in Se, PA. Just looking for
this particular truck, though.
>> Where at? I'm sorry.
>> See, Pennsylvania.
>> Oh, I'm from Youngsttown, Ohio
originally. Oh, okay. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're like north, like, you know, middle
of the state, north.
>> Closer to New York than Pittsburgh, but
go Steelers.
>> I I have a hunting camp up in the
Alaganis.
>> Oh, wow. Hey, what are the chances?
>> South of James Town. Yeah,
>> I expect that get that local discount
then, right?
>> I don't know about a local, but do you
get any type of General Motors
discounting?
>> I don't I don't get any General Motor
discount. No, I get the the the Tommy
Makula, I'm super cool discount. Does
that count?
>> Who do you work for? I I own my own
company.
>> What's the name of your company?
>> It's a construction company, so Oh,
>> okay. I was just trying to see if I
>> There's no discount that would come with
if that's what you're worried about. I
already I already went down that avenue.
I already looked
>> at pricing.
>> The pricing. Yeah.
>> I'm just checking a couple things out
here on this end just to make sure.
>> No, you're good. Check all the things.
>> $500. I know there's a $500 rebate.
That's not much when you're buying a big
car like this.
>> Yeah. You know, that doesn't wake me up
in the morning, you know.
>> It doesn't wake you up.
>> Doesn't wake me up. As long as I wake
up, I'm a happy man. All right, Tommy, I
can sell this truck to you for I'll get
you a supplier discount. Uh, which is it
knocks it from 84055 down to 78615
minus 500 bucks. So now we're at 781
1115 and 20 cents plus tax and doc.
>> It's really trying to be closer to 76 if
I'm honest.
>> I already gave you supplier discount and
I can't get you the employee discount.
So
>> I mean I'm not looking if you're not
looking.
>> I've looked. I've come down about six
grand because I'm getting a supplier
discount through one of my General
Motors friends.
>> Oh, okay. Yeah, I get No, I I get that.
I I appreciate the $6,000 discount.
>> But yeah, but it's it's coming down to
78615 minus another 500 is 78115 and 20
cents plus tax.
>> Okay. Yeah. And do you guys have any
add-ons or tax?
>> Are you putting in your name or the
company name?
>> Uh we're debating on that. So there's
multiple there's a few people that could
uh that are involved in the purchase
there for the business. So we might put
in the business name might put in one of
the names. I'm sorry.
>> It's an advantage to put it in whoever
owns it in their name because I'm
getting you the supplier discount.
>> Got it.
>> In other words, if you put it in a
business discount, I can't get you that
discount.
>> Got it. Okay. So I'll talk to I'll talk
to the other owners and see what they
say. My business partner. Uh that's
fine. Um Okay. And you you can't do any
better than that? I was really hoping,
like I said, we're really trying to be
right around that 76k mark. That That's
the best I can do.
>> Okay. Do you guys have any add-ons,
fees, or anything crazy?
>> No, it's just a dock fee, but they go uh
it's a since I'm getting you the
discount, it's a $75 dock fee.
>> Oh, 75. That's not bad at all.
>> And then um they go by your tax in your
state or any county or city tax and the
finance people.
>> Yeah, we'll figure that out. My tax is
what my tax is, right? Like you can't
change that.
>> No, you got some big friends upstairs,
Jim, but I don't got that big friends.
>> No, no, no. I used to work for the
government, but I don't work for them
anymore. So, in order to own this truck,
if you want to purchase it, I would
suggest me giving my secretary your
number and calling you and you putting a
$500 deposit down. That would hold the
truck for you.
>> I mean, I'd love that, but I'd love that
at 76K, we would do that in a heartbeat,
>> partner. I can't go any lower.
>> I know.
>> No, I appreciate it. Like, I appreciate
that, but that's the number we're trying
to be at. So, this might be the best
deal I got. This might be I might be
crazy for saying let me think about it
for a minute. But 76K puts us in the
moment where we're like let's do it. 78K
is like let me think about it.
>> Okay. You got my number if you if you
want to move forward. I'm not in uh I'm
not pushing you. You do you make your
own decision. So
>> Oh yeah. No, I appreciate it. I
appreciate the pressure. You've been
great, Jim. Um so
>> but I've got the truck here. So
>> yeah. Yeah. AB absolutely. I appreciate
that. And if you have any other
questions, uh you can call me or if you
guys change your mind, uh let me know.
But let me think about this for a little
bit. Uh, that'd be great.
>> All right. Thank you.
>> All right. Sounds good.
>> Bye.
>> I'd like to get to that.
>> Thank you for going, sir.
>> Hey, I just want to see if you guys have
a car available.
>> Sure. Uh, which vehicle are you looking
for today?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Okay, go ahead with that stock number.
>> Uh, stock number T is in Tango 251995.
like a Chevy Silverado 2500
LZ
and Sterling metallic. All things that I
see here in front of me indicate that
this vehicle is available for sale and
here I'm going to check one more system.
>> That'd be great.
>> Double check. Yeah, ma'am. Thank you so
much.
>> No problem.
>> Yeah, it looks like everything's showing
it's here. Yes, sir.
>> Bada boom, bada bing. I'm excited.
Awesome. Love it. Really? Yeah. Hey,
well, this is the truck I want. This is
the color I want. been looking around
trying to find a good deal on one and I
heard there's no one better to call but
>> that's correct. We we are the we're the
we're the leader, you know, we're we're
selling more which means we don't have
to we're trying to sell more. That's
we're a volume guy. We're not a we're
not trying
>> Ricky Bobby always told me if you're not
first, you're last, you know.
>> That's right. All right. Hey, what's
your name, by the way?
>> My name is Tommy.
>> I'm Paul.
>> Paul, nice to meet you, Paul. All right,
Tommy, are you going to be able to come
in today or come in tomorrow or when you
come in?
>> You know what? Being a volume guy like
yourself, I, you know, I prefer to do
this all uh remotely. I work a busy
schedule. Ideally would like to uh do
this all remotely.
>> Okay. Tell me, what's your last name?
>> Mula. M I K U L A.
>> Deal. I love doing remote deals. I'm
really good. We'll get this thing locked
up, locked down, and get you in and in
and out as quick as we can.
>> I like it.
>> You live You live nearby or where would
we be? Yeah. Um, I'm actually out of
state, but like I said, I heard good
things. Uh, I'm I'm in uh Pennsylvania.
>> What's the zip code?
>> And what's your what's your address?
>> I don't like to give that out. Sorry.
I'm just a private guy. I'll give it out
once we agree to numbers and all the fun
stuff, but
>> All right, Tommy. I get you, man. You're
afraid I'm coming to get you. What's
your email, Tommy?
>> Can you text me? Just easier via text.
I'm a I'm a text. I'm a texter.
>> Okay. Would you rather do all this over
text then?
>> Yeah, it' be easier for me if you don't
mind. I just don't even I don't even
know my email. My my assistant checks
that.
>> I need a email before we get off. Do
>> you need an email? Why do you need an
email?
>> Got email.
>> We can probably find one, but I'm never
going to like email. I mean,
>> I'm trying to communicate here. I'm
trying to get I'm trying to get all my
stuff in here so we can get this. You
want this deal done smooth? And I'm just
trying to do it smooth. So,
>> yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, I did I mean
that's something you absolutely I just
never check it. So, you're just grabbing
something to grab something. I don't use
email.
>> Well, have services with this vehicle.
All kinds of stuff like that. Um, I I
know you're a private guy, but I mean,
this thing gets I'm going to be all up
in your business here in a little while,
Tommy.
>> No, I I get you're going to be in my
business, but we can't we can't get a
quote without an email.
>> Sure, no problem.
>> Yeah, I mean, give me the I promise you
I'll give you everything you need the
second we have all that.
>> Okay. All right, Tommy. I got your your
zip code, your phone number, the vehicle
you want. Are you are you planning on
trading anything, Tommy?
>> Uh, no. No trade. Just just adding
adding to our fleet.
>> Okay. Adding in. All right. Do you get
text messages on this? I guess you do.
That's what you
>> Yeah, you can text me all day. Okay. All
right. There's my text.
>> So, you just want to out the door quote.
>> That'd be great. I just opted in. See,
look. I'm super fast when it comes to
text.
>> Sure. Sure. And now, do you have uh are
any military prior military?
>> No prior military. No. No supplier or
nothing like that.
>> Supplier discount? No. You have anybody
that works for the company directly or
indirectly?
>> Nope.
>> Okay. So, just straight numbers then.
I'll uh
>> Easy peasy.
>> What's that? I said easy peasy,
>> right? And then Yeah, like I said, we
can do all this remotely. I can send you
I can email you or hard mail you the the
all the paperwork. Are you planning on
having it shipped back to you or are you
going to come get it?
>> Yeah, I mean I'm open to either one or
we're fine making a road trip. We're
fine shipping it. Ideally shipping it.
We can we can set all that up. We ship
cars across country all the time, so no
big deal. But we can come in if needed.
>> What I usually do is if if you're going
to have it shipped, you know, you you
you book that through Ready Logistics or
anybody that you like to use. Um, but
then it's only released once the funding
is done for whatever loan or however.
>> Of course. Yeah. Make sure you guys get
paid.
>> All right. And this isn't in a business
name or anything. Just straight.
>> It's it's for business, but it's going
to go in a personal name. So,
>> Okay. Yeah.
>> Sounds good, Tommy. All right. Let me
get the let me get the numbers together
and I'll I'll uh text you when I got
them, let you know.
>> Okay. Sounds good. I appreciate it.
>> All right. Bye.
>> That being said, email isn't the most
efficient way to communicate. It doesn't
work for me well. And honestly, that's
the only thing that matters. Texting is
very possible to send numbers. There's
no negative side of texting, but most
sales people prefer texting. There's no
reason to force me to give additional
information that I don't want to give or
don't need to give. Sure, when I buy the
car, you're going to enroll me in a
whole bunch of things. You're going to
need my email. I get that. But to get a
quote, name, number, email. I mean,
email is not needed. You need phone
number or email. You need one or the
other. But if somebody doesn't want to
give your information, that's fine.
Like, people need to be weirded out by
that. It's It's just a weird thing to
like dig down on.
>> Thank you for calling Lander. This is
Caitlyn. How can I help you?
>> Hey, I'm so sorry. I can barely hear
you, but I I just want to see if you
guys have a car available.
>> I'm sorry. Okay, I know you're good. Is
it new or pre-owned?
>> It is brand new. I have a stock number
if that helps.
>> Yep. Go ahead.
>> Stock number is 5C is in Caterpillar
2716.
Okay. Give me one second for it to load.
Okay. The Silverado LTZ. Gotcha. It
looks to be still available. Are you
looking for info on it or you just
confirming that to come and see it?
>> Yeah. Yeah. So, so I've already driven
one. Already know I love it. Trying to
buy a vehicle today hopefully just
shopping around getting a good deal and
saw this one was available matches all
the needs and I'm hoping we can maybe
get some a little bit better pricing and
and buy it today.
>> Okay, gotcha. Are you going to be
trading?
>> No trade, just buy.
>> Okay, gotcha. Okay. Um, this
>> that is the best sale I have.
>> Okay, understood. And what's your first
and last name?
>> My first name is Tommy, last name
Makula. M I K EU L A.
>> All right. Well, what I can do, I'm
going to have someone reach out to you
in just a little bit. Get some numbers
going. Um, what's your zip code?
>> Zip code is uh Are you ready for it?
It's one
>> Okay, gotcha. You don't look local to
us. Are you local?
>> I I don't live local, but I've heard
really good things about you. So, you
know what? I'm always willing to make a
fun road trip.
>> I gotcha. Okay. Well, let me see what we
can get going then. Um, hopefully we're
able to earn your business.
>> I love it. Thank you so much.
>> Of course. Thank you.
>> No problem. Bye. Bye. Bye.
It's
>> a great day. This is Nick. Are you
calling for the plan?
the location.
>> Okay. How can I help you out today?
>> Hello. Uh, I was just seeing if you guys
have a car available. Oh,
>> I can definitely check and make sure.
Here, give me one second. Do you by any
chance have like a stock number for the
vehicle I can use to look it up?
>> I do. I can give that to you whenever
you're ready.
>> All right. And then wait, is it new or
pre-owned?
>> It is brand new.
>> Okay, I am ready whenever you've got it,
sir.
>> Let me go grab my score. One second.
>> You're all good.
>> Okay. Sorry. I'm learning this here.
Okay. Stock number is going to be S as
in Sierra, F as in Foxtrot,
264302.
LTZ.
>> That's it. Bada boom, bada bing.
>> All right, perfect. Give me just a
couple of seconds. Let me check a couple
of places just to make sure it's still
here and available. And then while I'm
checking, did you see this one on our
website or was it on like a third party
one like Autotrader, Cars, or one of
those.com?
>> Okay, awesome. From what I am seeing, it
does still look to be available. Let me
just check one more spot really fast.
>> I appreciate you doing the triple check.
>> Yeah, of course, man. No worries at all.
I don't want to bring you in on
something that's not actually 100% here.
Yeah, from what I'm seeing right now on
my side, it looks like it's here and
good to go. Uh, did you think you would
have availability to come by and check
it out today? I'm happy to, you know,
have someone pull it aside and make sure
it's all good to go for you.
>> Well, I appreciate that. You know, I've
already I've already looked at it,
already driven it, already fell in love
with it. I'm hoping that you can help me
as as good as you are with discount
double-checking the price and getting me
a really good deal on the Silverado.
That'd be great.
>> Yeah. Did you like already come by our
dealership and check it out with
>> it? It was a different dealership, but I
heard I I really wanted to relax and
enjoy the difference of your dealership.
>> Completely understand. Um Yeah. Did you
have a trade-in vehicle or were you just
purchasing a truck?
>> I'm just purchasing.
>> Okay. Um give me just a second. We want
to verify there's no like additional
rebates that GM has going on on the
2500s right now. Don't give me just one
second.
>> Oh, I thought you said Jim for a minute.
I was like, who's Jim?
>> No. Uh, I do have a gym in my store,
though. It would be dope if you could
just throw some discounts on our
>> 2500. Let's Let's call Jim up. Me and
you will call him up. We'll have a
conversation.
>> It does look like there's a $500
customer cash rebate that everyone
qualifies for, so you're in luck there.
Other than that though, it's not they
don't have any sort of like uh Conquest
rebates or loyalty or Costco going on. I
do want to ask though, are you by any
chance either retired or active
military, an educator, or a first
responder?
>> I am not.
>> Okay. All right. Let me go ahead and do
this. Uh, is this a mobile phone number
that we're talking on right now?
>> This is a phone number that is mobile.
>> No, you're all good, man. I I just said
I'm going to go ahead and send over
something called an opt-in text. We have
to follow communication law. So, I've
got to opt you into our text system in
order for me to send you my information.
Uh, but once you reply yes to it, I'll
send you over all the info that you
need. So, my name and then my direct
line. Um, and then let me get with my
director just to get the out the door
and everything for you. Uh, really fast
though, I forgot to ask. Were were you
going to be transferring a tag onto this
vehicle that you already had or would
you be needing a new one?
>> We'd be transferring a tag.
>> Okay. And then you are a Florida
resident, correct? Like it's going to be
registered in the state of Florida.
>> Nope. Actually, I'm out of state. I just
heard that difference.
>> Awesome, man. That that complicates it
just a little bit. Um, I need a little
bit more information from you just cuz
we've got to submit you to our All
States company to get your tax info.
What was your full name, sir?
>> Full name Tommy. Last name Makula. M I K
U L A.
>> Um and then what's your like mailing
address?
>> I can give you my zip.
>> And then would you be putting any money
down on the vehicle? Like just cuz we do
the all states to get you the out the
door. So I don't know if you want any
down payment shown on the worksheet or
anything.
>> Let's just say I mean I'll probably put
some cash down, but just for the
worksheet to keep it simple, let's just
put $0 down to make it simple on the
worksheet.
>> All right. I just went ahead and I sent
over that text. Uh, so whenever you get
it, just go ahead and reply yes to it
and then like I said, I'll send you over
all my information. Um, and then let me
go with my director to get your tax
information. Uh, and I'll get the out
the door for you and then as soon as I
get it, I'll send it your way.
>> All right, sounds good.
>> Oh, really fast. Um, are do you by any
chance have another phone number? Uh,
>> uh, that sounds familiar.
>> Okay, let me try this. Do you by any
chance have an email address t?
>> That's a really old email. Yeah.
>> Oh, I guess that you were previously in
our system. It looks like you may have
done business with us. Um, let me just
go ahead. That phone number is no longer
that email.
>> Uh, yeah. I mean, I don't use that phone
number nearly as much. I'm a business
guy, so I do business things, so I
change the number quite often.
>> Okay, no worries. This is the best. This
is the best one for you to be reached
at, though.
>> Yes, this the one I'm calling out. It's
better than the other one.
>> All right, perfect. I'll go ahead and
send you over my information to that
one. Um, and if you've got any questions
in the meantime, feel free to reach out.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> All right, man. Have a great rest of
your day.
>> All right, sounds good. Bye. Thank you.
>> This is Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. It's Nina here at Chevrolet.
How are you doing today?
>> Hey, I'm doing well. Nina, how about
yourself?
>> I'm doing just fine. So, I just got a
note from Kaitlyn that you're interested
in buying a truck today.
>> You know what? She got the perfect note.
Kaitlin Kaitlin nailed it. 10 out of 10.
>> Oh, yeah. Awesome. So, we have you on
this 2500 uh LTZ truck, the 5D 2715.
>> That's it.
>> Okay. Awesome. Let me get some
information from you real quick. Hold
on. All right. What is your address of
where you live at?
>> Oh, I don't I don't like to give that
out, but I can give you my zip code.
>> Okay, that'll work. What's your zip?
>> Yeah.
>> What county is that?
>> That's Bradford County.
>> What state is that?
>> That is Pennsylvania.
>> Pennsylvania. Okay. And then I have your
phone number at
>> Yep. That's the number.
>> Yep. That's the one the one you call me
at.
>> And you're not trading anything in,
correct?
>> Not trading in anything. Just Just
adding.
>> Okay. And do you have any like GMS
supplier discounts or anything like
that? Are you military?
>> No military, no supplier, no nothing.
>> Okay. Did you want cash to finance?
>> Uh c out the door cash fine, but I'll
probably finance.
>> Okay. Are you wanting to come in and
pick this thing up or you want us to
deliver it to you?
>> Yeah, I'm liking to I mean I can always
get a shipping quote myself. I'm open to
either or, but probably uh probably
looking to ship the car.
>> Okay, no problem. I will get you a quote
and then I will call you back shortly.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> Okay. All righty. Thanks, sir.
>> No problem. Bye.
>> Fun fact about car sales. Um, the end of
the month for the manufacturer, which is
really what matters, right? Or does not
end ever almost on a weekend or a
holiday. So, because the last day of the
month actually was Sunday, that means
the end of the month for the
manufacturer would end on Monday. And
the reason why they don't end it on a
weekend or end it on a holiday is
because not every dealership is open.
So, it' kind of be unfair to have the
last day of the month where they have to
close all the business out when part of
the country isn't available of Nashville
gave you a $1,780
discount. Let's go look at the Let's go.
$89,000 out the door for this truck. I
was hoping for a bit bigger of a
discount. Okay, sounds good. Wait,
Nina's calling. One second. This is
Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. It's Nina. Nina.
>> Hey, so I got you a quote.
You like the picture? That truck is very
pretty. I like that green.
>> It's a pretty truck for a pretty guy.
>> There you go. Well, I'm a pretty
salesman, so we're going to make a
pretty good deal right here. Okay,
>> I like it. Let's rock and roll. What do
we got? Let's hear the numbers.
>> Okay, so that one was848
before the discounts. There's like
$6,500 uh dollars in discounts. So, it's
plus your taxes and fees. You'd be out
the door at 82, 3566.
>> Okay. So, it's 84,000 MSRP. You guys are
giving $5,000 off plus a $500 rebate.
>> No, it's uh 6,500.
>> Oh, 6,500. So, you're doing $6,500 plus
a $500 rebate?
>> No, it's just it's the $6,000 discount
and then $500 rebate. So, 6,500 total.
>> Okay. I already have 6,300 off plus
rebate.
>> How do you have 6,300 off
>> from another dealership?
>> Cuz it's Oh, what's their out the door
number? can get it for you. But it was 6
$6,300 plus tax title license and their
doc fee was
>> 6300.
>> So they gave you 6,300 and
>> 6,300 plus the $500 rebate. So it was
6,700 total.
>> It was in Indiana. I can get you the the
dealer.
>> Okay.
>> He's a nice guy. His name was Jim.
>> And then the discount or the fee was 75
bucks.
>> 75 bucks.
>> What number would it take to earn your
business today?
>> I was trying to be a 7K discount is what
I what I told him. And he was like, I'm
stopping here. And I said, I'll keep
going, Jim. And that's what I told him.
I said, that's fine. If you can get 7K,
you can get 7K. And that's what I said.
And I said, "I'll call Nina."
>> Okay. So, let me go see if I can get you
7K. I'll call you right back.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> All righty. Bye.
>> I know a lot of people say competition
doesn't drive the price down. I want you
to go from that discount to Oh, I have
another deal. Oh, shoot. Let me beat
that. Boom. Competition drives the price
down. If she gives me 7K down, bada
boom, bada bing, easy peasy. It's the
last day of the month for the
manufacturer. Nah's great. Good energy,
good involvement. She laugh with the
jokes, which sometimes are crazy. My
jokes aren't always the funniest. I
know. I know. Um, get your phone call
back.
This is Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. It's Kevin.
>> Hey, man. How's it going?
>> Not too bad. How are you?
>> Hey, I'm doing well, Kevin. I'm hoping
you got great news for me.
>> Uh, yeah. That one there is 83559
before taxes. And I didn't quite
calculate the TA taxes, so I don't know
exactly what that is, but they can do
that for you.
>> Please hold on. Maybe I'm going crazy.
835 before T. Isn't the truck like 85?
Wait, what? What? What? Give me one
second. I'm pulling the truck back up.
>> So, when the trucks land here, oh, I'm
sorry. Plus minus 500 more. So, 80.
Yeah. 83059.
When the trucks land here, we put tint,
we put door guards, we put nitrogen in
the tires, and we put floor liners in
the trucks.
>> Oh, I thought it was done today. What
are we What are we doing?
>> Well, it's a unique truck. That's a deal
for the truck.
>> What price you trying to hit? Well, I
already have $6,500 off plus rebate
>> from Oh, I would definitely probably
take that.
>> Well, I mean, you guys said your manager
was trying to GM was trying to do all
these deals and I got excited.
>> Oh, we are. But in this market here,
that truck sells really quick and it's a
good piece. Um, but yeah, if you're at
6,500 off and then a $500 rebate, that's
probably
you've had the truck for 5 months.
>> Stop looking around. That's a Okay,
>> you guys said it sells quick. It doesn't
sell.
>> All right. What number makes it where
you buy the truck?
>> Yeah. What what I was trying to be at is
is what I told the other dealership was
7K plus rebates is where I was trying to
be at with no none of those dealer
add-ons or anything.
>> What rebates do you get? Well, we
already put it on the truck. So, that's
what I'm trying to get. Where where are
you trying to be for the bottom number
of the truck before rebates?
>> Okay, let's let's go bottom dollar on
the truck. So, right now I have out the
door with my state taxes at 818. I would
like to be at 81 flat. Out the door.
>> Okay. And are you purchasing it for
yourself or are you purchasing it on
behalf of somebody else?
>> I don't know what that I mean where
we're where my business partner is
probably going to put it in his name,
but it's for the business.
>> Oh, there's companies that call purchase
for other people. And I'm just making
sure this is a like a customer purchase,
not a business purchase.
>> Yeah. No. No.
>> Like another like another dealership
purchase is what I'm getting at.
>> Nope. No dealership. Nothing like that.
Uh it is it is for my business partner.
We're about
the cut $500 from General Motors. Is
there another rebate that you guys
qualify for? Be a first responder.
>> Military?
>> Nope. Just that.
>> All right. So, you're trying to be at
what is 818 out the door?
>> I I have 818 out the door. That's what
the other one that I was just about to
take and I was waiting on you to call me
back cuz your you said your GM was ready
to make some deals last day of the
month. So then I was waiting. I was
giving you guys the respect. But
>> no, no. So, you're trying to be at 81
out the door bottom line including
taxes.
>> Correct. And just so you know, their
sales price is 77 805 to give you an
idea of where they're at with the
discount.
>> Okay. All right. Let me go talk to them
real quick and I'll budge you right
back.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> All right. Thank you, sir.
>> Bye.
>> Chevrolet, this is Nick.
>> Hey, Nick. This is Tommy from my house.
>> Hey, Tommy. How are you doing, sir?
>> Hey, man. I'm doing well. I saw I saw
the your text and you know what? Like I
called you back cuz I was just figuring
out make sure there wasn't like a typo
in it or something. Uh you guys are only
doing $2,500 for that truck.
>> Yeah. I mean that's $2,500 off the MSRP.
I mean were you seeing higher discounts
with like lower out the doors on same
MSRP trucks elsewhere or
>> Yeah, dude. Man, I've I just just got a
dealer that was doing $6,300 off.
>> I mean, was it it was on like a 2500 25
model year LTZ like a 83575 MSRP.
>> It's a 2026 model. That's even crazier.
But no, it's a 2025 model.
>> I mean, if you have a worksheet or
something that you could text over my
way for me to have him take a look at
it, I can see if they'd be interested in
increasing the discount. Um, but
generally speaking, we're relatively
aggressive for our market on our
Silverado discounts. But, I mean, if you
have a worksheet you want me to pass
along to them to see what what we can
do, I'm happy to do that.
>> Yeah. I mean, I'm more than willing to
pass that on. You know, I don't want to
get in a world where uh we're wasting
your guys' time, right? That's not the
idea. I mean, if you guys don't think
you'll It's almost triple the discount,
right? Like discount triple check, you
Yeah, exactly. So, I mean, if anything,
you can send over a worksheet to just to
the same place that you texted me and I
can have them take a look at it and just
see if there's anything that we can, you
know, do as far as additional discount
or something like that. Um, is that
something you'd be interested in doing?
>> Yeah, I mean, yeah, once I get these
numbers, I can definitely send them over
to you. But, um, like I said, I don't
want to waste your guys' time either.
So, if you guys can't do it, no big
deal.
>> Awesome. Yeah, whenever you get it, just
text them my way. I'll have them take a
look and I'll let you know the
consensus.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> I mean, have a great rest of your day. I
look forward to hearing back from you
soon.
>> Okay, sounds good. Bye. Thank you.
Bye-bye.
>> There's Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. It's Kevin A.
>> Hey, what?
>> Yeah. I mean, we might have another
thousand or so to take off, but if
you're at 818, I would run I would grab
that and run with the wind to be honest
with you. That's a great deal on that
truck.
>> Cool. That's what we're going to do.
>> All right. Cool, man. Have a good
afternoon.
>> Hey, thank you. You, too.
>> Yep. Bye.
>> Hello, Nina.
>> Hey. So, I got you the extra 500 bucks.
So, it was 77805
plus your taxes and fee. You'd be at
and66.
>> Okay, awesome. Perfect. So, it's going
in my business partner's name. Can you
just send that down to me real quick?
I'll just give it to him and we'll get
this all wrapped up right now.
>> Okay. What is the his name?
>> Uh his name like you wanted to know or
the business name because his name is
going to be Corsen, but I can I can get
you all of his
>> Is it going in the business name?
>> Let me talk to him real quick because we
haven't decided if we're going to put in
the business name or not. It might just
go in his name, but
>> Okay. All righty. No problem. talk to
him and then call me back.
>> Yeah. Hey, can you just send me that to
him so I can go through the numbers with
him real quick?
>> Yeah. Yeah. When I sent it to you, I
highlighted the numbers. They put the
gap and warranty on there. It's totally
optional. It's kind of down below the
out the door number. So, that's 6 year
100,000 mi warranty and gap is like if
you total the vehicle, it covers the gap
from what it's worth to what you owe on
it. Those are optional. They put them on
every quote. Okay. Yeah, you don't have
to do that, but it will be four
different things highlighted and I'll
send you information on it all. Okay.
>> Okay. Hey, I appreciate you making it
easy, Nina.
>> Yep. No problem, Tommy. I'll talk to you
soon, dude.
>> No problem. Bye.
>> And this is why we say presence is not
power. This is why we say competition
drives the price down. Let's talk about
the lessons. First off, don't put all
your eggs in one basket, right? That's
not good. Two, competition drives the
price down. Presence isn't power. The GM
isn't desperately trying to get a deal
today. They're doing whatever they can
to get you in the door. Because when
you're in the door, statistically, they
have a higher percentage of closing. If
I don't like you on the phone, hitting
end call is really easy. It is difficult
for me to stand up and leave. Especially
once I start to stand up, they're like,
"Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Let me go
get my Hey, you wait. You wait right
there." Yes. This is one of the biggest
tricks that people do not understand. A
good car salesman is trying to get you
in the next step of the process. So,
most times when you sell a car, there's
like a 10step process on how to sell a
car. So, there's the meet and greet,
then there's a needs assessment, then
there's the trade appraisal, there's a
walkound, then the test drive, then the
value walk, then the presenting numbers,
gathering information, finance, and now
we're trying to get you to close a deal.
Now, you're a numbers, let's close
deals. If I can make this car
affordable, would you take it home
today? And if you give any semblance of
a yes to that answer, guess what's going
to happen? They're going to use that
against you. My goal with this company
is really simple. I want to reinvent the
way we buy cars. That is my mission
since day one. You can go find every
single time that I've ever made a video,
first video I ever made. My goal is to
reinvent the way we buy cars. I
understand me reinventing the way I buy
cars will probably put me out of
business. I'm good with that. Yes, we
are making money, but the fact of the
matter is if car buying becomes easier
because I've made it more transparent to
the point where dealerships can't
compete with me and the only way they
can do this is just making it easy to
buy cars, I go out of business.
[Music]