I'm just really trying to get a great
deal on the Kia 2026s. I know the new
model year, they're just doing crazy
deals, crazy discounts on them. But you
made that you made that really easy,
man. Just let me just see that
breakdown. I think we might we have two
trades, so I can send you that
information and we can lock this all up.
I don't use email. You know, I'm not not
into that. You can text me
>> if you're going to do a deposit.
>> I don't know. What do you guys charge
for a deposit? Oh,
>> as I said, I'm just trying to put
something together for the sales manager
to reach out to you.
>> Yeah, $4.
>> $4?
>> I mean, whatever you want me to put a
deposit, but if I get to choose, I'll
pay $4. You are not a veteran, were you?
>> I was not. Should I? Should I be? Hey,
maybe this for me.
>> No.
>> Okay, this client wants this deal ASAP.
Let's go. Okay, this person's in
Florida. Carnival SX Prestige Hybrid.
Person has a lot of colors they'll take.
They They do want a bench though. So, we
go 46 to 48. They're asking if we can do
84 months. So, can we do 84 months?
Yeah, that's really pushing it. I mean,
they could do that. I mean, there is an
abundance. We're gonna have to go gas.
We're gonna have to go as cheap as we
can to make this work.
>> It's a great day at this. This is Lisa
speaking. How may I help you?
>> Hello, Lisa. It's a great day at my
house. Uh, I just want to see if you
guys have a car available.
>> I could check for you. What What type of
vehicle is it?
>> I have a stock number if that helps with
the inquiry.
>> Yeah, that works.
>> Stock number 26. Kia K is in Kangaroo
82.
>> And what vehicle is that?
>> Uh, it is a Kia Carnival SX. That's the
Carnival SX. That one is nice. Let me
just make sure it is still here.
Actually, let me make sure that that one
came off the truck already. If that
one's not here yet, are we open to any
other colors or just that specific one?
>> I'm pretty open. Yeah, ivory, black,
white, you know, all the the generic
gray colors. All the I'm good. But this
is the one I like.
>> Yeah, I got you. Yeah, for sure. Let me
just double check for you. What's the
best number to reach you in case we get
disconnected?
>> Yeah, that is myself.
>> All right, perfect. And then let me just
get your name. What's your last name?
>> Last name Makula. M I K U L. Glad you
spelled that for me. I would have never
got that correct. And then what was your
first name?
>> First name Tommy.
>> Tommy.
>> Yeah, Tommy.
>> All right, I got you, Tommy. Let me just
put you on a brief fold. I'll go double
check that one for you. Okay.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> Meanwhile,
>> hey, thank you for holding for me,
Tommy.
>> Uh, yep.
>> So, I do still have it here and
available. Now, when are you available
to come check it out? Do you have some
time today or did this weekend work
better?
>> Well, I already driven it. I already
know I won it. Really? Just looking for
the for the best or best numbers on it?
>> Yeah, for sure. Let me get some
information from you. Do you have a
trade in?
>> I do have a tradein, but I might just
sell it to Carvana CarMax. I'm not too
worried about that. Really worried about
numbers on the car first.
>> Yeah, I got you. And then did you need a
new tag or a transfer tag?
>> We'll transfer the tag.
>> All right. Transfer tag. And then where
you coming from? What's your zip code?
>> The zip code? I I live in Orlando, so
like a hop and a skip.
>> All right. What's your zip code then?
>> And then are you doing a cash deal or
did you need financing?
>> We'd be financing, but we're more
worried about the outdoor
>> financing. Yeah. Yeah, I got you. And if
before I can go to my Kia manager and
get this pricing for you. These are all
the questions he's going to ask me. So,
if I don't ask him, he's going to be
like, "No, go back and ask him." Um, and
then, do we have any military history?
>> Nope. I'm not a military.
>> No military. Do we have any current Kia
in the house?
>> I do. We do have a Kia.
>> Oh, good. So, then you'll get Kia
loyalty. So, current Kia owner.
>> Nice.
>> And then how about any Costco discount?
Are you a Costco member?
>> We are a Costco.
>> All right, perfect. So, we also can get
a Costco discount. We're local in the
We're local enough. We're in Orlando
area.
>> Yeah, we're hoping to scale.
>> All right, Tommy. Yeah, for sure. Let me
get a good email that he can send that
pricing over, too.
>> Uh I don't use email. Can you just text
it?
>> Yeah, he can just text it. All right,
let me get with my manager for Kia and
I'm going to have him email or I'll have
him text you over that pricing. Okay.
>> Okay, no problem.
>> All right. I'm going to shoot you a text
so you have my information. As soon as I
get over to him and get him that
pricing, I'll have him send it over to
you. Okay.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> All right. I'll talk to you soon. Okay,
bye.
>> Byebye.
>> Thank you for calling. This is the sales
department. How can I help you?
>> Hey, I just want to see if you guys have
a car available.
>> I hope we do cuz it sounds like you want
to buy it.
>> You You nailed it. Yeah, I love it.
>> What kind of car is it?
>> I have a stock number whenever you're
ready.
>> I am ready when you are.
>> Stock number S is in Sam 6547361.
Okay, that is the Carnival SX and that
vehicle is here at our location. Are you
close to the dealership?
>> Uh, I'm in Orlando. Yeah.
>> Oh, that's even better. Well, I'm here
until 9:00 today and we have a lot of
deals and discounts. Can you make it in
to meet with me today? Uh,
>> yeah. I mean, as long as I can create a
numbers if you want to just send them
over to me and out the door, then yeah,
I can come in today as long as they all
look right.
>> Okay. So, the only thing with that is
we're going to be able to give you the
best numbers on, let's see, here at the
dealership since we're offering a lot of
promotions with this car. Uh, let me
see. So the best foot forward we have is
the 47 41,720 but we do are you have a
trade by any chance?
>> We do have some trades. Yeah. Uh we do
two two trades but we have some like
Carbon offers as well.
>> Okay. So as far as your trades go, we're
offering a buyback program. So we're
going to satisfy the loan that you
currently have invest whatever equity we
can get inside.
>> They they are they're paid off.
>> Oh, they're paid. Oh, okay. Beautiful.
All right. So you'll be using those
vehicles as a down payment.
>> Correct.
>> All right. So, I can work out the
numbers, but I can't work you anything
out as far as the trade goes.
>> We're going to figure out the trade
after, but if you can work everything
else out, that'd be great.
>> Okay. Okay. And let's see. You're going
to be registering where?
>> In Florida.
>> All right. And you'll be financing with
us, correct?
>> Yep. Yep.
>> All right. So, um, let me get started on
this. Is your name Matthew?
>> My name is Tommy.
>> Tommy. Okay. Comes up as Matthew. All
right. Tommy, your last name?
>> Uh, Makula. M I K U L A.
>> All right. I'm not supposed to give you
numbers over the phone through text, but
I'm going to I'm going to speak to my
manager and see what we can do. Okay.
>> Okay. I appreciate that.
>> Absolutely. But I will immediately get
back to you as soon as I get these
numbers. Okay.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> All right. Take care.
>> All right. Bye. Ready?
>> How can I help you out?
>> I just want to see if you guys have a
car available.
>> Yes. Is it new or used?
>> Brand new.
>> Okay. What's the vehicle? The stock
number.
>> Stock number 656005.
>> Is it the Carnival SX?
>> It is the Carnival SX.
>> Yep. It's showing it's still available.
Uh, what I can do is double check in the
key track to make sure cuz it looks like
we just got like two of the um 2026
available.
>> Okay, awesome. Perfect.
>> Do you have a good name and number and I
can call you? Right. I'm sorry.
>> No, no, no. I said perfect. Sorry.
>> Okay. What is your uh first name?
>> My first name is Tommy.
>> Okay, Tommy. And what's your best
contact phone? Phone number?
>> Yeah, phone number is going to be
>> perfect. And is this a good number? I
can send you a text as well.
>> Yep. That's great.
>> Okay, perfect. Um, and if it's still
available, are you looking to stop in
today or sometime tomorrow, this
weekend, and test drive the vehicle?
>> Yeah, I mean, yeah. As long as it's
available and we agree to numbers, I'll
come buy it.
>> Okay, perfect. I got you. Give me about
5 to 10 minutes. My name is Heather. I'm
going to send you a text message. If you
can just reply yes and then I'll let you
know within just a few moments. Okay.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> All righty, sir. Thank you.
>> No problem. Bye.
>> Okay. Bye-bye.
>> This is Carla speaking. How may I assist
you?
>> Hi, Carla. Uh, I just want to see if you
guys have a car available.
>> Okay. What car was that?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Yes.
>> Stock number Kangaroo
15779.
>> 15779.
>> You got it.
>> Give me one second.
>> No, you take your time.
>> Okay. The Kia K5. The white one.
>> No, not at all. The Kia Carnival. K is
in Kangaroo 15779.
>> Oh, I said 78. Sorry.
>> Oh, my I might have said 78. I'm getting
old.
The blue one, the SX.
>> Uh, the blue Astra blue.
>> Yes, that's the one I got here.
>> Awesome. Perfect. Well, I love it.
Already drove it. Really just looking
for the best possible numbers and I
heard there's no one better to call but
>> Okay. How much were you looking to get
it for?
>> Easy peasy. Just a simple $3,500 off
MSRP.
>> And if we agree on numbers, one's the
soonest that you can come and get it.
>> Okay,
>> I'm ready.
>> Can I get your name? The last Okay, I
hear that. Can I get your name and last
name?
>> Uh, name is Tommy. Last name Makula. M I
K U L A.
>> And what's a good email for you?
>> Uh, I don't use email. It's the devil's
work.
>> Okay. Um, your phone number?
>> Yeah, my phone number is going to be 9.
>> Um, I'll have my manager reach out to
you with that number.
>> Awesome.
>> And then I'll set a 10ip appointment for
today. Okay.
>> Awesome. Perfect.
>> Okay. Thank you. Have a good night.
>> Bye.
>> Good afternoon. Thanks for calling.
Nicole is speaking to whom do I have a
picture of speaking with?
>> Hey, my name's Tommy.
>> Hello.
>> Hey, can you hear me?
>> Yes, I can hear you now.
>> Hey, my name is Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. How you doing?
>> Yeah, I'm doing well. How about
yourself?
>> I'm good. I'm good, thank you.
>> Awesome. Perfect. So, I was just seeing
if you guys have a car available.
>> All right. Not a problem. I can take a
look for you. Are you calling me
locally, Tommy?
>> I am in Orlando. So, I'll hop in a skip.
>> Okay, it's not too far.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, okay. What vehicle is that? Is it a
new vehicle or a used vehicle? Uh, I
have a stock number if that helps or uh
VIN model code.
>> The stock number helps, but is it new or
or or used? So that way I'll know um
what platform to go on right now.
>> Uh stock number. Sorry, you said stock.
I'm sorry, I got distracted. I
apologize. You have my full attention
now.
>> No, I was saying is it a new vehicle or
a used vehicle? So I'll know what
platform to look for the vehicle.
>> Yeah, brand new vehicle.
>> Oh, it's a brand new. What brand is it?
>> Uh Kia.
>> Oh, it's a Kia. Okay. All right. No
problem. Go ahead with the stock number.
>> Yeah. Kia. Kia Volvo 60181.
Kia Volvo 60181.
>> Correct. Okay. 26 Carnival.
>> Kia Carnival.
>> 2026. Yes, it's available.
>> Awesome. Perfect. Well, I've drove it.
Love it. Want more of it. I know that
the car looks like it's in like a
forest, but I'm pretty sure it's a new
car and not a junk car. So, this is the
one I want. As long as it's brand new
and not
>> It's brand new. It's a 2026.
>> Yeah, the pictures are just taken like
in a forest. I don't even know how you
guys did that, but this is the one I
want. So, as long as it's in new car
condition, u just send me some numbers
and as long as they're great, I'll buy
it today.
>> Okay. You said your name was Tommy,
correct? What's your last name?
>> Makula. M I K U L.
>> Said you're in Orlando. All right.
>> Yeah. And you're looking to purchase
this cash today.
>> Finance. Yeah. Finance.
>> Oh, finance. Okay.
>> Yep.
>> And are you going to do this the
financing with a deposit?
>> Uh yeah, deposit as long as I agree in
numbers.
>> So, I'm just putting I'm just putting um
some information together to have my
sales manager reach out to you. They
normally, you know, want enough
information. Or what's your zip code in
Orlando? Zip code in Orlando is
>> Okay. And no trading, correct?
>> No. Uh I have trades, but I'm not
worried about them right now. I'm more
worried about the out the door on this
one.
>> Okay. And then what would your deposit
be if you're going to do a deposit?
>> I don't know. What do you guys charge
for a deposit?
>> I mean, deposit varies. We have zero
deposit to, you know, whatever you can
put down.
>> Oh.
>> As I said, I'm just trying to put
something together for the sales manager
to reach out to you.
>> Yeah. $4.
>> $4.
>> I mean, whatever you want me to put a
deposit, but if I get to choose, I'll
pay $4.
>> Okay, I got you.
>> I mean, you're the one that told me to
pick a number.
have a number
>> and you said you're ready to purchase
the vehicle now?
>> Yeah, I'm ready to pick it to buy it
right now.
>> Okay. And this is the best one to reach
you back at the one that you're
>> correct.
>> All right. I'm going to speak with my
sales sales manager and have him reach
out to you. Will you be able to answer
the phone call anytime from now?
>> Yeah, I'm I'm free and available. I'm
just just here waiting to buy a car.
>> Okay. All right. No problem, Tom. We'll
call you back soon.
>> All right. Sounds good. All righty. Bye.
>> What's going on, boss? Uh,
>> I'm doing well. How about yourself? the
26 Carnival.
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah. I see that. I just got
some numbers from you guys.
>> Oh, perfect, perfect, perfect. Are you
coming in?
>> Well, I mean, I looked at the numbers.
I'm not super happy with them. You guys
have the What is this? Kia advantage
protection package.
>> That is basically a Vance package, which
we include into the pinstripe, the door
guards handle. You have the value
shield, which you know, God forbid you
get the car accident, the car, you get
an accident. Normally, the insurance
covers you what the car is worth. We put
$5,000 on top of that. Then you have a
year warranty on tires. uh year warranty
on your uh key fog, you know, a lot of
more. I can even, you know, send you a
picture of of our stuff we have included
in it.
>> Oh, I'll pass on all that. Thanks.
>> Is it a number you were trying to Is
that a ballpark you're looking for?
>> I was hoping to get $3,500 off without
that protection package.
>> So, what was like out the door number
you wanted to be if you don't mind me
asking?
>> Sure, I can do some math for us. Let's
Let's do the math. 5324
minus $29.95 minus uh about 1,500 bucks
like 49829 out the door.
>> All right. So, that would be lower than
my MSRP.
>> Yeah,
>> I can, you know, I can take out the
$29.95 if I can get you uh 51 out the
door. Is that something we can do?
>> I mean, I'm really trying to get 4989
out the door. You told me what's the
number?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I'm just asking.
>> 51's close. We're getting closer. We're
like almost there. We're so close.
>> Okay. Okay. Okay. It doesn't hurt. I
mean, it doesn't hurt to ask my manager
here. Look, let me go ask bring the I'll
let him know I got on the phone with
you. The 49K. I'll bring it up and then
if anything, I'll call you right back.
>> Right. Are you local?
>> Uh, I'm in Orlando. So, I'm pretty darn
close.
>> Orlando, if we work something out, you
coming in today or
>> Yeah. Yeah, I'll come in today.
>> Perfect. All right, let me get with you
right back there.
>> Okay, sounds good. I'll be here.
>> Bye, man.
>> Bye.
>> Thank you for calling. This is Rich in
sales. How may I help you?
>> Hey, Rich. I just want to see if you
guys have a car available.
>> Oh, we have several.
>> Awesome, dude. Thanks. Have a nice day.
>> What are you looking for?
>> Hey, I have a stock number if that
helps.
>> Okay. Yeah, give me one second here. I'm
sorry. What' you say your name was?
>> Oh, my name's Tommy.
>> Tommy. All right, Tommy, let me get into
my inventory here. Are you looking at a
new car or pre-owned?
>> Uh, brand new.
>> Okay. All right. Fire when ready.
>> Stock number K is in Kansas. C is in
city. 6508.
>> You are not a veteran, were you?
>> I was not. Should I? Should I be?
>> No, your uh alpha numeric there are a
little off, but yes, that car is
available.
>> Anyway, uh I'm super interested in this
car. Uh ready to buy. Uh really just
trying to get some numbers. I already
drove one. Love it. Great. Just trying
to get a great deal on it. call today.
>> I like the way you work.
>> Tommy, let me get some information here
together and I will help you any way I
can. Hang on one second. I got to Have
you talked to anybody here before? First
time.
>> I have not.
>> Safe to say you're a Thomas.
>> I'm I'm a Tommy, but I can be a Thomas
if you want me to be a Thomas.
>> What's on your driver's license, Tommy?
>> Uh, well, Thomas Slav is on my driver's
license, but that's a whole different
conversation.
>> Last name, I'm sorry.
>> Makula. M I K U L A
>> from like Hawaii or something? No.
Croatia.
>> Oh, okay. All right. Cool. Uh, how about
your zip code, sir?
>> Zip code is
>> your phone number.
>> Phone number is going to be
>> Bear with me here a second. I'm just
trying to get through a couple of the
stupid screens here.
>> You're good.
>> I assume you saw the car online.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I saw the car online. It
looks It looks like the car I'm looking
for.
>> Okay. Are you looking to trade anything
in, Tommy?
>> I have trades, but I'm more worried
about the out the door. We'll figure out
the trades next. I have other offers in
the trade if I need them. Okay. An SX
in Ivory Silver, correct?
>> Yeah, that's it.
>> Okay. We're not talking about tags right
now, but I will or uh I'm sorry, we're
not talking about trades right now, but
I would assume then you're transferring
a tag.
>> I will be transferring a tag. Yep.
>> Previously discussed, not a military
vet.
>> Not a military vet.
>> The only reason I even brought it up is
there's a small, you know, rebate for
military vets. So, just uh get that one
out of the way. Uh financing, leasing,
or paying cash?
>> Uh financing.
>> Okay. And you got a certain amount
you're looking to put down?
>> You know, uh we have our trades which
we'll be putting down as cash. But
again, that's like I'm more worried
about the out the door. I heard there's
some crazy deals going on the 2026s
right now because life is good and
everything's going great and Kia's
basically have an overabundance of them.
So,
>> okay. Are you say trade you trade
multiples in? I
>> I have two cars that we're going to
trade in. And it's like worth they were
going to be worth like 15k in theory.
But again, I'm not worried too to worry
about that. I'll sell them to the
Carvana if I need to.
>> Gotcha.
>> Yeah. I'm just really trying to get a
great deal on the Kia 2026. I know the
new model year. They're just doing crazy
deals, crazy discounts on them.
>> All right. For your zip code,
>> I have a V
seinal. Is that correct?
>> Yes, correct.
>> Okay. All right. I think I have
everything I need here. Tommy, give me
about 10 minutes if you could and I will
call you back and Oh, you know what? Be
easier to actually send an email here
with some numbers.
>> I don't use a good email. I don't use
email, you know. I'm not not into that.
But you can text me. You feel you feel
confident you're going be able to give
me a great deal on this car, you know,
with everything going on. I think I
think uh just great deals to be had,
right?
>> Yeah. I will I'll put it together and I
will call you right back.
>> Okay. Yeah. Okay. Sounds good.
>> All right, Tommy. Thanks. No problem.
>> Bye.
>> Hey, Mr. Tommy.
>> Hey, you do this for me?
>> No, not yet. Not yet. Um, before I bring
the offer, do you have a tag you going
to transfer or you
>> We do have a tag. We're going to
transfer
>> tags. Transfer. So, you're not trading
anything, right?
>> Uh, we have trades. I'm not too worried
about it. We'll figure out the trades
next.
>> So, don't worry about the the trade.
>> Yeah, but we're going to transfer tags.
So, you know that.
>> Transfer tag. Any money down towards
anything like that or just buying cash?
>> It'll be 15k with the trades. But
>> what was that again? 15,000 with the
trades combined is what it'll be. But
I'm not worried. I'm more worried about
that out the door. That 49,000
>> first and then you'll you'll Okay, cool,
cool, cool. All right, let me call right
back.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> Perfect. Byebye.
>> Bye.
>> Thank you for calling. This is Dev. With
who do I have the pleasure of speaking
with?
>> Hey, this is Tommy, but I'm looking to
speak to Mark.
>> With Mark?
>> Yeah, Mark called me. Left me a message.
He said he said it's
>> Give me just a second, sir. Oh, okay.
All right. Hold on one second.
>> Meanwhile,
>> good afternoon. This is Mark here.
>> Hey, Mark. I got a call from you. Uh,
this is Tommy. Hey, Tommy. What's up?
>> Hey, what's up, man? You called me,
>> you know. Yeah, you called back. What
you need?
>> Oh, man. I'm trying to get I heard I
heard you're I should only call Mark.
Mark is the best guy to get numbers to.
>> Yeah. Well, whoever that is, you
shouldn't listen on.
>> Oh, okay.
>> No, you're from Orlando.
>> Well, I mean, we live in Orlando.
>> Gotcha. Okay. Yeah, cuz um I can't
imagine we're the only one unless it's a
specific pass package that you needed.
>> Uh I mean, no. I mean, I'm calling
around to see who has the best deal, but
>> Gotcha. All right. What did I have it
right? It was a It was a carnival,
right?
>> Yeah, you got it.
>> 2026. I got a a stock number here if you
0181 is what they had. KV6181.
>> That was it.
>> Oh, gotcha. All right. What do I got to
do to earn your business? Let's make
this easy.
>> 3500 off easy. Let me squeezy. 3500 off.
No ads.
>> Yeah. Luckily, we don't have any ads. I
do have the dealer fee, of course. Tax
tag, title, registration. Did you want
to finance through key at all?
>> Yeah. Oh, yeah. We'll finance.
>> Uh, actually, I thought I figured there
might have been a rebate, but on the
26s, it doesn't look like it. So they
got rates, you know, it looks like 48
months, 4.9%, then you go out to 72,
it's like 6.49%.
Just up to you. 3500. Let me check the
MSRP on the score. You're not from North
Carolina, are you?
>> I used to live in North Carolina once
upon a time.
>> Yeah, I'm from North Carolina. My uh
baseball coach used to say, "Easy peasy,
lemon squeezy." So there may be a chance
that you're from the east coast of North
Carolina. So
>> uh Well, I mean, this is all true, but
it's a that's a weird joke.
>> Yeah. Easy peasy lemon squeezy is what
they always said. I I never got it, but
it's just that was funny. I I haven't
heard that in years. Wow. That's
>> 3500. Yeah, I'll do that. I put the
sales price at uh 45 630. So, plus tax,
tag, title, registration, put you close
right around 50.
>> Well, you made that you made that really
easy, man. Just let me just see that
breakdown. I think we might we have two
trades, so I can send you that
information. We can lock this all up. We
can come on in.
>> Okay. Yeah. For the trades, I'd really
like to see them, you know, especially
if you've got numbers from other stores,
but we're pretty simple. You know, I I
can't imagine if if you're shopping me,
you probably already went to either
Kelly Blue Book, third party sources
like CarMax and stuff like that, but uh
you know, we kind of use a combination
of things.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I love it, man. Yeah. So,
yeah, this you guys make it easy. I
appreciate that. Let's let's rock and
roll and just send that to me so I can
see it, make sure there's no nothing
crazy, and then I'll, like I said, we'll
we'll come on, put a deposit, call
today.
>> Yep. I'll shoot over. Uh let me see if I
get your email. Text your email.
>> Text it is way easier for me.
>> Yep, that's it.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah. And then uh what was the uh zip
code? Is that uh
is that Florida?
>> That is.
>> Oh, somebody said Orlando. Kind of ask
you if you were from Orlando.
>> Oh, yeah. No worries. I would just say
Orlando cuz it's easier. Nobody knows
where it is.
>> Oh, is that close?
>> Kind of. Sort of.
>> Yeah. Just give me a few minutes. I'll
uh I'll get it shot up. I get printed up
for you.
>> Okay. Sounds good. I appreciate you,
man. Appreciate you making it easy.
>> Yeah. Thanks, Don.
>> No problem. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> Bump. Okay. Come on. Okay. We can we can
do this. Okay. That carnival might be
done. Thank you guys so much. If you
guys want to tune on, make sure you guys
like, follow, subscribe. I appreciate
each and every one of you. If you guys
want more of this kind of content, like,
follow, subscribe. I charge a flat fee
of a,000 bucks. I negotiate car deals.
We do anywhere between 150 to 200 deals
a month. Thank you guys so much for the
support. I'm out. Bye-bye.
[Music]