There are negotiable. I want
>> You guys have dealer add-ons as well. Is
it?
>> Everybody has it, sir. That's nothing
new.
>> You just said I should buy your car
because it doesn't have dealer add-ons,
so we're less expensive. But if you come
here, you can negotiate the dealer.
What? It shouldn't It shouldn't be like
that complicated. It's like this one
system that you I'd prefer to do uh
everything in at home. I'm really not
dressed for to be in public. It's weird
to ask somebody what they're wearing.
Sorry, it seems like I'm out of breath,
but I'm just in a bunny costume. I don't
like everybody know where my hole is.
I'm in a pink bunny costume. Does that
help? It's like an OF model, you know?
I'm just telling myself. This is the
Halloween edition. So many people have
asked about my history. Obviously
performing as Ralphie in the Christmas
story. I just wanted to show you guys
the full thing. You know, I still have
the costume. I still fit in it 25 years
later. Like Ralphie
Christmas.
I think you guys are all too young.
Story bunny outfit.
Juliana hadn't seen this outfit either.
Juliana didn't know. Boom. There. See?
See? Watch this.
Do I have to wear it?
That's what we are. We're Ralphie. But
we are going to play some bingo though.
Bingo baker, guys. Because I've been
gone so long. Guess what? You guys get a
bingo bongo. gotta get a card deal type
thing. So, guess what? If you guys don't
know who I am, my name's uh Ralphie the
Bunny. Okay, so we are going to be
looking for a Santa Fe. Okay, so they
want a calligraphy, they want a hybrid,
and they want a all-wheel drive cargo
cover 0% for 60 months, which would be a
25, right? Or the 26 offering that as
well. He only want the brown Napa
leather. wants the matte bronze. Let me
read their text real quick. Let me read
the text real quick between this client.
They have a peon interior, but not on
the 25s. The 25s they only have the peon
brown is only in the 26s. In the 25s,
they only have the beige, the gray, and
the black. All right, so let's go earthy
mask. There's 71 in the country. He
wants I don't care where the car going
at. We got the car finally. He lives
Let's write this down. This client lives
in, in my opinion, that's Southern
California. So, let's hop hop hop to a
deal. We got bingo going. This
dealership says they're doing $4,250
cash back. I want that plus a rebate. I
want like $9,000 off this bad boy. I
want the craziest deal to ever exist.
>> Think you just want me help you?
>> Hey, Juan. This is Tommy. How's it
going?
>> Great. Hey, I just wanted to see if you
guys have a car available.
>> Okay, let's take a look real quick.
>> Sure. Figured it was call. It was easier
to call than to hop on over there, you
know.
>> Yeah. And what kind of car are you
looking for?
>> You know what makes the most sense for
you? I have make, model, I have a VIN, I
have a stock number. I got it all.
>> Have you been at our store before?
>> I have never been to your store. First
time caller, longtime listener.
>> What city are you calling from?
>> I am calling from Torrance.
>> Torrance. Perfect. Just in case if I
lost phone call is this.
>> Yep, that's it.
>> Okay, Mr. Matthew. Perfect. So, let's
take a look. Uh, what's the stock number
are you working with?
>> The stock number I am work working with
is in T is in tick tock. H is in hockey
stick 0897
953.
>> This below to work on a cart.
>> I'm sorry.
>> What vehicle you look is this?
>> You are like so muffled. It's like you
went under a bridge.
>> Oh, it's just a phone line. Uh, let's
see.
>> Oh, yeah. Sometimes it helps pick up the
phone. That does help.
>> All righty. So, it looks like TS and
Thomas Edges and Henry 089
953.
Uh, let me see if it's sold already.
>> That's fine. Take your time. It could be
because we under a new um ownership and
they changed the stock numbers and this
happened you know like 10 days ago
roughly. So we are kind of going through
some details in here under that number.
I'm going to look into my internal and
see if I can pop it out. 089
953.
>> Yeah. Here it seems like you're looking
for a 2026
Santa Fe Calligraphy all-wheel drive
phantom black. You found it. Look at
you. You're hopping into business.
>> So now let me look activity on that car.
>> Sure.
>> Was it a front-wheel drive or all-wheel
drive?
>> All-wheel drive.
>> Allwheel drive.
>> Yeah. I never know what kind of terrain
I'm going to be in.
>> It was black with gray. Nope. It was
earthy brass with peon brown.
>> Okay. Early brass with peon brown.
>> With peon brown. Yeah.
>> The stock number you give me. Can you
repeat one more time? Was
>> you had it? You had it before. You named
the vehicle earlier and then you just
went somewhere else.
>> Right. Because it was calling for a
different color. I do had that one right
here.
>> You named the color the first time. I'm
pretty sure. Maybe I'm going crazy. This
call's going for I'm looking for an
earth. Oh, yeah. cuz it was before it
was kind of different color. I I I have
both colors. The one I was earlier I had
it under 089 but this one's under 087
953. Is that correct?
>> Zero. Yeah, it is 953. Correct. I'm
looking at the window. It's the last six
of the VIN, too. If that helps.
>> Okay. So, yeah, that car is available.
Well, what time you coming?
>> The earthy brass or the brown.
>> Do you want me to go and check if I have
the key in the on the key machine? Make
sure before you come in, we do have it
in the system. It shows we do. I just
make sure I pull the key.
>> Yeah. No, I mean I I I'm I'm glad I
first off I just want to see if it's
available and then I', you know, you
throw me through a whole loop loop. I'm
not bringing my aame. Um maybe it's cuz
I'm in a Halloween costume. I don't
know. But no, I'm I'm definitely
interested in buying the car. I need to
see if it's available. And if so, then
we could talk about, you know, hopping
into the pricing or whatever that is.
But you're saying you do have this brown
one this whole time.
>> And the system it shows available.
>> Okay.
>> And the system it shows available. I
need to go to the key machine and make
sure I grab the key in my hand because I
can be working the deal as yesterday and
it shows in the computer available and
when I'm trying to grab the key, someone
already has sold the car.
>> Got it. Okay.
>> So, if you have what you got to do,
whatever you got to do to to do to tell
me if this car is available, that would
be great.
>> You mind to wait a little bit?
>> Yeah, I'll wait. I'll be on hold. Set a
threem minute timer. Honestly, guys,
this guy is throwing me so far off
because he spent like seven minutes
trying to tell me if the car was
available and apparently it was
available the whole time, but then he
was on a different I am so lost. But he
was like, I don't find the car. I found
a gray one. And then I remember him
saying that he had the car available.
They just kept going. I'm so confused.
Uh we're at 1 minute something left.
Please tell me.
>> Thank you for holding, sir. So I had the
key in my hand. So the car it is
available. Okay. Love it. So, what's
your next question?
>> My next question is, I've already driven
it. I already know I want it. I want
more of it. Really? Trying to be dressed
for success and get a deal. And I'm
hoping you can get that for me.
>> What kind of deal are you looking at?
>> A great deal. The best deal. A day. A
deal that only a mother would give to
their kid on Christmas.
>> So, for this vehicle here online, let me
see what we got going on
>> online. You guys are charging MSRP for
it.
>> Well, in the vehicle like this from
other stores, they're adding markups. We
are not adding a markup. Everybody has
dealer Adams is what your question is.
Ours is the less expensive one. So you
told me,
>> "But yours is yours isn't less
expensive, but I I don't want to pay
MSRP." No.
>> Mhm. You don't want to pay MSRP?
>> No. I'd like to get a better deal.
>> All right. So, in that kind of case.
>> All right. All right.
>> You're in Colorado.
>> Nope. And remember, we talked about this
earlier. I'm in Torrance.
>> Yes.
>> I know it's been a long conversation,
but we went there before. So the deal we
have right now, sir, is uh obviously
every store is going to offer you
markups, which we're not doing that on
this car like everybody else is doing.
Everybody else has dealer add-ons. Ours
is the less expensive. If you see any
value on those items when you get here,
there are negotiable.
>> You guys have dealer add-ons as well.
>> Everybody has it, sir. That's nothing
new.
>> You just said I should buy your car cuz
it doesn't have dealer add-ons, so we're
less expensive. But if you come here,
you can negotiate the dealer. What What
is the pricing of your car, friend?
53,150
happened to a negotiation. I'm seriously
ready.
>> 53,150
is the price of the vehicle.
>> Do you guys have dealer add-ons?
>> Yes, we do.
>> Okay. So, what are the dealer add-ons
you're trying to charge me? Let me take
off my What are the dealer add-ons?
You're 53150. What are the dealer
add-ons?
>> Battery forever.
>> Battery forever. I get a battery that
never dies. Okay. A battery that can be
replaced if you have failure after 3
years on the 12vt battery.
>> Got it.
>> Not on the big battery.
>> Cool. Warranty on my battery. Is that
it?
>> Paint protection and interior
protection.
>> Paint protection
>> and interior protection.
>> And interior. So my paint will never
scratch and my interior will never rip.
>> I mean, if you get a knife and you
scratch, obviously that's not going to
cover, right?
>> It's not the best protection in the
world, but I get it. What else? We are
offering right now what is called for
the rings and the tires and the
windshield. We also offerings products
like that and all the vehicles has what
is called car alarm system and their
vehicles.
>> Cararo system.
>> Yes. K A R.
>> Oh car car system. Okay. Recovery
system.
>> What is that?
>> In case if your vehicle gets uh you know
stolen, they will give you up to $20,000
to you without using your insurance.
Well, what if my insurance What happens
if my insurance covers the full thing?
Do they still give me 20 grand?
>> Yeah, because it's stolen. You had to
have a police report and say your car
was stolen.
>> So, just to be write out a check,
>> if my car gets stolen, you will not only
pay me the full insurance payout, which
insurance will, but you will also pay me
a check for 20 grand on top of that
>> up to I say up to $20,000. That can give
you that can give you 19. They can give
you 20 because it's determine on the
price of the vehicle.
>> Huh?
I'm confused. If my car gets stolen,
you're saying I get money. Why? What?
And insurance covers everything. What?
What else would there be?
>> Because this is a recovery system, sir.
>> So, I'm getting 20 grand for it to be
recovered.
>> Do I get to hire like a private agent
that can like find it for me for 20
grand? Like, I'm just confused.
>> Okay, sir. So, our dealers are 4283.
That's what it comes to. Total 4283
RS are dealer arms and which I said they
are negotiable. So wherever you see that
you have some you see some value into
it.
>> None of them
>> you know the only one that we cannot
take it the only one that we cannot take
it off is uh for example the Colorado
cuz it's already pre-installed. It's
already wired to the car.
>> I don't even know what that is still.
You're telling me I get 20 grand if my
car is stolen but not really.
>> It's very difficult to explain all these
things over the phone sir. that then I
don't think you should sell a product
that you can't explain in two sentence,
you know, like it shouldn't it shouldn't
be like that complicated. It's like this
one system that you
a call back.
People say, "Why Tommy? Nobody should
have to hire you to buy a car. This is
so easy." This is pretty easy. Anybody
can do this. He's not answering.
>> Oh, hi.
>> Oh, there. Sorry. Sorry. I I got hung up
by by somebody, so I'm trying to figure
out who it was.
>> Oh, no. I'm so sorry.
>> No, you're fine. I was just talking to
somebody.
>> You sure?
>> Okay. Were you trying to figure out who
hung up on you from here from?
>> Yeah, I was just talking to uh his name
was um Juan maybe.
>> Let me see who called.
>> New car sales.
>> New car side. A one. Does that sound
familiar?
>> Is he in New car sales? Hyundai. Then
that would probably be it.
>> Yeah. Juan,
>> were you trying to get a hold of him?
>> Yeah, I mean, I was just talking to him.
I think the phone disconnected or hung
up or something. I don't know.
>> Let me get you over to him. Give me one
second.
>> Yeah, that would be great.
>> Okay, transferring now.
>> Thank you.
>> Your call has been forwarded to the
voicemail for No one is available to
take your call. At the tone, please
record your message.
>> Hello, Juan. Uh, this is Tommy. Um, I
don't know why, but it seems like our
phone line disconnected, which is kind
of crazy cuz we were talking about it. I
was trying to buy a car. You were
explaining about your car R system. Uh,
and then the phone just hung up and now
I'm like calling over and over. I'll
call back again. I'll keep calling until
I get somebody cuz I thought I was going
to buy a car from you guys as you're my
local dealership and I heard you guys
make it easy. But I don't know, maybe
the new ownership told you guys to
disconnect lines when you don't like
people. I don't know. Like that's weird.
But maybe I like the old owner better. I
have no idea. Uh, or maybe that's why
you guys got a new owner to begin with.
I have no idea. But I'd like to buy a
car car. So, uh, if you can please give
me a call back. That'd be great. So, if
you guys don't know who I am, my name's
Tommy. I negotiate car deals for a
living. My goal is to save you time,
energy, and anxiety. We save money, but
that's a byproduct. We charge a flat fee
of a,000 bucks. I do it all for you.
Price a car, trade, add-ons,
accessories. You sit back, relax. If you
don't want to deal with people like one,
you hire me. I'll call another
dealership. You know, let's ask for
somebody else. Let's see if we can get
somebody else.
>> Thank Hyundai.
>> Oh, is this one?
>> Yes, sir.
>> One, you disconnected from me earlier. I
got some problems with my my phone, sir.
How you doing?
>> Oh, you have problems with your phone.
Yeah, I've been calling back and stuff.
I'm glad that we can finally get a hold.
Okay. You have some problems with the
phone?
>> Yes, sir. So, let's get back to the
conversation. You say you're trying to
get the vehicle. You want to get the
best price. Um right now,
>> yeah, it's crazy. Okay. Yeah.
>> Perfect. So, so we have the price of the
vehicle and uh uh if you like to put an
offer on the vehicle, um you know, I can
bring it over to my uh general manager
and see what uh what he think about it.
What were you thinking to pay for this
vehicle, sir?
>> Let's do $4,500 off plus rebates with no
add-ons.
>> $4,500
off, no rebates. No.
>> No.
>> Plus rebates. Plus rebates, no add-ons.
So, none of I don't want the car system.
I don't want the battery, the paint
protection, the interior protection, the
rims, the tires. I don't want any of it.
>> So, you want to pay $45,000 plus back on
registration?
>> No. $4,500 off plus rebate. Whatever the
rebate is, if I want to take the special
rate or if I want to take that. So,
$4,500 discount plus whatever rebate
there is if I decide to go the rebate
route.
>> Okay.
>> No dealer ads.
>> If we do that, is that going to take for
you to buy the vehicle, sir?
>> Yep. That would be a good enough deal.
>> All right. So, can I call you back?
>> Sure, you can call me back as long as
your phone's not having problems.
>> Okay, sir. Not a problem.
>> Okay.
>> Thank you.
>> All right. Bye.
>> When you're on a work phone, because
you're on a work phone like this. Sorry.
Like this, right? I'm going to I'm going
to call, right? I'm going to listen. The
car run is already pre-installed. Wired
to the car.
>> I don't even know what that is still.
You're telling me I get 20 grand if my
car is stolen. But not
>> It's very difficult to explain all these
things over the phone. Sir,
>> it shouldn't it shouldn't be like that
complicated. Yeah. Thank you for call.
>> You heard the very end. You heard the
phone go down, right? Like it's very
like very very obvious if you're just
listening for it, right? Yeah. So, if
you ever want to hang up on somebody,
you're at work, right? I'm going to give
you the life hack. Right. You just you
hit the button. You just hit the button.
You pull it from your ear. Hit the
button. Don't hang up like this. You'll
hear it every time.
>> Sales. This is Laura. How can I help?
>> Hey Laura, this is buying Tommy. I just
want to see if you guys have a car
available.
>> Yeah, I can definitely double check.
What's the year, make, and model?
>> Uh, I have a stock number, too, but it's
a 2026 Hyundai Santa Fe hybrid
calligraphy.
>> 2026 Hyundai Santa Fe Hybrid
>> calligraphy. Yeah.
>> Calligraphy. Okay. One second. Let me
double check.
>> No, you're good.
>> May I get your name one more time?
>> My name is Tommy.
>> Tommy. Thank you. Um, Santa Fe Hybrid
Calligraphy. Yeah, it looks like we have
a couple of the 2026's here.
>> Yep. I have a stock number of the exact
one I'm looking for if that helps.
>> Oh, yeah. What's the stock number?
>> It's H's in Honda 8615.
>> Okay. One second. Is that the one with
the brass exterior? Brown interior.
>> That's the one. That's the dream in the
driveway.
>> Okay, let me just triple check. Yeah,
great news. That one is here and
available. It is on our spare lot. Um
but I can make sure that it's available.
Um if if you're planning on stopping by,
um do you have some time today or maybe
tomorrow?
>> Yeah, I've already I've already uh I've
already driven it. Already know I want
it. Really just trying to get some
pricing on it.
>> Okay, great. We can be ready to review
all of the pricing. It's all negotiated
here in our store with our managers. Are
you available to stop in today and
discuss everything with them?
>> Oh, I' I'd prefer to do uh everything in
at home. I'm really not dressed for to
be in public.
>> Okay, I understand. We definitely can
make it as convenient and as smooth as
possible, but all of the uh discussing
of the pricing is is going to be
accomplished here at our store with our
managers. Are you planning on financing?
>> Uh yeah, I'm open to financing if the
deal makes sense. I I know you guys do
some low APR and some rebates, but
>> are you planning on including a trade
in?
>> Uh I I I potentially have a trade. Yeah,
but I'm not really too worried about the
trade. More worried about the price of
the car.
>> Okay, I understand. Let me just take a
quick look here. Um I can review the
MSRP on this one is 53,540.
So basically for the out the door
number, uh you would take um the taxes
and registration is going to be
calculated based on your zip code. So,
we always say to add to be on the safe
side, anywhere from 9 to 11% for your
registration and taxes. And of course,
that doesn't include like any warranties
you might want to opt into once you're
here. But that would be the the out the
door price.
>> Okay. So, the out the-do price is 53540
plus some taxes,
>> correct? Plus the registration and
taxes. Mhm.
>> Okay. And do you guys have any like at
dealer add-ons that are on every car?
Typically, like most dealerships, we do
include like a protection package. Those
that is optional, but it does include
the third brake light, resist all paint
protection, vehicle like the tracking,
the standard uh or star guard GPS
tracking, and the clear protectant for
the door edges and the handles, the door
handles. Um, that's an additional
$3,996.
They can review that with you, but
generally at the end of the day, we're
not going to lose business over price.
And those items are optional.
>> Okay. So, I don't have to get any of
that.
>> Correct. Yeah. They'll review it with
you just to see if you find, you know,
any value of it. Eight out of 10 times
customers, I mean, especially if it's
maybe a pre-owned vehicle, they they may
see the value in adding, you know, some
of those uh items. they are already
included in the vehicle, but they'll
discuss that with you and then they'll
be able to narrow down if any of those,
you know, make sense to you if you'd
like to move forward with them and if
not that they are optional.
>> Yeah, I there's a lot of like whatifs
and probablys and I mean there's no way
I could just talk to somebody over the
phone on it. I just, you know, I'd like
to buy his car. I'm ready to buy it, but
I don't want to have to come drive all
the way to your dealership just to talk
about the numbers. That may or may not
happen. I just don't get why I can't
talk to somebody. Well, we don't have an
internet sales team. All of our managers
and um our product specialists are on
the floor, you know, showroom with our
customers. And the way that we're going
to be able to secure you the best price,
especially if you're planning on
financing, is having you here working
directly with our managers. Sometimes
the lenders, they do want to conduct
like an interview over the phone. Um so,
if you're available for that, it
shouldn't take too long if especially if
you know you love the vehicle. Yeah. For
the lenders, yes, sometimes.
>> Oh, okay. Well, what if I'm just paying
cash? Can we talk about numbers over the
phone then?
>> If you're planning on paying cash, let
me see. We may have some incentives for
that.
>> Yeah. I mean, I just don't like like all
the like like kind of like this. I just
want to talk to somebody definitively on
numbers. I don't want to have to run to
your dealership to figure that out. Your
your car salesman don't call people.
That just not something they do. They
sit around and if it's not busy, they
just twirl their thumbs all day. And if
they're busy, they they help. I I'm just
confused. You don't have car sales
people that call people.
>> Well, we're busy all day. So right now,
especially because it is the end of the
month, my managers are being more
aggressive with their offers. So we're
our showroom's pretty busy. That's why
we reserve, you know, the uh the
appointment, so you can come in and and
some people, they do want to take a look
at the vehicle. In your case, you know,
you've already test driven it, you've
already like it. Um so that won't be
part of it, but you know, to discuss the
the pricing and negotiation. Yes, that
is all going to be done here at our
store.
>> Yeah. I mean, I don't want to like
again, as you're saying all these
things, right, which is you guys are
super busy. The chances of me coming to
your dealership and being in and out in
5 minutes is not going to happen. I'm
going to have to wait 45 minutes to an
hour to talk to somebody because you're
so busy you can't even deal with the the
people you have in there. So, you know,
I don't want to play this game of
waiting hours at a dealership. Um,
that's that's not what I do. I try to
get this all done over the phone. And
the dealership that makes my life easy
is the one I'll buy from.
>> I understand. And and that's why we set
up the reservation so you're not waiting
for us. We'd rather be waiting on you.
So once you arrive,
>> what if somebody just randomly comes up
20 minutes before the reservation? Are
you guys are just going to let that
person sit there and the other person's
then going to twiddle his thumbs until I
get there?
>> No. Thankfully, no, that wouldn't be the
case. I mean, usually, you know, if the
reservations would come first and then
whoever, you know, any walk-ins or
anything like that. And we do have
plenty of um our guys are really good at
what they do, so they'd be ready to to
assist you at any time.
>> Okay. Yeah. I mean, I I I see your
manager saying they're aggressive to
sell a car. I'm aggressive to buying a
car. If they're in the mood of calling
somebody to be like, you know what, I
want to sell a car today and I have 5
minutes of time to talk numbers, then
I'm ready to do that. But if you guys
can't even accommodate me there, it's
2025, almost 2026. I can buy a car on
Amazon for that matter. The idea that I
have to go through all this RickMarole
to just get the real numbers is insane.
Uh again, I'm uh that's crazy. What
happens if I just would have bought it
on Amazon? What would you guys have
done?
>> Yeah, I mean ultimately that is up to
you. I mean that that is an option and
some customers do prefer to go that
route. Um but a lot of our customers
they do tend to be more old school. They
want to come in, you know, they want to
shake our hand. We want to do business
and a lot of our customers.
>> How do you guys how do you guys handle
what department handles those people?
Cuz isn't that exactly how that works?
Which is if I buy from Amazon, I just
get in contact with you anyway. So like
who do I talk to at that point?
>> Uh typically the Amazon purchases are
just done strictly through Amazon. We
actually don't even have any like I
wouldn't they they don't we wouldn't
interact with any of the customers that
shop on Amazon. That's all done
internally and then our managers handle
it from there. But let me see if someone
can can someone give you a call maybe.
Are are you available right now?
>> I'm free. I'm trying to buy a car today.
So
>> Okay. Uh is this your best number?
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> And may I get your And you said your
name is Tommy. T O M Y.
>> Yep.
>> Got it. I'll have someone call you back.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> Bye.
>> Bye. Juan did try to call me back. Okay,
I'm going to call Juan back.
>> How you doing, Mr. Matthews?
>> Hey, it's actually Tommy, but that's
okay. Um, I I just missed your phone
call.
>> Yes, I did. And I left a voice message.
So, I went and u bring request. I bring
your request to my manager uh that you
want a $4,500 plus whatever other
rebates, no Adams, no anything. So, uh,
the best number on the price of the
vehicle will be 51,481
plus tax license registration. Uh, that
will be the best price on the vehicle.
And then if you do want to get a dealer
choice, uh, with Honda Motor Finance,
they do have a rebate for 4250.
>> Okay. Uh, so I So, it's 51481
would be the best price you guys have on
the car, which is like $1,500 off. 40.
Wait, no, no, more than that. Trying to
figure out. It's like two grand, $1,700
off, $1,600 off. Somewhere in that
ballpark
>> somewhere there.
>> Some Okay, you know, I'll figure it out.
Let's do this one together. I'll pull
out a calculator here. Um, and what
about the dealer ads, the the car
system, and all that fun stuff.
>> Uh, nothing like that.
>> I got all I got all that off there.
Okay. Minus. And you said the sales
price was 51481.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Okay. So, 1669 is the discount. Okay.
Well, that's better than what we were
at. Uh, but I I really want to be less
than that. So, um, I mean, if you're
right and every dealership wants to
charge add-ons, I guess you guys will
have the best price, huh?
>> Uh, that's what we can give you, sir.
>> Okay. Yeah. If you guys want to come,
like I said, I'm looking to buy a car
today. I know it's the end of the month,
so I'll keep this here. And if your
manager wants to get a little bit more
aggressive, let me know.
>> I will, sir. Thank you for your phone
call.
>> Thank you.
>> Okay. Bye-bye.
>> Bye-bye. Okay. So, the best deal we have
right now is going to be $1,700
off.
Let's keep going.
>> Thank you for calling.
>> Hi, Hyundai of Vegas. This is Tommy from
buying. How's it going?
>> I'm doing well. How you doing?
>> I'm doing great. I just wanted to see if
you guys have a car available.
>> And which car are you looking at?
>> I have the make, model, VIN. What makes
most sense for you?
>> I'm I'm pretty much uh open. I want a
lot a lot. So, just shoot it to me. Uh
last eight of the VIN is good.
>> Last eight. Okay. Maybe count here. Um I
got a T as in Tom. H is in Hyundai
096540.
>> All right. So, can't find it in that
way. How uh did you see it on our
website?
>> I did see it on the website. Yep.
>> Let me check another way.
>> Sure.
>> Santa Fe calligraphy hybrid allwheel
drive.
>> That's it.
>> Earthy brass.
>> Earthy brass with a pecon
interior.
>> Yeah. Give me one second. I'm going to
actually check the key room just to make
sure it's here. Okay. Can I put you on?
>> Sounds good. I'll be here.
>> All right. Thank you. are here at
Hyundai of both electric and
electrifying. Our EVs represent the
future of driving. Not only do you get
instant torque from the motor, the
battery gives you impressive range up to
303 mi with Ionic 5.
>> Hello. Sorry, I can't get my V's on the
thing.
>> All right. No, you're fine. Uh, that car
should be here in about a about a month.
>> Awesome. Well, that's the one I want.
The peon and the earthy brown. So if we
can create a numbers, I'll put a deposit
on that bad boy.
>> Gotcha. But the only thing is I want to
tell you if it says a month, sometimes
it might take longer. Sometimes it it
might be here sooner. So let me do this.
>> I'm Patient.
>> Okay. And what's your first name again?
>> My first name is Tommy.
>> Last name?
>> Mula. M I K U L A. You're getting a
phone call.
>> Are you related to Ed? My wife.
>> No. No, I'm not. I'm not related to Ed.
I know Ralphie. Does that help?
>> No. Well, I I have a guy named Ed. I
sold him a few cars. He's got the same
last name as you.
>> No, no, Ed. Just Ralphie.
>> Gotcha.
>> He was in a few movies. Good guy.
>> Yeah. I'm just trying to get everything
in here so I can the system. Are you
going to be trading in anything in?
>> No.
>> All right.
>> No trades.
>> Are you looking at cash or fi? Well,
actually, here's the thing. The
incentives might change.
>> Oh, wait. Sorry. My timer went off. Uh,
yeah, I know. It's fine.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah. I mean, I'm just looking for what
kind of price can you do plus rebate or
plus incentive and then whatever the
incentive is. Bada boom, bada bing.
>> Okay. So, what I'll do is I can send you
the price, but I don't have the
incentives for next month. We don't get
them usually until about the second or
third. So, we can do that. Uh, are you a
military uh first responder or anything
of that nature?
>> Nope.
>> Okay. So, are you do you live in Las
Vegas? I I I live in a Torrance,
California, but I just I like to go to
Vegas. So, give me a good reason to go.
>> No, that's fine. I just have to do it
for the taxes.
>> Yeah.
>> What's your zip code?
>> All right, Tommy. What I'm going to do
is uh I'll have my boss uh send you some
information and we'll start it from
there. But he's probably going to send
you with the current. I'll try to tell
him not to. We'll just talk about price.
But whatever incentives and rebates are
happening when you purchase the vehicle,
that's what you're going to get. So, say
for instance, this car comes in December
and they have uh incentives in December.
That's what it's going to be on that
way.
>> No, I get it. I'm totally good with
that. Yeah, I know. This is a color
combo I want. So, I understand it'll be
plus incentive. Hopefully, they keep
their incentives rocking and rolling.
>> Oh, we try to.
>> Yeah. Awesome. Perfect. Great.
>> Okay. I'm going to send you a opt-in
text message so that way we can text
information to you unless you want to
email.
>> No, I don't use email. It's the devil's
work.
>> Okay. So, just say yes to that and I'll
get that the proposal for you and we'll
go from there.
>> Okay. I'm excited.
>> All right, Tommy. Thank you, sir.
>> Thank you. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> Hey, this is Paul.
>> Hey, Paul. This is Tommy.
>> Hey, how you doing, man?
>> Man, I'm living the dream. How about
yourself?
>> I'm trying to do the same thing. Uh, I
see I see your phone says North
Carolina. Is that where you're from?
>> I'm used to be once upon a time.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. I'm from the South. I'm
from Florida. Jacksonville, Florida.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I like
Jacksonville. It's a good area.
>> Yes, sir. So, um I'm hearing you're
trying to get into this particular
calligraphy we have or is it just
>> Yeah, I'm looking for this particular
one.
>> Okay. Um let me ask you a question. Are
you financing paying cash or what?
What's your
>> uh You know, the 0% sounds great. Um but
you know, I can pay cash if I want to,
but the 0%'s enticing.
>> I got you. I got you. Okay. And you were
interested in the 1000,000 mi wraparound
warranty as well?
>> I didn't know anything about that. Oh,
>> okay. I don't know. They just send the
notes. It says uh basically you want
pricing and that you would possibly be
interested in like a so basically we
have a 10 100,000 mi powertrain
warranty. The battery packs covered up
to 120,000 mi per California law. But
you can basically make the whole car 10
or 100,000 mi where the only thing
you're responsible for is tires, brake
pads, windshield wiper blades, uh rubber
belts and hoses, things that are
wearable.
>> Yeah, I'm interested in hearing the
price on it. Sure. I don't Yeah, I
didn't I didn't ask about that, but
sure.
>> Awesome. Um, do you have any other
pricing so far or are you just kind of
reaching out to us?
>> Good question. Yes, I do. I've gotten a
few different people that are giving me
some numbers, but nothing that's wet the
beak yet, if you know what I mean.
>> I got you. I got you. So, let me ask you
this, just cuz I'm I'm pretty simple to
deal with. Where are you technically
trying to be at? Like, what's your
ultimate goal? Because you can't get a
huge cash rebate and the 0%. That's just
not the way Hyundai Motor Finance offers
it. Basically, you know, our best price
would probably be MSRP plus tax tag, you
know, title, things like that. And if
you wanted the warranty, I could show
you that as well. But as far as maybe
they could take some money off, I'm not
quite sure. What What was your best
offer? Cuz I mean, we can either match
or beat it. I mean,
>> I have an offer for three grand off
right now.
>> Okay. And the 0%.
>> And the 0% with no dealer ads.
>> Okay. Who gave you that?
>> Hyundai.
>> Okay. Where where are they at?
>> Uh in Utah. Oh, where are you at? Are
you in California?
>> I'm in LA.
>> Oh, okay. So, you're all over the place.
So, are you gonna go there for a deal? I
only buy a car once in a life, you know.
>> Yeah, I got you. So, you're going to
drive out to Utah if that's the best
offer and drive it back.
>> I don't have to. I'm preferring that I
have to drive to you because you give me
you beat this deal.
>> I got you. I got you. Well, I'm not
going to lie to you, Tom. I mean, when
you're talking about out of state, like
that's a whole different market. So, I
mean, of course, they're they might be
in a smaller market where, you know,
it's just the auto industry is a little
bit different when it comes to that as
far as brand new cars, and those
dealerships, they might not have big
numbers. We're a high volume dealership.
So, we can try to to to meet or or, you
know, come somewhere compatible, but I
mean, are comparable. But, I can talk to
my boss and see where we're at, but with
an out of state offer, we don't really,
you know, we beat or match something
locally. But, yeah, let me see. I mean,
it's the end of the month. Who knows?
Obviously, we're close. We'll save you a
trip and a flight and gas and all that
time. So, let me see what we can do and
then I'll give you a shot back. How's
that sound?
>> Yeah, sounds great. Yeah, I said I know
you guys are a big dealership, which is
why I want to do business with you.
>> I got you. And uh quick question. This
is your cell phone. I can call you back
on this, right?
>> Yeah, cell phone call, text.
>> All right, cool. All right. Yeah, give
me a minute, Tom, and I'll I'll figure
it out for you. Okay.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> Yeah.
>> Why?
>> I will say this costume, actually, it's
not even a costume. I'm dressed for
success.
Hyundai dealer. Come visit us at our
newly remodeled dealership at
in California. Please press three to
speak with our sales department. Press
four to schedule an appointment for
service.
[Music]
>> It's a great day at How can I help you
today?
>> I would like to buy a car.
>> Okay. I understand you're interested in
buying a car. Would you like to speak
with someone in our sales department to
get started?
>> I would like to speak to somebody in
your sales department to buy a car.
>> Would you like me to connect you to our
sales department now?
>> Yes, please connect me.
>> One moment, please.
>> That was the best AI assistant they've
ever had.
>> It's a great day at How can I help you
today?
>> Buy car.
>> Okay. It sounds like you're interested
in buying a car. Are you looking to
schedule a test drive or do you have
questions about a specific vehicle?
>> Questions specific vehicle.
>> Sure, I'd be happy to help. What
specific vehicle would you like to know
more about?
>> Hyundai Santa Fe.
>> Are you interested in scheduling a test
drive for a Santa Fe on Monday or do you
have a specific question about the Santa
Fe?
>> Specific question on Santa Fe,
>> of course. What would you like to know
about the Santa Fe
>> price?
>> Sorry, I don't have that information.
Would you like to speak to someone in
sales who can help with Santa Fe
pricing?
>> Yes.
>> One moment, please.
[Music]
It's a great day at How can I help you
today?
>> Operator,
>> what would you like help with today?
>> one moment, please.
>> Thank you for calling. This is Connie.
How may I help you?
>> Can I speak to somebody in new car
sales?
>> Sure. One moment.
[Music]
>> Do I give up? Do I just give up? Is that
what we're going to do? Can we just give
up? Keep holding cuz I'm trying to
hippity hop into some deals.
[Music]
>> Thank you for calling. This is Moses.
How may I help you?
>> Hey, Moses. This is Tommy. How's it
going?
>> I'm good. How are you?
>> I'm doing just dandy. Uh, I just want to
see if you guys have a car available.
>> Perfect. Give me one second. Got to get
my computer up and running. It shuts off
every few seconds. Oh, it shuts off
every few seconds. You probably should
get a new computer.
>> No, it locks. Locks every 10 minutes.
So, you step away for a second, it locks
on you. Got to get back in.
>> Oh, okay. Makes sense.
>> And that phone number you're calling
from, is that
>> That's it.
>> All right. Can I ask what vehicle were
you looking for?
>> Yeah, I have a I have the last six of
the VIN if that helps. I have What do
you want?
>> The year, the name of the vehicle, the
model. 2026 Hyundai Santa Fe hybrid
calligraphy.
>> Good choice.
>> Thank you. I My mom always said I made
good choices.
>> I want you to know that I did think that
was funny. I was just too distracted to
give you a response. So, I was not
ignoring the funny thing you just said.
>> No, no, you're good. Most people don't
laugh when a man's calling you in a
bunny onesie, but you know.
>> Are is that what you're in? A bunny
onesie? It's weird to ask somebody what
they're wearing.
>> Okay.
Well, did you see that online when you
look at it?
>> I did. Yeah. On the auto hyundai.com.
[Music]
>> All right. One second. So, what I'm
going to do, I'm going to step away real
quick. I got your phone number down. Let
me shoot you a quick text so you got it.
And I'll just call you. I'm going step
outside and take a look through our lot.
And I'm going just send you some photos
of our options. And from there, I'll
just call you after. All right.
>> Okay. Sounds good. Perfect. Let me
double check. Make sure you got my phone
number.
>> Okay, that's it. Hang on a second.
>> Go touch the car.
>> All right. Let me know if you got that.
Your first and last name.
>> This is Moses. Yep. I'm texting Moses.
Hi, Moses.
>> H. So, when I search your name, I got
your full name.
>> Sorry.
>> I got your full name.
>> My full name? Like my legal name?
>> Yeah, your first and last name.
>> It's uh Thomas Lav Makula.
>> You spell that? Ooh. The last name
>> M I K U L A.
>> U R A. Oh, your name is one of those
names that sound more difficult than
they actually are.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I
>> was like, how do I spell that? All
right. I'll be reaching out to you soon.
>> Okay.
>> Bye.
Okay. Let's I'm looking for another car.
Car. Car. I'm looking for another car.
This dealership. I like I like this
deal. I like this deal already. Let's
just get to a little bit more off. Wow.
Take Oh my god. It's the hunt for the
red tag October. Now just hunt for the
red I got to hunt for the red tag
savings event. If I find the red tag, I
get an extra two grand off.
>> Thank you for calling. This is Vanessa.
How may I help you?
>> I know. Hello. Vanessa, are you in new
car sales?
>> Yeah, I'm in. Yes. Yes, I am.
>> Awesome. Awesome. I just want to first
off see if you guys are have a car
available.
>> Yes, sir. Can you do you have the stock
number or would you like to give me the
>> Yeah, I do. It's C as in cat 75634.
>> C75634.
Okay, let me pull that up. One second.
What type of vehicle is it?
>> It is going to be a Hyundai Santa Fe
hybrid calligraphy.
>> Okay, one moment. Can I get your name
just in case we get disconnected? Yeah,
my name is Tommy.
>> Okay. Can I put you on hold for two
minutes to look?
>> Yeah, totally fine.
>> Okay, one moment.
>> I'll hop through every dealership in
America. That's what it takes. If you
guys don't know, my name's Tommy. I
negotiate car deals for a living. But
for the month of November, I am giving
you guys the special of a lifetime
because I will be streaming five five
days a week. For the month of November,
all November, I'll be streaming five
days a week. We're going to be doing
guest negotiations where people come on
to the stream and negotiate. We're going
to do live consults. We're going to do a
lot of live negotiations. Juliana just
saw the costume for the first time. Oh
god. 5 days a week all month of
November. All month. Bada boom. Bada
bing. Juliana.
>> Um, yes, we do have that specific
vehicle. I actually have the keys right
now.
>> Hop, hop, hippity hop. I love it. Uh, I
just wanted to first off, it looks like
I clicked on it and it said this one was
qualifying for the red tag sales event,
which means give me two grand off
additional. Is that correct?
>> Yes.
>> So that this is 44355.
So $5,200 off.
>> Yes, if it's the red tag. Absolutely.
>> Bada boom, bada bing. I'll buy it right
now. Send me over the paperwork,
Captain.
>> Okay. Um, I will just need to collect a
little bit of information from you. Hold
on one second.
>> Yeah, just text me over the numbers
first. That'd be great.
>> Okay. Can I get your full name first? Is
that all right?
>> Full name. Uh, Tommy Mucula. M I K U L
A.
>> Okay. And how do you spell your first
name?
>> It's first name. Tommy. T O M Y.
>> Okay. I'll get those numbers right over
to you.
>> Oh, actually, let me get your uh email
address so I can
>> just text him. I don't use email. It's
the devil's work.
>> Text. Okay. Sounds good.
>> All right.
>> All right. Talk to you soon. Bye-bye.
>> All right. Bye.
>> We're We're not even going to mess with
this one. It's not going to be the
easiest sale in the world because she's
going to have thousands of dollars of
add-ons. Silly Wabbit. Rebates are for
people. My name is Tommy and I don't
always dress like this, but I do dress
like this on special occasions and I run
a company called Delivered. We negotiate
car deals for a living. My goal, time,
energy, and anxiety. That's what we save
you. We save you money, but that's a
product. Buy a product. I charge a flat
fee of a,000 bucks. I handle everything
for you. Price a car, trade add-ons,
accessories. You sit back, relax, and
sometimes watch me do this in a bunny
costume. Cuz guess what? Halloween has
never looked so good. And I have more
candy in the other room than I know what
to do with.
[Music]
I heard the phone.
>> I heard the phone. Sorry, it seems like
I'm out of breath, but I'm just in a
bunny costume. What's up?
>> So, yeah, I did a lap a lap around in my
uh lot. We will We have a few 26 uh
calligraphies, hybrid calligraphies in
the lot. Would you come thinking about
coming in today or tomorrow to come test
drive them?
>> Wait, I've already driven one. I already
know I want it. I I just need the one I
was looking for.
>> Okay, perfect. Which one? the the the
one I gave you the stock number of
earlier. Uh,
>> repeat. Can you give that to me one more
time?
>> Great question. Give me a second. Let me
get back to it. It's a brown on brown.
I'll find it. Don't worry. Calligraphy.
>> I think I'm looking at it right now.
>> Wow. Uh, yeah. Brown on brown. 9775 bin.
>> Give the full VIN or the full stock.
>> Sure, I can give you the full VIN.
>> Perfect.
>> It's five in new. M is in Mexico. P is
in Peter. Five. D is in dog. G is in
Gary. 1 six T is in Tommy. H is in hop.
096775. Okay, that was fast. Yes, sir.
>> Go slower. I can go slower.
>> It's currently in. Give me Let me double
check financing. Perfect. Yeah, it's in
the lot. Were you coming in?
>> I already know. I want it. I just need
numbers on it. Remember we talked about
all this.
>> Oh, you didn't mention you wanted
numbers. I'll go out there.
>> Oh, you want Let me No, you're fine. I'm
going to go out there, put it together.
Just a rough ballpark. Were you thinking
about when you want numbers? Were you
thinking about financing or just paying
cash?
>> Financing. 0%. 0% APR.
>> Yeah.
>> 0% APR.
And so the 0% APR is for qualified
customers. Typically, um, you're not
calling me with a negative 300 credit
score, right?
>> Is that possible? Is that a negative
300?
>> No, I'm just being sarcastic. But well,
obviously, you know, you know, just
making sure people are aware if you come
in 0% APR, very available for qualified
customers. We can work with that.
Theoretically though, off the top of my
head, um, or top of your head, what
number were you looking to stay around?
So, I can get numbers together, but if
you give me a target, I can get to my
manager to look for to get some rain for
>> like like what kind of payment discount?
What What were we saying?
>> What were you looking to get to outside
the door?
>> I don't know what the out the door would
be, but I'm looking for a I'm looking
for a 3750 discount plus rebate if
there's any rebate. I don't think
there's any rebate on 0%. So, 3750 plus
rebate. If there's any rebate, I'll take
it. Can you give me that deal and I'm
all yours?
>> All right,
>> I'll hop on over there right now.
>> Perfect. Um, 0% APR financing. I'm
trying to think if I had any questions I
can definitely ask. Uh, if you're
financing typically, what would you be
looking at for term length or what would
you looking for? Whatever 0% monthly
payment.
>> Okay. And for target monthly payment,
what what you want to say?
>> A million dollars a day. I don't It
doesn't matter. Like I'm pay I can pay
cash if I want to. I'm just taking the
0% because it's free money.
>> Perfect. So, the out the door is your
real concern.
>> Yep. Correct.
>> All right. So, I'm gonna get that over
to you right now.
>> Okay. I'm gonna I'll be I'll be all
yours. I'm waiting for your phone call.
>> Oh, yeah. Okay. I'm gonna be right with
you.
>> Okay. Bye.
>> Tommy, here.
>> Hey, Tommy. This is Vanessa.
>> Um, I was just giving you a call back to
get a little bit of information that uh
my management needs. Um, are you located
in Colorado Springs?
>> I am not.
>> No. Okay. Where are you guys located?
Torrance.
>> Lawrence.
>> Torrance.
>> Torrance. Is that in Colorado?
>> Nope.
>> Okay. Where is that?
>> California.
>> Okay. All right. And so you would like
you'd probably like the vehicle shipped.
>> I I'd be open to driving out there and
picking it up, but I'm also open to
shipping it. Whatever makes the most
sense.
>> Okay.
>> But I I've done that before. I'm
familiar with shipping cars, so I'm a
pro.
>> Okay. So, um, let me see here. Do you
have a trade in?
>> Uh, nope. No trade.
>> Okay. No trade. And it's gonna be your
daily driver.
>> Yep. We'll be the daily driver. I don't
I don't make enough money to have two
cars.
>> Okay. For sure. I'm sorry. Do you have
do you have a couple minutes to ask to
answer?
>> Sure. I have all the time in the world.
I'm all yours.
>> Okay. Excellent. Okay. So, let's see
here. Um and would it be would you be
doing financing or cash?
>> 0%.
>> Okay. All right. Can I please get your
address?
>> I can give you my zip code.
>> Okay.
>> We just met.
>> Okay. Okay. Well, I need your address so
that we can get the um the taxes correct
and you know the numbers to get the
right the right
>> is my zip. That should get you pretty
close. I don't like everybody know where
my hole is.
>> Yeah. No, I get that. Colorado and
Torrance. Oh, no. California Torrance.
Okay. All right. Okay. And where can I
get your social security?
>> Whoa. Holy moly. We just met.
>> Oh, well, you want the vehicle, right?
We need to And we're going to be doing
financing.
>> Okay. Um, driver, can I get your
driver's license number?
>> Wait, why do you need all this to give
me the numbers?
>> Okay, I'll try I'll try and get you some
numbers first and then we can go ahead
and run the credit then. Is that is that
okay?
>> Yeah, I mean, yeah, let's uh we we
haven't gotten through the I need to
verify the deal first. If the deal is
real and it's all there, then sure,
we'll get you everything we need.
>> Absolutely. Okay. All right. I'll go
ahead and tell them that and I'll give
you a call back soon.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> All right. Thanks. Bye-bye.
>> Bye. We're getting a phone call. I'm
going to hop on this call. This is
Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. This is Tyrese.
>> Harry.
>> Tyrese from Hyundai.
>> Oh, okay. How's it going?
>> It's going well. I can't see you in the
numbers because you haven't opted into
the text messaging.
>> Wait, wait. I haven't opted in the text.
One second. I'm going through Paul.
Nope. Wrong one. I'm looking. I'm
looking. Can Can you send it again?
>> Yeah, but I have to wait for like four
hours. I'll send it again.
>> Okay. One sec. I'm going through all my
texts. I thought I said I said yes to
all of them, but I'm going I'm going
through every text to see if I missed
one.
That is correct.
>> You know, do you have an iPhone?
>> Uh, no. I don't have an iPhone. That's
the devil's work.
>> So, there's
>> being that we're a company, a lot of our
stuff gets spam blocked. Yeah. So, uh,
give me give me the system a little bit
and it'll it'll let me, uh, text you
again and I'll get those information to
you.
>> Okay. I said yes to everything I can
find. So, if I have a yes, I said yes to
it. So,
>> I got you.
>> Can you tell me the numbers over the
phone? Well, actually, I just left the
hospital when I got to work and I'm
going right back. So, I'm working while
I'm driving to the hospital.
>> I can have one of the guys I don't know.
Uh I'll have one of the guys at work uh
just go over everything with you and
I'll have a call because I'm I'm on my
way. I'll try and get my manager to send
it. But, uh I'll have him uh reach out
to you and go from there.
>> Yeah, that'd be great. Yeah. I mean,
hopefully you're okay.
>> I'm getting a little older, so you know,
things aren't what they used to be.
>> Yeah. No, absolutely. I appreciate you
calling me back, but yeah, go take care
of yourself.
>> All right. Uh, let me reach out to one
of the guys and they'll they'll give you
a call. Okay.
>> Okay. Yeah, no problem.
>> All right. Thank you, sir.
>> Here's the thing. Honestly, guys, I've
called all the dealerships that make
sense in this deal. Getting a phone
call.
>> This is Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. I just want to touch base
with you. I got the numbers pulled up
here out the door. You're looking at 55
326.
>> Whoa. Oh jeez. Tell me to shoot my eye
out. What in the world? Where? Where?
Where? 65.
>> 55.
>> 55. Okay. Geez. Okay, that's good.
>> Okay. So, what's the what's the selling
price of the car
>> out the door? Oh, for MSRP is 51.
>> 51. So, you guys are just selling it for
MSRP,
>> right? So, MSRP we're at 51 price 48
350. Uh auto savings. Right now, we're
at 2,800 for a discount taken off. That
37 you you're looking for isn't
compatible with the 0% APR.
>> Okay. So, if you're at $2,800 off, how
do we get back to 55?
>> Vehicle selling price.
>> Yeah. Help me understand how I got to
55.
>> Give me one second. Sorry.
>> No, you're good.
>> A few moments later.
>> How you doing, Tommy? My name is Keith.
I'm one of the sales managers.
>> Oh, I'm doing well. Keith, how are you?
>> Good. I figured I'd go through this. It
was painful to watch there. So, hey, let
me help you out. So, the MSRP is 51185.
I took off 2835 for you. We have a
appearance protection and dent
protection which is $7.49 each. So your
uh vehicle selling price is $498.48.
There's 4,000 in government taxes, a 599
dock fee and about 83
and some change in registration which
gets you to 55 32635.
>> Okay. Well, I appreciate appreciate you
bringing that down. I I was looking to
be closer to like 3500 off with no ads.
I can do the 2835 and take off the 1500
and get you down to uh under 54 at the
0%. I can do that for you, but I can't
get you 35 off.
>> Well, I'm hopping that I can get a
little bit. What about 3250? No ads.
Close it up.
>> Okay, one second. Hold on. Let me um let
me let me call you back. I'm going to
have to push this one up the the ladder
real quick. Uh let me call you back in
like five minutes.
>> All right, sounds good.
[Music]
>> Hello. Hello.
Hey, Thomas. It's Keith.
>> Hey, Keith.
>> Hey, I can't do it. Um, how soon did you
need the car?
>> Sooner or later, but I mean, I'm
technically picky.
>> If I call you back on the first, which
is Saturday, I might be able to do it
Saturday.
>> But then what if the 0%'s gone?
>> That's the only I don't know if the 0%'s
going to be gone or there. That's my
only issue. I don't think they're
changing it. Let me see something.
>> Hold on for me. I'm checking one thing
for you.
>> No, you're fine. This is We're so close.
We can just put this deal together. What
do we got to wait till Saturday? I'm in
a pink bunny costume. Does that help?
>> What?
>> I'm wearing a pink bunny costume. Does
that help?
>> I want to dress up as Colonel Sanders
tomorrow and bring my two dogs in as
chickens.
>> Dude, I'll wear I'll send you the
picture of me in a pink bunny costume.
We get this deal. Just wrap up the 3250.
>> I can't do it.
>> I'll be just It's just like Ralphie, you
know? It's worth that's worth 500 bucks
to put on your wall and make fun of me
all day.
>> I like it. But give me one sec. Hold on.
>> It's like an OF model, you know? I'm
just selling myself.
Okay. So, I just went to Sunday's
website. 0%'s good till November 3rd.
I'll do the 3250 if you do it on
Saturday.
>> Okay. So, can I put a deposit to hold
the card and make sure it doesn't sell?
>> I'll just put a sold sign in and put it
in a hold for you.
>> I just don't want Well, yeah. Okay. Um
3250.
>> Here's the thing. I I don't want to lose
money and it's the end of the month. So,
Saturday is the start of the month.
>> I'll lose money at the start of the
month and you'll still get the 0%.
>> And Okay. Can you just send me that all
down writing so I feel better about it?
But then that's fine. You got it. I'll
send it. I'll have Moses text. I'll
print it out right now and I'll have
Moses text it to you.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> Perfect.
>> All right. Thank you.
>> Thomas, real quick. So, I'm going to put
you in in our system for the appointment
for Saturday. What time that works best?
You a morning person or you
>> uh just put me in for the morning and
we'll figure out the details.
>> Perfect.
So, let's say
>> 10 a.m.
>> 10 a.m. Awesome.
>> Mhm.
>> All right. And I'll text you the rest of
the information later. Give me one
second. All right, got you in Saturday
10:00 a.m. I'll be seeing you soon.
>> Yeah, make sure you send me the numbers
so I feel better about it.
>> All right, perfect. Sounds like a plan.
>> Sounds good.
>> Bye.
>> Okay, bye. Okay, wait. You sent me the
numbers. Um I'm going to like call call
Michael.
Hello.
>> Hello. Can you hear me?
>> Yeah.
>> Hey. Uh so I have another deal. You can
let the
client decide on what they want to do.
It's in Tampa Bay, so a little bit
closer. Arizona, I got him down to 3250
off, but they will only do the deal on
Saturday.
>> Okay. So, he has to have does he have to
be there in contract?
>> That's going to be the next question to
do it if a remote it's they should be
able to do a remote just by I didn't
even ask because it's thing to do things
remote. So, it shouldn't be a big deal.
But the the weird thing is they want to
wait till Saturday. That just throws me
a little bit through a loop. So,
>> okay. I thought you were saying they
wanted to have it done by Friday.
>> No, they No, they have like they will
not do it until Saturday. They're
claiming it's a new they're saying
they're losing too much money and it's a
new month, which technically if it's the
man if it's saying that, but it wouldn't
be a Hyundai thing, but it's I mean I
don't know. You let the client decide.
Otherwise, they can take the Oregon
deal, that's a guarantee.
>> No, absolutely. No, and that's a lot
closer, too.
>> Yeah. Yeah, that one's much closer. In
theory, they can even trade it. So,
because that one's that one's a driving
distance.
>> Okay.
>> Yep. And then Oh, wait. I'll tag you.
Wait, can I tag you? Tag you at Michael.
Yeah, let's see if we can get that one
wrapped up if he's watching the stream.
It's a strong deal. I just He's got to
decide which way he wants to do, but
there's only like two of those. But I
mean, theory people do that, which is a
little bit weird.
>> No. Yeah, I understand. Yeah, he's
looking out for his paycheck sales
manager.
>> Yeah. Yeah, that's exactly what he's
doing. Yeah.
>> All right. Okay, I'll get with him in
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> Thanks.
>> Bye. Okay, so let me explain this real
quick so you guys understand uh so you
guys understand what's going on. So how
sales managers get paid is they get paid
off of gross profit of the entire
dealership, right? So sometimes they
want to sell a car, right, by the end of
the month, which for Hyundai is going to
be the third. But if he takes a loss,
which on paper he might take a loss, he
doesn't want to lose pay his paycheck
for November. So he's trying to get a
unit for this month while not hurting
his paycheck for October. That's not how
it works. It depends on your store, but
100% that's how it works. 100% that's
how it works. Hyundai's sales cycle is
different than the dealership sales
cycle. Bada boom, bada bing. Happy
Halloween to everybody. And I'm going to
hop on out of here. I'll give you guys
the hop. Okay.
I still have to come back. I have to
come back, right? I've got to come back
to turn off the stream. So,
[Music]