for me to discount the truck. I I just I
don't have I don't I don't have it to do
that.
>> Well, would somebody that's shopping
your numbers not be a serious buyer? I
mean, I'm I'm not worried about you guys
hiding anything. I've never once claimed
that. I'm more just asking, is this the
best price you can do? If not, no big
deal. It doesn't hurt my feelings if
that's the best you can do.
>> So, right here, you're not Don't Don't
insult me, man. You're not Nissan.
Nissan is not taking any of your money
away with that $3,500 discount. You're
not losing money to give me a rebate.
That's Let's not be a Don't don't insult
me.
>> I don't know what you want me to do. I
don't know if you're just bored and
you're playing games. I don't know what
you're doing. I I don't know. Like you
you sound like you're very schooled in
this. Like then you should I don't know
what to do. I'm not frustrated. I've
been doing this for 21 years. I'm not
frustrated at all. Hypothetically, I
mean I get that's why I don't want to
give you a number. I don't know.
>> Plus rebates.
>> I am the manager.
>> You're the manager. You are the manager.
>> I am the manager. Yes, I am, sir.
>> What manager are you? You've been there
for 20 something years and you're a
manager and you don't know who prices
your inventory. So, so you're saying you
guys don't ever take deposits on
inventory on the way?
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. So, we're looking for a Frontier
Pro 4X.
I can see why she red. There's only 15
of these reds. 57 of the black ones.
Okay. I can see why she hired us. Proex
convenience package. Now, there's 42 of
these options. Okay. This dealership's
advertising $3,500 off. That's not a bad
deal to start the gate, but obviously we
want more.
Hello.
>> Hi. How's it going?
>> It's going. How you doing?
>> Hey, I'm doing well. I just wanted to
see if you guys have a car available.
>> Absolutely. Let me check that for you.
What are you looking for?
>> Yep. I have a stock number whenever
available.
>> Okay. One second. Okay. What's the
stock?
>> Stock number n is in Nancy. 909-525.
>> 909-525.
Let me check the key box for you.
>> Sure.
>> Yes, it's still available actually.
>> Awesome. Perfect. Well, I've already
driven it. Already know I love it. Want
more of it. really just trying to get
some awesome pricing and I'm calling the
best dealership I've known.
>> Okay. Um, do you have any time to stop
by the dealership to see the vehicle and
then we can run some numbers for you?
>> Um, well, I do I have time? Yes. Uh, do
I want to do that? No.
>> I mean, I'll be completely honest with
you. From what we normally see with, you
know, people not wanting to stop by or
just trying to get numbers over the
phone is they're shopping us. And we
don't normally get the person in after
giving them numbers. That's why we
normally try to get our customers in
just to make sure you know you're
actually serious about the vehicle and
then we can do the best on pricing that
we can do for you.
>> Well, would somebody that's shopping
your numbers not be a serious buyer?
>> Oh yeah, it's constant. We see it left
and right to be honest with you. Where
you located? Are you not close to
Milford?
>> I'm a mass. I'm I'm not too far, but I'm
looking for this particular color combo
and I don't want to drive all the way to
your dealership just to get numbers. I'm
guessing when people come to your
dealership, they probably also leave
too, right? It's not You guys probably
don't have a 100% close rate.
>> No, we don't. You don't have 100%
closed, but the numbers are definitely
more and I'll say that when people
actually come to the dealership. Let me
ask you though, what are you looking to
do? Finance or um lease or cash buy?
>> Yeah, I'm open to financing, open to
paying cash, whatever makes the most
sense.
>> Okay. All right. So, let me get your
information. I'll take your full name,
phone number, and get the numbers over
to you. What are you, if you're looking
for a finance position, what are you
doing for a down payment?
>> Five $10,000 down, but more more worried
about obviously the out the door as we
know.
>> Absolutely. Okay. Um, let me get your
first name.
>> Tommy.
>> Okay. And Tommy, your last name.
>> Makula. M I K U L A.
>> Okay. Tommy. And your phone number,
please.
>> Phone number is going to be Are you
ready for it?
>> All righty. And uh you just want the out
of the door numbers, right?
>> Correct.
>> Okay, you got it. I'll um speak to my
sales manager and then I'll get that
over to you as soon as possible.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> All right, Tommy. I'll shoot you a text
first so you have my contact
information.
>> Okay, sounds good. Bye. All right, bye.
Is it Tom?
>> Hey Tom, this is Tom. What are the
chances?
>> What are the chances?
>> Hey man, I just want to see if you guys
have a car available.
>> What? Which car?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Yeah, that helps.
>> Yeah. 105724.
>> Let me check that out for you. Where you
calling from?
>> From Massachusetts.
>> Interesting. Okay.
>> I like New York. Is that a problem?
>> Is it a pre-owned or a new?
>> Brand new.
>> Gotcha. You have questions on it?
>> First off, is it available?
>> Yes, it is.
>> Awesome. Perfect. Yep.
>> The uh the gray pro 4x.
>> Yep. With a six foot bed.
>> Yes.
>> Yep. Perfect. That's exactly what I'm
looking for. Um I already driven one.
Already fell in love with it. I know
exactly what I want. Ready to buy one
today. We can agree to numbers.
>> Okay. What do you have a trade in? Do
you have anything?
>> Nope. No trade. Financing the car, but
open to paying cash if the deal gets
better.
>> Well, we do what we are is internet
based pricing. That's why we're drawing
phone calls from all over. So it's uh
the nice thing about this it does have
uh it's already discounted 1,753
and then there is a rebate for 3500. So
if you factor that in final price right
now is that it was at 48710 it's now at
43457.
>> Okay. You guys can't do any better than
that is what you're saying.
>> Yeah. I mean it's already we're already
knocking over 5,000 off right there.
>> I know but 3500 of it's Nissan's money
not your money. So
>> right
>> and Nissan are struggling. What would I
mean?
>> All right, we're doing very well, but I
mean what what are you looking to do?
>> Uh I was hoping to get closer to about
8% off MSRP plus rebate.
>> I don't know if that's going to happen.
Are you looking to finance? What what
are you uh
>> hoping to finance in cash?
>> Yeah, I'm where we get our money from.
Is uh the same place. Uh are you in the
area at any time soon?
>> Uh I can be in the area once we agree
numbers. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Right now we we try to have
everything online so that we're not
hiding anything from the customers. We
don't we don't inflate to try to talk
down.
>> I appreciate that. I've read deals on
Nissan right now. I know that you said
they're not hurting, but I know that
I've read a lot of things about Nissan
being like on the verge of bankruptcy
and doing whatever they can to sell
cars, but maybe I just called the one
dealership that it's a it's a Nissan hot
market.
>> Yeah. No, we're doing very well.
>> Okay.
>> It's just like I said, it's we what
we're trying to do once again is is just
uh be upfront with everybody. We're not
we're not we don't inflate to try to let
let the customer talk down. We just put
the best price out there.
>> I I appreciate that. I just I' I've seen
better deals online. So, it doesn't I
appreciate you guys just making it easy
on the lower discount to give somebody
something, but I'd be looking for a
little bit bigger bigger of a discount.
So, if you can't do that, no big deal.
I'll uh uh I must have called the one
market that has a hot Nissan market. No,
no big deal.
>> Like I said, if if you're interested,
you know, we're definitely we're
definitely willing to uh work with you,
but what you're asking is a lot is is
way way off. I don't know if I'm asking
what's way off to be able to do it, but
it I imagine I'll find that deal.
>> Yeah. No, what I'm saying of what we can
do, you know, it's uh it's not uh you
know, we don't have that we don't have
that kind of money built into the price
if that's what you're asking.
>> Okay. Yeah. I mean, well, I guess what's
the best I mean, you said the internet
pricing is where you're at. So, like I'm
I'm not here to like I said, I'm just
looking for a competitive deal in the
Northeast and there's about eight of
these trucks in the Northeast. So, I'm
calling around the eight ones that make
sense for me, call it a day. So, if
that's the best you can do, no big deal.
I know Nissan is has it for two grand
off. So I mean that's just their
internet price.
>> Yeah, like I said, I don't know if they
inflate, but I know that it's internet
based. So where we arrive at that price
is based on the average of uh all the
all the exact same vehicle in our area.
I believe in a 250 to 300 mile radius.
>> Okay. But if people aren't just
inflating the price to discount it and
that's what other people are doing,
would that really be a fair assessment
of the market?
>> Well, like I said, I I don't know if
that's what they're doing, but like you
know, talking, you know, what we're
trying to do is internet based. We don't
try to hide anything. We don't try to
inflate the price. We don't try to do
anything. Everything is right there
right I'm not that's I'm not worried
about you guys hiding anything. I've
never once claimed that. I'm more just
asking is this the best price you can
do. If not, no big deal. It doesn't hurt
my feelings if that's the best you can
do. But yeah, I don't do what I'm
looking for.
>> What are you looking Are you looking for
a monthly payment or you just just So
Oh, yeah. So I don't Like I said, I I
don't know. Is is there a a price you're
trying to get to?
>> 8% off plus rebate
>> and a number 8% plus the rebate.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. That's that's I don't you know
that's something with the general
manager you know and I think that's uh
>> dude should I go talk to him?
>> I can put you on hold and ask you know
>> I mean I mean you're just the guy that I
want to talk to. I mean I'd love to talk
to you all day. You seem like a great
guy but but realistically if he's the
one he go to the No. He would just go to
the owner and
>> basically know what they're going to say
but like I said I could uh but if you
want to hold I could talk to him really
quick.
>> Sure. I'll go talk to the owner. talk
to.
>> No, I said I'll go talk to the general
manager and see what he says. Okay, hold
on one second. Okay.
>> Okay,
>> hold on.
>> Meanwhile,
>> he said he said absolutely nowhere. Best
price is right there.
>> Best price right there. Okay. So, I will
just call which is in your 250 mi radius
and less of a price.
>> Yes.
>> Good talking to you. Tire general
manager. I said hi.
>> I will. Okay. Take care. Byebye.
>> Bye.
>> Thank you for calling.
>> My name is Mark. How can I help you?
>> Hey Mark, are you in sales? I'm in the
Mrs. Velment Center. I might be able to
help you out.
>> Uh, okay, cool. Uh, first off, I just
want to see if you guys have a car
available.
>> Sure. Was it Bown or a new vehicle?
You're
>> brand new.
>> All righty. And do you have a stock
number or a model?
>> I do. S is in Subaru. N is in Nissan.
652155.
>> That looks like a 2025 ProX Frontier.
>> Yep.
>> Look into this for a customer earlier. I
just don't know if they set an
appointment or not.
>> No, you're good.
>> Yeah, it does look like it's still
available. Um, did you have some
additional questions? Were you hoping to
come check it out? How can I help you?
>> Well, I've already driven one. Already
know I love it. This is the car I need.
Uh really just trying to get the best
pricing on it.
>> Okay. Do you have um anything you're
replacing or anything like that? Or is
it just kind of a fresh vehicle?
>> Fresh vehicle. All righty. We'll just
need to collect a little bit of
additional information from you if
that's okay.
>> That's fine.
>> All right. Awesome. Let me start with
your name.
>> Uh Tommy.
>> Tommy. Great to speak to you today. And
what's your last name, Tommy?
>> Uh Makula. M I K U L A.
>> Right. And what's your zip code, Tommy?
>> Uh the zip code that I'd be registering
the car in? Yes.
>> Yes. Uh the zip code is going to be
Massachusetts.
>> Gotcha. And what kind of pricing were
you looking for? Were you looking to
lease the vehicle? Were you hoping to
purchase it?
>> Looking to finance or pay cash? One of
the two.
>> All right. And you're positive this
vehicle has all the features you're
looking for. Is the right one?
>> It's the right one. I looked at the
window sticker. I looked at the
pictures. It's the dream.
>> Perfect. Just wanted to make sure. All
righty. I mean, I think that's really
all the info I need other than, you
know, maybe what your timeline is like.
When were you, you know, provided the
right deal comes along? When were you
hoping to pick it up?
>> Today. Tomorrow.
>> Today. Tomorrow. ASAP. Okay.
>> Mhm.
>> We love to hear it.
>> Thank you.
>> And is this the best number for you,
Tommy?
>> Correct. That's the best number.
>> Okay. And just so I know, is that a
number that's a a mobile number or is
that a home number?
>> That's a mobile number. People still
have home phones.
>> You You'd be surprised. I dial a lot of
numbers a day and a lot of them sound
like normal normal home phone numbers.
So, it's very strange. And I do have two
numbers in the profile, so some people
are still doing it. Nope, not for me.
>> I agree with you. I think it's wild. All
right, let me get this over to the sales
team and someone should be able to reach
out to you relatively soon. Is it okay
if they just give you a call back right
here?
>> Yeah, that'd be great.
>> Okay, awesome. And as far as credit goes
or anything like that, is there any, you
know, um, hurdles we'd have to jump?
>> Unless Perfect Credit has a hurdle, then
no.
>> I mean, the only hurdle is just not
giving the thing to you. So, let me go
ahead and get this,
>> let me get this information over to
sales. the sales team, they should be
able to work up a proposal and have
someone reach out to you. So, just be on
the lookout for a phone call from a
number you're not super familiar with.
Okay,
>> got it. I'll answer all stranger dangers
today.
>> Perfect. Thanks, Tommy. Appreciate you.
>> No problem. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> Thank you for calling. How can I help
you?
>> Hey, I just want to see if you guys have
a car available.
>> Sure. Is it new or used?
>> It's brand new.
>> Brand new. Do you happen to have a stock
number available?
>> I do. It's S is in Subaru. N is in
Nissan. 632630.
>> Is it a Nissan or a Cadillac?
>> Nissan.
>> A Nissan. All right. That's why I didn't
find it. It was 25 Frontier.
>> 25 Frontier Crew Cab Pro 4X Long Bed.
>> Yes, I am showing it is still available.
>> Awesome. Perfect. Well, I've already
driven one. Already know I love it.
Really just trying to get the best
possible pricing. And I've heard there's
nobody better to call but Pine Belt.
>> Absolutely. Let me re Have you been to
our location before?
>> I have not.
>> All right. So, let me just get a little
information. and I'll have a sales
manager reach out to you. What is first
name, last name, best phone number?
>> First name Tommy, last name Makula. The
best number is 98.
>> Are you looking to lease finance? What
are you looking to do?
>> Open to finance, open to bank cash.
>> All right, so let me see what I can do.
I will have someone give you a call back
shortly. It doesn't look like our
showroom's too too busy, so I could
probably get somebody to call you back
real soon.
>> I love it. Can't wait to hear from
somebody.
>> What What is your zip code? My zip code
that I'll be registering the car at is
going to be zero.
>> And that's what's on your driver's
license.
>> Uh, yes, that is
>> perfect. All right, Tommy, let me let me
reach out. I will have a manager give
you a call.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> Thank you.
>> All right, bye.
>> Bye-bye.
>> Hello.
May I help you?
>> Hey, I just want to see if you guys have
a car available.
>> Sure. What car is it?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> What is the stock number? Stock number
is U is in uranium 50441.
>> What vehicle was it?
>> Uh it is a Frontier Pro 4X.
>> Sorry, I I had it 50441.
>> Have you bought and got it?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. So I see that you're interested in
the 2025 Frontier Pro 4X with the crew
cab, the five-seater, right?
>> Correct. Yeah. In the long bed. Yep.
>> Yeah. So you're questioning if it is in
stock, right?
>> Correct. Is it available as the cool
kids would say?
>> Yeah. So, I would have to just Yeah, I
can um double check that for you on the
keyboard if you just give me like 30
seconds to run over.
>> Oh, on the keyboard. Like the board that
has keys, not like the keyboard is in a
piano. I was very uh Yeah, go check go
check the keyboard.
>> I can't check with that keyboard. I have
to check with the other keyboard.
>> Got it. Go check on both keyboards. Let
me know.
>> Okay.
>> Meanwhile,
>> hey there, I'm back.
>> That was fast.
>> Yep. So, I was able to locate the key.
It is for the gray the gunmetal 25
Frontier U50441.
I have the keys. It's currently in our
secondary lot. I can walk over and bring
it over to our main building. Um, when
were you planning on stopping by?
>> Well, I already know I want it. Uh, so
you don't have to do all that. As long
as we agree to numbers, then I can uh
come buy it today, tomorrow. As long as
we agree to numbers.
>> Okay. Um, do you mind if I just get so I
can confirm your number? 98.
Philip, what's yours?
>> My name is Tommy. Nice to meet you,
Philip.
>> Hey, Tommy. Nice meeting you. Um, do you
have an email that I can send all of the
info over to?
>> I don't use email. That's the devil's
work.
>> If you're fine with me just sending
everything through text, I I'll do it
that way then.
>> That's fine.
>> Okay. So, U50441.
All I need now is the zip code that
you're going to register to, just so I
have the accurate taxes.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. The the zip code that
I'll be registering the car in is zero.
I'm assuming you guys are just doing all
this over the phone. You do not have a
trade in.
>> I do not have a trade in. You You got
it. That's a good assumption.
>> I think I have every piece of
information that I have so I can send
over all the details to you. Okay.
>> Okay. Sounds good. I'm super excited to
see the details.
>> All right. I'll uh send them over
quickly your way. Okay. Take care.
>> Sounds good.
>> All right. Take care.
>> Bye.
>> Thank you for calling. Emma Meyer
speaking. Who do I have the pleasure of
speaking with?
>> Hello, this is Tommy Mcculis speaking.
Hi, Tommy. How can I help you?
>> Hey, I just want to see if you guys have
a car available.
>> Okay. Yeah. Do you have the stock number
of the vehicle or the bin?
>> I do. Uh stock number is S is in SAM. N
is in Nissan. 656262.
>> Okay.
All right. Looks like you're looking at
a 25 Nissan Frontier Crew cab pro 4X.
Correct.
>> Wrong bed. Correct.
>> Yes. Yes. Um, it does look like that
vehicle is in transit, so it's actually
not at the dealership yet. Did you want
me to try to find out um when the
arrival date would be or would you be
interested in coming in and speaking
with the salesperson about it?
>> I already know I want this car. I
already driven one, already fell in love
with it. Really just trying to get the
best possible pricing. So, whoever I
need to talk to for that.
>> Okay. All right. Give me one moment
here, sir.
>> Okay.
>> Meanwhile,
>> good afternoon. This is Lance. How can I
help you?
>> Hey, Lance. I was just seeing if you
guys had a car and then getting pricing
on that car. Uh, getting a price on your
car. You said
>> getting a price on a car.
>> Yeah. Yeah. What you got?
>> Do you need a stock number?
>> Uh, yes sir.
>> Uh, S is in Subaru. N is a Nancy.
656262.
>> I don't Our stock numbers don't start
with SN. I don't know what that would
be.
>> I'm I'm going to call I'm going to call
some BS on something cuz I just talked
to somebody. Gave them all this
information. They confirmed the car.
Confirmed the thing. Said, "Hey, can I
transfer you to a salesperson?" Yes, I
can. Bada boom, bada bing. Here I am.
says SN656262.
I'm just saying here it says it's in
transit though. We don't have it. Yeah,
that's part of that's probably like the
last eight of the VIN. I can double
check to see when that vehicle is going
to be here.
>> Yeah, but as a consumer I see the word
stock number and that's what it says.
>> Yes, sir. I just didn't realize that it
was it in transit. I didn't realize that
was going on. It's the last of the VIN.
Our stock numbers start with NT 25 NT.
So, I just apologize. It just threw me a
curveball there.
>> I can let you know when we're going to
get that vehicle, though. Give me one
moment here. That's totally fine.
>> So that would be 6262. It says it's on
hold since production month was June.
It's saying that vehicle is on hold. So
some vehicles will tell us what date
they're showing up. I know it goes back
to this one says on hold. So I wouldn't
have an answer to when we were going to
get that one. I just got on the Nissan's
website and uh look at the last of the
VIN. Um I have the invoice and stuff
like that in the MSRP. I just don't have
a date that it'll be here. Okay.
>> Just says hold. How how long does holds
normally last?
>> I I have no idea honestly. It could be I
can't really give you an answer. It
could be a week. It could be it just
doesn't even have a status like if it's
invoice in transit if it's in the port
uh being built. I mean it clearly was
built in June. It just doesn't give me a
time frame on hold. Hold could be I I
don't really have an answer. Could be a
month, could be two months.
>> Okay. I'm assuming can you do pricing on
a car that isn't that have an ETA? I'm
not in a rush for that car.
>> Yeah. I don't have any way to I mean I
have the MSRP here. It's uh what the
it's 47280
and then our discount of 3500. So it' be
43,780 is what I have.
>> Is that 3500 your discount or the
rebate?
>> That's the customer cash rebate.
>> Okay. So there So are you guys doing a
discount at all on the car
>> right now? No. There was discount for
last month. We don't have any discounts
on the vehicle this month. It just ended
on July 31st was the last for the for
the discount. So,
>> so you guys don't
they they may No, there's no discount on
this vehicle. We don't even have it to
even discount it.
>> Well, I know, but also you don't know
when it's going to come in. So, like the
idea behind it is maybe get a deal on a
car that could be a day, a week, a
month. I could be waiting seven months
for this car. So, it's kind of you guys
don't know when you can even sell it by
then.
>> Yeah. That's why I don't want to give
you numbers on a car that I don't even
know when I'm going to get it. Whether
the the rebates might change from then
and by next month, Nissan might throw
another $3,000 in rebates at it. So
realistically, if we do the numbers, the
numbers are not might not be the same
from the time today till the vehicle
comes here. We might end up discounting
it once we get the vehicle.
>> I I I know there's a slight difference
between discounts and rebates. I'm not
concerned about the rebate. I'm more
consist or more concerned about the
discount. So uh if you guys there's no
discount on that vehicle.
>> Okay. So you guys just aren't doing any
right now.
>> You guys won't do any discount on the
car is what you're saying.
>> As of right now, I I don't I can't
discount a vehicle that I don't even
have like I can't I don't have it here.
Otherwise, I would I just can't do that.
I just I can discount a car that I don't
have. I don't know when I'm going to get
it. And like I said, the rebates could
change. That $3,500 could I understand
the rebate can change. I understand. But
I buy I buy a lot of cars in life, and
it's weird concept that you couldn't
discount a car that isn't there. It's
the same concept of discounting a car
that is there. It's just putting a T-
sheet together, putting the numbers
down, and saying, "This is what we sell
you the car at, plus rebate."
>> I mean, invoice. I don't even have an
invoice on the car. I don't even have
the vehicle for you. Literally, you
literally I have the picture of the
invoice. When I click on it, it doesn't
have says current ETA hold. It doesn't
have an actual price on it. I have the
MSRP. I don't have the invoice.
>> We'll assume invoice is what 5% back of
MSRP.
>> This amount is due here. This one here
says this amount. So the the MSR or the
dealer invoice on the vehicle is 45,415.
So I'm already below invoice on the
vehicle at that 43,000. So right here in
front of me,
don't don't insult me, man. You're not
Nissan. Nissan is not taking any of your
money away with that $3,500 discount.
Nissan is taking $3500. So, you're not
below invoice when you're discounting it
from rebate.
>> The amount is due on the invoice. I
promise you it's $45,415.
>> Will I fill out an NMAC Nissan rebate
redemption form when I buy this car?
>> Yes.
>> So, and that rebate says that Nissan
will be paying you guys the rebate and
you guys will be taking it off the car.
So, Nissan is paying you that 3500. So,
you're not losing money to give me a
rebate. That's Let's not be a Don't
Don't insult me,
>> sir. I don't know what we're doing here.
I don't have the truck, sir. I'm trying
to give you the information that I have
right now on it. I can't discount a
vehicle that I don't have. I don't even
know. You know what I mean? Like, you're
I have the invoice here. It says 4514.
We're selling it cheaper than what the
invoice price is. I don't know what you
want me to do. I don't know if you're
just bored and you're playing games. I
don't know what you're doing. I I don't
know. Like, you you sound like you're
very schooled in this. Like, then you
should I don't know what to do. I don't
have the truck. I don't know when the
truck is going to be here. It's below
invoice what we're selling the truck
for. So, for me to discount the truck, I
I just I don't have I don't I don't have
it to do that.
>> So, so you know the the slight
frustration, just do me a favor. Go
listen to your BDC. Go listen to me give
all the information to my BD BDC and
then watch me get transferred to you and
then it's a it's a cold transfer as if
you never heard from me. So, I wasted 5
minutes of my life to give her all this
information, tell me the car was
available, tell me we could get pricing
on it, then get to you.
>> Should have never told you that it was
available. should have never told you
that. So that
>> she did tell me that.
>> I can tell you that it's on hold. That
that she said that it was on hold.
>> No, she told me it was available.
>> That's what I'm saying. But BDC
shouldn't be doing that. They don't have
access to the Nissan.
>> How is that my problem? How is that my
problem as a consumer? Like you just
>> It's not your It's not your problem. I
can't discount a vehicle that I don't
have. I'm not frustrated, sir. I'm not
frustrated. I've been doing this for 21
years. I'm not frustrated at all. I'm
just trying to figure out what you're
trying to to get out of me that I can't
give you. You're trying to get a price
of a truck that I don't have that's
already below invoice. I can't I can't
do that.
>> It's more than at this point that's just
the insulting to ask. You're not selling
this car below invoice by giving a
rebate. You're not losing. If you sold
this car MSRP minus rebate, you were not
below invoice on the car. That is not
how that works. And you know that.
>> I was telling you what the invoice was.
I didn't say that. I said what the
invoice the question by saying invoice
by by saying you're selling it below
invoice you are implying you are losing
money to sell this car that is what is
implied
>> we are losing money on every new vehicle
that we sell here we lose between $2 and
$3,000 on these frontiers every one we
sell so yeah we do lose $2 to $3,000 on
and that's not your problem it's
actually a great problem because that's
why people are buying them but we lose
$2 to $3,000 on each frontier deal that
we sell so I definitely miss our fee
>> no below invoice
>> okay so you I don't know what we're just
We're just going around the ring here,
sir. I I don't know what to do. I don't
know what more. I don't have the truck.
I cannot discount the truck for you. I
don't know when the truck is going to be
here. I can take your name and number
when I know the truck's going to be
here. I will gladly let you know and
then I would be able to do some numbers
on the truck. I can't do numbers on a
truck that when those things can change.
I don't know if we'll even get the
truck. I mean, who knows what could
happen. You don't know. It says it's on
hold. I don't know. It doesn't even say
it's at the port. It doesn't say where
it's at at all. Some of these will say
like the week of this is when it's going
to be here, month of October, month of
September. Like they tell me when the
other this one just doesn't have
anything. So I don't want to work a deal
on a truck that I don't even know I'm
going to get.
>> And I'm I'm assuming I'm assuming you
looked and saw that you have no other
trucks exactly like this or coming on
the way or anything other alternatives
on the situation.
>> No, cuz you didn't tell me you were
looking at any other. You said this is
the truck that you wanted to look at. So
we've been stuck on this truck. I didn't
know. I mean, I have some trucks online
if you if maybe you looked. I just
thought there was a certain specific
reason why you wanted this truck. Yeah,
I I didn't know this is why we're still
talking about it. So, I just thought
this was the truck that you wanted.
>> Again, it's it's more that you're saying
like it's just you know, like part of
the reason why people don't like buying
a car, just so you know, is that they
feel like they're getting lied to. And
the idea that you're telling me that
that you're losing $2 to $3,000 on every
truck, but selling at MSRP because of a
rebate, just not true. So,
>> like for instance, we have a 2025 Pro 4X
here in uh Boulder Gray. They do have
the discount on it's down to, you know,
they have a $3,494 discount plus the
rebate. That's $39,941.
They're already discounted. That's when
they get discounted. I don't know what
the discount's going to be. I don't set
the discount. I don't know. I I don't
set it. So, the trucks that we have in
stock, we have $7,000 between discount
and rebates on the trucks, but I don't
know what this one's going to have. I
don't know.
>> So, so like isn't
>> that's what I'm trying to say to you.
>> Yeah, I know. But wouldn't it be like
not a crazy concept to say, "Hey, we
normally discount our cars between $300
to $4,000. We'll probably take care of
you on this one. Go talk to a manager to
see like, hey, this guy's really
interested in this truck. He's willing
to wait for the truck. We're going to be
discounting a 3,600 plus rebate anyway.
Can we just get a deposit on the car and
just hold it?" And yeah, I mean, it's
just crazy that clearly you're going to
discount this truck when it arrives. And
the reason isn't arrived isn't
>> maybe not that maybe we don't
discount. Every frontier in your every
frontier on your inventory is discounted
$3 to $4,000.
>> Some are 2,900. Yes. Some are 30.
>> A manager that would be like, "Hey, this
guy wants this frontier. He's willing to
wait for this frontier." Dude, let's put
a deal. Let's put a dream in a drive.
Let's do something, right? Like why the
idea of being like, "We're not
discounting.
>> Buy one in my inventory." Then if you
buy one in my inventory, I would gladly
I could gladly give you the exact
number. I mean, I have a couple in in
stock here. Can we agree that the reason
why this is not in your inventory isn't
because it just got released, but
because it's on quality hold. And that's
the reason if this car wasn't on quality
hold, it would be on your lot and be at
this same discount. So, sure, if you
guys have another long bed, which I
don't think you do, then I'd be
interested in it. I don't think so.
Again, if you if you guys want to die on
this hill that you guys don't want to
give any discount on this car and then
hope you sell it for MSRP before it
arrives and the second it arrives,
you're giving a $3,600 discount. Let's
be real. Like, this is what's going to
happen. And the car is going to arrive.
Your manager is going to discount it for
3,600 bucks and you guys are going to
sit on it.
>> But maybe the Nissan customer cash goes
away though. What I'm saying, maybe the
Nissan customer cash goes away. Maybe
that goes away by next month. So now
we're only at 35. But maybe that rebate
goes away next month when I get the
truck. So the $7,000 went out the
window. Now we're back to the 3500 is
what I'm saying. These rebates changed.
This truck might come next month. And
that $3,500 customer cash rebate doesn't
exist anymore. Now we're just
discounting the truck. So now we're just
we're I'd rather mess with real numbers
with you know what I mean? Like I
understand what you're saying. Maybe
when this truck comes there's no rebates
on it and all we're doing is discounting
it. So now what did we do now? Now now
you're $3,500 more than what I quoted
you. Yeah. I'd still discounted it but
you lost the you lost the the rebate
because it doesn't exist because the
car, you know, they're not doing it
anymore is what I'm trying to say. I
have to get the truck to realize is a
discount. Obviously we're going to
discount the truck. I totally agree with
you. I just don't know how much but the
rebate may go away is what I'm saying.
So then we're still at the $3,500.
>> Yeah. But but if I but if I as a
customer agree that I would take a let's
just say $4,000 discount plus rebate,
right? And I understand the rebate can
change from month to month. I I I'm not
disagreeing with you at all.
>> That's what I'm trying to say, sir. I
don't know when I'm getting the truck,
so I don't know if this rebate's even
going to be available then.
>> I don't care about the rebate discount.
Yes, I don't care about the Yes, I can I
can discount the truck 3500. Yeah, I can
do that.
>> Okay,
>> but I don't know about the rebate. I
can't give you an exact number.
>> I've never won.
>> That's what I'm trying to say is I can't
give you exact number. I don't have the
truck or know when I'm getting it.
>> Okay. So, what what can what can you do
on this truck understanding that the
rebate could 100% change and we can we
can do this deal with a plus rebate
involved and I'm considering if it's
worth me waiting for this truck or not.
That is what I'm trying to figure out.
>> I mean, hypothetically at 45,221's
invoice minus $7,000, you're looking at
about 38,221.
I mean, that would be a rough rough
number on that.
>> If you can give me for 38,221 plus TTL,
no add-ons, no dealer ads, nothing like
that. Hypothetically. I mean, I get
that's why I don't want to give you a
number. I don't know. I don't know if
it's going to be discounted 2900 or 36.
We're We're just going around the ring
here.
>> No, but but how do you figure out what
kind of is is there nobody that is
available that can just say, "Wait,
dude. Man, I can't wait for you to hear
this, man." But that's a whole different
conversation. All I'm asking is I
understand the rebate can change. The
3500 is on limbo now. I've looked at the
Frontiers for months. Frontiers are
probably going to keep the rebate.
They're not It's not like Nissan's going
to start selling these things.
>> Probably is not an answer, though.
probably is not a guaranteed though.
Probably keeping the rebate is not
guaranteed.
>> That's why I'm willing to buy your car
plus rebate. Meaning that if the rebate
is 3500 or if it's 7500 or if it's 2
grand, I'm willing to buy the car with
whatever discount your manager puts on
it as long as I agree to the discount
plus rebates.
>> I am the manager.
>> You are the manager.
>> I am the manager. Yes, I am, sir.
>> Okay. Well, so do you are you the are
you the manager that prices the
inventory?
>> No, I do not do that.
>> Okay. So, which manager prices the
inventory?
>> I have no idea to be quite honest. We
have seven stores. I have no idea who
does that.
>> What manager are you? You've been there
for 20ome years and you're a manager and
you don't know who prices your
inventory?
>> No.
>> What manager are you? BDC manager?
>> What manager are you?
>> Is this some type of like game? Are you
Is this like a test or something or like
what are we doing?
>> You just said you just said you're
>> 20 minutes and we're now we're still at
we're still talking about the same
thing. I mean,
>> we're still like now now you're
belitting. Now you're coming at me. Now,
now you're just like, "How far? How far
does this go till we just end the call?"
And I told I gave you a price.
>> You didn't give me a price.
>> Hypothetically 30. Yes, I did. I told
you 38,000 221. If we took 7,000, you
know, realistically from the ones I have
on my lot, that's what it would be.
>> Okay. Can you send that down to me in
writing on what your dealer discount
plus rebate is? Understand?
>> I'm not sending nothing in there till I
get the truck and I know what the
discount and everything's going to be.
I'm not putting I can't put nothing in
writing until I have it. That's what I'm
saying. I'm just saying we're talking
hypotheticals here. Maybe this, maybe
that, probably that, probably this. I
don't know.
>> So So you're saying you guys don't ever
take deposits on inventory on the way.
>> Yes. When I have a date that it's going
to be here. Yes, I have. I've never
taken a deposit on a vehicle that is on
hold. No, I have never done that. Now,
if it tells me that the vehicle is going
to be here in a week, 2 weeks, or a
month, absolutely, I will do that. But
on hold, I don't know when it it could
be it might never come here. That's But
if it said a date, 100% I'd be sitting
here absolutely absolutely would take a
deposit and try to sell you the truck.
>> Okay, I will I guess there's no going I
mean you you won't put a number on the
truck. That makes sense. So I mean like
there's nothing I'm just trying to buy a
truck, man. That's all I'm trying to do.
So
>> I understand, sir. I would love to sell
you a truck. That's my job. I love to
sell you a truck. I'm just trying to
give you some information. The only
information that I have that the truck's
on hold and I don't know if it's even
going to make it here. I don't know. To
put a number on a truck that I don't
even know I'm going to get. It just
doesn't make sense right now until I
that's why I said I could get your name
and number. I can keep checking on here,
you know, week, couple days here and
there and see if I can get a date and
then we can figure it out. But other
than that, I don't I don't have I don't
have any information I can give you for
that other than, you know, $7,000 off of
that.
>> $7,000 off. So, you guys are willing to
do $3,500 off as a dealer discount,
$3,500 hypothetical rebate whenever the
car hypothetically arrives, but you guys
don't know if it's going to arrive cuz
it's been hold since June and it might
not move.
>> June 25th. Yep. So that's still it's
been two months since the vehicle's been
the vehicle has been on hold for two
months. So it could be another two
months. I don't know.
>> Okay. Well, I don't want to waste your
time or wait. I'm looking to buy and
make a deposit here in the next week or
so. So I mean I'm hoping I was hoping to
do it today. So if you guys aren't
willing to put a deposit on this car or
do anything on that car, then that's not
going to help me. But if you guys I'm
willing to wait it out if that took that
time. Um and I'm willing to risk that uh
on that quality hold. I understand how
quality holds work. They most of the
time check out. If you guys aren't
willing to do that, I can't force you
to. So,
>> I don't know, man. I just I don't I
don't have fun. I I don't know. I just I
guess if you want to give me your name
and your number, I can keep checking on
the truck and, you know, try to keep
you, you know, when we're going to get
the truck and that's all I can do.
>> Yeah, that's fine. You you uh you Yeah,
you can take my name and number. That's
fine.
>> What's your name?
>> Yep. Tommy.
>> Tommy.
>> Yep. My phone number is
>> Nope. Calling from Massachusetts.
>> Okay. What's your phone number?
>> Yep.
What I will do is I will continue to
check on this until I can get a date for
you and then we will work something out
and I will get a deposit and I'll let
you know when I can get it.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> Thank you, Tommy. Bye.
>> Okay, bye.
>> If you guys uh anybody who doesn't think
that was a problem, then you are the
problem with this car industry and I
cannot wait for you to be out of a job
in the next 3 years. To be blind
transferred from one car person to
another. Again, the hostility that came
from the moment I got off that phone
[Music]