Tra tradition. I mean, I don't know its
political preferences, but I mean, it's
a it's a hybrid for sure. Traditional, I
don't know.
>> Okay. There's no discount on this
vehicle at this moment. It's MSRP.
>> I'm so sad.
>> That one won't be here to somewhere
around the beginning of September.
>> I'm a patient man. I'm engaged. So, I
have to be patient.
>> No worries. Well, I don't want to steal
somebody else's cuz I am engaged and I
am loyal. So,
>> unless it's the same price, then no bada
boom. know about a bang.
>> Would you like me to get one?
>> I got a wedding to pay for. I can't get
$5,000. We are going to be negotiating
on some Toyotas today. We're going to be
going on a Toyota RAV 4. We need a S.
Okay. So, we need a plug-in hybrid RAV 4
SE. Okay. This one is in Connecticut.
They only want white and they don't care
about anything else. 125 of these cars
available. He lives in Connecticut. Let
us make some phone calls.
Good afternoon, Toyota. This is Lillian.
How may I help you?
>> Hey, can I speak to somebody in new car
sales?
>> Yes, of course. You know, um, and your
name, sir?
>> Uh, my name is Tom.
>> Mr. Tom. Uh, my name is Lillian. What
vehicle are you looking for? Actually,
>> uh, I have the last six of the VIN
number if that helps.
>> Okay. Is that a new vehicle or pre-owned
vehicle?
>> It is a new vehicle.
>> A new vehicle. Okay.
>> Correct.
>> And is it a Corolla, Camry, Rav 4,
Corross?
>> It is a RAV 4. Raph for what term?
>> SE
>> I have the last six of the VIN if that
helps.
>> Yes, please.
>> Uh 276
56.
>> What's the letter?
>> The letter is D. That would be the
seventh.
>> Okay.
>> D as in dog.
>> Okay. Is this a traditional hybrid?
>> Tradition I mean I don't know its
political preferences, but I mean it's a
it's a it's a hybrid for sure.
Traditional I don't know.
>> Okay. Traditional is the G, you know,
gas the hybrid. It's the hybrid. It's
the plugin.
>> It's the hybrid. Okay. Oh, the plugin.
Okay.
>> I've never heard the traditional versus
the like is it like the unconventional?
>> Yes. Okay. Yes. That vehicle should be
arriving in 17 days, actually.
>> Bada boom. Bada bing. I love it. Well,
I'm super the silver sky metallic. Um
black fabric. Yes.
>> Sorry to cut you off. Silver sky
metallic. That's the dream.
>> Yes. Okay. Are you going to be having
any vehicle as a trade in or just making
a purchase, Mr. Tom?
>> No trade. Just buying.
>> I'm buying. Okay. Are you here local in
in Miami?
>> I'm in Orlando.
>> You're Orlando. Okay.
>> Yeah. I'm a Disney adult.
>> Okay. Well, you know, I could get you
information if you're interested in the
out the door price. You could actually
reserve the vehicle.
>> Bada boom, bada bing. I'm super
interested in the out the door price. I
like this.
>> Okay. So, are you going to need a new
tag or transfer tag?
>> Actually, I'm going to transfer a tag.
>> Transfer tag. Okay. Uh, zip code where
the vehicle is going to be registered.
>> Yeah. Zip code is
>> And Mr. Tom, what's your last name?
>> Last name is Mula. M I K U U L A
>> M I K U L A.
>> Okay. So, give me a few minutes. I'm
going over the manager so they could
give me an out the door price and
definitely this is the best number to
reach you back then.
>> That is it.
>> Okay, Mr. Tom, give me a few minutes and
I'll, you know, without I'll give you a
call back with out the door price. Thank
you.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> Okay, bye.
>> I got this one.
>> Hey, can I speak to Sarah?
>> Sarah.
>> Sarah. Yeah. Meanwhile,
>> hey Sarah, Tommy, Tommy boy, Tommy gun,
Tommy business. Uh, hey, uh, hopefully
I'm talking to the right Sarah, not the
wrong Sarah. There's two Sarah. There's
a really cool Sarah and then there's a
Okay, Sarah. Hopefully talking to the
cool one. If you know, you know.
Hopefully you are working and selling a
car and not watching Tik Tok. Yeah, I
have a client in the area looking to get
a deal and I'm hoping, you know, we can
bada boom, bada bing, put a deal
together. You know, that'd be fun.
Anyway, if you are watching Tik Tok,
make sure you enjoy your break. Uh, make
sure you drink eight cups of water and
have a nice day. Don't know who this is.
This is Tommy.
>> Yes. Hi. Good afternoon, Mr. Tom. This
is Lily with
>> Oh, hey.
>> Okay. So, I got the out the door price
from the manager.
>> Okay. I'm here for the door price.
>> Okay. The out the door price with
transfer tag and everything will be
53,614
with 86.
>> Is that with the $6,500 rebate?
>> You're planning to lease or purchase?
lease.
>> You're planning to lease. Okay. Give me
a moment because I don't have to tell
him, you know, it's going to be for a
lease because he gave me what he gave me
was an out the door price actually.
>> Yeah. I guess what was the dealer
discount on that so I know
>> there's no discount on this vehicle at
this moment. It's MSRP.
>> I'm so sad.
>> Okay. So, give me a few minutes. Let me
call you back and I do
>> waste your time. If you guys can't give
me a discount, then I have other other
dealerships that are giving me a
discount. So,
>> Okay. Yes. Unfortunately on this
vehicle, the lowest price, you know,
MSRP is 47,650.
>> Yeah, people down the street's doing
better. So, I appreciate it.
>> Okay. No, you're welcome. Have a nice
day.
>> Okay. Bye-bye.
>> Thanks for calling.
Does Courtney speak? Can I assist you?
>> Hello, Courtney. I would just like to
inquire upon a car to see if it is
available.
>> Okay. And what's your name, sir?
>> Uh, my name is Tommy.
>> And which vehicle are you inquiring
about, Tommy? Uh, I have the last six of
the VIN number if that helped.
>> Okay.
>> Was that okay? You want to hear it?
Okay, cool. Uh, two Yeah. 27549.
>> And what's your last name, Tommy?
>> Last name is Makula. M I K U L A.
>> And what vehicle is it? A new vehicle or
pre-owned? I'm sorry.
>> It is a uh it is a brand new vehicle.
>> Okay. Which one is it?
>> It is the Rav 4 Prime hybrid SE. The
picture shows it's still in the factory.
>> Okay. Is that one gonna be That one's
gonna be the blueprint.
>> That is blue and printing.
>> Yes, sir. Looks like that one won't be
here to somewhere around the beginning
of September.
>> I'm a patient man. I'm engaged, so I
have to be patient.
>> You know what? I'm sorry, but that one
is already sold. Pre-sold already. Yes,
sir. Just looked at the the screen. I'm
sorry.
>> No worries. Well, I don't want to steal
somebody else's because I am engaged and
I am loyal.
>> Now, we do have a XSSE here, though.
>> No, I only want the SE.
>> Yes, sir. Yeah, that's the only one we
have in stock right now is the XSC just
like that one. Well, similar to that
one. So,
>> unless it's the same price, then no bada
boom. No bada bing.
>> Let's see what the Yeah, it's about a
little different than that. See, that
one is So, it's about $5,000 difference.
Would you like me to see if we can find
one?
>> I got a wedding to pay for. I can't I
can't have a $5,000 difference.
>> Would you like for me to see if that's
one we can find for you, though?
>> No, I'm still looking. I I don't want to
risk not finding one before the end of
the timeline. So, I'll keep looking. I
appreciate your time.
>> When is your timeline?
>> Uh, well, the the end of September when
the tax credit goes away.
>> Okay. Let me see if I can find you one,
though. My manager is pretty good at
finding vehicles for customers. So, let
me see. I can call you back and let you
know either way. How about that?
>> Sure. If that fine.
>> Okay. All right. Well, I'll get that
done for you.
>> Okay. Sounds good. Salutations. Have a
great day.
>> Okay. You too. Thank you. Bye-bye.
>> Thank you for calling Toyota. To book a
service appointment with ease, simply
say service appointment. I'm Stella,
your digital assistant. How can I help
you?
>> Can I speak to the Asel department? Let
me connect you to a team member to
assist. Please hold
>> Toyota.
>> Hutch Toyota. Tommy Makula. How's it
going?
>> Good. How are you?
>> Hey, doing well. I was just seeing
Hutch. If your car is available,
>> which car?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> All righty. Is it a new or pre-owned
vehicle, sir?
>> Brand new.
>> All right. Hit me with that stock
number.
>> Hit you with the stock number. S is in
South, D is in Dakota. 2720007.
>> 25 RAV 4 plug-in hybrid. It is
available.
>> I love it. I love that car is available.
Awesome. Well, I'm super interested. I
want more of it. Uh really just trying
to get some pricing on it and hoping to
buy it today or tomorrow.
>> That sounds great. What's your name,
sir?
>> My name's Tommy.
>> Tommy, what's your last name?
>> Makula.
>> Spell that for me.
>> Yeah. M as in Mary. I K U L A.
>> Perfect. Uh what's a good email address
for you so I can send you the spec sheet
on it?
>> I don't even use email. If you can text
me, that'd be great.
>> Yeah, I can do that. That's not a
problem. Not a problem at all, sir. And
are you looking to finance this vehicle,
pay cash?
>> I'm looking to lease the car if
possible.
>> Lease. Okay.
>> Lease and then Yeah, I can provide that.
Lease and buy. The lease and dash is
what they call it.
>> There we go. Absolutely. And if you
don't mind, can you give me your address
so I can make sure taxes are correct?
>> Well, I can give you my zip code. I
don't like giving you my address. We
just met.
>> That's not a problem. Not a problem.
>> 32.
>> Zip code's fine. That is just fine,
Tommy. No worries there. I understand
that.
>> No worries.
>> All righty, sir. So, here's what I'm
going to do, Tommy. Uh, let me get you
in the system with this limited
information. I'm going to text you the
spec sheet on the vehicle, and then I'm
going to put together some leasing
proposals for you, and I'll shoot those
over to you as well via text message.
>> I love it, Toyota. I'm excited.
>> No problem, sir. Thank you so much. And,
uh, I will be hitting you up. Give me
about 5 or 10 minutes. Okay, sounds
good.
>> Thanks. Bye.
>> No problem. Bye. He didn't correct me
for the 19th time. What if his name is
Hutchinson Toyota? Have we ever thought
that was a possibility? I think it could
be. Okay, I got two sets of numbers in
here. Let me look at these numbers. So,
this dealership is doing $1,200 off. I
was hoping for a bit better of a
discount. Here's the lease proposal.
Okay, this guy did it upside down. What
is the HUD an advantage? What is the hot
advantage?
Toyota home director call.
>> Can I speak to new car sales?
>> Sure. Would you like to speak with a
manager in new car sales?
>> Sure.
>> All right. Hold on one moment.
>> Hold on two moments.
[Music]
>> Oh, I can't even mute. Darling,
>> the person at extension 235 is
unavailable.
>> Hello, extension 235. My name is Tommy.
Tommy Mula. Uh, I was calling because I
was looking for a car to see if it was
available and I was transferred to you
235. I don't know if you're in the Squid
Games. It'd be kind of cool if you're in
the Squid Games cuz that'd be a sick
name. But anyway, they didn't tell me
your name. They just transferred me to
you. And hopefully 235 can uh do it.
Otherwise, that'd be bad. Anyways, I'm
looking for TT251835.
So, if you can give me a call back,
name, number, and all the fun stuff,
I'll get back to you. Anyway, bye.
>> Sales department, how may I help you?
>> Hey, sales department. This is uh buying
department. I just wanted to see if you
guys have a car available.
>> Yeah, certainly. Which uh vehicle are
you looking at?
>> I have the last six of the vin if that
helps.
>> Yep. One second. Uh what is the last six
of the VIN?
>> Last six of the VIN is 278247.
>> All right, sounds good. Do you mind if I
just place you on a briefold just so I
can check my inventory?
>> You can put me on a brief hold all you
want. Thank you so much.
>> Meanwhile,
>> all right, thank you so much for
holding. By the way, my name is Dan
Wicker and I have the pleasure of
speaking to you today.
>> My name's Tommy.
>> Nice speaking with you, Tommy. So, yeah,
as of now, this vehicle has not arrived
yet at our dealership. It's supposed to
arrive between September 3rd and
September 20 or September 17th, sorry,
sir.
>> Awesome. Well, I'm super interested in
securing it. Just really needing
details.
>> Okay. Yeah, certainly. I mean, to place
a deposit usually $500. Would that be
something you like to do?
>> Yeah, I mean, as long as I agree to the
numbers on it.
>> Okay, sounds good. I mean, um, I can get
with my sales manager and see what we
can do for you.
>> I love it.
>> All right, sounds good. Uh, have you
gotten quoted any other numbers at any
other dealership yet?
>> I've just started calling around. Uh,
you know, locally I have about $500 off,
but I was looking for better than that.
>> Okay, sounds good. I mean, I'll get with
my sales manager and see what we can do
for you. You said your name is Tommy.
>> My name is Tommy. All
>> right, sounds good. I'll certainly give
you a call or text back, whatever you
prefer. Yeah, text is perfect.
>> All right, sounds good. Tommy, thank you
so much for calling in.
>> No problem. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> I'm going to answer the phone. This is
Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. This is Mark, sales manager.
>> How are you?
>> Hey, I'm doing well. But yourself?
>> I'm doing good, thank you. I uh just
wanted to reach out. I I apologize. Dan
forgot to mention where would you be
registering the vehicle?
>> In Connecticut.
>> Oh, okay. So, not too far away.
>> Yeah.
>> So, you know, I can definitely get the
the final figure worked up for you. Um,
pretty simply though, you know, we'd be
selling it at the listed MSRP. Uh, looks
like that one's 48,973.
Uh, plus tax, title, uh, registration,
and our $400 document fee.
>> Okay. So, you guys couldn't do any
better than that?
>> I I mean, we don't have much inventory
on them, unfortunately. We are awaiting
an allocation of vehicles here tomorrow.
I can definitely kind of, you know,
revisit things with you. Um,
>> well, I have a I have another deal that
I literally just got texted not two
seconds ago, and I'll probably jump on
that one instead if you guys can't do
any better than MSRP.
>> Okay. Well, what they sell it to you at?
>> They are doing with the rebate. MSRP
48,0009.
They're doing a total savings of 9,273
with the rebate included. Six dock fee
with the rebate. The lease the lease
rebate 6,500 bucks.
>> So, you're not looking to finance the
vehicle. You're looking at lease it.
>> No. Yeah. Lease it with the $6,500
credit, right?
>> Oh, okay. Yeah. Let me uh let me take a
look here on the riff. So, that's
interesting that they're including that
because we don't know what the
incentives will be at the time of
delivery. I'm not showing.
>> Yeah. I mean, I know the $6,500 credits
been there for a while and this credit
ends at the end of September. I'd be
shocked if Toyota took it away a month
earlier than everybody else.
>> Yeah. No, that's fine. So, I I could
definitely run up. So, being that you
want to lease it, what are you looking
for? 3 years, 12,000 mi a year?
>> Yeah. I mean, yeah, we're looking to do
a three-year lease. Yeah.
>> Were you planning to put anything down?
Well, we asked them to show $0 down just
so we had the idea.
>> Yeah, that's fine. Let me work out a
lease here with you uh on that and I'll
give you a call back here in a few, sir.
>> Okay, I'll wait to call this other
dealership back.
>> I appreciate it.
>> Hey, no problem. Thank you.
>> Yeah, thank you.
>> Bye.
>> I just want to uh just point something
out. I say this all the time,
competition drives the price down. The
second I was like, "Oh, MSRP, sorry, we
don't have inventory." All these things.
The second I said, "Okay, I'll just take
this other offer here. No big deal."
Look how quickly and easily that
changed. Like that's that shows that
this this is how this works. It's very
simple, very easy. Competition drives
the price down 100% of the time.
Sometimes I just don't know. Maybe
buying a car is as easy as just calling
and saying your name is Tommy and you
just get good deals.
>> Thank you for calling Toyota. My name's
Charard. Who have a pleasure of speaking
with?
>> Hello. My name is Thomas Love.
>> Hi. How may I assist you?
>> Hello. I would like to inquire upon a
car to see if its availability is still
there.
>> Absolutely. Is this new or used?
>> It is brand new. Brand new. Okay. What
are we looking at?
>> I have a stock number if that does
assist.
>> That does. So, I'm ready for the stock
number when you are.
>> Uh, it's Sierra Delta 272069.
>> All right. That vehicle is a 2025 RAV 4
plug-in hybrid SE.
>> That is correct.
>> Perfect. So, that vehicle is available
and ready to go.
>> Awesome. Perfect. Well, I have already
driven this car. I know I want this car.
I'm really just trying to inquire about
the out the door numbers so I can make
an educated decision on buying the car.
>> Absolutely. Um here, let me get you put
in the system. Uh could you spell your
first name for me?
>> Yeah, first name is Thomas. T O M I S L
A V.
>> And your last name?
>> Makula. M I K U L A.
>> And this is a good phone number for you?
>> This is the best phone number for me.
Correct.
>> Perfect. Just give me one moment. Just
getting you in the system. That way I
can get you this outdoor number. No
worries. I appreciate your assistance.
>> Of course. Um, for text purposes, uh,
what is your zip code?
>> Uh, my zip code that I will be
registering the car is
>> Okay. Um, is this Aelia Park or Orlando?
>> I'm sorry. Can you can you repeat
yourself? I was confused.
>> The city.
>> Oh, the city is Orlando.
>> Okay. What I can do is um, give me give
me a moment. I'm going to get everything
put in the system. I'm going to get with
one of my managers so that way I can
make sure the taxes are correct since
you are not a Georgia resident. What I'm
going to do is I just sent you over a
text. It's from a I will be able to send
you over the outdoor price um here or I
can email it to you. Whichever which do
you prefer?
>> I have opted into the text messaging. So
if you could text that over that would
be the best for me.
>> Perfect. Okay. So give me about not even
5 to 10 minutes. I just need to run over
to one of their offices so that way I
can get this final price for you.
>> Awesome. Thank you so much and I
appreciate your assistance and I can't
wait to do business with you.
>> Of course. Likewise. I'll talk to you
soon.
>> Okay. No problem. Have a great day.
>> You too. Bye-bye.
>> Salutations. So, this dealership is
saying they're giving me $9,273
off. Now, $6,000 of it is rebate 100%.
The rest I'm confused. Like that that
matches my out of state deal. We do have
a we do have a phrase in this industry,
right? And by that it's it's a delivered
delivered trademarked deal. And this is
something you have to learn when buying
a vehicle, especially in our department.
It's called chasing ghost. The idea
behind it is sometimes you have a good
deal in front of you, but you either you
you think you could do better uh or you
don't know it's a good deal. So, what
you do is you chase ghost. You chase
something that's not actually there and
you go on this punt. And some people,
conspiracy theorist, right? uh they go
down this crazy rabbit hole of chasing
ghosts until they can't find the ghost
anymore. So they go back to the original
deal and the original deal is gone cuz
it's sold. So the idea behind it, like
one of the things that Deliver does
really well is we know when there's a
good deal in front of us. And this is a
good deal. Like just point blank. So I
could keep calling 40 other dealerships
seeing if I could beat this deal. I'm
going to put two dealerships against
each other here to see if I can get
anybody else to do better than this. But
this is strong. I don't want to lose
this deal.
[Music]