Okay. That's so funny. I You don't You
don't know some guy named Dakota? Some
guy just called like 10 minutes ago for
that exact same car.
>> My mom's insane for years.
>> Oh, she's been with us for years.
>> Well, I think you disappointed me just
like my mother did cuz she also called
me the wrong name. My name isn't
Matthew. It's Tommy.
>> Me?
This is not This is This is This doesn't
like wake me up. This one doesn't get me
excited.
>> What's the number can we need can we be
together in your business right now?
>> Yeah. I mean, the 2500 be great.
>> 2500. Bada boom, bada bing. I'm buying
your truck right now. I'll be I'll be
walking on in. So, if you guys don't
know, my name's Tommy. I negotiate car
deals for a living. My goal is to save
you time, energy, and anxiety. We save
you money, but that's a byproduct of it
all. I charge a flat fee of a,000 bucks.
I handle the literally the entire
process. We have an entire team of nine
people dedicated to making sure you have
the best buying experience possible. If
you want to save money, guess what? Just
do this on your own. Watch my tips,
watch my videos. You can do this all for
free without hiring anybody. You're
looking for an XLT, brand new Maverick.
We need frontwheel drive. Must be
frontwheel drive. Must be the luxury
package, must have the 360 package, and
must have the bedlininer. He says he
wants Velocity Blue as his number one
color. So, I'm going to go there first.
There's only 96 of these cars available.
They do live in Sunnyvale.
>> Hi, this is Tim. How can I help?
>> Hello, Tim. This is Tommy. Uh, I just
want to see if you guys have a car
available.
>> Yeah, I can help you out with that. And
which one are you after?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> I'm sorry.
>> Oh, yeah. Yes, that's perfect. Okay,
it's 25. T is in tango 514.
>> Okay. Yeah. Besides availability, what
uh other information you can give for
you on this?
>> Well, I already know this is the truck I
want. You know, this is the dream in the
driveway. Really just trying to make
sure it's available and then get the
best pricing and then buy it. Step one,
step two, step three.
>> Okay, perfect.
>> Can't give me more than three
instructions, though, otherwise I'll
fail.
>> Okay. All right. And and I'm sorry, your
your first name again?
>> My name is Tommy.
>> Tommy. Okay. Tommy. And your last name?
>> Mula.
>> Can you spell for me?
>> Sure. Uh, M I K U L A.
>> Perfect. My name's Tim.
>> Yeah. Let me I'm gonna pull this truck
up for you. And if it is available, do
you think you'd be able to come out this
afternoon or
>> uh if we can create a numbers? Uh, sure.
We can buy it today.
>> Okay, perfect. And would you be trading
anything in or just a add vehicle?
>> You know, I'm just adding to the fleet.
Looking to pay cash, adding to the
fleet. I'm a simple man. Simple goals.
>> Okay, perfect. Perfect. Yeah. And this
is the Ford Maverick, correct?
>> This is the Ford Maverick, correct? Yep.
The Ford Maverick XLT hybrid.
>> XLT. Yeah, it looks like this is a new
arrival for us. I want to make sure it
it looks like it's in stock and I can
like say go put my hands on it for you.
Like I say, it has generic pictures. So
like say it's a new arrival.
>> Oh, you think the real pictures? I
thought I thought those were real.
>> Yeah. So let me uh Yeah, let me call you
back from my cell phone or at the
vehicle too and I can um go over any of
your questions and but what's is this
the 98?
>> Yep, that is my phone number.
>> Okay. All right, Tony. I'm going to give
me just a couple minutes and I will call
you back from my cell phone. Okay,
sounds good.
>> All right, thank you.
>> Thanks for calling. This is Victor. Can
I assist you today?
>> Hey, I just want to see if you guys have
a car available.
>> Of course. Uh, is it a new vehicle or a
pre-owned vehicle?
>> It is a brand new vehicle. I don't even
know if it's on your lot yet.
>> Okay. What's the stock number or what
vehicle is it?
>> Uh, good question. I don't see a stock
number, but I do have like the VIN,
make, model, the engine type, the
interior color.
>> Can I get the last eight of the VIN
number? I should be able to look it up.
>> Last eight. I can count that high. One
second. Let me get that. 1 2 3 4. Okay,
it is R is in Ralph. B is in boy. 68304.
S is in Sam are the very first letter if
I forgot one. Yeah, S is in Sam is the
first letter. S is in Sam. R is in boy
684.
>> S is in soy. R is in Roy. B is in boy.
68304. My bad.
>> Okay, no worries. Let's see.
>> Yeah, so
I got you. Let's see here. And who do I
have the pleasure of speaking with?
>> Uh Tommy.
>> Tommy. Okay, Tommy. Let's see here. What
kind of car is this? This would be the
Ford Maverick XLT.
>> SR. Okay.
>> I don't know if this is a test, but
hopefully I passed.
>> SRB68304.
>> Yeah. So, Royal Boy 68.
>> Your name was Okay, that's so funny. I
You don't You don't know some guy named
Dakota?
>> My name is Dakota Allen and I'm a deal
coordinator here at Delivered.
>> Some guy just called like 10 minutes ago
for that exact same car. I was able to
find a lot of info on that car, but
yeah, it is coming in on the It's coming
in from the 10th to the 16th. It's a
Maverick, right? Yeah,
>> it's XLT Maverick. Yeah, that's the same
one.
>> Well, if you give me a better deal than
you can on this Dakota fellow, I'll buy
it before he can buy it.
>> Well, I mean, I'll I I can send you the
exact same quote that I I do better than
that guy. I don't know who this Dakota
fella is, but I've never lost a Dakota
in my life.
>> I got you, brother. So, listen. The out
the door at 9.5 tax rate is 43,549.
Do you know your tax rate?
>> I don't know, like 9% somewhere in that
ballpark. What kind of What kind of deal
are you doing on the car? Let's just go
through the What's the MSRP is 37. And
what are you guys doing on the car?
>> We're selling it to him at Sticker. The
only thing we have is the service care,
which is just paint protection. It's
$14.95. That's it. And just easy. I I
got I got a way that we can get this cuz
you're never going to hear from that
Dakota guy ever again. Take the paint
protection off. Give me two grand off.
So, a total of $2,500 off that car. Uh
and now we're sniffing at a good good
deal.
>> So, you're saying 2K off the car and
then let the paint protection go bye-bye
and then we and then we take this deal
right from Dakota Boy.
>> Okay. Let me see here.
>> I'll call him myself. fall. No, I don't
know who this Dakota kid is, but I stole
your car.
>> What's your uh zip code one more time?
I'm sorry.
>> Yeah, uh zip code registering the car is
>> Have you driven these cars before? Do
you have any questions on it?
>> No, I've already driven one. I already
fell in love with it. Uh it's a great
car, man. I just I'm looking for the
gray is the color I'm looking for.
>> Okay, I got you. No worries. You're not
going to believe this, brother. It's You
guys are calling from the same city.
>> What?
>> It's 9.1. I'm not I'm not even kidding.
You guys, that's your total.
>> This is what the dealerships do. You
tell us, "Oh, we have somebody from the
same city in the same area." You both
are looking at it. Uh, I see what you're
doing.
>> I wish I, brother. But you know what's
funny? It could have been any other
salesperson that got it and they would
have never told you this, but I answered
the phone. But listen, that that I mean,
that's why I have everything here. I I
was just texting this guy. So, his total
was $43,549.
That's that sticker with the accessory.
You're you're basically asking for
$2,500 less than that. So, you're like
41 flat. Is that
>> I'm trying to be 40 flat. I want to be a
40 flat.
>> Oh, so 3,500 off.
>> Yeah, but 1500 is your add-on package.
That's That's a big part of it.
>> I got you.
>> I think you put the I'll say no to it.
You can just You can save the money
there.
>> Okay. Let Let me see what I can do.
Tommy, is this a good number to get back
to you then?
>> Is that the same number, too? What are
the chances?
>> No, no, no, no. Okay, look, let me let
me talk to my manager, see if he can do
a better deal on this. But like I said,
I don't I don't even have the car yet.
Uh like I said, it'll be here between
the 10th and the 16th. Are you were you
able to do a deposit if if the numbers
make sense?
>> Yeah. I mean, we get these numbers down.
I'll get the deposit right now.
>> Okay. So, give me a few minutes. Let me
talk to him. Let me talk to my manager
and then uh I'll give you a call back.
Is that okay?
>> That sounds great.
>> Okay. Give me a few minutes, Tommy. I
I'll get back with you. Okay. Thank you
so much.
>> Sounds good.
>> Okay. Bye-bye.
>> Hello, Tommy.
>> Hey, can you tell him you bought the car
you bought and bought elsewhere? I'm
competing with I'm competing the
competing with the same salesperson you
called and he wants the same car in the
same zip code and I told him I was going
to beat you up if I didn't get the deal.
I didn't I the chances that happened was
slim but yeah I'm this Ford Maverick if
you can tell if they've texted you to
say I bought elsewhere.
>> Yeah, I'll let enough.
>> Okay, keep killing it today. You got a
few more out I think maybe.
>> Yeah, I'm trying to get two more. I just
sent a loom and then waiting on an email
back.
>> Okay, cool. Um don't be afraid to pull
from the funnel too or if you need to or
anything like that.
>> Okay, I'm I may end up doing that. Thank
you again for all your hard work. I
appreciate you.
>> Yes, sir.
>> All right. Bye.
>> You got it.
>> Boom. If you guys don't know, just the
funny part is Dakota is one of our deal
coordinators. Uh he I'm asking the team
to what team deals they needed help on
because he couldn't get progress. So,
this was the deal he gave me. He
probably called on this. So, how we
handle this, we don't normally like to
double up like this. Uh but I'm trying
to help out the team where I can. So,
he's going to tell the dealership he
bought elsewhere. So, the competition
doesn't exist cuz right now what they're
probably going to use is competition.
Now, this is like a mental game, right?
If we have Dakota now text them saying
we bought elsewhere, now they're like,
"Oh, shoot. People are buying these cars
left and right and we're not selling
them. This dude just sent me a picture
with the biggest business card that I
have ever darn seen. I wish I could show
you this because it just has all of his
personal info including their address,
which I'm not going to do. But I'm
telling you, this guy's holding a
business card like this. Like, it's
bigger than this. This is bigger than
this. It's like it's like he won the
lottery type check with his business
card. I appreciate this dude's
enthusiasm. That's a good method. I love
it.
This is Eric speaking.
>> Hello, Eric. This is Tommy. I just want
to see if you guys have a car available.
>> Yeah. What were you looking for, Tommy?
>> Yeah, I have a stock number if that
helps.
>> Sorry. Say that one more time.
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Yeah. And what's that stock number?
>> Let me know when you're ready for it.
>> I'm ready.
>> Okay.
>> S is in Sierra. R is in Romeo. B is in
Bravo. 35782.
>> Okay. Ford Maverick XLT.
>> That's it.
>> Yes, we do have it in stock.
>> Awesome. Well, I love it. want more of
it. Already driven it. It's a great car.
Really just trying to get some great
pricing. And I heard there is nobody
better to call than
>> There is nobody better. That is correct.
>> My mom's been saying it for years.
>> Oh, she's been with us for years.
>> No, no, she's just been saying for years
that I should buy a car from She's heard
good things. She watches your ads.
>> I agree. I agree with your mother.
I can always go ahead and um set you up
here, Matthew, if you want with an
appointment if you're looking to stop
by. Well, I think you disappointed me
just like my mother did cuz she also
called me the wrong name. My name isn't
Matthew. It's Tommy.
>> Oh, Tom, you know what? Matthew pops up
on the caller ID. I apologize, Tommy.
>> No, it's okay. My mother called me the
wrong name a few times, too.
>> All right. You have our address at all,
Tommy? I
>> I do have the address. I do see it on
the website. Yeah, but I'm just looking
for some pricing on it.
>> Okay. Well, we have the listed price
right now going for 347.43.
That's the advertised price. It's the
same prices that we offer or if you come
in, we can always go ahead and take go
into further detail and see if we can go
ahead and uh negotiate the price.
>> Yeah, I mean I'd love to negotiate the
price. Uh I mean I'd like to do it all
over the phone if possible though. I
don't like to go out in public if I
don't have to.
>> Okay. Now, if we're going to do
everything over the phone, it's when we
do the pools as far as the the pricing
of what it would cost. Um everything's
going to be based off an estimated
score. So it's not going to go um
everything's going to be estimated. We
can't get the exact numbers unless we
have you in here, but I can go ahead and
see if I can go ahead and just get some
numbers from pre some pre-drafted
numbers for you.
>> Yeah, that'd be great. I'm paying cash
so life's easier that way.
>> Okay. Um, let me go ahead and place you
on a brief fold here. Okay, you want
>> sounds good.
>> Thank you.
>> Meanwhile,
>> Tommy,
>> it's me.
>> Hello. All right, perfect. So, what I'm
going to do, let me go ahead. Yes, I am
here. Let me go ahead and I'm going to
go ahead and take your information and
add you to the system here. And we're a
little busy, but I'm going to follow up
with you regarding the Maverick here,
okay? and we can go over some numbers
over the phone.
>> That's That's works for me.
>> Okay, perfect. All right. And Tommy, can
you just go ahead and spell your first
and last name for me?
>> Yeah, Tommy. T O M I Mula. M I K U L A.
>> All right. And your good contact number
for you?
>> Yeah, the number you're see I think
that's right on the call.
>> Perfect. It is. All right. Perfect. I
have your information here, Tommy. I'll
go ahead and follow up with you here
shortly. Okay.
>> Okay, that sounds great.
>> All right. Have a great rest of your
day. We'll talk to you soon.
>> Hey, thank you. Bye. Bye bye.
years.
>> This is Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. Tim,
how's it going? Manager. Good. Good. On
that Maverick, it's in transit. It's the
truck should be arriving maybe today or
tomorrow or the next day. We're It's
going to be arriving. It's going to be
here any day. So, it's just Yeah, it's
just not here at the moment.
>> Awesome. Well, I'm interested in it if
we can go to numbers.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And like I say, I know we
have it um like I say at a our sale
price of 35,943 plus your DMV fees and I
want to see if you'd like to secure
before it lands.
>> I was hoping to be a little bit more of
a discount off than that. That's just I
mean that's not that doesn't really wake
me up and get me super excited.
>> Okay. Can I ask how close to that 35943
can we be plus your fees?
>> Yeah. Uh do you guys have first off do
you guys have any like dealer fees or
anything crazy that I should worry
about? Um, we do license title
registration and then of course the
Oregon luxury tax. So,
>> okay, I appreciate that. So, nothing
nothing extra crazy above and beyond
those two things.
>> No, we do have an interior and exterior
protection. It's called Zurich Shield
and also a theft benefit of $5,000 if
your truck gets stolen. That's called
Zurich Shield. That is additional, but
it is optionable, but it really protects
the vehicle. You get a seven-year
insurance policy. Okay. I might see
value in that, but you're saying that's
that's optional. I don't have to do that
if I don't want it.
>> Correct. Yeah.
>> Okay. Yeah. I mean, I'm trying to be
right around 2500 off MSRP is where I'm
trying to be at.
>> Okay. Yeah. Um the only thing is the
Mavericks don't have the there's not a
lot of, you know, margin on the the
Mavericks at all. Um I know I'm going to
need to be pretty close to my 35 9 43.
Um I'd like to help you and earn your
business because I'm not going to have
thousands. That's the thing.
>> No, I'm not. Yeah, I don't disagree that
where the markup is on the car. I, you
know, I've seen them around in this area
around 1,500 off is kind of where I've
been seeing
>> already. So, I mean, that's already a
bit better than a deal than this. So,
I'd like to do a little bit better than
that.
>> What's the number like can we need can
we beat in your business right now?
>> Yeah. I mean, the 2500 be great. 2500,
bada boom, bada bing. I'm buying your
truck right now. I'll be I'll be walking
on in.
>> Yeah. I mean, like you say, how close to
that 35943
can we be? I'm not going to be a 2500.
>> I'll do some math.
>> I'm just trying to get a yes for you
instead of a no.
>> No, I get it. I'm doing I'm doing the
math here. Okay. So, you said 359 is
your price.
>> Yep. 943.
>> Okay. Put on my calculator here.
>> Math minus Okay. What about 3341?
>> I'm kind of thinking like that's 355 is
kind of where I'm thinking to get a yes
for you.
>> I I already have a deal for $1,500 off.
So, I already have a deal for 359 minus
1,500. So, I already have a deal for
344.
>> Okay.
>> So, I would need to be better than that.
>> 344. If I can do a little bit better
than that, I can earn your business.
>> If you can get down to 34. 34.
>> Okay. I'm going to try. Okay. Let me
work on that and I can give a call back
and we'll try to wrap this up for you.
>> Okay. Let's wrap it up. Call it a day.
Let's not I don't want to hear a no.
Let's just hear a yes.
>> I'm trying. Okay. All right. I'm going
to go work.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> Thank you.
Yo, I'm live. Just so you know.
>> Hey, Tommy. How are you, sir?
>> Hey, I'm doing well. I see your text,
but I just want to let you know I'm
live, but I was trying to work. I saw
your text.
>> Hey, um, you mind putting me on mute?
It's about yourself.
>> Oh, it's about myself. Oh, jeez. Okay,
one second.
>> Yeah.
[Applause]
>> Meanwhile,
>> I want to do a deal, too. Sorry, I'm
You're unmuted now, just so you know.
>> But I want to go through and work this
deal. So, I have a Maverick frontwheel
drive hybrid XLT Azure gray or the
velocity blue co-pilot luxury package.
Maybe one other thing. They're in
California, but the California deals are
lame.
>> Yeah, let me see. Maverick. What were
the colors again?
>> Uh, Azure gray or velocity blue.
>> All right.
>> Velocity blue is the one. Number one.
>> Do they want the XLT Lux package or no?
>> Mhm. Autopilot 360, uh, hybrid, and lux
package are three things they need.
>> Oh, dang. I've gotten EcoBoost don't
have the hybrid. Checking.
>> Yeah, I feel like there's so many on the
East Coast. There's like six on the West
Coast, and then the East Coast, there's
a million.
>> Yeah, I have 32 hybrid XLTs. So, I'm
bound to have something.
>> Yeah, but you don't have those two
colors.
>> What was the other one? The other color?
Auror gray and the other gray or
velocity blue?
>> Yeah, I've got a velocity one.
>> Oo, there it goes.
>> Frontwheel drive.
>> Must be frontwheel drive. That's a
That's a must. Yep. Frontwheel drive has
it. I'm gonna shoot you the window
sticker.
>> Okay. I need I need a stupid I need a
Scott deal on it though.
>> Oh boy. Here we go.
>> I need I just ship it across the
country.
>> It doesn't have the co-pilot though. Mr.
>> Oh, it needs a co-pilot. Needs
>> Yep. So, you need rear sensors.
>> You're killing me.
>> Hold on. I've got them. I've got more.
I've got two.
>> You got 32 of them. You better have
something here.
>> Yeah. I was going to say, do they have a
color preference on two of them or is
just any of them work?
>> Velocity blue is the ideal color.
>> Oh, okay. Perfect. All right. Velocity
blue. See what is what does one of those
deals entail? I don't know. Like I mean
I I love the 10%. That just makes my
life easy.
>> Okay. Yep. I'm gonna send you the window
sticker. I got one.
>> That's just that's just that's just a
that's just a me and Scott deal. Like I
mean Scott wouldn't even think of that.
Scott' be like, "Yeah, no big deal."
Just just like my trade. I negotiated my
trade. You saw what I got for my trade.
Did you guys sell that trade?
>> I understand. Yeah. No.
>> Oh, yes. But you can't do anything with
it because you don't have a title.
>> No. Exactly. I It's just sitting on my
lot.
>> I'm sorry. I Dude, I Dude, I've just
It's been sitting in my driveway
forever, so that's why we did it. Okay.
Anything I can do to help, don't be
afraid to let me know. Yep. Sounds good.
I just sent me a window sticker. Give me
Give me the number on it. If you can get
that number, I'll close this deal up.
>> Okay. Zip. Good.
>> All right. Sounds good. Talk to you
later, Jake.
>> What's the zip? All right.
>> Oh, zip. Sorry. Zip.
>> So, I'll get that sent over shortly.
Thanks, bro.
>> Okay. Sounds good. Bye.
>> All right.
>> Okay. Ready? This is Tim. This is Okay.
Am I hearing a yes?
>> Um, actually, you're hearing this is
Tim. I just wanted to You also have You
get a bundle buying from us. get extra
you get an extra year of like door dings
also if you scrub the wheel and a key
free key replacement and what I'm going
to be is giving you a yes at would be
plus your fees so out the door you'd be
366.90
96 cents is what a yes would be for you
>> you know I appreciate that they need
your full address
>> but like that's like like I asked a girl
out and she said yes I will not go out
with
Like I mean you did say yes so I give
you that but like
>> you gave me no in every sense of the
word. I don't I don't want the the the
the key protection or whatever we want
to call this.
>> It's free with the vehicles. It's the
benefit of buying from us.
>> I mean I feel like I feel like you just
added one thing on and then you kept
saying
>> I'm just not there at the like your your
price. You just you just said this is
just the definition. You should just
said no.
>> Yeah. That would have been added
something on and we're like, "Oh, well,
I'm giving you the same price, but now
I'm giving you key protection."
>> I'm giving you a little bit better uh
bigger discount like say 748 instead of,
you know, the the three. So, yeah, I'd
love to earn your business. I think
it'll be a great vehicle and we don't
have a problem selling Mavericks here at
the dealership at all. So, and we're
looking for trades and, you know, help
you with financing. So, you know, if you
have a trade, it's all difference, but
it's a great buy. And like say, you get
that bundle like I was talking about.
And um yeah, we do everything on a
computer, try to build good
relationships, all that stuff. So,
>> love your business.
>> Yeah. You know, I'll have to pass, but I
appreciate it.
>> Okay. All right. And um also, would a
used one make sense as well? If I get a
used one, maybe in that more in that
price range.
>> I wouldn't get a new one.
>> Okay. All right. Well, let me know if
things change. Appreciate you.
>> All right. No problem. Bye.
Yo,
>> I thought we were friends, man.
Honestly, I know I go to Scott more than
I go to you, but that's just cuz Scott
told me he likes me more.
>> What do you mean,
>> dude? This is not a Scott deal. This is
a Jake deal.
>> It's a $3,100 loser.
>> Man,
this is not This is This is This doesn't
like wake me up. This one doesn't get me
excited. I have so many deals right now.
I'm really I'm actually even more mad
that we have no more Ford deals. I think
I know why. Cuz cuz because because I
feel like we haven't been getting I have
how many four deals? 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8
nine four deals. I never had nine four
deals. Plus the ones the employees
that's 12.
>> We just knocked one of them out. There's
one's a Broncos. So that one's done.
>> 14 four deals. I just added them up. 14
four deals. And like one's in Apex,
North Carolina.
>> No way.
>> Oh my good. I I'm calling now.
>> Actually, I'm calling
>> Bro, it's it's a rough one. I mean, what
do you I mean, where do you want to be
on it?
>> I told you I want to be at 3500.
>> It's just I had
they told me Scott once told me, "It's
just metal."
>> And Scott, what was Scott's exact words
were, "Dude, I'm just trying to be top
10 in the country." What? I'm just
trying to be top 10 in the What number
were you guys last month?
>> I don't know. I can't even top 10. A
little bit of a slow month. I don't
You haven't been doing business with me.
>> I know. Well, you don't even call me
back.
>> Well, to be fair, my team calls you
back. I don't I don't I don't call much
money anymore because I'm I'm I'm
training. But
>> no, you're busy. No worries.
>> But here, let's just go.
>> 3500. 3500. How about three grand?
>> 3250. And that is my final offer. And
that's because chat got me all riled up.
So now you're just getting lucky.
>> Hey. Yes. You want to do 3250 for Tommy?
3250 off. He shrugged. Sure.
>> I'll do 3250.
>> Okay, cool. I'll send you this deal.
It's actually an angier, not Apex, but I
mean it had an A in it.
>> Oh, really?
>> Yeah. But it's I'll get I'll get
somebody uh well this is this one's a
F150 and they have so many packages I
don't want to keep reading them to you
but I'm going to text it to you right
now. Okay, cool. I appreciate you. Thank
you for
>> I'll send you I'll send it to you in
writing and uh you can have that. All
right.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> Thanks.
>> No, thank you. Bye.
>> Remember when when that guy here was
like, "This guy needs to read a book on
negotiating because he's really bad."
Well, take that. I used the leverage of
they're not top 10. I took a risk
because if he said he was top 10, I
would have looked like a fool. But guess
what? We haven't done as much business
with this dealership as we have in the
past. So, I assumed they fell down the
rankings. I utilized that. Got the
discount to 3250. These dealerships have
been giving me $1,000 locally. I'm now
going to call Dakota and let him know.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Okay. So, this is the best thing I got
so far cuz I've called all the other
ones. I don't know if you know this, but
this car in the West Coast just doesn't
exist.
>> Yeah, it's Yeah.
>> Okay. So, I'm working. I just worked a
deal. I just beat up Jake. So, we just
need to get a shipping quote. I have
Velocity Blue everything he wants. I
just got 3250 off. So, I'm only seeing
like a,000 bucks locally, 700 bucks
locally. So, if we can get shipping as
low as possible, I think that might make
sense. Sometimes that shipping path is
not as bad as you think. So, with 3250,
even if it's 1,500 bucks in shipping,
we're still coming up AC up ahead.
>> Yeah, for sure. Okay, cool. I will work
on that. He said you have Windows stick.
>> Uh, yeah, I I have everything. So, if
you want to present it to the client,
let's rock and roll. Let's get this deal
wrapped up.
>> Sweet.
>> Okay, it's in it's in my FTC phone.
>> Okay, awesome.
>> All right. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> All right. I'm kind of fired up. Oh,
wait. Oh, wait. Here. Just deal. Uh here
at Dakota. This one is like 10k off as
well. They say he's not good at
negotiating.
[Music]