Crazy. Uh, so why why do you guys have
so so many ads? It's crazy.
>> Uh, it's it's what every dealership is
doing. It's just which dealership's
going to be able to work with you.
>> Oh, okay. So, basically, there's not a
lot of profit in it, so you guys just
add a lot of profit to like, you know,
Toyota didn't give you enough money, so
you guys take your own piece.
>> And ours is cheaper.
>> Yours is cheaper with a $6,000 add-on
package. That's crazy.
>> Well, I'm not the used car director. I
wish I can give you an appraisal number.
That's definitely something I'm not
allowed to do, but talk to the boss.
I'll show you the final price.
>> Can I just do it over the phone?
>> Well, over you have more leverage face
to face. Like in co the price has
skyrocketed and you could say for no
reason.
>> I'm calling on some Toyotas now. Sienna
Woodland Edition. This This can give me
some can't find stock number options.
Sienna Woodland. Okay. So familiar with
this car. No big deal. Green new only.
Okay, perfect. I don't ever call on
these blindly. Like this is not a car I
call on blindly for a lot of different
reasons. There's a good chance I get
recognized here. That's fine.
>> Thank you for calling.
>> My name is Kareem. To whom do I have the
pleasure to speak to?
>> Hey Kareem. Uh the pleasure is all mine.
My name is Tommy. How's it going?
>> Good sir. Thank you for asking, Tommy.
>> Hey, thank you. Awesome. I just want to
see if you guys have a car available.
>> Go ahead. What is it?
>> Yeah, I have a stock number if that
helps.
>> Yes, sir. Give me one second. What's the
stock number?
>> 66913.
>> Okay. Give me one moment. No, it's still
it's still probably needs another 10
days, probably maybe two weeks. And I
want to say somebody's putting a deposit
on it. I just want to make sure it's
even still available.
>> Oh, but have they done it yet?
>> Do you mind giving me like 60 seconds?
Let me run to my manager and ask him
real quick.
>> I would give you as much as over 3
minutes. If you needed three over three
minutes, that's totally fine.
>> Awesome. Thank you. One Give me one
second. Thank you. Meanwhile,
>> yes, sir, it is available.
>> No, you had 8 seconds before 3 minutes.
Okay, that's fine. It is available.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Awesome. Perfect. So, I would just to
explain the website, what what is the
pricing on this car?
>> I got it at 60, I believe, 580.
>> I know the MSRP is 54,585. Like, why is
that additional cost coming on? Well, we
have some dealer installed accessories
and it comes with a clear coat on the
woodland edition since we only get one
in. And you got to understand where
we're coming from on that one. There's
only one coming in, right, for the whole
dealership. So, there's a clear coat
paint protector that's put on there.
>> Okay.
>> Also, there's an anti- theft. So, with
the Sienna and a Camry, I don't know how
they became the number one stolen cars.
It's awkward, but you have an anti-
theft put on there. And for the tires,
with a Woodland edition being it's kind
of off-road, the tires come with a tire
hazard warranty on their pre-applied for
the first 3 years. Damage a tire, hit a
pothole, environmental damages, they're
replaced.
>> Okay. Uh yeah, that's that's crazy. Uh
so why why do you guys have so so many
ads? It's crazy.
>> Uh well, that's kind of what all the
it's it's what every dealership is
doing. It's just which dealership's
going to be able to work with you. I
mean, I'm sorry. Let me see. But it's it
does come it does come on most of the
high-end Siennas, high-end Highlanders,
it's a paint protection on the emerald
green paint that you see on there.
>> Emerald. Oh, I was looking for the
Cyrus, but that's cool. Um like why why
are all these dealer why are all the
dealerships doing that?
>> Be honest.
>> Yeah.
>> One is because they only have one car
coming per dealership. Like some
dealerships might not have a Woodlands.
They're going to get an XLE and then
they'll call us to trade or we'll call
them to trade. But with minimum
inventory like this, like every month we
only get like two or three and they're
pre-ordered months in advance. There's
not much not much profit in these things
and they want to, you know, show it to
the customers that we're, you know,
we're protecting the paint, we're
protecting your tires, we're giving you,
you know, a warranty on the tires, but
because the inventory is just not there.
We only have one car. Oh,
>> okay. So, basically, there's not a lot
of profit in it. So you guys just add a
lot of profit to like you know Toyota
didn't give you enough money so you guys
take your own piece.
>> So if you look at it you could look at
you could look at Toyota or Toyota you
probably have a heart attack if you seen
theirs and then you come down
this way with Yeah. It gets a little bit
lighter but on all of the high-end
vehicles the Land Cruiser. No, we all do
it. No matter who you call you're going
to see dealer added accessories at the
port. You're going to see them put the
tinted windows on there. You're going to
see them put the film protected on the
paint. You're going to see them put the
anti- theft on there.
>> So, every
dealer does it. So, I wouldn't be
putting it on our price and then you
could call somebody else and they don't
have it. And ours is cheaper.
>> Yours is cheaper with a $6,000 add-on
package. That's crazy. Oh, I thought,
you know, I appreciate that, but that
seems insane that you guys are I thought
Toyota wasn't marking up any of their
cars or anything, but clearly that's not
the case. I thought they made a big
announcement about that. If I guess the
example would be like if we were selling
an iPhone 16, we're going to sell it
with a screen protector in a case.
>> Yeah. But like but with a screen
protector like if I buy a screen if I
buy a phone, right? Let's just say I buy
an iPhone 16. I don't have to put a
screen protector in a case on like the
the the cell phone store Verizon doesn't
force that on me and charge me $5,000
for that. Like my phone right now has no
case, no screen protector. I can take a
picture and send it to you, but it has
>> I totally understand.
>> See like like I just threw it behind me
because like I don't like I I risk it
for the biscuit
>> 100%. And you know, coming from a
business point and no cracks, it's
crazy. It works.
>> I totally understand and respect what
you're saying, but coming from like a
business standpoint on the one and only
car, we slapped everything on there to
protect it, and it does add value to the
car, you know, it does protect that
paint that's so precious, you know.
>> So, that's good news. Uh, so I have a
Sienna I'd be trading in. I got all of
those protection packages last time. So,
does that mean I get $6,000 more than
Kelly Blue Book when I trade mine in?
You will get more than Kelly Blue Book
when you trade it in. If it's in good
shape and you you got those protections
applied and they worked, of course, we
would just have to see your vehicle.
>> So So you guys are going to be more How
much more value does it add on my trade?
>> Well, I'm not the used car director. I
wish I can give you an appraisal number.
That's definitely something I'm not
allowed to do. But we would I know he
would want your Sienna and I know he
would.
>> And he would pay me $6,000 more than
like CarMax would give me cuz CarMax
didn't even ask if I had it. So, if I if
I just go get a CarMax offer, I feel
confident I'd get probably at least four
to $6,000 more than what CarMax is going
to offer for it because it's it's
because I have those protections I did
on my other car.
>> Well, you can you can use that as your
leverage. You know, you could go around
and see which
you know, you can sell it to CarMax and
then come to us.
>> Well, no. Why would I do that? You guys,
you guys are willing. You guys see all
this value and all these protection
package and you say that adds value to
the car. CarMax told me that it wasn't
it didn't add anything, right? CarMax
was like, "This doesn't like I I told
CarMax and they're like, "Oh, yeah. We
don't care about that. will offer you
the same either way. So, like, but you
guys, but you guys said it adds value.
So, like what what about I just bring my
Sienna and if you guys want to offer,
you can just buy it off of me and I
won't even buy a car from you guys. You
can just pay me $4 to $6,000 above
CarMax's offer because I have those
protection packages on there.
>> We might. Oh,
>> I've seen him do it. I've seen cars come
in with that little plastic film on the
hood like 10-year-old car with that
plastic film and the car is almost brand
new. You know what? If you let the boss
see it, we'll probably give you, you
know, a good value for it face to face.
You know, you can talk to the boss. I'll
show you the final price.
>> Can I just do it over the phone?
>> Well, over you have more leverage face
to face. If you want, give me your trade
information. I'll give it to the boss.
No, if you want to give me your trade
information, I'll give it to the boss. I
got your phone number here as
>> that is my phone number.
>> Okay. I just text you. If you want to
reply yes, I'll shoot you.
>> Okay. And you're and you're saying that
the reason why this is happening is just
coming to availability. There's nothing
else in the world that'd be causing all
these prices to go up.
>> Just availability. And you know when
when things just like in co the prices
skyrocketed and you could say for no
reason.
>> For no reason. There's no particular
reason why now all of it's happening.
>> Well, it's a inventory shortage. But
>> but why is there an inventory shortage?
>> A lot of customers love these things.
Oh, yeah. I don't know, man. You know,
Toyota and Nissan, that's a big world of
their own. Inventory shortage as well.
Okay. Wow. I didn't know that. I'm
learning so much.
>> No, Nissan doesn't. Nissan doesn't. And
they'll never have a shortage. I think
they're okay for the next two years.
Nobody has a shortage but Toyota cuz
they're the best brand out there. If you
look at any other brand, you can find
any model you want, any anything you
want, but not Toyota.
>> Oh, okay. Got it. Okay. Okay. Well, I
don't think we're getting anywhere, but
I appreciate the conversation. It was a
good conversation.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Thank you.
>> So, if you guys don't know, my name's
Tommy. I negotiate car deals for a
living. Every phone call we are making
is for a client. We are not calling just
to waste people's time. We are calling
for clients. People pay us a flat fee of
a,000 bucks. We handle the entire
negotiation. We do 150 to 200 car deals
a month.
>> Thank you for calling. This is Christian
who I have the pleasure of speaking
with.
>> Christian. My name's Tommy. How's it
going?
>> Doing good, Tommy. How you doing, man?
>> Man, I'm living a dream every day of my
life. I just want to see if you guys
have a car available.
>> Yes, sir. Which car was it?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Um, yeah. Just give me one second. My
computer's loading up.
>> No, you're good.
>> Is it a new or used vehicle?
>> Brand spanking new.
>> Awesome, man. All right. I'm ready for
that stock. Stock number is going to be
H as in hybrid 422190.
I
>> think it's available because most of the
time whenever we have a stock number
included in it. It is. And it doesn't
say that it's sold. But do you mind if I
go outside real quick and try to touch
it?
>> Yeah. Yeah. If you want to put your
hands on it, that
>> second. Yes, sir. Just give me one sec.
Okay. I got
>> I'll give you take literally take all
the time you need. I'm in no rush.
>> All right. Thank you, man. I'll be right
back.
>> No problem.
>> Meanwhile,
>> hey, Tommy, you still there?
>> Yep. I'm still here.
>> All right. Awesome, man. The car is
available. Well, would you like to come
in today to take a look at it?
>> You know, I've already driven it. I
already fell in love with it. This is an
awesome car. It's Subaru chef's kiss. Uh
I'm really just looking for the best
numbers on it. Ready to buy it today.
>> Okay, I got you, man. Um are you are you
local?
>> Uh you know, I'm in Florida. Uh I'm in
Tampa area, but you know, I'm want to
drive for a good deal.
>> I got you. What was your zip code?
>> My zip code would be
>> Awesome, man. Just got to make sure I
get everything right with the taxes. And
then what was your last name, Tommy?
>> My last name is Makula. M I K U L A.
Awesome, man. All right. Well, I'll put
together some numbers for you. Um, I'm
assuming that you've already gotten some
numbers somewhere else if you've driven
one. Can I ask you what the best out the
door price you're trying to achieve or
payment is?
>> I've gotten 10% off the car.
>> 10% off the car. Okay.
>> Easy peasy.
>> Yes, sir. All right, man. Well, let me
put together you something and then I'll
give you a call back. All right.
>> All right. Sounds good.
>> All right. Thank you, Tommy. I'll talk
to you soon. Bye-bye.
>> No problem. Bye.
>> This is Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. It's Christian with How You
doing, man?
>> Hey, man. I'm doing well. How about
yourself?
>> I'm doing good, man. So, um, this is
what we were able to do for you. We can
discount the car $3,586,
leaving your sales price at 42260 from
the MSRP. So, that's really the best
that we could do, man.
>> 35.86 is the best you could do on the
bronze.
>> Yes, sir. That's the best uh discount
that we could do.
>> Okay. And do you guys have any add-ons
or fees or anything crazy?
>> Um, no add-ons to that. The only thing
that you will see is we have a dealer
fee and then of course, you know, your
DMV stuff.
>> Okay. 35.86 off. Okay. Can you just send
that to me? I just need to compare and
contrast to what color we want now.
>> Yeah. I mean, I didn't get a breakdown
of the numbers. They wrote on a sticky
note for me.
>> Okay. Do you need a whole proposal? So,
>> something I have I just got to compare
and contrast to see what color we want
now cuz we have a better deal on the
other color. I just need to decide if
we're are we going to be that picky on
that or not. So, having it side by side
makes it easy. But whatever you send me
is fine.
>> All right, man. Well, I appreciate it.
>> Yeah. Yeah, no problem. Like I said, I'm
hopeully hopefully we get this wrapped
up. We really like this color. So,
>> all righty. Well, um yeah. I mean, if
you guys would consider this color, I'll
definitely go grab a proposal. But if
it's just going to be one of those
things, not trying to sound like, you
know, a jerk or anything, but where I go
have them printed out for you guys just
to, you know, work us some more. This is
really all that we have.
>> Yeah. No, that's fine. Like I said, I
have a better deal already. Like, so
like I'm not shopping your deal. That's
what you're worried about. It's more
just comparing, contra I have a bigger
deal on the white one. I just need to
decide side by side. Do we want the
white one? Do we want the brown as well?
Go from there. But no, I'm not.
>> Okay, I got you. Yeah. Let me uh let me
grab your proposal and I'll send it
right over. All right.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> All right. Thanks, man. Bye.
>> Talk to you soon.
>> Bye.
>> Thank you for calling. It's Britney. How
can I help you?
>> Hey Britney, I was just seeing if there
was a car available.
>> Yeah. Do you have the stock number?
>> Uh, yes. It's 418996.
>> And what's the year, make a model?
>> 2025 Forester Hybrid Touring.
>> Okay, let me see.
>> Take it down.
>> Does it show us at the um Subaru
or the Subaru?
>> Uh,
>> okay. Let me see.
>> Good.
>> Okay, I do see it here. It looks like it
is still available. Did you want to come
in for a test drive?
>> Hey, I've already driven it already.
Know I love it. Really? Just trying to
get some numbers on it.
>> Okay. Yeah. Um, do you want me to get
you over to somebody to speak on the
phone with it?
>> That'd be great.
>> Okay. Um, would I be able to get your
name so I can let them know who's
calling?
>> Yeah. My name is Tony.
>> Okay. All right. Just one moment. Okay.
>> Mhm. No problem.
>> This is Shane. How can I help you?
>> Hey, Shane. I just uh did I was Do you
have that car numbers?
>> Yes, Tony. How are you?
>> Hey, I'm doing well.
>> Hey, so the only question I did have for
you real quick um actually I have a
couple questions. First one. Did you
test drive it here or did you test drive
somewhere else?
>> Somewhere else.
>> Okay. I just wanted to make sure you
weren't working with anybody here.
That's all. I didn't want to step on
anybody's toes.
>> Yeah. Yeah. No. No. No toes being
stepped on. We're not dancing on a
floor.
>> I got you. All good. Hey, so um are you
looking for cash pricing? Finance
pricing? What are you looking for?
>> Uh we are looking for cash or finance.
Either way, whatever makes the most
sense.
>> Okay. Absolutely. So now, do you have
any sort of trade in or anything like
that?
>> No trade.
>> Okay. Now, did you get a price from the
other dealership that you drove it at?
Uh, yes.
>> Okay. Do you have that on paper so I can
see if my manager is willing to beat it
right off the bat and make it easy and
earn your business that way?
>> I have 10% off. I haven't I literally
just got the phone with them, but they
had white and I was looking for bronze.
So, I was hoping to get one on a bronze.
>> Oh, I got you. I got you. So, it was 10%
off at that point. Perfect. So, let
>> me You guys can beat just beat that.
Bada boom, bada bing. I'll buy yours cuz
you have the color I want.
>> Hey, I completely get it. So, let me get
with my manager here. The number you
called in on.
>> Yep. That's the best number for me.
>> All righty. Give me maybe 5 10 minutes.
I will get with my manager and I will
call you back. The only other question I
do have is are you transferring a plate?
>> We do have a plate. Yeah.
>> Okay. And then what's just the zip code
that you're going to be registering it
to so we can figure out taxes and all
that.
>> Three.
>> All righty. Give me a few minutes.
>> Number. Thank you. Have a great day.
>> All right. Take care.
>> Bye.
>> Thank you guys so much. If you guys want
to tune on, make sure you guys like,
follow, subscribe. I appreciate each and
every one of you. If you guys want more
of this kind of content, like, follow,
subscribe. I charge a flat fee of a,000
bucks. I negotiate car deals. We do
anywhere between 150 to 200 deals a
month. Thank you guys so much for the
support. I'm out. Bye-bye.
[Music]