I'm here cuz I'm calling for price.
>> For the price, we have a dealership
markup is sitting at $57,000
from the manager.
>> Huh? Can you say what? I I don't want to
play the game. I'm just telling you the
price. I'll pay. And if you don't want
to do it, I get it. But I'm not willing
to pay 5,000. I'm going to say no deal.
>> There's hundreds of if not thousands of
Honda dealerships nationwide. Maybe
someone will sell to you for MSRP.
>> Yeah. My aunt said there was a sucker
born every day and I feel like you guys
just found the right sucker that was
want to pay 15K above sticker. I'm gonna
like buy a billboard right outside your
building saying don't pay for this
markup at this dealership. So then you
guys have to keep holding it on forever.
>> Yeah. I mean I get it if you're like
dude these these cars sell before they
ever hit the lot but you guys have had
it for 3 months.
>> You know what they're thinking? This is
the last red one on the east coast and
anybody and everybody's calling about
it.
>> Oh I've I've called like 10 on the east
coast so I can tell you that it's not
the only red one.
>> Do a type dealio. I do have a type
dealio. This is going to be a Honda day.
Just so you guys know, we're a Honda
family today. I'm going to do a Type R
negotiation. Let's have some fun.
There's only 29 Type Rs in red. Okay,
red. There's only 26 of these cars.
Okay, this client lives in the West
Coast. Uh, this dealership says they
have one.
>> Thank you for choosing
the 20 or 200,000 mi powertrain
protection plan. This is Alex from
sales.
>> Hello, Alex in sales. This is Tommy from
buying. How's it going?
>> Doing good. How about yourself? How can
I help? How can I help you out? And I I
just want to see if you guys have a car
available.
>> Sure. What car are you looking at?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Sure.
>> It is W is in Walmart 501514.
>> Oh, yeah. The Type R.
>> Type R and rally red. That's That's the
car.
>> Yep. That vehicle's here. Were you
thinking of coming on out and seeing it?
>> Well, I've already driven one. I already
know. I love it. I It's the car I want.
Really just trying to get some great
pricing on it and hoping you can help me
out.
>> I can go and ask. I do know that we are
when it comes to pricing, it's
definitely like exclusive pricing for
people who want to come on in, but I can
run it off my manager.
>> Exclusive pricing like
>> I do not have a available price at the
moment. I can ask my manager to give it
to you though.
>> Yeah, I mean that'd be great. The good
news is like on your website it says
it's 47045 if I do the estimated price
summary. So I mean can I just buy it at
that price and call today?
>> I can ask.
>> Yeah, I mean that'd be great. It's on
your website. I know it says customize
your deal and free shipping, pick up the
car and all that. So yeah, 47045 I'll
buy the car.
>> Sure. Would you mind holding one second?
I can ask my manager for you.
>> Sure.
>> All right. Please hold.
>> Meanwhile,
>> all right. So I just asked my manager.
So we're offering the vehicle for 48585
because what we're what we put in was a
ceramic coating New England season
package which can which includes like
the all weather mats and well the
ceramic coating.
>> Okay. So you're saying it's it's what
like $1,500 above MSRP? We're putting it
at 48682 before taxes and fees.
>> 682. So like $1640
or $37,
>> I'm sorry.
>> So it's like $1637
of add-ons.
>> Yeah.
>> The vehicle's tricked out because we've
got a full-on ceramic coat. We've got
the all weather mats. We've got wheel
locks on it.
>> So you guys are willing to sell would
would you guys sell it for the 47045?
I'm not authorized to to go any lower
than that that price, unfortunately.
>> So, the lowest price that you're
authorized to do is 48637.
>> 48682.
>> 682. Sorry.
>> 48682
>> 682. Who So, who's authorized to go
lower?
>> I got this directly from my manager just
now.
>> I mean, if you can send that down in
writing, I mean, that doesn't seem like
a horrible deal. It's 1,500 bucks above
MSRP. I don't love it. Um, but I mean,
I'd really like to be at MSRP.
>> It's mostly in packages.
>> Yeah. No, I get I get that it's in
packages extra packages. Yeah.
>> Yeah. No, I get that it's in extra
packages. Um, like I said, that's why
I'm considering it
>> be it be the 47050, I think, before all
this.
>> Yeah.
>> 47090. My fault.
>> 47090.
Wait, 4709. Okay.
>> Before all these packages.
>> And then there's $1600 in packages.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. Yeah. I mean, if you send that
down in writing, I can look it over. I
mean, again, I'd like to be an MSRP. If
you want to tell your boss that, that's
that's a done deal for me.
>> Sure. If you give me your name and if
you give me your name and number, I can
create a file and send it over your way.
>> Yeah, that'd be great. My name is Tommy.
Last name Mula. M I K U L A.
>> M I K U L A. And I assume this is your
cell phone.
>> This is Yeah. The number.
>> That is it.
>> Awesome. I just sent you a text message
optin. So, if you respond to that, I'll
we'll make sure you get the pricing and
everything we just discussed. All right.
>> Yeah, that'd be great. I appreciate it,
Alex.
>> It's my pleasure.
>> Okay, sounds good. Talk to you soon.
>> Talk to you soon. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> Thanks for calling Honda Kenny.
>> Hey, Kenny. How's it going?
>> Good. How are you?
>> Hey, doing well. Doing well. Hey, I just
wanted to see if you guys have a car
available.
>> What kind of car are you looking for?
>> I I have the uh stock number if that
helps.
>> Is it used or new?
>> It's It says new on the screen, so I
imagine it's new.
>> Okay. What is your name, by the way?
>> Uh my name is Tommy.
>> Tommy. Nice to meet you, Tommy. Uh what
is your stock number, by the Uh yeah.
Stock number is 254194.
>> Oh, this is Type R.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Do you want to come in?
>> Well, I've already driven one. I already
know. I love it, man. You know,
obviously when you see a Type R that's
red, you're just like big eyes. Yeah. I
love it. So, uh I'm I'm here cuz I'm
calling for price.
>> For the price. We have a dealership
markup is sitting at $57,000
from the manager.
>> Huh? Can he say what?
>> $57,000 before taxes and everything
>> before taxes. Correct. Markup for my
manager.
>> So, it's your manager's fault.
>> I have no control over that because
that's the only one you need.
>> Do I got to talk to your manager to get
it off?
>> So, what are you currently looking at?
>> This car?
>> I know, but like the pricing.
>> Yeah. Mr. RP
>> 47,000.
>> Yeah. Be a great price. I'd be happy
with that price. I'd buy that car at the
price.
>> You buy the car if if if it's that
price?
>> Yeah.
>> Let me give you a call back. I I'll talk
to them right now. Let's see what what
they say.
>> I love it. Let's get Let's get the Let's
Let's talk to the manager. Let's get
them to get off the markup. I'll buy it.
>> Okay. Tommy, right? What is your last
name, Tommy?
>> Last name, Makula. M I K U L A.
>> M I K. One more time.
>> U L A.
>> Okay. Mula. Okay. Call you back in a
bit. Okay.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> All right. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> Good afternoon.
>> Hey. I I just want to see if you guys
have a car available.
>> Yes, sir. Absolutely. Let me take a
look. May I have your first name,
please?
>> Uh my first name is Tommy.
>> Mr. Tommy. Okay. And what kind of
vehicle are you looking for? New or you?
>> Uh yeah. It's a brand new car. I have I
think the stock number. I thought I saw
Yeah, I have the stock number. That
helps.
>> That just the last four of that would be
appreciated.
>> Of course. 5255.
>> Let's take a look. Civic Type R. It is
here and available, Tommy. It's It's
red. Are you looking to come out today?
>> You know what? I've already driven one.
I already knew I fell in love with it.
Really just trying to get what kind of
pricing you guys do. I know a lot of
people play some crazy games on these
cars, so calling ahead of time.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Are you um are you
calling from the area?
>> I'm not actually. I'm I'm out of state,
but you know, I'm always down for a good
road trip.
>> I got you. Sounds like me. I mean, we
have a market adjustment if I shoot you
straight, but I mean, what do you what
are you looking to accomplish? What are
you What are you comfortable or what are
you looking to pay for one?
>> I'm looking to pay MSRP, the
manufacturer suggested retail price.
>> Okay. Yeah, we don't I mean, we're
willing to come down, but we don't sell
them for for MSRP. If you can find that,
I'm sure you'll you know, you'll take a
road trip anywhere, but um we won't even
sell it for MSRP for a local. We only
get one a year. Well, maybe two a year.
Are you flexible at all or is that just
>> I'm an MSRP or bus type of guy. My mom
would not let me go come home if I
bought a car at MSRP. Not for
Thanksgiving or Christmas.
>> Okay. Well, we don't want that. But I
will say it's probably acceptable to pay
a little over MSRP on some vehicles out
there. And I I would say the Type R,
even though we don't have to get the
full 8,000, I would say it's probably
worth a little more than MSRP in my
professional opinion. But there's
hundreds of if not thousands of Honda
dealerships nationwide. Maybe someone
will sell to you for MSRP.
>> Yeah, I mean that's kind of that's kind
of what I'm thinking here. I mean I
think there has to be somebody. I mean
there's there's enough of these cars.
It's not like there's four in the
nation. There's there's hundreds that
are sitting on lots that are all
charging the same thing. So I imagine
somebody wants to sell a car at the end
of the month, right?
>> I mean, yeah, but we won't we won't let
it go just just to move a unit. We only
get two a year and usually they sell
closer to eight. Are you willing to
negotiate anywhere or is it just got to
be that or nothing?
>> I'm you know what? Like a lot of people
get mad because they say like customers
are liars and customers play games. I'm
not a game player. I don't I don't go to
board. Uh um you know for me I'm an MSRP
or bus type of guy.
>> I got you. Okay. Yeah. And I'm not not
trying to play games. I'm just trying to
be
>> Oh, I'm not saying you're playing games,
but I know a lot of people say the car
that the customers play games, right?
Like I tell you one price. I I don't
want to play the game. I'm just telling
you the price I'll pay. And if you don't
want to do it, I get it. Okay.
>> I got you. Yeah. I just I won't be right
there, Tommy. I'm sorry. But I do
appreciate your call.
>> Okay. Hey, no problem. Have a great day.
You too, sir. Thank you.
>> Hello. I'm so sorry. I'm back.
>> Hey, Tommy. Tommy, this is calling back
from
>> Kenny. What did What did the big man
say?
>> So, the big man said $5,000 above the
MSRP, not 10 anymore. So, 52,44 bucks.
>> I feel like right now, have you seen the
show Deal or No Deal with Howie Mandel?
And somebody has a case and I have the
case here and I can't open the case and
the banker just made me an offer. I just
don't think it's a good offer. I feel
like I have the MSRP case that I can
find and I'm willing to keep calling
around until I can find it, but I'm not
willing to pay 5,000. I'm going to say
no deal.
>> I mean, I would love to help you out,
Tommy. You know, I'd love to buy a car
from you. This would be great. Match
made in heaven, Kenny and Tommy.
>> I know, but here's the thing. I don't
make that decision, right? I just talk
to him. He just immediately said, "No."
So, I said, "Can we do like, you know,
at least better the pricing?" He's like,
"Yes, 5,000. No more 10,000." You know,
I don't I don't control the price.
>> I get it. But um honestly man, just you
know, shop around. Let's see, you know,
who offer you the best and go for it. If
not, I'll be here for you because this
car is the only color, the only interior
that we currently have around the the
district. So that's why they mark it up
at that price.
>> I get that it's the only one in your
district. It's not the only one in the
in the world, though. So, you know, I I
I appreciate it, but I'm not willing to
pay 5 $10,000 of MSR above MSRP. That's
I mean, that's just crazy talk, you
know. I know it was 15,000. 15,000.
>> See, the thing is you guys keep lowering
it. Nobody's buying it. You guys have
had it, you know, a few almost a month
now on your lot. So,
>> so somebody bought it at over $15,000
above M RP a few months back. That's why
that's why they did it again. And
honestly, we have a lot of interest
lately, but people kept on shopping
around too before making a decision
buying from us.
>> Yeah. My aunt said there was a sucker
born every day. And I feel like you guys
just found the right sucker that was
willing to pay 15K above sticker. That's
crazy. That's crazy. And just think
about that. If they just would have
listened to me and you talk, they would
have saved 10K cuz now you're down to
5K, you know?
>> Yeah.
>> Wow. That's crazy. Like we I Me and that
customer would have paid a $10,000
difference uh within a few months apart
on the same car.
>> Yeah, I know. I get that. I mean, Tommy,
just you know, I encourage you to like
shop around if you can find it. We can
talk about that later on. Honestly, I
would love to save you some money.
>> I'm going to keep I'm going to keep
shopping around. I feel confident I will
find one at MSRP. Okay, awesome, man.
Talk to you later.
>> Talk to you later. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> I'm going to be like straight up. This
is the reason why consumers don't like
buying a car because two people can walk
into the same building, buy the same
product, and pay a $10,000
difference. That's why people don't like
buying a car. And also, for all the
people that say the price is online,
just the price is online. None of these
dealerships are adver that dealership
advertised the car at 47K. Every
dealership we're clicking on is
advertising at MSRP. They don't
advertise it at above MSRP because guess
what? They'd get in trouble by Honda.
>> Honda, this is us with
>> Hey, uh, I just wanted to call and see
if you guys not only have a car
available, but the price of said car.
>> Sure. Let me check and see. What car
were you looking at?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Yes. Give me one second. Let me just get
there.
>> No problem. Let me grab my scroll. Let
me know when you're ready.
>> Go ahead. What was that stock number?
>> Okay. It is S as in Sierra. X is in
X-ray 004620.
>> What kind of car is it?
>> This is a Civic. Just an old Civic. Just
a normal old everyday Civic.
>> What year?
>> 2025.
>> Oh, was it a new vehicle?
>> It is a new vehicle. Yeah, I was looking
for a new vehicle.
>> Okay. Okay.
>> And Zach Morris, I'm not scaring anybody
into anything. Literally, that's what
happened on that phone call. Somebody
came in and spent $10,000 more.
>> Yeah. You reached the used car desk.
That's all I got.
>> Oh, I'm sorry. All I just pushed the new
car button on the phone.
>> No, no, you're totally good. It's just I
don't automatically uh see their stuff.
600.
>> I'm muting him when I'm talking to you
guys, too. So, like he can't hear me.
Hi, car salesman.
>> Looks like there was a deal working on
it yesterday. Let me banana if that is
uh
>> that's good. Take your time.
>> Hey, David. This is a good deal from
yesterday at Red Civic was sold. You
know, I don't know why the deal I don't
know.
>> I'm not staring at anybody into
anything. That literally is what
happens. Zackmore. Somebody I just
called the saleserson said somebody just
paid 15K the other day.
>> I was just making sure that it's a sold
unit.
>> And if that that person literally paid
they were not educated on buying a car.
Nothing to do with me. They didn't need
to know me. If they watch my channel,
they wouldn't have paid it. They didn't
have to pay me to learn that
information. But an uneducated buyer now
is overpaying. How hard is that to
understand? I'm not scaring. If if you
guys don't hire me, then you're going to
get screwed by Zack Morris. Hey, if you
guys just watch me and be educated, Zach
Morris will never screw you over. Like
that's that's the truth. If you just
watch me, you don't have to hire me.
It's a Civic.
>> It's a Civic Type R.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. Just the Civic. Uh,
yeah. The Type R.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So, it says, "Please call
for price." So, I'm here calling for
price.
>> Okay. I got you. Here, let me Sorry. Let
me Let me put you to the new car desk,
man. Um, cuz they'll have everything
right in front of them.
>> Perfect. That's great.
>> Okay. Give me one sec.
>> Honda, come help you.
>> Hey, uh, I was looking to see if there
was a new car available. I was talking
to a used car guy and he was like, I'm
not helping you. and not really, but he
was like, "I can't help you. I don't do
this." So, he's like, "Let me get you to
somebody cooler." And then I got to you.
>> Okay. Can I help you with, sir?
>> Oh, awesome. So, first off, I want to
see if a car is available. And then I
wanted to get the numbers on said car.
>> Okay. Is it the red tap bar?
>> It is. Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> Correct. Zach Morris. This is one of the
ways they can get set information. How
does somebody find information on buying
a car? They look online like on TikTok.
Watching me is educating on how to buy a
car.
>> You calling me from, sir? Oh, I'm
calling you from um from a few states
over, but I just looking for a Type R.
>> Are you in the States or
>> I'm in the United States? Yes.
>> What state are you in?
>> Yeah. I mean, are most people calling
you outside the United States?
>> Yeah, a lot of them. Yeah, we've been
having this this week.
>> Oh, wow. That's crazy.
>> North Carolina. We had Washington,
California.
>> Wow, that is insane. No, I'm in Nevada.
I'm in Vegas.
>> Nevada.
>> Yeah.
>> But I like a road trip for a good
>> Carvex, Kelly Blue Book, NADA. any of
those research will help you do prior to
going. That is not going to be good
research on buying a new car. What are
you saying? If you're going to be like a
legitimate, right, and you be like,
"Yeah,
>> 50 grand plus tax on license." I don't
know what the taxes over there are. Like
I'm sorry, what was the price? Sorry,
apologize. I was talking to somebody
that was annoying me. Not you.
>> Yeah. 50,000 plus tax on license.
>> 50,000.
>> Yep.
>> Okay. So, and the MSRP is 47.
>> 470 or 45. Same as
>> Okay. So, you guys are charging Is it a
3K markup?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Okay. Um Well, I'd love to buy the car.
or I'm just wasn't interested in paying
a markup. So, if we can do MSRP, we got
a car deal.
>> Yeah. That's why people calling out of
states cuz nobody can find them.
>> Yeah, I've called a few dealerships. You
know, everybody's trying to charge crazy
markup on it. My my goal is to get one
MSRP. You know, I'm not selfish or
crazy. I'm not trying to be below, but I
know somebody will sell it for MSRP. You
guys are close. I mean, you guys are
almost there.
>> Yeah. Good luck, buddy. Okay.
>> Grand is where we at.
>> Yeah. No problem. I'll keep a good one.
>> All right. Bye.
>> This one said, "Please call for price."
So, I'll give them some benefit of the
doubt. This one here, 215 days, that one
is not a car that's available. We called
this one here 47045 MSRP. The sales
price is 47045. This dealership was
charging 10K markup. I think this one
was charging 3K. This one didn't have it
listed. This one was charging what? 5K.
This is the one said, "Have a nice day."
This one here was the one I just called
that had a 5k markup on the car that is
advertising it below MSRP. I know you
Oh, shoot. You guys can't see. Sorry,
you guys can't see. This dealership is
advertising this below MSRP. And now I'm
going to call this dealership right here
in real time. This dealership is
advertising MSRP. Let's see if they
charge it.
>> Hi, this is Timber at
Sorry I missed your call. Please leave a
message and I will get back to you as
soon as I can. Please keep in mind that
I'm typically off on Wednesdays. Thanks
for calling.
>> He's not available to take your call.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Hey man, it's Tommy boy. Uh hopefully
you're doing well. Hopefully kids are
doing well. Uh school starts soon, so
you know, life is good. Life is great.
And uh hopefully you are just having the
most awesome day you've ever had on a
Thursday. It's not Wednesday, so that
means you had your day off, so you
should feel refreshed and energized. If
you don't, I get it cuz Labor Day
weekend's coming up. Anyway, I'm looking
for a car on your website. If you can
give me a call back. Uh my phone number
again, this is Tommy Boy. Uh some people
call me Tommy Business. So uh if you
want to get down to business, let's um
call me back. Bye.
>> 100 sales is Sterling. How can I help
you?
>> Hello. I am looking to purchase a
vehicle and I would like to inquire to
see if it is available.
>> Okay, gotcha. Who do I have the pleasure
of speaking to?
>> My name is Tommy.
>> Tommy, what's your last name?
>> Mula.
>> How do you spell that?
>> M I K U L A. I'm sorry. What was your
name?
>> Ashley. Sounds awesome. My name is
Sterling.
>> Sterling. What was the last name?
>> Last name.
>> Okay, got it. Sterling guy. I'm writing
that down, too.
>> And what vehicle are you looking for?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Okay. What is it?
>> It is S as in service. X is in X ray
004334.
Couldn't think of anything that started
with an X.
>> Got you. Give me one sec. You're looking
for the Type R.
>> Civic Type R. You got it.
>> Yes. In red. Okay. What question do you
have about it?
>> Well, I already know I want it. I'm
trying to buy one. It says please call
for price. So, I'm calling for price.
>> Yes, you are. So, I would say honestly,
man, just come in. It says please call.
Uh, the price is the MSRP plus the
protection package that we have plus the
10K markup.
>> Sorry, I literally just fell over. What?
Sorry, you literally just knocked me
unconscious. What? What? I'm What?
>> Yeah. So, it's the MSRP plus a
protection package plus uh the 10K
markup adjustment.
>> I I guess I have so many questions. What
is the What is a protection package?
>> The protection package is splash guards,
window tent, wheel lock, and the
lifetime powertrain warranty. And how
and how much is that?
>> 13.95.
>> 13.95. And you said there was another
package.
>> It's the uh the 10K market adjustment.
>> Okay. So the Okay. So 10K market
adjustment and the 13.95. So why would I
come in?
>> You said why would you come in?
>> Why would I come in? I'm confused. You
said come on in. And then he told me
that all that.
>> So cuz it says on the website, please
call for the price. I'm obviously I'm
going to honor that. I'm not going to
just go against the website, but if that
price is good with you, come on in. And
yeah, we make something happen. It is
Labor Day. So
>> I appreciate that. I'm down to buy the
car. I know you guys have had it for 103
days, but I can see why maybe you've had
it for 103 days. You're charging, you
know, $11,000 a markup.
>> I mean, it's a it's a Type R. So,
>> I get it, but you've had it for 100
days. So, like, it's not like it's like,
oh, it's flying off the shelf.
Everybody's trying to buy it. You've had
it for 3 months.
>> I mean, you know what's crazy? When I
first started working here, we had a
white Type R. They had that. They had it
for months. So, somebody somebody's
going to buy it. Somebody's always in
the market for a Type R, and they are
willing to pay that. I'm gonna like buy
a billboard right outside your building
saying don't pay for this markup at this
dealership. So then you guys have to
keep holding it on forever.
>> I mean here's the thing. Everything is
negotiable. Obviously you just come in
and talk about it and then we come to a
number that's agreeable for the
dealership and you then I'm more than
happy to get it cleaned up for you, get
it gassed up and get you on the road.
>> See I'll save us all time. I'll pay
MSRP. Call it a day. Exactly what the
manufacturer suggested.
>> Manufacturer. So that that is not even
including the um the premium color
that's on it. I mean, the red is not a
premium color for Honda, but if you were
to get a white one or blue one, it would
be that's not including destination
either. And that's not including dealer
add-ons.
>> MSRP does include the the paint color
and the destination. MSRP does.
>> So, the sticker that Honda prints, it
actually does or I guess if you So,
there is two numbers on the sticker. The
top one where it says MSRP, that's what
the manufacturer recommends. And then we
go to the bottom, it does include
destination handling. That's if that's
the number that you're talking about.
Perfect. I'll pay that price. The one
that includes the destination and
handling of the what? Probably 13.95,
which is probably 47,065.
Somewhere in that ballpark.
>> Yeah. Yeah, it is somewhere in that
ballpark.
>> Yeah. That's what most people would
consider manufactured suggested retail
price. It's on the Monroy sticker. I'm
not talking about the top number. I'm
not being crazy. I'm talking about the
bottom number. I'm just not talking
about the extra piece of paper on the
right hand side of the window sticker
that says dealer addendum. I I just
don't want to pay. I like just rip that
one off, right? That you just throw that
away. You can play basketball with it.
Swish. Sterling makes a three-pointer.
>> I'm sorry.
>> I said you can't just rip it off. It is
on the car. The protection package is
something that we're not going to come
off of. And
>> the 10k markup is on the car. There's no
way to get rid of that. How?
>> No, I'm talking about the protection
package, not the markup.
>> Okay. So, you guys will sell it for the
1395. 10K markup.
>> Yeah. When you come in, we can talk
about it.
>> Well, why don't you just do it with the
1395? No 10K markup.
>> Can't do it. My managers literally will
not allow that.
>> What do you mean? That's the 10K markup
isn't on the car. There's is on the
addendum on the car.
>> Yeah, but the addendum is just taped on
with some like double-sided tape. Like
it'd be really easy to rip that off.
>> I'm sorry. Say that one more time.
>> The addendum that's on right next to the
window sticker would be very easy to rip
off. Like it wouldn't be hard to rip
that off as if it didn't exist.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I mean, it's just paper. At
the end of the day, this is a business
and this is a rare car. Obviously, if
you find another Type R in the market
that the dealer wants to just sell you
it at MSRP, please just bring me the
buyer's order. I I still doubt my
manager would do that, honestly.
>> Yeah. I mean, I get it if you're like,
"Dude, these these cars sell before they
ever hit the lot, but you guys have had
it for 3 months." Clearly, you guys are
just waiting for a sucker. Like, that's
what you guys are doing. It's not this
vehicle's hot. This vehicle is crazy.
It's hey, here at Honda, we just want a
sucker to to buy this vehicle cuz we're
hoping somebody pays for it. I mean,
that's kind of your business model right
now, which is I mean, that's okay. I
mean, some people have a business model
of hoping that people aren't going to do
research, but that's the business model.
This car first got here, we had a blue
Type R and so that one was displayed in
the showroom. This one was put up in the
parking garage and I believe it wasn't
on the it could have been on the website
initially, but that blue one sold and
then that's when we moved this one up
front
>> and then the white one that was also
there for months on end that eventually
sold.
>> Yeah.
>> I mean, you guys noticed it on your Type
R for months on end. I mean, again, it's
it's fine. Like that's your business
model. Like we want to overcharge for
the car and hope that somebody is
willing to overpay for it. we're willing
to wait months for that to happen rather
than just selling it at the what Honda
tells you you should sell it at cuz
there's a reason why you're not
advertising that price, right? There's a
reason because Honda would, you know,
smack you upside the head if you were
advertising 10K above MSRP. They don't
allow that because they don't want their
man their dealers to charge above MSRP.
So, yeah, I'm I'm willing to do it. I'm
just not willing to uh do, you know, the
1395 I'd consider, right? I'll consider
that. Oh, he hung up. You know what
happened? The second I said the
dealership name, he started getting
phone calls, which is fair. I did say
the dealership name, but like this is
and this is again this is like this is
this is a business philosophy some
people have which is fine but he said it
very clearly. We have it for months. We
know if somebody we will wait long
enough somebody will pay for it. So what
you're waiting for is a sucker to come
in to pay 10 $15,000 a markup. That is
what you're waiting on. That is the only
answer that is legitimate there. Like if
that's what you want to be your business
philosophy then own it. Call it a day.
Yep. We're waiting for the biggest
sucker to come in here and pay above
MSRP. And this is why I don't like
Honda's Type R. The Type R has a
artificially created markup system. The
reason why there's a markup is like
every dealership has agreed there should
be a markup. If we look at a Porsche
911, right, those cars don't hit the lot
and dealers are charging markups for
them. It somewhat makes sense because
the cars don't sit on the lot for 3
months. If a car is sitting on your lot
for months, it's no longer a super hard
to get car because if it was, somebody
would pay that 10k mark up without
thinking about it. Maybe not in day one,
but 3 months later. 3 months later.
Uh, I don't know who this is, but it's
going to be dangerous, but I'll answer.
This is
>> It's Tommy, right?
>> Yeah, this is it.
>> Okay. Hey, Tommy. This is Josh down
here. How are you, buddy?
>> Oh my goodness. I told you to take your
time, and you took your time, and I
appreciate that. Did you get that sale?
>> I'm a man of Oh, yeah. Yeah. It's been
uh Yeah. Once you get into vacation
season all the way to Christmas, it's
basically Honda's time to shine. So,
it's been pretty hectic in a good way,
you know.
>> Hey, that's Hey, that's a good that's a
good problem to have. I want to Let's
make it quick and easy. What do you got
for me, boss?
>> All right. So, here's what they got on
the vehicle. They have an they have an
addendum on it. It's a $49.95 addendum.
So, the price on it is $52,40
plus your TTNL. Did you say you lived in
North Carolina?
>> I don't. No. I used to live in North
Carolina, which is why I call back cuz I
think the dealerships are better here.
Uh, but I don't like $49.95 a markup.
>> Yeah. Wow. They are open to, you know,
reasonable offers. You know what they're
thinking? This is the last red one on
the East Coast and anybody and
everybody's calling about it.
>> Oh, I've I've called like 10 on the East
Coast, so I can tell you that it's not
the only red one.
>> The red one? Yeah. Well, I mean, last
time we checked, but I mean, that's
where they would like to be. I mean, do
you have any
>> I'll give you the secret intel. There's
two in Georgia, two in Tennessee, two in
Ohio, six in New Hampshire, one in
Philadelphia, one in New Jersey, and two
in Eastern Pennsylvania, or sorry,
Western Pennsylvania, but I wouldn't
call that I didn't call it the East
Coast.
>> Absolutely. Have you tried to purchase
any of them off of any of them?
>> Yeah, I've been calling around today.
That's why I was waiting on your
numbers. The best offer I have right now
is 1,800 above MSRP.
>> Yeah. I mean, you tell me and I'll take
it to, you know, the owner. It's not
It's not me. I mean, these are
specialty, you know, cars that this is
the fourth one in five years that we've
had. So,
>> no, I get it. I'm trying to be an MSRP.
That's my goal. Like I said, I have 18
above, 1,800 under above MSRP. Really
like to be an MSRP. Call it a day. Bada
boom, bada bing.
>> Absolutely. Um, you know, I mean, all I
can do is take it to him, you know, if
uh me a little bit and I'll call you
right back. Okay.
>> Yeah. I'll tell all my friends about
you, too, if that helps.
>> Well, I mean, we really appreciate that.
Would you be financing or just paying
cash?
>> I'll be financing.
>> Okay. All right. Well, um, let me call
him and I'll call you right back. Okay.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> All right, man. Bye.
>> Bye. Profit.
Somebody's calling me back. This is
Tommy.
>> Hey Bobby, it's Josh.
>> What do you got, Josh? Good news.
>> Well, I got one question. How you going
to get up here?
>> Uh, I mean, I can ship the car. You want
me to fly out there? What do you want me
to do?
>> It's up to you, Bob. Um,
>> can if I can ship the car, that's great.
>> He said I can uh sell it to you for
MSRP.
>> Okay. Boom. What What do we got to do?
You want to just send me the numbers?
Let's Bada boom, bada bing. I'll pay
right now.
>> Let's um You said you want to finance
it, right?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Finance. Just send me
whatever forms you need to. We'll get
this started up right now. I love it,
Josh. I appreciate you making it easy.
>> Absolutely, man. Uh let me track down
one of my salespeople. Uh it's either
going to be Deb, Shane, or Tyus. I'll
have one of them call you and they'll
grab all your info and let's put this
together, Bob, and we'll figure out
everything else.
>> I appreciate you making it easy.
>> Absolutely, Bob. Uh give me a few
minutes and I'll have one of them call
you. Okay.
>> Okay. Can they text me? Just I'm just
about to jump in a meeting. Is that
possible?
>> Say that again, Bobby.
>> Can they Can they text me? Is that
possible? I'm just about to jump into a
meeting.
>> Absolutely. Nope.
>> Awesome. Let's rock and roll, man. Let's
get a tight bar. Dream in a driveway.
>> All right. I'll have them reach out to
you. Okay, sounds good. I need to get
this client on ASAP. H client. Client.
Okay, wait. No. Okay, one second. I
gotta get this. Help me. Oh, no. Wait.
One second. I gotta get the client. Ah,
panic. Didn't make this happen. We'll
have a video for you. Boom. Okay. Texted
the client. Bada boom. Bada bing. If
anybody knows what dealership that was,
uh, Cole something. Rock and roll. Give
them love. We end up getting MSRP. Saved
the client 15,000 bucks. And there was
nothing local to him. There was no local
option. This guy was going to have to
ship a car either way.
[Music]