Hey, Eulia. Are you in new car sales?
>> Uh, no. I'm not in sales. I'm service.
Uh, did you wanted to speak to someone
in sales?
>> Yeah, if I can speak to somebody in
sales, that'd be great. Should I call
that other dealership? Is that the more
effective way to do that? I thought I
could buy a car from anywhere, but if
I'm only going to buy one at the one I
test drive. I didn't even know that. I'm
so sorry.
>> Yeah. No, you're fine. You're safe.
>> I'm trying to pay cash. I I have I guess
I have a check, right? I don't I don't
have 60 something,000 in blends in my
house, but I do have a check or I have
uh I can write you a check or
Okay. Ooh, that's not good. Yeah, I'll
jump. I'll I'll I'll pivot. I'll pivot.
Uh fire fire. We officially are EV free.
What that means is we've gotten all EVs
out of delivered before the timeline.
Bada boom, bada bing. That is exciting
cuz that was nerve-wracking. We're
locked and loaded. F yeah. Congrats on
the EV closeout. Thank you. An MDX
Advance SH all-wheel drive advance
package. Paying cash. Solar silver with
ebony interior. Ebony interior. 142 of
those in the country. And they want a
spec.
>> Thank you for calling. To ensure the
highest level of customer care, this
call may be recorded. Please hold while
we connect your call.
>> This call may be recorded for quality
assurance purposes. Thank you for
calling Acura. To help us direct your
call, please choose one of the following
options. For sales, press one. For
service, press.
>> Sorry, that was my fault. I wish. I
panicked. I had two. My fault. My fault.
>> Thank you for calling. To ensure the
highest level of customer care. This
call may be recorded. Please hold while
we connect your call.
>> Hi, Acura. This is Julia speaking. How
can I help you?
>> Hey, E Julia. Are you in new car sales?
No, I'm not in sales. I'm service. Uh,
did you want to speak to someone in
sales?
>> Yeah, if I can speak to somebody in
sales, that'd be great.
>> Okay. Anyone specific or just a sales
representative?
>> Just any of the sales representatives.
>> Okay. Give me just a moment.
>> Good morning. Thanks for calling. This
is Terry. How can I help?
>> Good morning, afternoon, whatever you
want to call it. Uh, I just want to see
if you guys have a car available.
>> Let's check. I'd be delighted. Which one
are we looking for, sir?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Okay, please do. I'm ready. Uh, stock
number is going to be 611545.
>> 545. And while I'm doing this, who am I
talking to? I'm And you are?
>> Tommy.
>> Hi, Tommy.
>> Hi. Nice to meet you,
>> Tommy. My pleasure. So, very specific.
What are we trying to buy? Let's see
here.
>> Very I'm a specific guy.
>> That's all right. We like specific. It
makes my world. You'd be surprised at
those that show up and go, I don't know
what we're looking for.
>> Let me Let me go pull the keys. One sec.
>> Okay, you're good.
[Music]
Okay, thank you.
>> Hey, CL Mark, as close as I can see,
that car is due here on 105. So, it's
around the corner. Silver on black. Is
that correct?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So, yeah, correct. The
beautiful silver.
>> And it is Mark, right? I walked away, so
I probably got something wrong. Uh,
Tommy, thank you. Let me write it down
this time so I can sink it in. So, I
don't I have others and you're welcome
to. The beauty of the car incoming is
you can now decide what options or
accessories you want on the car or I can
try, you know, let you know when that
one shows up.
>> Uh yeah, I mean this is the color combo
I want in the advanced uh spec. So, I
mean, if you have another one that's the
same build, right? Um
>> I don't think I do. That's what I was
trying to research and that's what took
me so long.
>> Yeah. I mean, if so, I mean, do you guys
do like deposits and agree numbers
beforehand or do you guys make them wait
till the car?
>> Absolutely. I can do any and all of that
for you, whichever you decide. Yeah.
>> And then do you have a trade in or I'm
very 21st century with the car deal or
you're welcome to join me?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I mean, I have a trade, but
I'm not too worried about that side. I
have somebody who want to buy it. So,
uh, if you guys can do that, that's
great. If not, I'm more worried about
the price of the vehicle and going from
there.
>> Okay. Let's talk about it. And Tommy,
what's your last name?
>> My last name is Makula. M I K U L A
>> and I got your phone number. What's the
address or at least I can put everything
in here for you?
>> Yeah. 98.
>> And then um should I text you some
information and I will start at the top
and then we'll work our way down from
there. All right. Let me get this
together for you right now.
I'll text you and then if you need to if
you want to converse by email, we can do
that as well.
>> Yeah, text is throw some things.
>> I use email. So text is great.
>> That's fine. All right. I'll get that
together. You'll sit in about 5 to 10
minutes and we'll go from there.
>> I love it. Awesome. Great. Make it easy.
>> Thank you.
>> All right. Sounds good. Talk to you
soon.
>> So, you guys don't know, my name's
Tommy. I negotiate car deals for a
living. I don't advertise this as a
money-saving service cuz you can
literally do this on your own. You don't
need to hire me. But if you don't want
if you want to save time, energy, and
anxiety, and you just don't want to do
it, I charge a flat fee of a,000 bucks.
I handle everything for you. Uh, price a
car, trade, add-ons, accessories. We do
the whole thing. I'm I'm going to be
non-confident to see how this Let's just
see which one you think does better.
>> Thanks for calling. here. This is Carlos
in Sales. How can I help you?
>> Hello, Carlos in Sales. I was just
seeing if if you didn't mind if there's
a car available. I see it on your
website. I just don't know if it's
available.
>> Oh, yeah, sure. Which vehicle is it?
>> I don't know what's easier for you. I
have a the make, model, the VIN, the
there's a stock number, price. What
makes the most sense for you?
>> Anything is okay. Yeah,
>> anything. Okay, cool. It's a 2026 Acura
MDX advance package if that helps. If
not,
>> perfect. Yes, the advanced package,
right?
>> The advanced package. Yeah.
>> Ooh. Okay. Yeah. Let me look into that.
It's going to take me a couple minutes
to see what we have here. You mind
holding for a little bit?
>> Sure.
>> And by the way, is it the A-spec advance
or is it the just the advanced package?
>> Um, it says advanced package on the
website.
>> Okay. And what particular color were you
looking for?
>> Yeah, it's the silvery color. The like
light silver silver. It's like in the
pictures it looks more white than
anything else, but it's silver. I think
>> 26. The solar silver metallic, right?
Solar, silver. That sounds right. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm looking on the website. That
That sounds right.
>> Perfect. I would love to double check.
Make sure. I think we had two. I just
want to double check and make sure with
the black interior, right?
>> Yeah. Are they called Ebony? I think
that's what it's called, but I think
that's just black.
>> Yeah, I would love to double check for
you. It's going to take me a couple
minutes. What is your first and last
name?
>> Uh, yeah. My first name would be Tommy.
My last name would be Mula.
>> All right. And how do you spell your
last name, sir?
>> Sure. Uh, it is m i k u l a.
>> Awesome. And then just in case I
disconnect, is this a good phone number
for you?
>> Yeah, I think that would be the best
number for you. For me? I have a work
number, but I don't think you need that.
>> Perfect. Here, just give me a couple
minutes. I'm just going to make make
sure it's still here.
>> Oh, yeah. No, take your time. Whatever's
the normal process. Uh, what? You're the
expert.
>> Awesome. Okay, one moment.
>> Just going through the right boat. I
just want you to be very clear. We'll
keep going. Right. Do you understand now
why I'm confident? Because rather than
having somebody else control the entire
narrative of the conversation, I can be
much more efficient with my time because
I know exactly what I want. I know
exactly the name of the color. I know
all of these things.
>> Yes, sir. It is available. Um, do you
want to come in right now and take a
look at them?
>> Oh, um, yeah. Um, you I've already
driven one. I to prever like not to I
don't need to come in. Um, recently for
me,
>> you drove it here.
>> Not not there. No, I drove it at a
different dealership. I already know
it's the one I want. Um, I've done all
the research. Uh, followed all the
videos and really now I'm just trying to
get the the pricing side where I'm just
trying to figure out a good deal on the
price.
>> And by the way, why uh you drove it
somewhere else? Why didn't you purchase
it? What makes you want to come check a
look at ours?
>> Mhm. Yeah, that's a good question. Um,
really it just comes down to um I'm
looking for the best deal. And uh you
know, I've always been told if you look
around um you'll find a better deal. So
I'm I haven't got numbers even from that
dealership yet. I didn't I guess I
didn't even think of that yet. Um, I
just saw you guys had I thought two of
them. The color I wanted, the trim I
wanted, and I said, you know, I'll call
you, see what happens. Should I call
that other dealership? Is that the more
effective way to do that?
>> Should I call them and buy I just I
guess I don't know. I'm just I'm
learning as I go here, but I guess I can
call them instead if that makes it
easier. I thought I could buy a car
from, but if I'm only going to buy one
of the test drive, I didn't even know
that. I'm so sorry.
>> I was just curious. Yeah. Like I mean
you you went over there, you test drove
it and I was just curious like you know
you test drove theirs but you didn't end
up buying there. I see you're like
shopping around. These ones are pretty
hard to come by the advanced. So you
want me to send you the like the
numbers, right? Like what the payments
would be or the
>> Yeah, the fees and everything included.
>> Yeah, the out the door number. And just
to verify the one that you have two in
stock, I understand maybe that's hard to
find and maybe that's super low
inventory, but I have two of them. Yeah.
>> Um, you know, again, I'm not in the car.
I'm not the expert. But, um, if that's
hard to find, I get it. But, yeah, I'm
looking for numbers on that car. I
haven't shopped. You said shopped
around. Um, not to get um argue, but
you're my first call. Uh, I hadn't
called the other dealership, but if I'm
supposed to call that dealership and buy
it from that, I I must have broke the
rules. I'm so sorry. I just saw you guys
had two, which is why I called, but I
can certainly call my other dealership
and do that instead. I just didn't.
Maybe I'm I'm new to this, so maybe I'm
just breaking the rules of what I'm
supposed to be doing. I
>> don't believe there are any rules, but
>> I don't know. I'm just again, this is a
you're you're more the expert than me.
You just asked a question. So,
>> no. No worries, sir. You didn't break
any rules. So, you're
>> Okay, cool. I'm not trying to follow the
rules, I don't think.
>> Good. Okay, good. If the if the police
came out right now, that'd be
devastating.
>> Yeah. No, you're fine. You're safe.
Okay, so I'm going to just send you an
opt-in for text.
>> Optin? Yep. If your reply is to that, if
your reply is to that, I'm able to send
you. Uh, and do I just type yes here?
>> Yes. Correct.
>> Okay, cool. I know it says reply yes. I
just It also says help. So, I just want
to make sure I say the right thing here.
Um, perfect. I think I I think I typed
that in, right?
>> Yes. Perfect. Okay, received it.
>> Perfect.
>> So, yeah, I'll just be sending you over
here all the By the way, are you in
Oregon or Washington?
>> I'm in Washington. Yeah, I'm in
Washington, not Oregon.
>> What zip code?
>> Uh, my zip code would be
>> All righty. Perfect. I believe that is
all the information that I need in order
to put some numbers here. Do you want to
even see financing options or you're
just um paying cash?
>> Yeah, you know, I'm I'm you know, I'm
trying to pay cash. I I have I guess I
have a check, right? I don't I don't
have $60ome,000 in ones in my house, but
I do have a check or I have uh I can
write you a check or wire transfer. I
have the money in my bank account if
that's what you're asking me. And all
right,
>> I don't know if it needs to be checking
or savings or whatever it is, but I have
whatever. I have it in either and I can
just pay.
>> Okay.
>> Check for the card. I don't know if
that's the proper word.
>> Yeah. Know, you can do uh you can do
check or you can do financing. I'm just
curious if you even wanted to see the
financing options.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. I mean, if it helps,
then I'm all for looking at. But
realistically, I'd like to pay with my
check with the bank transfer, whatever.
Zel. Um I don't think you guys would
take anything like
>> Okay. All righty, sir. Here. Just give
me a couple minutes and uh I'll send you
over that information. Sounds good. Did
you have any other questions?
>> That sounds great. No, I I think uh
you're going to get me out the door
numbers in the car. I'm not going to
call the other dealership cuz I didn't
have to do that. I didn't break any
laws.
This is I think I'm good. I think I'm on
the same page.
>> All righty. Okay. And then just to let
you know, at our dealership on our brand
new cars, we do put ceramic coating on
our new vehicles. So, you're going to
see that in the numbers. You're going to
see Northwest protection package, which
is wheel locks, modiflex, mud guards,
all season weather mats, trunk cover.
You're going to be seeing that. And
you'll most likely be seeing a service
contract. I have to double check with my
manager. I think they'll be sending you
like a 7-year 60 or 70,000 service
contract, which is going to cover the
engine, transmission, all the
electronics in the car. You're going to
be seeing that.
>> Oh, okay.
>> And like a service contract. Is that is
that all built into the 68250 price on
the website? Is that how that works?
>> Give me one moment, sir.
>> A few moments later.
>> All righty, sir. So, sorry. My
appointment is here, so I'm going to get
back to you. Okay.
>> Yep. That's fine. I guess I'll hear from
you later.
>> All righty. I'll talk to you soon. Okay.
Bye-bye.
>> Okay. Bye. That conversation, I want to
I want to point something out, which I
acted like I didn't know what was going
on. And when that happened, the guy
immediately started setting up for
add-ons, which how many deals have we
negotiated on this channel, and I have
almost never seen a dealership, it's
like one out of every 50, right, that
will go through and start naming all the
add-ons. But guess what? Like that's
exactly what happened. Now, he might
have he might have got a call saying he
knows who I am.
>> Thank you.
>> This is Becca. I'm a director call.
>> Hey, can I speak to somebody in the new
car sales department?
>> Uh, of course. Are you currently working
with anyone in service?
>> No. No. New car new car sales, but no,
I'm not working with anybody in the new
car sales department.
>> All right. I'm going put you on a
briefold and we see if they're
available.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> I have Tony on the line to further
assist.
>> Awesome. Great.
>> This is Tony. How can I help you?
>> Hey, uh, this is Tommy. Uh, I just want
to see if you guys have a car available.
>> Sure.
>> We have lots of cars available.
>> I love it. Awesome. I have a particular
one I'm looking for. I have a stock
number if that helps.
>> Sure.
>> Uh, stock numbers H is in Honda 7894.
So, we are looking for
it is Yes. Still here. The MDX.
>> Yeah. Awesome. Well, I I've already I
love it. Want more of it. Already driven
one. Fell in love with it. Is awesome.
Really just trying to get some pricing
and looking to buy a car last day of the
month. Get a good deal.
>> Sure. Absolutely. Uh what's your phone
number so I can put you in the system to
get some pricing for this?
>> Of course.
>> And where's that? What do
>> Well, I used I used to live in North
Carolina, but I'm in Washington now.
>> Oh, okay. I was like I was like, "Wow."
I was like, "That is I haven't seen that
one yet."
>> No. Yeah, you're good. Yeah.
>> And I'm sorry. Your name was Tommy.
>> My name's Tommy. Correct.
>> Yeah. And then what uh let's see here.
Did you want me to email over to you the
pricing or did you want to send it back?
>> Uh texting would be great. You can text
me.
>> Sure. And then I will get that for you.
And then a few quick questions. Are we
trading anything in?
>> Uh I have a trade, but I'm not too
worried about that. I have somebody
willing to buy it. So, you know, we can
look at that later. More focused on the
outdoor numbers on this one.
>> Yeah, absolutely. And then the other
question is the trade vehicle that you
are going to have. Um are you or sorry
are you going to be financing? Are you
going to be paying cash? What's there
are some different rebates that you will
apply for?
>> Oh yeah, ideally I'm paying cash. Uh we
have an Alfa Romeo that we drive right
now. So if that qualifies us for
conquest then that's great. Um but yeah,
we have an Alfa Romeo till 2018 right
now.
>> Perfect. That's what I was getting at.
>> Yeah, I got you.
>> That's what I wanted to make sure of.
Okay, perfect. All right, so then I will
get you that pricing and I'll text it
over to you.
>> All right, awesome. Great. Let's just
start there and we'll go from there.
Okay, bye.
>> Hey, no problem. Bye. So, that phone
call took three minutes. You can see the
difference.
>> Thank you for calling. My name is Jenny.
How may I help you?
>> Hey, my name is Tommy. I just wanted to
see if you guys have a or can I speak to
somebody new car sales?
>> Yeah, let me go ahead and get you to the
sales department.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> A few moments later.
>> Here, I've been speaking. How can I help
you?
>> Hey, I just want to see if you guys have
a car available.
>> Which car?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
Yeah, absolutely. Uh, what is the stock
number?
>> Stock number is 260003.
>> And where are you calling from, if you
don't mind me asking?
>> Oh, I am calling from the beautiful
state of Washington. Don't know why I
said it like that, but uh, yes,
Washington.
>> All good.
>> Feeling goofy today. Federal Way is
where I'm from.
>> Gotcha. And this is Solar Silver MGX
Advance.
>> That's it. You got it?
>> Yes. The I do have the car in stock. So,
>> awesome. Perfect. Well, I love it. want
more of it. Already driven it. Uh
already fell in love with it. Really
just trying to get some pricing. And I
heard there's nobody better to call.
>> Oh, see that last part? You said it
really fast.
>> Oh, sorry. Uh I heard that there was
nobody better to call, which is why I'm
calling you.
>> Sounds good. Well, uh let me see what I
can do. I mean, are you planning to
lease it? Are you planning to finance
it? Cuz there's If you're planning to
lease it, there's, you know, incentive
money for leasing.
>> Even better, I'm looking to pay cash.
>> Okay, let's see. Cash doesn't give us
any incentive to work with. But let me
see what I can do on the price of the
car. And then, um can I get your name
and phone number? I got to talk to the
sales manager and see.
>> Yeah. Yeah. My my name is Tommy.
>> You want it?
>> Yeah. Name Tommy. Phone number.
>> Okay.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> Thanks. All right.
>> All right. Bye.
>> Thank you for calling. This is sales
department. How can I help you?
>> Hello, sales department. This is buying
department. I just want to see if you
guys have a car available.
>> Sure. What car?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Yeah, that will help. Where where did
you say you were calling from?
>> From the buying department.
>> Okay, gotcha.
>> You said you're from You said you were
the sales department, right?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Sorry.
>> Yeah. Okay, cool. sales buying. We're on
the same page. I think we're I think
we're I think we're meant to be.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. We're on the same
That's why I was kind of like, "Okay, I
got you. I got you."
>> I It's called funny. I think it's not a
joke.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Uh stock number, let
me scroll. Sorry. Okay. Uh stock number
is going to be T as in tango. L as in
limma
008008.
>> Okay, perfect. And then can I get a
name?
>> My name is Tommy.
>> Tommy, nice to meet you, Tommy. Give me
one second. I'm going to put you on
hold. Let me go ahead and check if that
stock is still in in our in our stock.
All right, give me
>> So, just to point out, he still hasn't
given me his name. And yes, it's it's u
it's like guys, if you're going to call
me and not give me your name and then
say you're from the sales department.
Thanks for calling sales department.
Like, okay, cool. Like, I'm going to
make a buying department.
>> Yeah. Sorry. My name's Edgar
Edgar. Awesome. Love it. Okay, Edgar.
Love it. Edgar from sales. Uh, awesome.
Love it. I want more of it. I've already
driven the car. I already know I want
this car. Really just trying to get some
great pricing and uh I heard this is a
good market to buy it, so I'm ready to
buy it.
>> All right. Um, so when would you want to
come in?
>> The second we agree to numbers, I'm I'm
I'm in there.
>> I'm in there. Okay. Sure. Sure. Give me
one second. Do you plan on financing or
leasing the car?
>> I'm actually looking to pay cash, but
I'm open to financing if the deal makes
sense.
>> Okay. Cash open to financing. Just want
to ask you all these questions just so
when I bring it up to my manager, we
could see what we could do for you.
>> Sure, that'd be great.
>> Okay. And then what's what's your zip
code? My zip code is
>> and then do you have any uh vehicles
2015 or newer?
>> Uh I do have a 2018 Alfa Romeo.
>> 2018 what was that?
>> 2018 Alpha Romeo.
>> Alpha Romeo. Cool. Okay. And then you
said you prefer cash, right? Over
financing. But if the deal is right,
you're open to finance.
>> Absolutely.
>> All right. So, let me run this by my
manager. Can I go ahead and give you a
call back in about 10 minutes?
>> Okay, that sounds great. I'll be here
waiting for your phone call.
>> All right. And then just to verify the
phone number is going to be
>> that is my phone number.
>> All right, Tommy, I'll go ahead and give
you a call back very soon.
>> Okay, sounds good. Can't wait.
>> Yep.
>> Bye.
>> May I direct your call?
>> Hello. Can I speak to the new car sales
department?
>> Yeah. Is this your first time calling
for sales?
>> This is my first time calling.
>> Perfect.
>> A few moments later.
>> Carlos in the sales department.
>> Hello, Carlos from the sales department.
This is Tommy from the buying
department. How's it going?
>> Pretty good.
>> Awesome. Perfect. I just want to see if
you guys have a car available.
>> Yes, can definitely help you with that.
Do you have a stock number for me by any
chance?
>> I do. Yeah, it's a 22619.
T is in Tyrannosaurus Rex.
>> Uh MDX Advance.
>> That's it.
>> Yeah, looks like I still have that one
available.
>> Awesome. Love it. Want more of it.
Already driven it. Ready. Fell in love
with it. Last day of the month. Just
trying to get an awesome deal and I'm
hoping you can help me deliver that. Um,
I actually have a customer in here right
now who called saying the same thing and
she's actually getting signed up for her
MDX Aspec. So, different package is
yours, but the same uh 2026. So, yeah. I
mean, when do you think you can make it
in?
>> Well, um, I'm looking to come in the
second we agree numbers.
>> Okay. I mean, I could always send you a
link to our express store. I mean, are
you looking to do a lease? Are you doing
financing? Just curious.
>> Finance or cash? Pray cash, more than
likely.
>> Okay.
>> You said you could send me a link to
what? I'm sorry. From what I'm looking
at right here, it looks like your MSRP
would be uh 68250.
Total out the door based off open tax
would be about 76140.
>> 76140.
>> Mhm.
>> Okay. So, last day of the month, the no
deals or anything crazy.
>> So, I would definitely be able to do
that for you. Um I don't have access to
any discounts that aren't in my system.
Um that would also be like my sales
manager, the one that has the access to
it. He is signing up a customer right
now. If you were to be in here, we would
definitely have room for discount. I
know this customer, she got a great
deal. Um, I can't really go into
specifics of her deal, but we are one of
those places. Hey, the month we want to
we want to give you the best discount
possible. Um, let me
>> Why don't you just just give me a good
idea? I mean, why don't you just tell me
what she got and I'll determine if
that's a good deal or not.
>> Well, she's doing a lease, so it would
be a little bit different from what you
were doing, right? There's more
discounts, lease incentives, money
coming from Acura. That would be a
little bit different. And then also,
she's on a different kind of car than
you. So, different discount, different
MSRP.
>> Are you local to us? Are you in the
Oakland area?
>> I'm not in the Oakland area, but I can,
you know, I can do all the deal remotely
and have it signed today and then come
pick it up in a day or so. But, you
know, really trying to get the best out
the door numbers. I don't want to, you
know, do the back and forth and going in
the dealership. As you know, it's the
last day of the month, so the idea of me
sitting in a dealership for hours on end
as you guys are super busy doesn't make
super amount of sense compared to just
calling a dealership, getting some
deals, and seeing who gives you the best
one.
>> Sure. No, I totally understand that. For
us here, we do things a little bit
differently. The only thing that we
would do remotely, like we would send
you the credit application to get you
pre-approved, all the documents and
stuff and everything would have to be
signed here in store. So, for us here,
we don't like to waste time either. Uh
we like to do everything pretty easy and
clear and concise. Um like I said, I
don't have access to all the other
discounts. That'll be my sales manager
and he's I'm occupied with my customer
at the moment.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You know, obviously I don't
want to bother your sales manager when
he's selling a car to not sell another
car. That'd be crazy. Just so I'm on the
same page. And again, if there's your
policy, it's your policy. You're willing
to get all the private super secure
credit app information over the phone.
No problem. Email, no problem. But you
won't give the price of the vehicle over
the phone.
>> And I just want to make sure I don't
know what the idea or the thinking of it
is though. I don't collect any
information over the phone. A link is
sent to our customers, right? They fill
it out. They do that application. We
would typically go over via our express
store. But if you're asking for like the
best deal, the best price, that's not
something, oh, oh, here customer calls
in for the best price, this our best
price. It's not the way we operate here.
You know, we
>> I mean, I guess not for the best price.
>> Sorry. I mean, I'm just crazy. Like, I
just thought most people would call and
they want the best price. I'm like, I
don't want to pay the the average price.
>> No, totally understand. I mean, for us,
we like to discount everything up front.
I know these 2026s, there isn't much
room um as far as discount like there
would be on the 2025s. So again, that's
part of the reason why I don't have
access to it at my level, but it would
be for my sales manager or even my
finance director who's not in today. I
mean, the best thing that I could do, I
could always give you a call back and
let you know. So I don't want to give
the perspective that we're in here just
collecting customers information without
going over numbers or anything like
that. Um, for us, we give really good
deals. I mean, we have really good
ratings on Yelp. Um, and it's not
because we do bad deals, it's because we
do good deals, right? We have customers
coming in from Santa Cruz, flying in
from LA. I mean, and it's part of the
reason because the way we do it things
here. But um like I said, I can give you
a call back and then see what we can do
and hopefully if you can make it down
here to us today, then you would get the
best deal.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I mean, you know, I've
always gone through the philosophy that
any dealership that makes my life easy
over the phone's going to make my life
easy in store. I appreciate you saying
you you'll make it easy when I'm there,
but you know, I don't even know what
kind you're saying it's a good deal.
What you consider a good deal and I
consider a good deal could be completely
different numbers. I'm buying a car
today. So, um if you guys want to sell
one, nope, that's great. Like I said, we
can create numbers. I'm all for it. I'll
sign the dotted line today. If you guys
are super busy and you guys can't do
over the phone or that's not your phil
philosophy, no big deal. But I am doing
one today. So,
>> sure. No. Well, I I'll tell you this.
Look, if you want to go around because
it looks like you have a couple other
phone calls to make trying to get the
best deal possible, and I totally
respect that. Um, one thing I will tell
you that we have here is a price match
guarantee. So, if you do have the best
price and you end up wanting to get one
of our in stock vehicles, then we'll you
can go ahead and bring it over. We'll
match that deal. For whatever reason, we
can't match it, then you get a $100 gift
card to our parts department. Have we
ever had to give it out? No. because
most of the time we match the deal or we
end up beating it. You know, just really
depends on what the numbers are looking
like. But unfortunately, my hands are
tied at the moment. I can't provide you
the best number. But, you know, if you
want to make the phone calls and you
want to see who's going to give you the
best deal, I I totally respect that. Um,
but like I said, that's something that
we would be willing to match and we'd be
able to do so really easily. So,
>> yeah. Yeah. I mean, I'm not like I said,
I I can call around if you need me to
call around. I was calling hoping just
to get this one and done, call it a day.
But, yeah, if you need me to call around
and do that, that's I guess I can go
that route. So, just to make sure I'm on
the same page. If I call around and get
numbers and get those numbers and then
show you those numbers, you can beat
that over the phone.
>> I don't want to again I want to make it
as clear and I can I don't know. So, we
do what's called a price match guarantee
and that's in store, right? As far as
what we can do as far as a discount
going over the numbers. Yeah, we could
do that, right? I don't have access to
it. My sales manager does. Um I don't
have an additional sales manager. I
don't have an additional finance
director. So, just a couple things that
I can't provide you currently off the
top. If it were a 2025, I'd have all the
discounts readily available for me. But
just on these 26s, not everything is
uploaded into what's called our express
store yet.
>> Okay. Yeah. Yeah. No worries. If uh I
guess whatever if you guys get free and
available, and I know it's last day of
the month, so if somebody gets a free
and available, wants to call me, that's
great. I'm not going to come in though
to shop the number to maybe beat the
deal, maybe not. Like, I don't need $100
parts. Like, it's either yep, I can beat
the deal or no, I can't. So, no big
deal. That's that's your guys'
philosophy. And you guys are too busy. I
completely understand. I'll uh look
somewhere else.
>> Okay. Thank you. Have a good day.
>> No problem. Bye. What what I wanted to
hammer down is he said we do things a
little bit differently here. And then he
went on to say that he collects the
credit app via over online which just
doesn't make any sense like if you're
going to and he started off the
conversation by saying it's the last day
of the month. We're doing good deals. My
customer just bought a car. They're
getting a good deal. This is the best
day to buy. I didn't start all that
conversation. I just said I'm looking to
buy this car. He said all of these
things. He prepped me by saying that I
should get a good deal at a car and then
he said the only way to do that is to
come on it. I'm sorry, but if your
philosophy is I don't want to do this
because it's private, then you can't
collect a credit app over the phone
either. The things you're doing
differently is you're a dealership in
the 1980s is what you are like that.
That's what you're doing things
differently because you're you're not in
the modern era. A salesperson is not
wasting their time bidding for your
deal. So, just to be clear, he explained
this whole process to me, went through
this whole thing and wasted 10 minutes
of his time rather than all the other
salesperson. Like, let's go through this
last dealership that just sent me
numbers in a car. They spent 3 minutes
on the phone with me and in 7 minutes
later they had numbers. Which one is
faster? Seriously, just take 10 minutes
on the phone with me saying, "Well, I'm
sorry. We don't do but if you come on
in, I promise you we'll give you the
best deal." Or, "Yeah, cool. I'll get
your numbers." Boom. Boom.
>> This is Tommy. Hey Tommy with
>> Hey, sorry I don't I'm sorry I'm so rude
about saying hi. This is Tom. This is
Tommy. How's it going?
>> Good, man. How are you doing?
>> Doing doing well. Sorry. I was just
having a great conversation. Uh now I'm
here.
>> Gotcha. Good time to talk.
>> This is the best time to talk. Honestly,
if there was a better time, I would uh
be at dinner.
>> Awesome, man. Well, hey, got some info
from my sales guy. You're interested in
a 2026 uh MDX. That's right.
>> That's it. That's the car I'm interested
in.
>> Awesome, man. Well, I had one of my uh
sales managers send you over some
numbers. Uh this one does have some
optional um you know items and equipment
in there, but right now um last day of
the month obviously we're trying to make
you a great deal. Uh so we've got total
savings of $2,750
there.
>> Okay. And then just uh so I know I'm
just going to go through all the stuff.
There's Bright Line total care for
$3,000 or sorry $2,995. Battery for life
$895. Gap for $1,95. Warranty for
$4,995. And Acura maintenance for
$2,495. So, a total of $12,475
of add-ons.
>> Uh, those just optional equipment. So,
we like to show everything, all your
options up front. Some people choose it
all. Some people choose one or two. Some
people choose nothing. Just kind of
comes down to whatever the best the best
fit for your deal is.
>> Okay. So, you're saying that I can say
no to all of that. No problem.
>> Yeah, absolutely. The one thing you are
going to get no matter what is our
engine for life warranty. That's
something that we provide at our
dealership at no extra cost.
>> Okay. Awesome. So, that's and that's uh
that's $0. It shows on the line there.
So everything else optional, everything
else um if I decide to buy it and maybe
I see value, I don't know yet. I'll look
at these here. So 2750 is that with a
rebate, without a rebate?
>> So the only rebate that's available on
these 2026s is the loyalty. Uh based on
the info that I got on the Alfa Romeo,
that one wouldn't qualify. So this is uh
all just dealer dealer incentive
basically.
>> Okay. Oh yeah. Well uh I mean I like the
car. I was hoping to get just a little
bit better of a deal than this,
especially on the last day of the month.
>> Yeah. What are you thinking? You know, I
was really trying to be close to about
10% off. Uh right around six grand off
is what I was trying to be.
>> Gotcha. Okay. Yeah, that's definitely
pretty steep. I mean, I can run some
numbers and see, you know, see exactly
what we're looking at. Just um just to
be clear though, if I could do something
like that, I mean, are you ready to wrap
it up today or what?
>> Yeah. Yeah, I'm ready to sign the dotted
line today. That's 100%. So, we can go a
numbers. I'm I'm rocking and rolling. If
you can get six grand off, it's a done
deal.
>> Okay. Yeah, I'll double check my numbers
here. See what we can do. Um have you
have you gotten a quote that by chance
better than ours so far or?
>> No. I mean, I've only called a few
dealerships here. You know, everybody's
a little bit different, but I haven't
got any. You're the first one to ask me
what I'm looking for, so that's what I'm
doing. Um, yeah, trying to get six grand
off, I haven't got six grand. If I got
six grand off, I I would have bought
their car by now.
>> Gotcha. No, totally understand. Well,
let me let me plug some numbers together
for you, Tommy. I'll give you a call
back here in just a little bit and
hopefully we'll be earning your
business.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> Awesome. Thank you.
>> No problem. Bye. And just so we're
clear, a lot of people say, "Tommy, you
asked for crazy numbers." Normally,
we're asking for numbers that make sense
to the deal. If I look at all of the
last deals that I've done, just so we're
clear, $5,000 off a 2026 MDX on a lease.
We did $9,750. That was a lease. There
was a lot of rebates when we did that
one. And then $6,500 off an Acura MDX
with Tech or the last three we did. So
like that's how we get the data. Uh a
lot of people like say like, Tommy, like
how do you know like you're asking for
crazy numbers, you're crazy. Like no,
it's just data. Like we have data. We
know what we've done before. We've done
this before. Let's go. Bada boom, bada
bing. We've got the deal.
Thank you for calling. This is Jeremy in
the sales department. Who do I have the
pleasure of speaking with?
>> Hey Jeremy, my name's Tommy. Nice to
meet you.
>> Tommy, is this for real?
>> My name is Tommy. Yeah. Should I not be?
>> No, no, no. Are you Tommy from Tik Tok?
>> No. I work at my own business. Is there
a Tommy that works at Tik Tok?
>> Yeah, it's okay. How can I help you?
>> I'm just messing with you. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Uh, you have a carne.
>> Let's do it.
>> 15460. Stock number. You know the game.
Let's play. Oh, you're also No, it's
okay. I understand. Uh, let make sure
this vehicle is still here and
available. By the way, my name is
Jeremy. I'll be uh, assisting you today.
>> I love it. This is great. Let's make a
nice, easy end of month deal so you can
sell one. Bada boom, bada boom.
>> Perfect. And we're looking at the 2026
Acura MDX advanced package. Uh, solar
silver with ebony interior.
>> That's it.
>> Perfect. This vehicle still here and
available. What can I do for you?
>> I'm really just looking for pricing,
paying cash. Uh, don't qualify for
Conquest because I have an offer of
Mayo, but our client does. Really just
trying to get the best deal. client is I
can give you a zip code for it, but uh
looking to make a decision today.
>> Okay. Uh yeah. What's a good zip code
for the the person?
>> 98.
>> Unfortunately, this is in Washington.
Correct.
>> Correct.
>> Our dealership does not do out of state
deliveries.
>> Can the client come in and pick it up?
>> They would have to register in
California.
>> Oh, I see what you're saying. Yeah, I
don't think they're going to want to do
that. Let me see if I have any other
options here. Oh, wait. We can we can
still we can still play the game. If you
want to still play the game, I got
another Acura or
>> if you got any California people, man,
I'd love to help you out.
>> I got a Hawaii one here. And then I got
another Lala. Okay, let's go. I don't
know if you have the car. Um, Integra
Type S.
>> I do have some.
>> Oo, urban gray. Silver white.
>> No, urban gray.
>> Silver or white?
>> I have white. White. Black and white and
red.
>> The silver white. They will take either
one. They will not consider black.
Absolutely will not. With a passion in
all caps is blue. They said urban gray
is number one and then they're open to
the silver or white. So, let's just go
with white.
>> Okay. Yeah, I have a white one. I have
white with red and white with black.
Both 2025 versions.
>> 20. They're open to either one. So,
whichever one you think you deal on.
>> Perfect. And then for the zip code for
that one,
>> zip code for that one is
>> perfect. So for both of them I can do
MSRP on both of them which is 155
which would be based off their zip code
MSRP 546.95 basic tax title and license
out the door price would be 59767 and45.
>> Well as much as I would love to rock a
deal with you the last three of these
I've done have all been 3k off and they
were all in
>> 3k off. Yeah that's crazy. It's not that
crazy.
>> That's a pretty good deal. Yeah, that
is. We haven't sold one for anything
under MSRP.
>> Um, well, I can't I can do MSRP. Dang
it. That's okay. If you guys want to do
one, you let me know and you guys if you
get 3K off, we'd have a deal. But
otherwise, doesn't make sense.
>> No, I'd love to help you out, man. I
watch you every day.
>> I appreciate it. Well, end of month. If
you guys want to sell, you guys need one
more unit, don't be afraid to let me
know. But otherwise, um uh we'll just
call you in the next one.
>> All right. Have a good day, sir. Yeah,
no problem. Have a great day.
>> Thank you. All right. Byebye.
>> Okay, I got numbers from this other
dealership. This other dealership is at
MSRP plus $7.95.
Thank you for the numbers. I appreciate
you getting them to me. Was hoping for a
bit better deal than that, though. So,
just you guys know my strategy when
buying a car. I'm not saying this is
going to be the most effective for most
people because I believe it takes a lot
more confidence to do and you have to
have some data that not everybody's
going to have, but if you have the data,
it's great. Is I go through and I know
the number that I am aiming for because
I've just done enough deals, right? So,
like on this car, if I can get 6K off,
that's a deal for me, right? Uh 6K off.
Bada boom, bada bing. Uh shi text.
[Music]
Okay.
That's not good. Yeah, I'll jump. I'll
I'll I'll pivot. I'll pivot. Do we need
to do Do we need to do a deal in Texas?
That's going to be crazy. Oh jeez. Uh
fire, fire, fire. If you work at GMC and
you have a Hummer EV lease deal on a
demo, let me know right now. We'll get a
deal done. Uh we had a client that they
just sold their EV last second. Happens.
It's life. We're going to pivot. All
hands on deck. But if you work at a GMC
dealership, you have a demo Hummer EV.
Cheapest lease possible. We're trying to
achieve. We'll get a deal done right
now. We'll do it on live.
[Music]