Can you get a wacky waving inflatable
tube man when you negotiate a car deal
for free? That's the question I wanted
to know. I'm just kidding. Well, kind
of. In the negotiations you're about to
watch, you're about to see some
highlights of a charity stream that we
did. Now, during this charity stream, if
you donated 250 bucks, we spun a wheel
and I had some type of punishment. These
two I felt like the ones that were the
most educational and honestly the ones
that you could learn the most from. The
first one is going to be the longer one
where we go through and actually
negotiate a car deal, but I have to
teach a firsttime buyer that's sitting
right next to me what's going on. So, as
this dealership is using certain tactics
and trips, I'm calling them out right in
front of them and letting them know how
to respond so the salesperson can hear
all the things that I'm thinking. The
second negotiation, I have to get
something thrown in for free. And you
will be shocked with the dealership's
response when I asked for a wacky waving
inflatable tube man thrown in for free
because another dealership's doing it.
Remember, this was all for charity. And
these were all negotiations we're trying
to get for a client. In my opinion, the
way I was negotiating is just another
tactic we were testing out. I know it's
a little bit goofy and it's a little bit
funny, but sometimes you got to have a
little bit of fun, especially when
you're trying to raise money for St.
Jude's. Enough with the talk. Let's get
into the video.
>> This Chelsea, how can I help you? Hello,
Chelsea. Can I speak to somebody in new
car sales?
>> Yeah. What can I answer for you?
>> Oh, awesome. Are you in new car sales?
>> Uh, yeah. Well, I work with new, but
yeah. Is it one for you or is it one for
someone else?
>> Uh, well, I'm actually here with um with
Russ. Um, I'm I'm helping him. He's
never bought a car before, so I'm giving
him the the rundown of of how this
works. Okay, Russ. This is where we're
going to give her the stock number of
what's available. So, we do have a stock
number whenever you're ready, or we can
give you the last six of the vid.
>> Stock number is great. Go ahead when
you're ready. 861467.
Now Russ, they really prefer you give
them the stock number, which means
you're showing you're serious, which
means they'll give you a better deal.
Sorry.
>> No, you're good. You're good. Good to
meet you both. You said you're helping
Russ and what was your name?
>> My name's Tommy.
>> Tommy, good to meet you both.
>> Thank you. Sometimes I like to use your
name just to build some trust, Russ.
That's That's normal. That's good.
Sorry. Continue.
>> You guys have called in. No, you're
good. I find the car. Uh it looks like
it's the new Sportage, right? The EX.
>> No, no, it's a Kia Sportage EX.
>> Yes. Awesome choice. I love that color
combination.
>> Did you say Ford Edge or did you say I
thought you said Ford Edge?
>> I'm sorry. Ford is what I said and I
probably just said it too fast.
>> See, that's sometimes sometimes it gets
confusing. That's my fault. I'm just
getting old.
>> No worries. And I I'll speak up and and
it'll all work great.
>> Yeah. Yeah. No, you're good.
>> That's an excellent choice. Has Russ
been looking for something like it for a
while or just kind of started exploring
today?
>> Uh we just we actually drove it last
week. We loved it. Really just trying to
get the best possible numbers. Russ, you
want to make sure you ask for the best
possible numbers? If you don't ask that,
then they'll give you some mediocre
numbers to start.
>> Oh gosh.
>> Oh, sorry. I was talking to Russ.
>> I don't know what dealerships No. Yeah,
you're good. No, we're pretty
straightforward as far as dealerships
go.
>> So, yeah, best numbers would have been
usually when he was here checking it
out, but when was that that he got to
test drive it? And he did.
>> Oh, so we weren't at your dealership. We
were at another dealership, but we drove
it last week.
>> Oh, gotcha. Okay. No, we're pretty
straightforward as far as like numbers
and pricing and all of that goes. So, we
want to help take care of folks and um
so that one is 33,360
on that one.
>> Okay. And we would I we're hoping to get
a little bit better than MSRP.
>> We can check it out. Yeah. If it ends up
being the one and is Russ trading
something in?
>> No, we would just be we'd be adding to
the fleet. You never want to accept
their first offer, Russ. That's always
the worst way to do it.
>> Are you with the dealership, Tommy, or
can I ask what? Um
>> No, no, I'm just an experienced car
buyer. All my friends and family call me
to negotiate the car deals. So, I'm just
teaching Russ the the methods.
>> Gotcha. So, you haven't worked with us
then before, huh?
>> No. Should I have?
>> No. Absolutely. Yes. We really strive to
take care of folks. I mean, the
experience is super important. So,
that's why I mean, when you're here, I
mean, obviously showing the u you know,
that kind of motivation and that kind of
um oh, you know, leverage essentially to
the dealership and to the bank. So,
yeah, that's why I'm really surprised
that they didn't get the best numbers
when you guys got to check them out.
>> Yeah, I wasn't at your dealership. As I
said, I was I was I was somewhere we
drove in on vacation.
>> Oh, gotcha. Okay. And are you guys here
in Joplin or where are you out of?
>> Uh I'm in Kansas City, so pretty darn
close.
>> Yes. That's awesome. And Russ is as well
or is
>> Russ Yeah, correct. Yeah. Yeah, Russ is
as well.
>> Oh, to Kansas City.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, wow. So, just calling around and not
hearing the right numbers from the
dealerships up there closer to home or
>> Yeah. Yeah. We're just calling around
trying to get the best possible price
and we heard that was a good thing to
do.
>> Kansas, you always want to call. Well, I
mean
>> competition competition drives the price
down. So, calling multiple dealerships
will help and she'll know that and
hopefully give us a better deal. Sorry.
Continue.
>> Oh, no. You're good. I want to invite
you guys in. Um cuz car shopping um I
mean I don't know what kind of offers
you're getting from other dealerships.
The best price has to go right online or
we wouldn't get any clicks or get any
calls on our second best price. So, I
mean MSRP is what we can offer. um if it
ends up being the perfect car. I mean,
we've been known to work with guests on,
you know, on getting the best price to
get to the best payment and the the
right fit for Russ. But, um, can you
guys make it today before seven or when
would that put you here so we can work
on the new one for him?
>> Yeah. So, we wouldn't be looking to
come. We've already driven the car. I
already know we want it. Really just
trying to get this all done over the
phone. It's going to be the best for us.
Russa, sometimes buying a car is
emotional. So, when you do it at home,
you have less emotion involved.
>> Well, finding the right car is
important. So, the one that he test
drove, was that not
It's the perfect car. We just That's the
perfect car. Yeah. We told one thing I
taught Russ is that once he drives the
car, he falls in love with it. Then you
go home, make sure you think about it,
make sure you love it, and then you call
around to get the best deal. But if MSRP
is the best deal, that definitely I feel
confident we could do better than that.
We had another dealership that was
willing to pay us per mile, right, Russ?
>> Pay per mile for what?
>> Yeah. For how many miles we took to
drive up there up to 500 bucks. So
>> Oh, wow.
>> Okay. I mean, we're just we earn folks
business, you know, by being an upfront
business. Um, this is a car coming
that's not even in stock yet. Um, that
one's in transit, so I don't have any,
um, discounts that I can offer on that
one. It I mean, they usually sell pretty
pretty quickly after they show up on the
lot. Um, so yep, like I said, six of
them in stock, right? Different. Um, the
Kia goes ahead and puts them on the
website when they are in transit still.
I mean, the the stock number that you
gave me, it's still in transit.
>> Okay. Do you have another 2026 portage
GX in stock?
>> Probably. So, yeah. And MSRP can be
different like depending on what exactly
it's equipped with. So it can narrow it
down from there.
>> Looks like I've got them as low as like
31 I want to say.
>> Yeah, I see you guys have six on your
website. So you don't want to believe
this.
>> Awesome. Which one's the one that he was
um is he wanting that one that you had
said given the stock number?
>> Yeah, but we're not picky. We'll take
silver, black, any of those. That's
totally fine.
>> Okay, cuz I'm showing the one um for
$319.90. Um it's a black one, I don't
think. Let me look. I think it has the
uh lighter interior also. Yeah, it has
the gray interior. Did he was he a fan
of that interior or does he like the
darker?
>> Yeah, he preferred the darker interior
ideally. Okay.
>> Um but would take the gray interior. I
mean again we're we're uh Russ our goal
is to get the best deal here. U so if
it's a gray deal the gray interior you
know we can definitely make that work.
>> That's the one that is um $319.90
I believe is that one.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So if you can do I mean
obviously that's just the is that just
the MSRP of the car? Yes. Yep. Are you
talking with dealerships that's doing
like certain specific discounts off of
MSRP?
>> Yeah, that would be the that would be
the goal. Yeah. Yeah. Russa, don't fall.
Sometimes dealerships like to give you a
lower MSRP car and make it seem like
it's getting a better deal, but in
reality, you're just getting less stuff.
So, make sure you want to discount.
>> Well, if that's a better fit for him, if
less, you know, if less Sorry, I was
speaking to Ross. I apologize. Yeah. Oh,
you're good. I was just making sure that
we're informing him, you know, of of why
I mentioned that. Um, I don't I'm not
really experienced with the light that
you're painting dealerships in because
that's not how we operate. I'm sorry. It
kind of it threw me a little bit. I'm
sorry.
>> Yeah. No, I know. I apolog So So I I
know you guys just showed me a a cheaper
car uh is what you just did. So
>> car different equipment. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Different equipment. Yeah.
So that's totally okay. What I guess
let's ask is there anything you can do
for the price or is MSRP just the best
you guys can do? Uh I mean generally any
offer to purchase a vehicle is here like
in person once he's met it and you know
once we're sure that it is the right one
>> but we already know it's the right one
we have about the well you met um a
different one and it had if it had a
different MSRP because of different
equipment I guess what about that one
wasn't quite a fit where he was able to
to take it home
>> well as I said earlier one thing I told
Russ is that when you buy look a car you
don't just buy it on the spot right 60%
of people have buyer remorse right Russ
um so because of that you want to make
Sure. You go home, you think about it.
It's a big decision. You're spending $30
something thousand. So, he thought about
it. He still loves it. Now, as Right,
Russ, we're calling around. We're just
trying to see who's willing to give us
the best deal. We've gotten a few
discounts some so far. Uh but MSRP
wouldn't be the best deal. And we
thought, you know, a lot of these
dealerships that have a lot of these
cars, like you guys have six, um means
that you guys would normally be willing
to do a little bit better than MSRP, but
if not, no big deal. We can call
somebody else. But we're hoping to have
you guys earn our business. I just know
the best deal for someone is on is on
the right car. Um, this is the right
car.
>> Yeah, that was one that he checked out.
Oh, okay. Well, I mean, I just meant the
one that he did get to to test drive.
Are they not are they not working with
him on the numbers on that one?
>> I guess let me ask you this. Is is there
is there a difference between two 2026
Kia Sportages with this? Should are they
going to drive different, feel
different, look different?
>> Um, a lot of it down to like the
additional equipment. So like the C each
package will come equipped with the you
know the standard equipment for that
package and then the difference in the
MSRP is due to like the additional
equipment that Kia puts on.
>> Okay. Uh yeah and that's yeah I know
that they have slightly different
equipment on these two cars. Uh you guys
wouldn't wouldn't give us a deal on the
first one. So we're not super picky on
the options but really we're just trying
to figure out what kind of deal you
could do on it.
>> I mean I can definitely appreciate that.
like we're we're here as a family
business, you know, to help Russ, you
know, the let's say the next time he's
in the market for a vehicle. That way,
he's not dealership shopping as well,
you know, so we're just we're really
upfront with pricing. We want to earn
someone's business by being the right
choice and the right fit. And um I mean,
I don't have thousands to discount.
Like, do you have an offer to make on
that one site unseen and I can take it
to a manager?
>> Yeah, I mean so so we we already have a
deal for $500 off. Um and remember like
we want we want to keep building on
that. So, like we don't we wouldn't want
to go backwards, right? So, you know, we
would really be we're really trying to
get to around $2,500 off is what we're
trying to do.
>> So, you have $500 off
>> so far. And you're a second phone call.
>> Okay. Gotcha. I just I know K every
dealership pays the same thing to Kia
for the car. So, we've been known to
work with folks, you know, over a few
hundred, a couple thousand dollar, not
as likely cuz dealerships across the
board. Like I said, if if they send it
to Kansas City or if they send it to
Tulsa, you know, the dealership owes the
same amount to Kia for it. So, if
they're discounting something based on
something specific in their market or
something specific like that's going on
with the car, uh maybe it has a few more
miles, there's a lot of reasons for a
discrepancy in price.
>> Okay. So, so what the dealership owns,
it's not crazy to see that some
dealerships might sell the car under
what they own it for, right? Like that's
not impossible to hear, right?
>> They might have a they may have a
specific reason to do that, right?
>> Yeah. Yeah. So, like again, what you
guys, you know, you could tell me your
invo. I don't know what your invoice is.
That that's not my business, but I just
know is what kind of deal you can do,
which at this point, you know, that's
what I'm asking, right? We have $500 off
right now. We're trying to get the
$2,500 off. I know you guys have six of
them. I understand you're a family-owned
business. That's great. We love that. Uh
we would love to do business. And maybe
you can teach me that I'm wrong about
all dealerships and then teach Russ the
first time he buys a car, he just gets a
great deal right off the bat and he
doesn't have to play all the back and
forth games I was saying.
>> Warranty. Absolutely. And I mean, I
don't know how long he plans on
obviously keeping it either, but we
match Kia's warranty, too. Um, and
there's not really not a dollar amount I
can put on that, but it's a 200,000 mi
warranty that he'll get or 20 years. So,
I don't, like I said, I doubt um that
the Let me look at what that offer would
be. And thank you for the offer, and I
don't want to assume what they will say,
obviously.
>> Of course, um, we always stretching to
um, what are you want me to offer? and
I'll take it to the the new car manager.
>> Yeah. $2,500 off uh is what we'd have an
offer. Want to go a firm offer here
>> off of MSRP?
>> Correct.
>> Okay.
>> Clear with what you want.
>> So for a 33,360
on the Kia Sportage, you want me to
offer 30,860?
>> Correct.
>> Hold on just one second. I'll be back.
>> Thank you.
>> Meanwhile,
>> well, are you there still?
>> Yes, I'm still here.
>> Hey, I appreciate it. I had my adviser
working on that for us. Um we looked
into that one. That one is still in
transit. So, I don't have it today. Um,
it is projected for end of the week. I
think he said the 11th. So, it's it's on
its way from Kia. Um, and we can do
invoice, he said, on that one. Um, which
any lower than that, I mean, is less
than what we owe to Kia for it, but it's
32313.
Uh, is the invoice on that one. That's
the original one you gave me with the
darker interior.
>> So, I'm sorry. What was the discount?
>> The Oh, the invoice price on it is
32,313.
>> 32313.
And so is that like 7 800 bucks off?
>> I can subtract it. Hold on one second.
Uh 1,047.
>> 1,047.
Um Okay, awesome. Can you uh send me
just an out the door breakdown of that
so I know what's going on? We always
want to get an out the door breakdown so
we can not only confirm the numbers, but
if we need them, we can utilize them
later
>> to send to other dealerships.
>> Yeah. Yeah, that's what I was explaining
to Russ.
>> Yes, for sure. And it sounds like you're
trying to help him get the best price on
one car one time. Is that
>> I'm hoping he he's learning a skill that
he's going to be able to teach for life.
So, you know
>> Oh, absolutely. I just know we could be
his dealership for life, too. You know,
somewhere that really is gonna work with
him, help him out when it comes down to
trading it.
>> Watch this. You could be our dealership
for life with a $2,500 discount.
>> What would stop you from calling around
for another $2,500 discount the next
purchase, though?
>> What do you mean? If a $2,500 discount
buys um a dealership for for life, would
he be trying to get that same discount
next time?
>> I mean, sure, why not
>> from a different dealership?
>> No. I mean, you go to you first every
time. You made it easy. Why are we
worried about the next purchase when we
can get this one? Let's step step one.
Like, you know, you're like like, you
know, Russ, it's kind of like when you
uh you first start you start meet you
meet a woman for the first time. You
don't want to talk about marriage right
off the bat. You want to talk about like
the first date, the second date, third
date, fourth date, right, Russ? So, like
right now we're just trying to like
figure out the first step and eventually
we'll figure out the rest, but let's get
the step one. That was hypothetical,
>> right? Well, step one was yeah, finding
the right car. Um, so I'm glad he's
decided that he loves the Sportage and
um
>> I mean if you found the right dealership
>> Okay. Yeah.
>> All right. Can I um send an offer to my
finance manager for 32,313?
>> 323
>> and that can I earn your business?
>> No, that'd be $1,000 off. That'd be,47
off.
147. Absolutely.
>> No, we were trying to get the 2500,
remember?
>> And you've gotten $500 so far. So, we're
around twice the discount of what you've
heard so far.
>> Yeah. I mean, at that rate, right, Russ,
we just keep calling around. We double,
you know, it's like double it, pass it
down, pass it to the next person. You
know,
>> you might find a dealership that's
that's wanting to do that. Absolutely.
Like you said, it's not unheard of. And
best of luck. If I can't, you know,
submit an offer and earn your business
at the 32,313,
I guess, let me know if we can earn your
business. That's with double key as
warranty as well. And um like I said, we
can help out with tradeins in the
future. We have an excellent service
department.
>> But what what ensures you in the future
is going to give me a great deal? Like
like what? Like I just I have to trust
you that moving forward you're always
going to give me a good deal or are we
going to do MSRP next time and you'll be
like that's a good deal. I'm your
dealership for life and then we have to
play this game. Like you're just
assuming like you I have as much trust
in you as you trust in me, right? Like
>> absolutely.
>> So that's why we're trying to get a good
deal now. If we get a good deal now then
that makes more sense, right?
>> Absolutely. Yeah. I mean the world's a
small place because of the internet. I
mean if your if your deals from a way
different market where they want, you
know, where they are able to or have the
desire to, you know, to discount
something that hasn't showed up yet, you
know, then that's really that's just
trying calling around and trying to find
someone in a situation where they want
to make that move. So like I said, thank
you for the offer. Um the counter offer
I was able to get back is for invoice
for the car, which is 3213. If I can
help you submit that, we can get the
financing together and uh and get him
squared away if that's the one for us.
>> Yeah. I mean, you want to send us that
offer so we can look at it and maybe
that's the best offer we get today and
that's what we do.
>> Is he getting one today?
>> It might be the best one we get. I mean,
if you feel confident that nobody will
or that the card invoice be a good deal,
then I'm all for it.
>> So, is he getting one today? Then
>> he's looking to buy a car today. Yeah.
By the end of the day, we're looking to
buy a car. Yeah. We're not just doing
this for funsies, right? Yeah. I've I've
I've told Russ, right? Russ, we never
call a dealership to waste people's
time. We always want to call when we're
serious. So, he's already driven and he
always wants it and if he gets the right
offer, he'll buy it today. Right, Russ?
Thank you.
>> Absolutely. I don't I will have to pick
a different one then and start from
scratch cuz I don't have that one in
stock until um the 11th. That's us
>> and like a deposit works, right? Like
the idea behind it is we're willing to
put a deposit. We're willing to lock a
deal up today. We don't need to
physically drive the car off the lot
today. So, like the idea behind it is we
are ready to commit to a vehicle today.
>> Take it off the market.
>> Yeah. So, like this car will be here,
you said in like two weeks. He's fine to
wait.
>> Okay. Is he replacing one or is this
like first car?
>> He's he's he's adding to the fleet.
We're in the first first first car.
First car.
>> Oh, exciting.
>> Yeah. Exciting.
>> That's why we're just teaching him a
life lesson, you know. Hello.
>> Is that Yes, I'm here. Yeah. Is that an
offer that I can submit for him for? I
mean, they discounted it to invoice for
us. I I know he's wanting to get the
best deal and you're wanting to help him
out with that, but that's the offer I
can submit. That's uh
>> yeah, I mean if you want to if you want
to throw us the offer if that's the best
you guys can do and you feel confident
you can't get to the number we're asking
for because remember you asked us what
what it would take to close the deal
today. We said this so you came back at
this totally fine maybe maybe I'm the
one that's crazy right Russ maybe like
you've seen me be crazy before um may
maybe I'm the one that's crazy and maybe
I can't get any better than this and47's
a great deal and if that's the best deal
we can get on it then we'll be calling
you right back.
>> Absolutely. Eager to help out with it.
Yeah, definitely let me know. Tell me
what's a good email and I can send this
over.
>> Can you just text it to me? It's easier
that way.
>> Yeah. What number?
>> Uh, yep. My phone number, if you're
ready for it, is
>> I'll send you um the system does have us
make sure that your permission is
acquired for any texting because some
some people don't prefer it. So, the
first text you get, it'll say um
>> is it all right if we text you message
back yes when you see that one.
>> I'm waiting for that.
>> Send it over. Adding the details to the
system here. You did say Tommy and
what's your last name?
>> U Mula. M I K U L A. and let me know
when you get the text.
>> Just waiting for that text.
>> You should get in anytime. Do they come
through when you're on the phone?
>> Yeah, I'm I'm just waiting on it still.
>> Oh, okay. Sometimes they don't come
through when someone's on the phone is
why why I asked. Or is that a different
number?
>> Yeah. Yeah, that's u I mean I can You
have the 980 number?
>> Yep. Uh 980.
>> That's it.
>> Okay. It sent 403, so I'm sure it'll
probably come through as soon as we hang
up. Okay, I will hang up the phone.
Hopefully, it goes through.
>> Sounds good. And then send over um I'll
send over a stock number, the vehicle
with the package, and um just the the
invoice price. Is that all you'll need
in the in the tech?
>> Yep, that's it.
>> And then I can take a look for rebates
and that kind of thing, too. Or is he is
he financing and wanting the best
interest rate he can get, or would he be
interested in extra $500 off um and
avoid the introductory interest rate?
>> He would be interested for the financing
if it gets him a better deal. Otherwise,
he can pay cash. Okay, gotcha. And then
I'll see about um there may be an extra
I'm not sure if financing is required
for it, but I can see about um about Kia
incentives as well. And um that I mean
is across the board as far as what he'll
qualify for wherever he gets it from.
>> Awesome. Perfect. This is super your
way.
>> Okay. Hopefully we can get this rocking
and rolling and uh get you or get sorry,
Ross, right? Get you into your new car.
He's very excited for hopefully uh we
can figure this out. And if you guys
decide to come a little bit lower, let
us know.
>> Sounds good. Well, if you decide, you
know, that the 200,000 milei warranty is
right for him, let me know. It
definitely makes a difference. So,
>> okay. Yeah. Well, we're hoping the car
doesn't break down for 200,000 miles,
but I I get it.
>> Absolutely. I'll talk to you guys soon,
Tommy.
>> Talk to you soon. Bye.
>> Thank you for calling me. This is Jeremy
and sales. How can I help you?
>> Hey, Jeremy. First off, I just want to
see if you guys have a car available.
>> A car available uh in terms of to
purchase or service?
>> Yes, to purchase.
>> Okay, awesome. Which car were you
looking at?
>> I have a stock number if that helps. Uh,
that'll be perfect. Actually, let me
just pull up my website so that I can
input that stock number. Okay, I'm ready
for you.
>> All right. Uh, stock number is 16881.
>> Okay. So, I have that one here on my
website, but if you don't mind, I want
to double check and make sure it's in
the key box cuz if it's there, that
means we definitely have it. It's a
possibility it could be an incoming unit
or one that's already been sold. So, I
want to double check for you.
>> All right.
>> Do you mind if I put you on hold for
that?
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. Awesome. One moment, please.
This is Joe.
>> Uh, hi Joe. I was talking to somebody
else and then I guess they u put me
here. So, quack quack. Guess we'll call
him back.
>> Great day. This is Stephen. How may I
assist you?
>> Hey, I just want to see if you guys have
a car available.
>> Okay. What vehicle was it that you were
interested in?
>> I have a stock number whenever you're
ready.
>> Okay. What's that stock number?
>> It's K is in Kangaroo 9062.
>> Okay. And where you seeing this vehicle
on our website or is that on auto trade
or anything like that
>> on your website? Should I see it
somewhere else?
>> No, we do so much advertising online. I
just want to double check and see
exactly which way it was that you saw
this vehicle.
>> Okay.
>> Was that the uh 2026 Kia Sportage, the
Wolf Grey one?
>> Uh correct.
>> Okay. It's still showing to be here and
available, but let me do you this favor
real quick. I'll double check and just
make sure we don't have any deposits or
anything else like that going on with
this footage. Should take me roughly
about 10 minutes. Were you calling
though sir from your home phone or your
cell phone?
>> My cell phone.
>> Okay. And that number is
>> uh phone number is
>> And sir, how do I spell your last name
correctly?
>> Mula. Mazan Mary I ku l a.
>> And what was your first name, sir?
>> Uh first name is Tommy.
>> Okay, Tommy. And was it just this
Sportage that you're looking for in
particular? Or if I have any others kind
of close to this price range, would you
be open to it?
>> I mean, I'm open to any Sport GX that's
in white, gray, or silver. Okay. Has to
be ex. And you said white, gray, or
silver.
>> And are you open to the 25 models if I
had that available or were you only
looking for the
>> I only want the 26.
>> Okay, no problem. Just wanted to see
exactly what all we'd be open to. Let me
do us this favor real quick, Mr. Tommy.
I see my new car director is actually
walking past me here on the showroom
floor. If you don't mind holding for me
one second, I can double check with him
and make sure this is still available. I
got you. Okay, perfect.
>> Meanwhile,
>> hey, Mr. Tommy.
>> Hey. Hey, thanks for holding for me.
Okay, I just checked with him. He said
that this one is available. But speaking
of being available, uh were you wanting
to come in and see this vehicle now or
possibly later on this afternoon or
>> Well, I've already driven one. I already
know I love it. Uh really just trying to
get the best price and I saw your offer
that you'll do any offer or give you
$1,000. So, I thought that would be uh
uh definitely worth um calling you guys
on.
>> Absolutely. Were you here locally in
town or were you calling from out of
state?
>> I'm calling from out of state.
>> Okay, no problem. Where were you calling
out of state from?
>> Uh from Kansas City.
>> Kansas City. Okay. Were you wanting to
have this vehicle shipped to you if
everything worked out or were you
planning on wanting to come in and pick
it up?
>> Based on how everything's going to go
down, I think it' probably be best that
I pick it up rather than have it
shipped.
>> Okay, no problem. And there in Kansas,
do they charge you guys your taxes there
at the dealership or uh do you take care
of that whenever you title your vehicle?
>> They do.
>> Okay. Here in Oklahoma, they don't
normally charge you your taxes here at
the dealership. Did you want to include
that here in your financing or are you
okay?
>> No, we can we can pay cash for those. No
big deal.
>> Okay, no problem. If you can definitely
do that and have the money uh have the
means to be able to take care of your
taxes, I tell everybody, hey, you might
as well take care of them out of pocket.
That way you don't have to worry about
paying interest on this money right
here.
>> Okay. Yeah, that sounds great.
>> Perfect. And were you planning on
wanting to trade in anything with this
purchase?
>> Nope, just uh just uh financing the
vehicle uh with no trade in.
>> Okay. How much were you planning on
wanting to put down with this purchase?
>> I'm not I mean 510,000 I'm not too
worried. I'm more worried about the out
the door number.
>> No problem. I at least want him to be
able to see everything and that way he
could show us all of your different
options, but at least that way I can get
with my new car director and he could
price out everything for me. Are you
guys uh current or retired military or
possibly own a Kia vehicle?
>> We are not.
>> Okay. And you said you guys don't own a
Kia vehicle, right?
>> We do not own a Kia right now. No.
>> Okay. I know they have some rebates and
incentives normally tied to uh military
and owner loyalty. Let me get with my
director and that way he could price
this out for us then and that way I
could show you exactly what everything
will be.
>> Okay. Did you want to know the offer
that I had from the other dealership?
>> Yes, sir. That'll be fine.
>> Okay, awesome. So, um you know, my my
family calls me the master negotiator. I
always try to get crazy cool things on
my deals here. So, I uh was willing to
do 2727
off. And this might sound a little
crazy, but uh it's been a dream of mine,
so I'm trying to make it happen here. Uh
they're also throwing in a wacky waving
fl inflatable tube man as part of the
deal. Like a fullsize one.
>> Okay. And was that a uh EX Sportage kind
of stickered around the same MSRP as
what mine is?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Same same car, same MSRP.
Everything's same. Uh with the wacky
inflatable tube man.
>> Okay. If you could do me this favor,
when we get off the phone here, I'm
going to shoot you a text message from
my phone. Tommy, if you could do me a
favor and send me over that offer that
you got from them, that way I can show
that to my director and that way he has
also some something that I can show him
of the actual uh competitive pricing.
>> Okay. Yeah. I I don't want to waste uh
too much time, so I can definitely send
that over. I just want to make sure not
crazy enough that that you guys would be
able to throw in the wacky inflatable
tube man too along with the discount.
That that'd be a deal breaker for me.
>> Okay. I'll get with them and I'll see
with my director and see if that's
something that uh if that's even
something possible that he could
definitely do or make work out for you.
>> Yeah. And I had to send them the link of
where to buy it. They're you can buy
them at like big stores. You can even
find them on Amazon. So like I I sent
them the link and they're willing to
order one right to their store.
>> Okay. Well, no problem then. I can tell
my director that and that way he could
take a look at everything for us and see
exactly what'll be able to work. Okay.
>> Okay. Yeah. Yeah. U Okay. So, I'm glad
that this doesn't seem crazy or weird to
you guys. That's that's always a good
sign.
>> Trust me, we we have seen some crazy and
weird things here at our dealership. So,
don't worry. You fit right in with the
rest of us. So, that's perfectly fine.
>> Okay. So, you need me to send the offer?
Do you want to text me?
>> Yes. I'm gonna shoot you a text here
shortly as soon as we get off the phone.
And then if you could send that back
over to me and at least that way I have
some information that I could show my
director. Here's the vehicle. Here's
exactly what they're offering and and
here's exactly what they're telling you.
>> Okay. Yeah, that's that's totally fine.
Um I can make sure that they also add
the inflatable to man to the offer that
was more verbally said, but they seem
pretty serious about it. They let me
pick my color and everything, too.
>> Oh, yeah. They weren't playing then if
they let you pick the color and
everything.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Pick a color of the car to
match the inflatable tube, man.
>> Well, then hopefully we could beat their
deal and earn your business here then.
>> Yeah. Otherwise, I get $1,000, right?
>> That's what it says. Let me get with
them then and uh get everything for you
then. Uh and at least that way I'll put
everything in front of him and that way
he can get me an answer. Okay.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> All right. You have a good one.
>> Okay. Bye.
>> Bye. Bye. So, overall consensus of this
deal, we ended up getting a little under
$3,000 off the car after everything was
said and done. We did that via text. It
was not with either one of these
dealerships. Now, the communication with
the first dealership was on point. They
texted us constantly, kept asking us for
updates, but they were really stingent
about not giving a deal, which is fine,
and communication is better than none.
We see a lot of dealerships that don't
communicate with us at all. The second
dealership here, we ended up sending
numbers and they ended up refusing to
match the deal. It wasn't the wacky and
inflatable tube man. It actually ended
up being the discount. That being said,
they were more than willing to throw
that in, which is kind of crazy. Uh my
client would have got a pretty cool
surprise if that ended up happening, but
that's okay. We'll have to try next time
on the wacky wavy inflatable tube. Man,
if you guys like these kind of outros
where I'm giving updates on the deals,
please don't be afraid to let me know.
Again, I would love to just show
screenshots of all the text. We're
trying to find a better way to do this,
but at the very least, I want to give
you closure so you have that on each one
of these videos. You like this, let me
know. Like, follow, subscribe, and I'll
see you next time.
[Music]