I mean, you would have to be
ridiculously dumb to think that it cost
that much money to do it.
>> Like, the only thing that's the weird
thing is you have fairly priced things
like ceramic tint for 400 bucks isn't
unreasonable.
>> Do you mind if I FaceTime you that way?
I I can just show it to you better.
>> Oh, I don't I don't use Apple. That's
the devil's work.
>> Okay.
>> Some things to make it cooler. And then
you guys added your logo that doesn't
even look pretty on there.
>> You know, next time you should tell
somebody if you're streaming a
conversation. You shouldn't, you know,
shouldn't do that because my my manager
wanted to just let me know it was being
streamed and you're being cute about it.
Have you ever heard of a markup before
in a car?
>> I I have heard of markup. This looks 10
times better, man. Let me show you the
pictures. Let me show you how bad it
looks with the chrome. Much better looks
with the black. Rather than just being
like,
it's markup. I know. Like, this is your
job. This is your career. This is how
you feed your family. By all means, you
should know these things. If you guys
don't know, my name's Tommy. I negotiate
car deals for a living. My goal is to
save you time, energy, and anxiety. We
save you money, but it's a byproduct. I
charge a flat fee of a thousand bucks. I
don't advertise as a money saving
service because you could do this on
your own and save a thousand bucks.
People hire me because they don't want
to deal with being on hold for 7 minutes
waiting for the specs of a car that may
or may not be available to know about
the add-ons. We're going to do an Acura
TLX Type S. Let's go, people. TLX. Let's
look this one up. 2025 new condition.
Type S. Only 102 of these in the
country, boys and girls. Urban gray.
There's only 16 in the country. Holy
moly. Somebody's hiring us to do a tough
car. This is a tougher meino. Oh, and
they only want red interior. There's
only eight. There's only eight. Okay,
this is good. We jumped on this car.
Okay, remember there's a lot of
inventory on this car. We're going to go
be calling in the Northeast.
>> Going to go call Tony. I can help you.
>> Hey Tony, it's Tommy. What are the
chances? I just want to see if you guys
have a car available.
>> A new car.
>> New car.
>> Yeah. Let me let you talk to uh Bruce.
Can you hold on one second?
>> I was hoping to speak to Bruce. Perfect.
It's an Acura. Thank you. I appreciate
it, Tony. Give me a Bruce.
>> All right, hold on one second.
>> Meanwhile,
>> it's Bruce. What car are you looking
for?
>> Bruce, man, I'm looking for I got a
stock number if that helps you, man.
>> Yeah, hold on.
>> I'm holding.
>> What's the year and model?
>> Uh, it's it's brand new one. 2025 Acura.
>> Okay, cool.
>> I was told you're the new car man,
Bruce.
>> That's incorrect. I'm the used car
manager. The new car manager is not in
at the moment, but I'll
then I guess I was I was lied to.
>> I don't think he lied to you. He was
standing right beside me.
>> Oh well. Okay, cool. I just want to see
if car's available. It's me. I make a
joke. Fun. The dad jokes don't land. I'm
not actually a dad yet. I'm just trying.
Not actually trying. That's actually a
joke. That's totally not real. Not
>> listen. My kids give me the whole uh dad
joke stuff all the time, so I'm with
you.
>> Yep. Yep. Uh okay. Do you Are you going
to stock number? Make model VIN. What do
you got?
>> Yep. Give me the stock.
>> Stock number L as in L41390.
>> TLX Type S.
>> That's it.
>> Yeah, that's We do have that in stock.
It came in uh with a little body damage.
We're waiting to send it out to the body
shop. Uh I don't have an ETA on it right
now.
>> Soundry. What kind of body damage?
>> You know, it wasn't that bad, but it's
worthy enough to go to the body. I
actually didn't see it. I just heard it.
I just I saw it in the back lot, but our
body people were a little bit backed up,
so it hasn't been through that yet. I'm
just being upfront with you. I'm just
>> No, I appreciate you being up front. Up
front and honesty is the way to go.
That's my mom when we said so.
>> Exactly.
>> Okay. So,
>> status on that one.
>> So, we just will won't know anything to
it till it's fixed.
>> Yeah. Do you want us to give you a call?
>> Yeah, that'd be great. Yeah, give me a
call. Give me a ring. Give me a jingle.
>> Sir,
>> sorry. Sorry. I think I lost you there.
>> That's okay. Yeah. What's your name?
>> Yeah, my name's Tommy.
>> Tommy. And it's a good number to reach.
You have a trade or anything?
>> Nope. No trade. Just buying.
>> North Carolina. What's Alton buy?
>> Uh, well, that's that's where I used to
live. I live in Brooklyn now.
>> Oh, okay. Gotcha. No, I had family down
in North Carolina. Just curious.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> All right. Um, I'm going to give this to
Tony. He's the one that answered the
phone. He's one of our greatest sales
manager or salesman and uh we'll keep an
eye out for this and give you a holler
when it's done.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> All right, buddy. Take care. Bye.
>> All right. Bye.
>> Rep.
>> Hey, uh I just want to see if you guys
have a car available.
>> What was the car you're looking for?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> You can try that. What's your stock
number?
>> Yeah. 25782.
>> 25782.
>> You got it.
>> It didn't pop up. So, let me try a
different way. So, used car, new car.
>> Brand new.
>> Okay. What kind of car is it?
>> Uh, it is an Acura TLX Type S.
>> Was it the gray one?
>> The Urban Grey Pearl with the red
interior. Yep.
>> I think that was sold I believe it might
have been sold yesterday.
>> Oh, bada boom. Bada bing in the worst
way.
>> Hold on a second. Let me make sure. Let
me see if it's available. Okay, here.
The car is available, but it does have a
lot of um other stuff in that it put
into the car like tinted windows and
other stuff that goes, but all together
the price of the car uh is $633.99.
It is available. The original price of
the car was 59,845.
Okay.
>> Like I said, it does have a lot of
accessories are nice in the car. Really
nice was showroom car. They took it out
of the showroom yesterday and I thought
they were s they sold it, but no, it's
still available.
>> Okay. Uh you said a lot of things and
you just kind of said I think tint like
what what is the nice things? That's 4
grand. So I know
>> this is your cell phone number here.
>> Yep. This is my cell phone number.
>> Are you calling me on another number?
>> Hello. Yeah, it's Peter.
>> Oh, okay. Hey. Yeah, I know. What
happened?
>> Okay, one second. Hold on. Hey, sir.
>> I'm still here.
>> Okay. I'm walking through the car now.
Oh,
>> okay.
>> One second.
>> You're good.
>> Which city are you calling from?
>> Brooklyn.
>> Oh, New York. Okay.
>> New York.
>> Wait a second. So, the car it's got the
glass black emblems.
>> Glass watch em.
>> No, glass black emblems.
>> Black glo. Okay. So, you guys added
black gloss emblems. Okay.
>> Got the side rear under under body um
spoiler. Okay.
>> It's got the valve M caps.
>> These are all things that you guys added
onto the car.
>> Yeah, these these are all things we
added to the car, right?
>> Okay.
>> A showroom car. That's the reason why we
have a showroom car. We always add
things to the car.
>> Okay. Anything else?
>> That's it.
>> So, the bloss the the emblems, the
spoiler, and the emboss cost 4K. And
there's no tint.
>> There's tint. Yes.
>> Cuz there's also tint. Is there
anything?
>> No. No. I I named that for you when we
straighten everything. I don't know if
you heard me, but yeah, the ceramic
window tints. The tinted windows. So,
the $4,000 is the black gloss emblems,
the side spoiler, the embossed whatever,
and the tint
>> all together. I'm actually going to take
a picture so I can show it to you right
now. Hold it a second.
>> Yeah.
>> All right. I just text it to you.
>> Okay. I'm waiting for it. So, you guys
are charging $1,220
for the gloss black emblems, $1,790
for the side underbody spoiler. You're
charging $119 for the valve stem caps,
and $425 for the ceramic tint. Okay.
Gloss blacks. I'm trying to like look at
the pictures on the cards to see like
and it says that that's 5,000. Wait,
never mind. Okay. Price before for it.
Okay. I see I see what you're saying.
What What did you guys make black? I'm
just trying to like I'm looking at the
pictures online. I just see normal
emblems like the TLX's the the the Acura
logo, the front's silver, the Sakura
logo on the back silver, the TLX is
silver, the Type S is silver, the like
what's black.
>> Hold on one second, please. One second.
>> Sure. Take a time. Yeah. I mean, I see
the pictures. I'm looking at the
picture. I muted him. I'm looking at
pictures of the car and there is It
looks like they just He just sent me two
more pictures of the car and they
blacked out the TLX logo.
>> Did you get that picture? I Yes, I see
the pictures you're referring to. I
mean, the only thing that I can maybe
see based on these two pictures is the
TLX logo in the back. Might It also
looks silver to me. I can't really tell.
Is it black?
>> What part? I'm sorry. I can hear you.
>> I'm I'm trying to figure out what you
guys blacked out for $1,200. $1,200 is
not a cheap amount of money to black
out. I mean, I like my car looking cool,
but I'm trying to figure out what you
guys blacked out for the emblems for
1,200 bucks. I'm looking at the pictures
online versus this, and like they look
the same. I don't even see anything
blacked out. See the letters? I think
maybe. Hold on a second. I think the
letters are actually I'm trying to
figure out I mean I I read the list. I
think I picture the list. I'm trying
>> I see I see the list. I'm trying to
figure out what the blacked out. I mean
like let's be really clear. If all you
guys did was change the TLX to black
letters and you're charging $1,200
for that.
>> You ever seen the on this the Type R?
They put $10,000 in markup. So I mean
we're allowed to to mark up the car. I
mean, I'm sure that it doesn't cost that
much money to do that if you're trying
to figure out the procedure if it's that
costly to do that. No, it's of course
it's not, but you know, we're entitled
to to mark up the car just like the Pipe
R. Is it Why do they charge you $10,000
more in the price of the car? What does
it do to it? It's so special. You know,
they mark up the car. It looks nicer.
Does it cost that much money to do it?
No, I don't think so. I mean, you would
have to be ridiculously dumb to think
that it cost that much money to do it.
Well, I mean, you could feel as a
consumer that just sees the sticker
would be confused. I mean, I I would
just feel like a dealership would be
honest about what like things are. If
you want to charge markup, charge markup
on the car, right? Why why lie and hide
it in your ad about stem caps that are
$7 that are 119. Like the only thing
that's the weird thing is you have
fairly priced things like ceramic tint
for 400 bucks isn't unreasonable. So
like gloss emblem like if you're like
trying to make an extra two or 300 bucks
on the emblems, I get it. But if that's
the only thing that's blacked out is
three letters, you you can understand
why I'm confused, right? I didn't
question anything else. Spoiler makes I
I see the spoiler. I get I get the
spoilers on the side. I don't get your
emblems.
>> Uh maybe the u see you see the the
letters like TLX behind him all drive
and see if I can take a picture of it
for you.
>> Yeah. I mean, you didn't give me a good
enough picture to identify. I just see
TLX. It kind of looks blacked out.
>> Do you mind if I FaceTime you that way?
I I can just show it to you better.
>> I don't I don't use Apple. It's the
devil's work.
>> Okay. You know what I got to do?
>> But you guys, like the worst part is you
guys added your logo on the back of this
car. So you guys like blacked out some
things to make it cooler and then you
guys added your logo that doesn't even
look pretty on there.
>> The logo. We can take it off. That's not
a problem. That's a sticker.
>> Why don't you just take all the stuff
off and just give me an MSRP?
>> That's what we're not going to do.
They're going to do that at price that I
gave you.
>> In fact, the guy who was going to buy
the car, which the reason why they took
it out of the showroom, he started
trying to deal all the emblems and all
that in the markup on the car.
He he did exactly what probably
everybody's doing, which is are seeing
$1,200 of emblems.
>> That's why I'm going to be very clear to
you and let you know that it ain't going
to happen. If that's the car's
available, as long as you pay for that,
if it doesn't pay for that, then
obviously the car is not available. I'm
just being honest with you. I don't want
you to come over here, look at the car,
and think you need to get an MSRP. My
boss made it very clear to me. I was not
even the person who was going to sell
this car before. It was somebody else,
which is the reason why I thought it was
sold already. And I found out the reason
why the guy backed out of it was because
the guy, even though he knew everything
about it, like I'm telling you, he knew
it already. He tried to back out of it
and tried to say, "I just want to pay
MSRP." And that's why it didn't work.
>> I I I mean, I could see his side. I
mean, paying what the manufacturer would
suggest you sell it at would be seems
like a fair, not a crazy concept. To
call me crazy rather than paying $1,200
for some emblems that took your tech 20
minutes to put on. That probably wasn't
even your tech, like your lot guys.
Worst part is is the TLX. Like the the L
and the X is like separated. So like
it's not even like properly spaced. It's
just like a hack job.
>> Which one?
>> The L if you look at the gap between the
L and the T and the T and the X. It's
just not even like it doesn't even look
natural. Looking at I'm looking at an
original one. I guess this is what
happens when you change logos on cars.
You now get people questioning.
>> Everything's original. They didn't they
got letters or anything like that.
Everything is the way it's supposed to
be. It's just
>> Oh. Oh. Are you just saying somebody
just wrapped them?
>> I don't know how they did it. I don't
see the process. If you Are you talking
to me about the TLX?
>> You're the one charging $1,200 for it. I
mean, I think like you're saying they
wrapped the letters because that's the
only way to do it. You either paint the
letters, you wrap the letters, or you
replace the letters. Replacing the
letters seem to be the make the most
sense. You're trying to claim that they
they didn't take them off.
>> I see it here. Yeah.
>> Is it just wrap? Is it paint? If it's
paint, it's just going to chip off
eventually. It's going to look bad 5
years down the road. If it's wrap, then
I can take it off.
>> No. You know what? It looks like
metallics. I wish I can FaceTime so that
way I can show it to you.
>> Yeah, I don't do that. I don't need Tim
Cook getting into my life.
>> Who? Tim Cook.
>> Tim? Yeah. Yeah. He's he person he
personally watches every single iPhone.
That's what I heard.
>> Okay, forget about that.
>> Yeah, close up.
>> Yeah. No, I mean I guess I'll cut to the
chs insane. $1,200 for for some emblems
seems insane. I'm I'm in the same boat
as your last customer, which is I think
and I feel like you're I'm not going to
be the only one u that isn't going to
want to pay for all these crazy add-ons.
If you want to charge markup, just be
honest and charge markup. If you think
your car is worth it,
>> there's people who do markups and they
don't put anything in the car. They just
do $10,000 markup. All we are we
charging is just you're getting a little
something extra.
>> If you give me a Q-tip and say, "Hey, I
gave you a Q-tip. Here's a $1,200
Q-tip." It still doesn't make any value
to me. Like, right? Like, it's not like
I'm like, "Oh my god, I can't believe
you gave me an Alani for $1,200. Oh,
you're so much better than the
dealership charging 1,200 bucks. Oh,
then he just hung up. Okay, dealerships,
I'm sorry, but if you're adding any like
add-ons onto the car, if you want to be
honest, right, just be honest. If you
think your car is worth $10,000 a
markup, by all means, just advertise on
your website. And this is the problem
that I have with car sales right now.
You should be able to sell the hell out
of this. Let's let's be real. You're
about to buy an Acura Type S. You're not
buying a Honda Civic. You're buying an
Acura Type S. And one of the reasons why
people love this car, not only they fun
to drive, not only they are just
beautiful in the interior, but people
look at this car on the street, and I'm
sorry, when you have blacked out wheels,
red interior, beautiful tint, and a
blacked out spoiler, nobody wants chrome
emblems. So, what we did is we had all
of our emblems prof professionally
plasti dipped or whatever it is to not
only look better, so it actually matches
the vibe of the car, but it actually
gives a better, more mean appearance.
Like in theory, if this guy had any
sales skill at all, that would make the
difference.
This is dummy.
>> Were you streaming that conversation by
any chance?
>> I am.
>> You are? Why would you do that?
>> Because I'm trying to buy a car.
>> I know, but why would you stream it?
>> Because I'm trying to tell buy a car.
>> You didn't tell me you were streaming
it.
>> You Yeah, you told me the call was
recorded for quality assurance.
>> No, no, you you didn't say nothing to
me. I thought I called you and you
didn't tell me you were streaming the
the phone call. That's okay. That's the
way you do things. Uh, just so you know,
they the these are original u letters.
They put the letters I guess they took
the old letters and they put new
letters. That's how they did it. Just
let you know.
>> Um, so they did what I said. If you're
trying to catch me off guard with all
these questions, I don't know how they
do when they put these things on guards.
I saw them do it on the showrooms. A
company came in to do the windows, all
the other stuff. I don't know how they
did it. So, if you're asking the wrong,
if you want to know the truth about
everything on how they did it, just call
one of their managers and then you can
ask one of the managers how they did it.
You know, next time you should tell
somebody you're streaming a
conversation. You shouldn't, you know,
shouldn't do that because my my manager
was want to just let me know it was
being streamed and you're being cute
about it. That's not
>> Why Why am I being cute? I'm literally
asking about the add-ons you have in
your car. I didn't put the add-ons in
the car and you guys are charging. Is it
Is it not crazy for me to not expect you
to know what is on your car? And if
you're new at this, you just be like,
"Hey, dude. I'm kind of new at buying
I'm selling cars like my only been doing
this for a little bit. let me go get
some answers rather than like like just
being like I don't know how this $1,200
thing is on like is that like a crazy
you ever heard of a markup before in a
car?
>> I I heard of markups but again if you
guys are positioning as a product you
have to at least know about the product
you're selling rather than being like
yeah we're ripping people off. We just
have markup. It's just we're throwing
some nice things.
>> Smart guy. You're smart guy. You know I
can tell by talking to you. Smart guy.
So you would know that. You would know
the difference. It was Listen, when they
do the the type S, they don't just uh
you know put 10,000. They don't put any
accessories. They just mark it up.
$10,000. At least we put in a little
something. That's at least that's the
way I would look at it. But it's okay.
>> Does your manager know you called back?
My my recommendation if your manager
knew you like you called back. I don't
think he probably wanted you to call.
Maybe he did, but I think you're digging
yourself a bigger hole, man.
>> What am I doing? What am I I'm trying to
be courteous to you because Anyway,
listen.
>> Yeah. I mean, dude, what what I'm saying
is and just like I talked to a lot of
dealerships. When it comes down to it,
if you're going to charge an add-on, you
can't just hide behind, oh, it's a
markup. Like add some value to it. I
have an M5. My M5 has black emblems on
it. It looks way better on there. And I
can defend this looks 10 times better,
man. Let me show you the pictures. Let
me show you how bad it looks with the
chrome. Much better it looks with the
black rather than just being like
I'm like it's markup. I'm not
>> Why would you say Why would you ask me
if I would get in trouble cuz I called
you back? Do you know
>> because your manager you hung up you
hung up the phone and then you just
called back saying, "The reason I hung
up the phone is my manager told me you
were streaming this."
>> Yeah.
>> The idea of the phone disconnected
wasn't happening. Your manager told you
that you're being streamed. You hung up
the phone and now you just called back.
So, like
>> I just found out that you were being you
were streaming me. My operator just told
me you're streaming a phone call. And I
was like, are you serious? I don't think
so. I was talking to the guy. I didn't
hear anything about streaming. There's
nothing to me about streaming.
>> I mean, it shouldn't be like we're being
transparent about buying a car. I mean,
this should be like super You should be
super excited that I'm streaming you in
front of thousands of people that could
be wanting to buy a car right now. Like,
you could be advertising yourself to
thousands of people right now.
>> Yeah. But I rather you be I'd rather be
ready for the product, not the
>> Yeah, but but let me let me ask you
this. If I said, "Hey, you're about to
be on live TV. Are you going to act the
same exact way as you normally would, or
are you going to
>> I'm going to prepare myself. I'm going
to prepare yourself with knowledge and
everything."
>> So So what you're saying is you're going
to treat it differently than you would
every other interaction.
>> I would try to get some knowledge on the
car. I would try to get every detailed
knowledge that I could because that's
the kind of person that I am, honest
person. And then I would talk to you and
say, "Listen, when you ask me a
question, at least I would know what to
tell you. You think we know everything.
Every salesman knows everything how we
how we do things here. It's not the way
it works, sir. you know, um I don't know
how they what they what procedure, what
kind of paint they use. I don't know if
it's wrapped or not. I don't know. We
don't really do these kind of things
here. And when there's a showroom car,
they do these certain things in certain
cars. That's the honest truth. I'm being
honest with you. You know,
>> I appreciate you being honest. But I'll
tell you, you just nailed the exact
reason why I don't tell people that I'm
streaming because if I told you I'm
streaming, you are now going to do above
and beyond extra work to be prepared so
you look better than what you actually
are. You should know these things. You
work at the dealership. I don't know why
you work there. You should know that.
And I bet your manager watches this and
he says, "Oh, wow." You should Yeah. If
you're charging $1,200 for some for some
black emblems, you should know if
they're wrapped, plasty dipped, or if
they're new emblems. Like, that's not a
crazy concept, man. Like, you can't just
hide behind, oh, we sell an Acura. Most
people charge 10K. At least I know.
Like, this is your job. This is your
career. This is how you feed your
family. By all means, you should know
these things. And I'm betting if your
manager watching is right now, your
manager is going to be like, "You know
what? You're you're right. You're right.
You should know these things, man."
>> Not really. You know why? because I
don't I sold many cars here and I've
never sold a car where I sell emblems or
over MSRP. That's why it's a showroom
car. I never sold a showroom car. I've
been here for a couple of years. It's
just not my my thing. So, what you
think? It's not necessarily the truth.
Always just to show you proof. I've been
here for 5 years now. But it's okay.
Listen, you didn't know and I didn't
know. Put me off guard. All that
matters.
>> Yeah. And it's okay. And if you don't
know the answer, you just say, "Hey, you
know what? I don't know that. Let me go
get that for you." And then you put me
on hold. You go get an answer. Hey, how
are these?
>> You were you were playing a train. you
you were asking question after question
after question. I was like, "Oh, this
guy's just asking me every credit." And
if if anybody would hear the streaming,
they would they would understand. They
were basically almost attacking me on
every you're trying to justify
everything that I was telling you.
>> You just said the person yesterday did
the same exact thing. The person not
streaming that heard about the emblems,
started questioning the emblems. Like,
this isn't just a Tommy thing that's
streaming. It's it's people see car,
they see $1,200 emblems, they question
this. People don't just look at the car
be like, "Oh, yeah, that's normal.
$1,200 for a TLX logo makes sense."
Like, people don't do that. Like,
>> well, you spoke to somebody here
yesterday.
>> No, what I'm saying is you said somebody
literally was about to buy the car
yesterday and then they started trying
to question all the add-ons and all the
all the stuff like this you just said.
>> Same thing.
>> I heard that question. They didn't want
to pay for it. They didn't want to pay
for it. They knew about it cuz they saw
it in the showroom. We had it in the
showroom. It's not like it was
surprised. They saw it in they came here
and I thought it was being sold. That's
why I told people in the beginning I
sold already. But then I found out it
wasn't. The guy started say I don't want
to pay for this. I don't pay for this. I
don't pay for this. He thought it was
just because they took it out of the
showroom. he was going to get away with
it and then I found out he wasn't.
That's not the case. So,
>> yeah. My recommendation again, you do
you do you. Uh but if you're selling the
product, you should like I don't care if
it's a one of one rare car and this is
the only car you've ever put emblems on.
It's It's crazy that I'm asking basic
questions on a markup you have $1,200 on
and you can't answer them.
>> Yeah. Well, guess whoever heard you, I
look very sick, very u ignorant, and
very guess not educated as far as the
the product. So, you you got what you
got? I'm trying to buy a car. I have
We're trying to buy an Acura TLX Type S.
That's what we're trying to do. And you
could turn this whole thing around by
trying to make a deal happen. But
instead, you still haven't done this.
You just complained that I've caught you
by surprise cuz you're being streamed.
Like, like it shouldn't change the
process at all. You could still sell a
car here.
>> Listen, my friend, if you interested in
the car, it's here. If you want me to
help you, I'll help. I'll be more than
glad to help you.
>> Again, I'm still trying to buy a car.
We're still trying to buy one. We're
just trying to get a good deal on a TLX.
if anything changes.
>> You know, it's crazy. Some people just
don't think it's a fun thing to buy a
car and they they believe that a lot of
dealerships lie and cheat and steal. I'm
not saying they all do, but we I just
film it. I just put myself in the camera
and see what happens.
>> Yeah.
>> Like it's it's not a crazy like it's
everything's live stream nowadays.
>> Well, I guess you're right. That's where
we live. Anyway, if anything changes, uh
I didn't catch your name. What's your
name?
>> My name's Tommy, but and this is
delivered. You can find the channel
online. But but but again, I'm I'm not
uh like again, I'm still trying to buy a
car. So, if your manager wants to sell a
car, wants to turn this all around.
Let's let's rock and roll. Otherwise,
like I mean, if you guys want to sell
the car, you guys want to sell a car,
but
>> I'll speak to him, I'll let see what he
says. And if he says yes or if he says
no or whatever, whatever he tells me,
I'll let you know.
>> Oh, yeah. You can just text me.
>> Be fair. All right, sir. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> Just so we're clear, this is the exact
reason why I don't tell people we're
streaming because he said exactly what
he did. Well, if I knew you were
streaming, I would have prepared for it.
I would have done all the research on
the car and I would have been ready.
Which would not give you the audience a
proper representation of what it's like
to buy a car. This is why it's like hard
for me to be like, "Oh, when somebody
recognized me, things get easy." And
you're like, "Oh, wow. Buying a car is
super easy." Like even then, like they
know they're being streamed. My BMW,
this is my M like the M5 emble. And
that's sick to me. I bought a sports car
and like for example, I have I have the
blacked out grill. I have a a lip. I
paid extra for all of these things when
I bought the car and we did the
modifications oursel. And you could
easily say, "Hey, what we realize is a
lot of people after they buy these cars,
they put these emblems on there because
it doesn't look good with the chrome."
If you think the chrome looks good, by
all means, we can go find you one with
chrome. But most people agree the
blacked out emblems look better.
>> Acur.
>> Hi Ricky. Uh, I just want to see if a
new car is available.
>> Okay. You mean you're trying to buy a
new car? I mean hopefully as long as
everything goes well.
>> Cool. We look at
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Give it to me.
>> Uh stock number S is in Santa. A is in
Alpha 001394.
>> What model is it?
>> It is a Acura TLX Type S.
>> The gray one.
>> The urban gray.
>> Urban gray. Yes, sir. We got that car in
stock.
>> Awesome. Perfect. Well, I've driven one.
Already know I love it. Want more of it.
Really just trying to get some pricing.
Hoping you can help me out.
>> Um yeah. MSRP on that car is what?
598.45 and we're not discounting. That's
the only type S we have in stock.
>> Okay. Um, so you guys are selling it for
59845.
>> Whatever MSRP is is what our price is.
No ads, no no anything. Just that plus
taxes.
>> Ads plus. So no ads, no nothing, just
this. And you guys won't discount that
at all either.
>> I mean, if we had incentives, most of
the time we have conquest or loyalty or
we have something. But right now, since
they're not going to be making the TLX
anymore, the type S is pretty desirable.
Um, we got a white one in last week.
Somebody from Austin came and bought it
because locally they're charging them
over MSRP. So, he bought it for MSRP.
But yeah, I really can't really I mean,
I'm not going to say I can't. I just
don't want to discount that car. It's
going to sell.
>> I appreciate that. I don't want to take
a car from you that's going to sell for
sure. I was hoping to be a little bit
below MSRP, though. Yeah. Call me Call
me trying to be a winner.
>> Yeah. No, I understand. Totally
understand. But supply and demand, I
just won't have that car. I won't have a
replacement. It is my last type S. This
is my last TLX I'm ever going to
receive. So, you know, I think MSRP for
that car. I mean, I know it's everybody
wants the best price possible, but I
think it's a good deal.
>> I appreciate that. I'm going to keep
looking just to be safe, but I mean,
MSRP doesn't seem horribly off compared
to some other dealerships. You're right.
Some are crazy.
>> Yes, sir. Can I get your name and number
and if something does change, I'll give
you a call. That's not fair.
>> Of course. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Uh name
Tommy Mucula. Uh phone.
>> Thank you for your time. time something
changes, we'll definitely give you a
call.
>> And if you don't find a better deal,
hopefully you snatch this one up from
us.
>> Hey, I love it, man. I appreciate your
energy.
>> Thank you, brother.
>> Okay, bye.
>> Byebye.
>> That's it. It's that easy. Like, that's
cool, right? Like that's it.
[Music]