Yeah. I mean, the way I'm looking at it,
they're losing several thousand dollars.
>> Maybe they really like me. Have you
thought of that? What if he's trying to
be the top 10 in the country? Would that
like maybe like maybe he's motivated to
lose some money on some deals, to make
some money on some other? I don't know.
I'm just thinking.
>> Well, big with the big old fat daddy
discount on that bad boy.
>> The big old fat daddy discount.
Yeah. Yeah. You want to tell me a little
bit more about the big old fat daddy
discount? You know, obviously I
understand it's a big daddy discount.
was really hoping for like a big mama
discount, you know, like try one more
time to get the mother-in-law. The
mother-in-law that we like, the
mother-in-law that we actually like, not
the mother-in-law that we like we have
to go see.
>> Okay. Merry Christmas.
>> Let's call this Ford deal. This is an
F350
Platinum with the Tremor package. This
is a fun one. They need the V8 turbo
diesel. Is it the 6.7 L? I think it
needs to be a 4x4 cuz why wouldn't they?
They want the rapid. They want the moon
roof. They want the dual alternator
wheel well liner, which they can get
anywhere. That's not a big deal. Engine
block, the 410, and the power running
boards. And they are looking for the
colors of carbonized gray is the only
color they'll take. Only 27 of these in
the country. I do have a dealership that
said they would give us one, but they
are not responding back. Advertising
$105,45.
We are going to go for the standard
oneofa-kind, never been done before, 10%
off.
Thank you for calling.
Please select from the following menu
choices. Press one for commercial sales.
>> Hey, are you in new car sales?
>> Yes, sir, I am.
>> Bada boom, bada bing. I love it. Hey, I
just want to see if you guys have a
truck available.
>> Yeah, give me one second. Let me get
logged into my computer and I will
answer that for you.
>> No.
>> Well, what are you looking for, though?
>> Uh, it is an F350.
>> 350. Okay.
Sure. Dang one second.
>> Drop my pen.
I see you're calling from the new uh I
mean North Carolina. Is that correct?
>> Nope. I'm from New Jersey.
>> New Jersey. Accent?
>> No, I could not. Not at first. Now I
can't. All righty.
>> Have you ever just dropped a pen before
and it just disappears off the face of
the earth?
>> Oh, yeah. Actually, that happened to me
about an hour ago. That happened to me
about nothing.
>> All right. Do you have a stock in the
vehicle available or the vehicle you're
looking for?
>> Yeah. Yeah, I do. U is in uranium. S is
in Subaru. 0028
>> US 0028
the platinum 2026.
>> That's it.
>> Yes, sir. Black. Yes, sir. That seems to
be available. Yes, sir.
>> Awesome.
>> Well, hey, I already know this is the
truck we want. Uh, want it, want more of
it. Really just trying to get some
pricing and I'm hoping you can help me
out.
>> Sure thing. Let me add you in here real
quick. It's a good number to reach you
at.
>> Yep. Best number.
>> That's correct.
>> All righty. What's your first name?
>> Tommy.
>> Yeah.
>> And Tommy, what's your last name? Last
name Makula. M I K U L A.
>> Got it. Perfect.
>> Where did this pen? I'm more sorry. I'm
more upset about this pen.
>> I'm going to ask you. I'm the whole time
we talk. I'm going to ask you if you
ever found it.
>> So, let me know when you find it.
>> Can I have the um the zip code of the um
the
>> Yeah.
>> All righty. New Jersey. Gotcha. Here we
go. I'm going to send you a text right
now. It's just going to say
text you. Just go respond back with yes.
And I'll shoot you over the pricing. I
love it. Make it easy.
>> Yes, sir. And then are you guys gonna be
looking to um just just drive down here
and like I don't know, you and somebody
else drive down here and then drive the
car back or
>> That's what we're looking to do.
>> You have a trade in we're working with.
Okay. No trade in.
>> No, no trade in. No,
>> no trade in. Okay, gotcha. All righty.
Give me one second. I'll send you over
the pricing.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> Perfect. He's in a seat looking for it.
I'll get back to you shortly. Bye.
>> Okay, sounds good. Where did it go?
[Music]
You guys have no idea. It's I have one
thing I stand on here and that's it.
I've lost three pens in the last two
days.
>> Thank you for calling Ford. How can I
direct your call?
>> Hello. Can I speak to somebody in the
new car sales department?
>> All right. Were you working with anybody
on our team yet?
>> Nope. Uh, brand new to the family.
>> One moment, please. Thank you for
calling. This is Felicia. Can I help?
>> Hello, Felicia. I just wanted to see if
you guys have a car available.
>> Sure. What is the stock number?
>> You know what? I would give you the
stock number, but I'm not even making
this up. It's just blank. It's just an
abyss. It's nothing there.
>> Okay. It may be an intransit unit. What
is the vehicle?
>> It's an F350 Platinum.
>> Okay. And is it a 25 or a 26?
>> It says new 2026.
>> Okay. One moment.
>> Take your time. It should be carbonized.
Gray.
>> I see two white ones and a black one on
our website currently.
>> Am I calling?
>> This is
>> awesome. I see one on your website that
says that 2026 Ford Superduty F350
Platinum and the F350 and the Platinum
are both trademark with the little R
button or a little circle. MSRP 10510.
>> Yeah, I'm looking. Okay, interesting.
I'm on our website right now. I don't
see it. Let me try to see if our
commercial manager is not at his desk
because he may have just updated the
website. It might be doing something
funny right now cuz I can only see the
three 2026s we have. Are you sure it's a
26, not a 25? I'm getting old and my
eyesight's not how it used to be, but it
says new in all caps and it says 2026.
I'm not mistaken. The six and the five.
I can see the five and 350. It looks
like a five and the six and the 26 looks
like a six.
>> Okay. Very odd. Yeah, our website must
be doing something.
>> I lost my pen earlier. So, it's like the
same thing. You lost your pen. You lo I
lost a pen. You lost a car.
>> What is your first and last name?
>> My first name and last name is Tommy
Amakula.
>> Could you spell your last name, please?
>> Sure. It's M I K U L A.
>> Thank you so much. and your phone number
in case we get disconnected.
>> Area's leading dealer when it comes to
providing exceptional customer
satisfaction in sales.
>> A few moments later.
>> Hello. I was speaking to somebody and I
was on hold and I was just chilling
listening to some jazz and now I'm here.
>> That's it. Yeah, you're a mind reader,
dude. You're good.
>> Plant right now. Looks like MSRP is
and $10.
>> That's it. That's the one I'm looking
at.
>> It looks like Yep, it is in the plant.
Hold on one second. Customer's name is
not on anything. It looks like it should
send to the plant this week. So, you're
looking I would probably say 6 to 8
weeks from this week. The end of this
week.
>> I'm open for that.
>> Okay. And what's your name, sir?
>> My name's Tommy.
>> All right. You're looking pay cash
finance. What do you
>> open to cash? Open to finance. How you
want to pick it? Okay. You have anything
to trade?
>> No trade.
>> Okay. So, what I can do is I can set you
up with my commercial manager. I'm just
a used I'm just a used car manager, but
Felicia couldn't find the car in our
locator system. Uh I can have I'm going
to print out this window sticker for him
and I can have him give you a call back
in about 15 minutes. Would that work for
you?
>> Sure. I I got nowhere to be.
>> All right. What is your phone number,
Tommy?
>> Uh my phone number is
>> 15 minutes and his name is Josh. I'll
give you a call back shortly. And I
already printed out the window sticker.
Sounds good. So he knows what what car
we're on. All right. Thanks a lot,
Tommy.
>> No problem. Bye.
>> The first dealership sent me numbers on
the truck. They're at $2500 off a
$100,000 truck. I was hoping closer to
10%. I'm calling Scott.
>> There's 2500 add-ons there.
>> What is the 2500? Oh, I see what you've
done there.
>> Yeah. I see, man. We can knock them all
out real quick at the bike. I know this
F350 we've been waiting for Jake for a
week on.
>> What is it?
>> It's an F350 2026
>> 2026 or 2025 2026. I think he's open. I
think he just wants new. He wants a He
needs have the 6.7 Power Stroke Super
Power engine tremor off-road power
running boards panel moon roof. Great.
>> Does it have to be a 350?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> So, can it be a 250? I mean, you're
putting a tremor on it anyway, so you're
losing all the
>> I didn't ask him. Let me see. He just he
told me 350 and the man tells me what he
wants. Um,
>> if you don't get the tremor, the 350
short box is the worst riding vehicle
that Ford makes.
>> Uh, the vehicle that he thumbsed up on.
I'm going to send it to you right now.
This is the vehicle that he you have in
your inventory right now that he said,
"You know what?
>> This is the one actually stock number."
>> Yeah, it's T is in tango 26004. He
thumbs up.
>> Oh, hold on. Hold on. 79 store.
>> Yep. This is the one that he thumbsed up
and just said if you give him a crazy
deal and then
>> see26004
I got what's
>> on October 2nd.
>> Okay. At 355 I'm in gray.
>> Sure. What's your crazy deal?
>> I think 11% off now cuz 10% was the deal
before.
>> Well, there's no I mean is this a 25 or
a 26? There's no rebate.
>> I know. Scott, remember the good old
days when we used to do all the crazy
deals?
>> What's that?
>> Remember the good old days we used to do
all these deals together?
>> Yeah. Yeah. And then they and then you
know you got busy and I got busy and
you're doing bigger things. I'm doing
bigger things. See how it works. You
know
>> I'm trying to get I'm trying to get you
to top 10 and we're trying to get me to
number one which I'm number one but we
need to get you to top 10 now.
>> I know I'm 21. So
>> you're 20. Dude, we got Okay, we're
we're going to fix that right now.
>> You can't climb a mountain without one
step at a time.
>> Eight grand. Can we do 10 grand and
let's go
>> 10 grand? I mean that's like $600 off.
Yeah, it's fine. Just send me Send me an
actual sheet so I can give it to him.
>> All right. And you just want to I
probably have this car here.
>> Yeah, I I'm literally looking at it. A
picture of it. Looks great.
>> Well, it's not here. I'm talking about
here in Apex. I probably have same.
>> Okay. Yeah, that's fine.
>> That's 350. Okay. All right. I'll send
you a sheet.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> Yeah, man.
>> All right. Bye. So, uh, just so you guys
know, the dealership I've done a lot of
business with in the past, but you can
see we haven't done business together.
Some people might be, Tommy, why you
giving them a hard time? I know this
dealership is watching the stream, but
also wants to be top 10 in Ford. And
what I can say is we did a good amount
of business together. They were top 10.
Now they're 21.
So people wonder why you want to do
business with delivered. Why would
people want to? Because they were able
to up their numbers all the way up to
the top 10 by doing a good amount of
business with us. Guys, if you guys
don't know who I am, my name is Tommy. I
negotiate car deals for a living. My
goal is to save you time, energy, and
anxiety. We save you money, but that's a
byproduct. I charge a flat fee of a,000
bucks. Again, we handle everything for
you. I don't advertise it as a
money-saving service because guess what?
You can do this on your own. Can you
take a call for my sales manager? I'm
going. This is Dummy.
>> Tommy, Josh at the Ford truck manager.
How you doing today?
>> Hey, Josh. How's house sales manager?
How are you?
>> Good, buddy. You're uh you're looking at
the carbonized gray incoming platinum.
>> Mhm.
>> Yeah, that's actually in the plant as we
speak. Got built 5 days ago. I should be
expecting that truck I'd say in about
two two and a half weeks.
>> Okay, awesome. That's great. I mean,
that's the one I mean, that's the one
we're looking for. So,
>> Okay. Where are you guys located?
>> I'm in Jersey.
>> Okay. What's your zip code real quick? I
just plugged it in the computer.
>> It's
got you. Are you trading anything in uh
your plan on this? Okay.
>> Well, they were planning to at least
might change our mind, but I don't think
so.
>> Okay. So, do you have any questions on
the truck?
>> No, I I'm already already interested. I
thought we were just going through the
numbers. I think you said you want to
talk to the about the numbers.
>> Okay. So, MSRP on the truck's 105. A
little over 105. Um, let's take a peek
here. I could do 101 on it.
>> Oh, yeah. I have a deal for 10% off is
what I was telling him.
>> 10% off.
>> Mhm.
>> Who's Who's doing that deal? uh a
dealership in North Carolina.
>> North Carolina is doing that deal. Did
you find out how much their fees are and
you have to finance and all that with
them?
>> $6.99 dock fee and I can pay cash or
finance.
>> Okay. As far as taking 10 grand off this
um I'm sure there's more than meets the
eye in the other states. Uh dock fees.
There's probably nitrogen filled tires.
There's a lot of add-ons if I had to
guess.
>> Guess we can look at this. We can look
at this together. Here they have their
price. They have a dealer dock fee.
Taxes 222 in non- tax fees. I measure
this registration and that's it. So I
have a dock fee $6.99 tax plus non tax.
>> How much is the truck?
>> The truck is 105,000.
>> And what are they selling you the truck
for?
>> 95,000.
>> And what year is it?
>> 226.
>> Well, I cannot do that deal. I don't
know why anybody would lose money on
that truck.
>> Maybe they like me.
>> Yeah. I mean, the way I'm looking at it,
they're losing several thousand.
>> Maybe they really like me. Have you
thought of that?
>> You know, New York State, it's a 175
dock fee. So that's another thing.
>> Cool. It's a 9.5% off. Boom. Bada bing.
Easy.
>> Uh, yeah. I can't do those numbers. What
dealership has this truck
>> board? Let's take a look at it.
>> They were saying their range on their
country. Gentleman was named Scott. Nice
guy. His sales manager, Jake, though, is
a little bit of funny guy. By funny, he
just makes a lot of jokes.
>> I'm not seeing that truck on their lot.
>> I was just on their website. I can give
you a stock number if that helps. And
give me two seconds.
>> Yeah,
>> I think it's one of the sister stores
and I tease something.
>> Yeah, go ahead.
>> Give me one second, please. Didn't
realize I would have to have quiz today.
Sorry, I had to pull up my notes here.
Crossroad 20226 F350 106340
T26004
>> T26004.
Got it right here. So, they've got it
listed online for 99184.
>> I understand what they have it listed
for, but what they what they're selling
it to me for is less. They had package.
They removed the add-on package. Yeah.
>> Okay. Yeah. I just I'm just curious how
they're getting there because I mean at
that number I I I can't take 10% off.
There's not $10,000 in markup on any
vehicle on this lot. So sometimes it's
kind of like too good to be true.
>> I I appreciate it, but there's just a
chance maybe he likes me.
>> Maybe he likes you a lot then. They're
willing to lose several thousand.
>> I make funny jokes. That might have been
enough for him to lose some money.
>> Possible.
>> Yeah. I mean, I have it down rating. I
mean, what else? What's the worst? I
mean, what what could he do to me?
>> You know, usually it's mandatory that
you finance window ad chain, all these
add-ons. You know, it's we see this
every day. you know, all these dealers
down south, big DAC fees, and then when
you get there, they're like, "Oh, no,
you got to buy this, this, and this, and
this." You know, no, we're no dealer is
going to lose thousands of dollars to
sell a vehicle. That's not how we
operate. You know, we're entitled to a
small profit and and if that's fair, I
mean, it is what it is.
>> Okay. What if he's trying to be the top
10 in the country? Would that like maybe
like maybe he's motivated to lose some
money on some deals, to make some money
on some other I just thinking.
>> I don't know how they work down there. I
mean,
>> all right. Well, I mean, I don't want to
waste all your time here. I mean, this
dealership gave me a full breakdown
about the doors. I don't know how they
could add the etch at the very end. I
can pay cash. So, like I just write a
check. So, I got you would do that.
>> $95,000. I mean, I would I would have to
I wouldn't have a job. I got to report
to somebody else. So, you know, at that
number, I mean, if you can get that
truck for for thousands below dealer
cost, I would say jump on it.
>> Awesome. Okay, cool. I won't literally
jump on it. We'll go and buy the car.
>> All right, sounds good.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you. Yeah. Byebye.
>> Bye. So, just so you guys know, for this
first four deal, $100,6,000
MSRP, 10 grand off, $96,340
tax title license brings it $6,000 in
tax, $1,200 in fees because guess what?
There's a lot of fees for registration
on that car. Brings up to 104,000. Bada
boom, bada bing. So, I'm going to copy
this. Add comment. Here is the deal.
Smiley face. I'm going to send that to
the client. Make sure the client is good
with it. We're going to move on. This is
a Ford F350.
I got a second one, but this one's all
the way in Washington. And this would be
much more expensive to ship. I'm going
to read. Okay, so this person wants a
lariat. So I'm going to undo all of
these. They're looking for an F350.
They're doing the same thing though. The
tremor. They want this tremor. I can't
even. Okay, so they want a lariat.
There's much many more Lariats in
platinum. So that's a good sign. For
options, they want the 67. No moon roof.
So this one's unique. They said they
don't want the moon roof. They do not
want to see the sun and stars. They want
the rapid. Everybody wants this rapid
fire rapid engine block heater. There's
not many of these Tremor off-road
packages. Oh, there's only 13 of these
in the country in every color. Oxford
white. So, there's 41 of these in the
country. They want the power running
boards as well. Now, the power running
boards are important, right? Like,
they're pretty darn important, but it is
something that we can add later. And if
we add the power running boards, it's
basically a non-existent car. There's
only one in the country and almost
nothing near them. Oh my gosh. This is
what the clients said on the F350.
Tommy, I just accepted the offer. This
is a great deal. Well worth the money.
Wait. Thank you. Appreciate it. So, I'm
going to have one of my team members
close this deal. DCS, can you close this
with Crossroads, please? Client info to
Jake. Okay, cool. Done. We're calling
another dealership. We're doing this is
on a completely different truck. I'm
waiting on the numbers still. This
dealership on this other truck here,
which is $94,000, is already advertising
$7,000 off. They're almost to the
discount. I want them to be.
>> Thanks for calling. This is Cter. How
can I help you?
>> Hello. This is Tommy. Uh, I just want to
see if you guys have a car available.
>> What available?
>> A car? A vehicle? A automobile?
>> Yeah, of course. What one?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Yes, 100%. What is it? What's the stock
number?
>> Yeah, it's an it's a it is an F350
Lariat. And the stock number is B as in
boy, N is in Nancy, D as in dog, 91600.
>> Okay, let me look. And is that a brand
new vehicle? What's your name? Tommy,
right?
>> Yeah, Tommy. Yeah, it says new in all
caps. So, I think so.
>> Okay. All right. Let me
>> Why am I wasting time doing this?
Because I think it's really fun.
>> Okay. Yeah. The Ford Superduty 350
Lariat.
>> That's it.
>> Little big with a big old fat daddy
discount on that bad boy.
>> The big old fat daddy discount.
Yeah. Yeah. You want to tell me a little
bit more about the big old fat daddy
discount?
>> Well, okay. So, it's what it really is
is so the MSRP is 94,955 and it's a 2025
vehicle and we're just trying to move
them and uh get make room for our 26s.
So, they just that's kind of a that's
kind of the dealership discount. I've
been here at this dealership for a while
now and that's one of the heftier ones
that I've seen.
>> Mhm.
>> So, that's kind of basically what that
entails. So, that's where they're at.
They don't really offer the financing on
the F-150s. They're offering some some
fancy financing to help get rid of them,
too. But, unfortunately on these,
they're not they're not offering the
fancy financing. But
>> so I don't even have the fancy financing
>> that that's going to be Huh.
>> So So no fancy financing on it.
>> Uh to my knowledge, no. I'd have to
double check. I I had a call yesterday.
I sold one yesterday. It was a 250 and
there was no no fancy financing on it.
So I might be able to check into that
and and kind of look at it. Where are
you at, Tommy?
>> I'm in Washington.
>> Washington. Okay. Right on. How do you
like it over there?
>> It's good. It's nice. I like it.
>> Yeah. I've been to Vancou Vancouver a
couple times and my uh brother got
married over there and it was just a
great time. It was nice cuz uh Oregon's
right on the other side right there in
Vancouver.
>> So, you can kind of dip over there and
ditch the ditch the sales tax and
whatnot. But, do you got a trade? Do you
have a vehicle you'd be trading in,
Tommy, or
>> I I don't have a vehicle I'd be trading.
I would just be adding to the family,
>> adding to the fleet, huh?
>> Are you a Ford guy? Do you got a bunch
of Fords out in your driveway or
>> Oh, I mean, we have it we have we have
one other Ford. Uh but, uh we're looking
to add this one here. We do we do right
now. The current truck we have is a
2500. Uh we're looking to maybe keep it,
maybe get rid of it. We haven't decided
yet.
>> Okay. I'd love my opportunity to get
some hands on that if you wanted to
trade it in. We do pretty good with the
250 used. But yeah, man, that this is
just pretty much available. Um, when do
you want to come pick it up? I guess
would be my next question.
>> First off, I just want to double check.
Do you guys have any like dealer
add-ons, fees, anything crazy?
>> So, what we'd have is we'll put the
taxes in there, whatever, whatever your
taxes in. We generally add that cuz
people don't want to pay that out of
pocket. And then our dealer dock fee is
$4.99, I believe. And then there's some
government fee at 20 bucks or something
like that. I'm not sure exactly, but
it's a a pretty small fee. But our
dealer dock pretty much other than
taxes, it's just taxes, dealer dock, and
that government fee. So, and I I want to
say ours is $4.99 dealer doc fee.
>> Dealer dog fee. Okay. $4.99. Okay,
that's not bad. Uh really well, I
appreciate that. You know, definitely
interested in the truck. You know,
obviously I understand it's a big daddy
discount. Was really hoping for like a
big mama discount, you know, like
>> big mama.
>> Yeah. You know, I was really hoping for
what are you thinking? What's a big
mama? Uh
>> big mama has like always been a 10%. You
know, I always feel like that's it. It's
like 9,400 off is kind of what I was
hoping for.
>> Okay. So, let's just do this. 9,400 off.
If I can get you 90 and I don't It's a
2020. It's It's If I can get you some
>> It's outdated. It's like instead instead
of seven instead of $7,69, you want
$9,400 off.
>> That's it. That's big mama.
>> That's it. The big mama.
All right, Tommy. Let me So, and if I
could get that, you'd buy it today.
You'd You'd buy it today.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. All right. So, let me let me go.
I'm just gonna I don't know how to work
this dumb phone. I don't know how to put
it on hold so you get the fancy music.
I'm just going to set the phone down,
walk into the sales manager office and
ask if we can do a big mama discount on
this. I'll figure it out for you next
time, dude. But as of right now, you're
just going to be sitting on this wood
desk of mine for a second.
>> No worries. I'll sing to myself.
>> All right,
>> stop being awesome.
[Music]
>> Guys, if you guys don't know who I am,
my name's Tommy. I negotiate card deals
for a living. My goal is to save you
time, energy, and anxiety. I charge a
flat fee of a,000 bucks. Again, we
handle everything for you. People hire
me because they don't want to deal with
the anxiety. They also can get a little
bit of a dinner and a show, which is
something people like. I do this all
online so people can see how easy or how
hard it is. You get to make that
decision. I want you guys to be
transparent. Hey, I'm still here. Sorry.
I I put you on mute. Sorry.
>> I was talking.
>> That's all right. Uh so so he got can't
do the big the big mama discount, but he
said he'd do the big uh big
mother-in-law discount and they'd come
down another thousand.
>> So 8,000
>> come down to So it' be 8,69 discount. I
don't know if that was your intention to
shoot me high and then get me to come
back. I don't know if that if your plan
just worked out or not, but
>> No, my my mama doesn't lie. I was trying
to get 94. That's what I was trying to
get.
>> Okay. Well, I can get you I can get you
eight.
>> We're close. Can we get 8,500?
>> You said as long as as long as you're
financing. Are you going to be financing
or paying cash?
>> Yeah, I'm open to finance. That's not
That problem's not the problem.
Okay. I really I really didn't think
this was going to go this way. You got
me panicking now. Uh are you sure?
>> Huh? I thought you were just going to
say yes. I thought I thought that line
was so good it would never you would
never say no.
>> Yeah. Right. Well, to be honest, I'm
surprised he was willing to come because
this that's price right now that what he
tell me his price the price that it's at
right now is a is a $2,000 loser. So,
that would move it into a $3,000 loser
for us. But,
>> okay. Well, I I I told uh that 10% is
what I was trying to get. That's where
I'm still trying to get. That's still a
strong deal. I'm not disagreeing with
you. I'm not I'm not saying you're a
liar. Uh but um yeah what this let me
let me think about this for a minute. If
it would have been 10% I would have just
said yes. Bada boom bada bing. Give me
give me give me like 10 minutes to think
about do you mind sending me those
numbers so I can look at them.
>> Yeah. What? So what do you mean like uh
>> just Okay. Well, let me get let me get a
little I need to get Tommy what's your
last name?
>> Last name is Makula. M I K U L A.
>> M I K U L.
>> Yeah.
>> Mula. And this is a good number to reach
out.
>> Yep. This is the best number.
>> That's it. Okay, let me uh give me a few
minutes. I'll I'll send give me a few
minutes. I got to build it up, put it
together, put you in the system, and
then
>> and try try one more time to get the
mother-in-law the mother-in-law like the
mother-in-law that we actually like, not
the mother-in-law that we like we have
to go see. Okay.
>> Christmas. Maybe another $500 off. Maybe
another $500 off makes it a little bit
better for me.
>> Okay. So, if I So 8 So 85 85 you'll do
you'll do a deal.
>> Yeah. Yeah. That that I feel better
with. Would you do the deal at 85?
>> You're ask all the right questions. Give
me two seconds to verify that we'll do
it at 8500. So, give me two seconds. I
just text him. I just want to text the
person in charge, make sure we're all
good, and then I think so. But 8,500
sounds better than eight grand.
>> All right. Okay. And you're talking with
Coulter just so I want to give you my
cell phone number to call me back on so
you don't risk losing you to other
person's desk.
>> Coulter. Got it. Coulter. Okay. Got it.
Okay. Let me see what I can do. Uh, give
me give me five minutes.
>> All right. Sounds good. Bye.
>> All right. Bye. He's good. No, I will I
will say he did everything right. Right.
One of the questions that sales people
are trained to do what a lot of people
don't do, which is ask rather than going
for the discount, would you buy the car
at this? There is no high better than
selling a car. I've sold a lot of things
in my life. I've sold things of
different quality. Selling a car, you
get like this emotional bump in high.
It's crazy. It's awesome. And that's why
I love what I do cuz I get to do that
215 times. The second I get a let's do
the deal. Let's go. Just do a little
dance, you know? It's so great. It's so
fun. I And I've been doing this for
almost a decade now, and that high has
not gone away. I love putting dreams in
driveways.
>> Tommy, what's up, brother?
>> Okay, man. Uh we're I think we're almost
there. Uh we talked it over here. We are
actually going to trade in our other
truck.
>> Okay.
>> But before we make this drive, I need to
make sure that we can actually get
pretty close in the truck. So, I have
some pictures of it. I got the van. I
got the miles. I got everything.
>> Let me let me get into my desk real
quick. I was just out lot dogging it up.
>> Lot dogging up.
>> Lot dog. Yeah. Back when I just kind of
prowled a lot looking for a deal.
>> Don't prowl. I think it'd be cats. Dogs.
>> Oh, I don't actually know what dogs
would Dogs meander be chasing your tail.
No, cuz cats would meander, too. But
they'd also
>> Okay. All right. So, what's the what's
the bin on the truck?
>> Yeah. Are you ready for it? I'm going to
give it to you.
>> Yeah.
>> What year is it?
>> It is a 2022.
2022. You said it's F250.
>> No, no, no. This one This is our Ram.
We're trading in our Ram AEV edition.
>> Okay. Okay.
>> It's the sickest truck. It's the sickest
truck you'll ever see.
>> Okay. All right. Well, how many miles
>> other than the one I'm buying?
>> Okay. How many miles?
>> 21,827.
>> Okay. So, I got that miles. Can you send
me over a couple pictures of it?
>> I got I got a little We got a little
iCloud folder we made for you. So, I'll
text that over to you so you get all the
beautiful pictures how great this thing
looks. you're gonna be like, "Dude, I
want to buy this truck." That's what
you're gonna say.
>> Okay. Well, where are you want to be at
on it?
>> Uh, we're we're you know, we haven't
done any appraisal on it just yet. So,
that's where we're looking. So, I don't
have if I I would be lying to you if I
told you I had a number on my head, but
>> Okay. All right. Good. I'll give you
Well, we generally like to go with Kelly
Blue Bub fair, Kelly Blue Bub good based
on the thing. So, and there's some where
we're at now. So, generally like we have
some wiggle room. We're discounting this
one quite a much. We're probably just
going to have to be cut and dry pretty
straight. Give you what it's worth
trading in value. I'm I mean I'm I want
to get more than it's worth. I mean
that's not fair to you. It's not fair to
me but it's fair to give me what it's
worth. As long as you what it's worth.
>> Yeah. Well, I'll get you I can get you
the Kelly Kelly Blue Book, you know,
Kelly Blue Book most likely as long as
it's not, you know, beat up and it
doesn't sound like it's beat up at all,
but
>> you're going to see pictures of the
truck. You're like, "Dang, man. This is
this is the best taken care of truck
keep you've seen the side of the
Mississippi."
>> Okay,
>> I'm texting I'm texting you over this
right now.
>> Okay, cool. And I will get um Give me
just a minute, Tommy. Let me get all
that stuff. Yep. I just came in. Let me
get all this uploaded up in here.
>> Done deal. Yeah. Let's get a fair number
in this truck. This is a done deal. Bada
boom, bada bang.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> All right, sounds good.
>> I'll be in touch. Call. Give me about 10
minutes.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> All right, bye.
>> Bye. When it comes down to Kelly Blue
Book, I don't care what like he says
Kelly Blue Book is. I'm not going to go
through and argue. I want more than
Kelly Blue. I want like let's just
figure out the number they throw on the
truck compared to the number we have on
the truck. The idea of arguing right
there doesn't make any sense. There's no
there's no benefit uh for me because
Kelly Blue Book can be so far off in
certain things. So, we're just going to
go through I'm going to go figure out
what I think is a fair number on the
trade. But, if I start arguing there,
he's not going to have his hopes he has
a deal. So, let's just figure out what
the number is. Um that's always step
one. Let's just give him the
information. Sounds good. And then we do
get a tax break if they trade and they
live in Washington. So, do anything
except a Toyota. We've just done two
Fords. We're going to go through and run
not only what a book number is, but
we're going to do Carvana, Car Max,
Clan, and Algo. We're also gonna shoot
it to about two to three different
dealerships that know who we are that
say, "Hey, we want to buy your
inventory, whatever it cost." And see
what that is.
>> This is Tommy.
>> Tommy, what's up, brothers? Culture.
>> Hey, man. What you got?
>> No. So, that's You're right, dude. That
was pretty impressive. I've never seen a
truck like that. Nobody around here has
ever seen a truck like that. Pretty cool
little truck.
>> Well, let's do a clean trade. Bada boom,
bada bing, right?
>> Bada boom. Clean trade. Kelly Blue Book
fair on it is 525. Dude,
>> I was seeing like 56. What are you
talking about?
>> Yeah, Kelly. So, I I knew you were going
to come at me like this, so I was
prepared for I was I was prepared for a
follow-up question. Top dollar that
we're willing to go is like right around
56, dude.
>> Wait.
>> And that's cuz we got a we got a MSRP on
that vehicle news 78. I know it has a
upload package on it.
>> The upload.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Well, we we have one of
those out on the lot right here. Like
it's a Ford Lightning or a Ford Black
Widow package and it's MSRP or the on
it's like 120 and we got it listed for
80. So, it's just a, you know, so 56 58
our top 56 and you're going to sell for
80. I feel like I'm getting screwed
here.
>> No, no. See, that's what a lot of people
think, dude. That's that that's Well,
like we're going to start trying to get
that probably we're going to start
trying to get 60 out of it. 62 65,
right? But then the price always goes
down and and I don't know if it'll sell.
Like, I've never seen anything like that
around here, but the MSRP of that
vehicle new is 78 like
>> without the upcharges.
>> Oh, yeah. Then the 27k. So the Kelly
Blue Book Fair is 525 and we'd be I I
told my boss I said what's what's the
top that you'd be able to go on it was
where's the gamble? He said you go up to
58.
>> So 58 there's the top.
>> That's the top.
>> Now I feel like it's 60. The number just
keeps going up.
>> I like you Tommy. I like your style. I
feel like you need to be a car salesman.
What I'm thinking here.
>> They said they said I would be a failure
in the car industry. That's what that's
what people tell me. They say I I
couldn't make it in the industry.
>> Oh I don't believe that for a second.
They say,
>> "Yo, you got what it takes, dude. You're
grinding me down to nothing, dude.
Grinding me into dust."
>> So, we're at 60.
>> So, we're at 58, bro. I mean, I jumped
right from the 525 up to the max just
cuz I know I just I kind of just want to
get this thing locked in and loaded. So,
>> so 60. Okay, cool. Let me go talk Let me
go talk to Let me talk to the Let me go
make sure we're good at 60 and make sure
everyone is
>> 575. Dude,
>> you just said 58. You're not going back
down.
>> Okay. All right. 58. All right. 58 then.
58 is You're right. I I jumped too high
too soon. I jumped too high too soon. I
should have went to 525, then I should
have came up to 55 and then you would
have said, "Oh, 56 and then I would have
won, dude." So, it's a learning curve
for me, man. I've just learned a Thank
you for the training.
>> Oh my gosh. Jeez. Don't Don't trainer.
So, 60 call it a day. Uh, that sounds I
appreciate it, Colton. You've been
great, man. 60 makes it nice and easy.
Let me go. Let me The real question is
if we're going to sell it to you guys or
not. So, um or if we're going to do it.
We like the truck. So, let me let me
talk real quick. Give me two seconds and
I will give you a call right back. Say
60.
>> All right, sounds good.
>> 60.
>> 58, bro. 58. And my boss is like shaking
his head at me like thinking I'm a
coward. So 58, dude.
>> The phone deals keeps cutting off when
you say 50. And I just hear 68. I think
you mean 60.
>> Well, you can tell it's not 60. If
you're in 50, it's actually what? I was
saying 55. So the phone's cutting off
the five.
>> Man, I'm trying to be nice to you here.
>> Maybe a new reception, huh?
>> 58, dude. 58. And that's a loser loser
loser for me. I don't make a penny, but
that's all right. I just to be honest, I
get played a flat minimum on all brand
new vehicles, so I make 300 bucks, so
I'm I'm not complaining.
>> You said 585.
>> 58, bro. 58, dude.
>> Okay, give me a second.
>> All right.
>> All right. Let me run it by and make
sure what we're going to do with the
trade and go from there.
>> All right, sounds good.
>> Okay. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> Now, what the client wants for the trade
is going to be a whole different thing.
But when I ran numbers on this trade,
the best number we got was 56. Now, the
client might want more. Now, this is the
tricky thing with a car like this,
right? The tricky thing with a car like
this is this customer has a lot of
aftermarket parts that you don't see the
value in when you're trying to sell this
car. So, if you sell the car third
party, you might be able to get a lot
more money for it. I'm not disagreeing,
but the highest number that we tried to
get third party was 56. We went up to
58.
>> Tommy Makula, what's up, bro?
>> What up? Tik Tok. Who Tik Tok like that?
>> I don't I don't know, dude. I don't know
how to spell Tik Tok, dude. I don't
watch it. That's why I probably never
heard of you. I know it is Tommy from
Ticky Talk. Yeah, but this is a real
client. It's on Andy Arn though. No,
it's not on Andy. They're ready to buy
the car. I think we're I think we're
better.
>> I was working with a guy that was trying
to trade in the same truck. Yeah, the
exact same exact same truck. Needed a
bunch of money for it. He wouldn't send
me the info on it. He just said he was
going to go the private sale route.
That's why I was like, what's what the
hell's going on here? But
>> was it was it like like was it was it
another like purse? That's weird. I
mean, maybe
>> weird. And he was on He was on a truckim
he was on a similar truck. He was on a
similar truck, too. So, I just I I just
didn't know. But
>> No. No. Anyway, they said their name was
Andy.
>> His name was Andy R.
>> Oh, that's not a name of my employees.
So, it's not I do have employees, but
none of them called you. I double
checked. But no, this is going to be a
done deal. Uh client, we're just calling
the client right now to verify. But yep,
this is Tommy from TikTok. You figured
it out. You're on TikTok right now.
>> Okay. Well, you're famous, bro. I feel
famous. Are you going to put me on?
>> You feel famous, dude. People love you,
man. You've been doing You've been doing
great. People People love you. That's
And And to get props on my channel is is
hard because people are people are mean,
but they they like you.
>> They do.
>> Yeah.
send my way, dude.
>> Okay, we'll keep sending your way. Let
me get this deal locked up, call it a
day, and the client's going to drive out
to you. But appreciate you being a good
sport. Let me get this all rocking and
rolling and I love it.
>> Okay, perfect.
>> Hey, awesome, man. Talk to you soon.
>> Can you send me some papers or what? Do
I just
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So, what I'll do is
the next step.
Yeah. Once once the once the client
gives you a thumbs up, I'll give you
their number, their email, and you can
reach out to them and and we can set up
a time for delivery. You you get to
contact the client. You get to do
everything. It's just as if you just got
a lead that's closed.
>> Okay. So, I get to do everything twice.
No, everything's agreed upon. You
literally you literally they'll give you
driver's license. You're just doing this
whole deal checklist. It's easy.
>> All right.
>> I promise if you if it's hard, you can
come back on the stream and say, "Tommy,
this was way more work than it needed to
be." You can tell.
>> Okay. All right, dude. You just make
sure the people know, dude, that Cter M
got it done for you, dude.
>> Okay, I will. Don't worry. Okay, I'll
talk to you in a minute.
>> Bye.
>> Bye. Good sport. He did figure out who
we were. Somebody must have been
watching the stream that works where he
is where he's at. Let's all say hi to
Coulter. He doesn't even watch us. He
doesn't know. I don't even know if he
knows that we're live. So, I want to
touch on the trade point. So, when we
come through and talk about the trade,
this is why when some people are saying,
"They came up way too easy. I would have
done this." I've done all of the
research I need to do before I actually
talk to the dealership. So, if you're
interested, uh, we do free consults.
I'll warn you, people book out of those
free consults literally like crazy. So,
my new commitment to people is there is
a contact us page where you can ask as
many questions. You can ask one, you can
ask a hundred. I personally read those
every single night. The reason why we do
this, the reason why we film these
videos, why we do these fun bingo
sports, a entertaining for you, b to
educate. Do you see it? I understand
you're telling me to let it go, but it's
not how life works.
Okay, letting it go.
[Music]