I know Toyota has planned their price
increases starting August 1st. So, I
just don't know.
>> Didn't Toyota or didn't US and Japan
just reach a tariff deal? Is that
something I can find online and see? I
just haven't seen that anywhere and I'd
like to say I'm a wellressearched
individual.
>> Yeah. So, like I said, I like I don't
know.
>> Is did Toyota make some type of
announcement about raising all their
prices in August 1st?
>> No.
>> Are you sure? Can you check the your
Toyota site?
>> I'm positive. Why do dealerships feel
the need to lie in order to get a sale?
This is something that has always
confused me. I talk to dealerships,
hundreds of them, on a monthly basis,
and sadly, there is a reoccurring theme
where sales people feel like when they
don't know the answer, rather than just
being honest and saying, "I don't know,
I'll get back to you." They feel the
need to lie. In this video, you're going
to watch a dealership just blatantly lie
about a price increase on a Toyota. And
spoiler alert, uh, I keep up with Toyota
more than most Toyota stores do. And I'm
telling you that the information that he
is saying that he heard directly from
Toyota, as we've seen many times in this
video, is not true. He is making this
up. And maybe he's mistaken. Maybe he's
not actually lying. But either way, this
is your profession. This is something
you should know. Enough about me
yapping. Let's get to the negotiation.
>> This is Kyle. How can I help you?
>> Hey Kyle, how's it going?
>> I'm good. How are you?
>> Hey, I'm doing well. I hear you're the
big dog in town. Oh man, it's the store
is not me, man.
>> Oh, okay. That's okay. I I honestly like
like I have a Chihuahua, so I like the
small dog. Anyway, um there you go. I
have a car here. It just says please
call for price disclaimer. Build phase.
So, I'm trying to figure out the price.
>> Uh which vehicle were you looking at?
>> Um I give you elastics of the VIN.
>> If you have Do you have the make in the
model?
>> Yeah, it's a 2025 Grand Highlander
Hybrid Limited all-wheel drive.
>> Okay. So, it looks like I got a couple
of them in here. Were you looking at the
heavy metal one? The heavy metal with
the black leather. Yep.
>> Heavy metal with the black leather.
>> Last six of the or last four of the
event is G915.
>> This one's going to be allocated to us.
I see something on here that says sale
pending. So, I have to see if this one's
already allocated to a customer or not.
Um, what brought you to this Highlander?
>> It's the color I want and it's the trim
I want and I was curious about the
price.
>> Here's what I can go do for you. Let me
see if this one, this particular one is
still available. Uh, and then I can get
a spec sheet printed off for you if it
is. If not, what I can go do is get you
printed off one uh one that would be
inbound. Uh it'll show you the price of
the vehicle as well, and I can let you
know exactly how far out it is before
reaching the dealership itself. Is there
anything else I can get for you in the
meantime? Like, were you thinking about
financing the vehicle, purchasing it
outright?
>> Yeah, I mean, I'm open to financing,
open to paying cash, whatever makes the
most sense. Just need the financing or
just need, sorry, just need a price.
>> Gotcha. All right, let me go uh get some
information on that one to start. And uh
just to follow a good phone number for
you is N.
>> That is correct.
>> All right. Perfect. Perfect. And then
could you spell your last name for me? I
just want to make sure I got it in.
>> Yeah. M is a Mary I K U L A.
>> All right. Perfect. Perfect. Let me go
ahead and get you some info and I will
call you right back. Okay.
>> All right. Sounds good.
>> All right. No problem.
>> Bye. Wait. Kyle's calling me back. One
second.
This is Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. It's Kyle from reaching back
out to you.
>> Hi.
You're here. What what I got for you is
um I actually got the spec sheet on the
one you put the inquiry on. It is it has
a pending sale on it right now, but it's
going to give you a good idea on you
know what your Highlander breakdown and
kind of the ones that they send to us.
Um so I'm going to text you over the
build sheet right now and the retail
price on the vehicle that's coming in.
It's it's about 58 5848 is what's
showing up. Uh that's with all the
features included on the vehicle. I'm
texting over that exact build page right
now.
Now, in terms of trying to find another
one that gets sent to us that's
identical to this. It could be anywhere
from like 30 to 60 days. We're just
really waiting on Toyota's next month
allocation to get updated to see what
they're sending us from the factory. The
only thing that we might run into is I
know Toyota has planned their price
increases starting August 1st. So, I
just don't know. You know,
>> they're increasing their prices, are
they?
>> Yeah. Um, that's Toyota held off for,
you know, as long as it could. Uh, but
they're projecting it to start August
1st. Does not necessarily mean the
entire vehicle is going to go up a
certain percentage. Uh, they're just
talking about the parts that would go
into assembling the vehicle. You like
precious metals and such that do come
from overseas. That's what they're
expecting to increase the price of
vehicle. I don't know exactly what that
would look like.
>> So, is that like rumor? Does Toyota give
you an insight on that?
>> No, that's a No, that's that's a
confirmed from Toyota. They're going to
start price increases starting August
1st. Um, you know, with all the talk
about tariffs, they they held true
without increasing prices if a
dealership around you. If they increase
their prices on it, that was on their
own accord. You know, we stuck to window
sticker the entire time. Uh, but
Toyota's following through starting
August 1st.
>> Okay. But you don't know how much those
are going
>> for cuz I I know that Toyota didn't
Toyota or didn't US and Japan just reach
a tariff deal? Why would they do it?
They got lower tariffs and they're like,
you know what, now we're implementing.
>> Yeah. So, it's not, like I said, it's
not necessarily on the entire car
itself, ones that would be assembled
from Japan. They're it's on the parts
that are coming to assemble the cars
like
>> Yeah, but those parts are now tariffed
less than they were before.
>> That's what they're projecting is the
price increase starts then.
>> Is that something I can find online and
see? I just haven't seen that anywhere.
And I'd like to say I'm a
wellressearched individual.
>> Yeah. So, like I said, I like I don't
know. I don't know exactly. That's why
I'm showing you this to show you an idea
cuz let's Somebody told you allocated to
us.
>> Somebody told you and it's it's for
real. Toyota told you, but you just
don't know how you can confirm it
>> cuz we won't know until the exact print
off for each vehicle comes in. Does that
make sense? Like this vehicle has this
price. Like this exact vehicle that I
just sent over to you, that's the price
of that exact one. Let's say we have one
allocated to us that's coming in in
August and it prints off at the same
price. Fantastic. Uh I just don't know
what that price is until that vehicle
spec sheet is sent to us.
Okay. I I just, you know, I just haven't
heard at all from anybody or read
anything online that the price increase.
You're the first person I ever heard
that from.
>> Oh, that's odd. Um, so
>> I mean, you might be right. I don't
know. I mean, but
>> so any car built August 1 is is going to
>> potential. Potential. I'll say
disastrous to say potential cuz some,
like I said, some models might be, some
models might not be. Some might already
have all the parts and they're being
assembled. So they're would make a would
make really sense to increase price on
something. That's why our prices have
kept the same all throughout, you know,
the talks about tariffs on a vehicle.
They've kept true to it because vehicles
already assembled, already allocated to
us or already at port. They already had
the price printed on the factory sticker
and we just price that factory window
sticker. So like I said, this was give
you an idea. If it does come in, it's
the same price. Like I said, that's
fantastic. But on the next one that's
due in, I don't know the exact price on
that yet. Yeah, that's even more
concerning. I guess until Toyota makes
an announcement. I'm putting a lot of
faith that Toyota is not going to just
raise the price by five grand.
>> Trust me, I get it. I get it.
>> Yeah. I wouldn't even want you to secure
me one anymore cuz the chances are I'll
probably get it after.
>> So, like I said, I don't I don't know
exactly what it looks like. I can check
to see if there's anything that would be
there, but it would be an order that
goes in at this point because we don't
currently have one allocated to us.
>> Yeah. I don't want to order one without
knowing the price on it. You're telling
me the price is going up guaranteed.
almost and not guaranteed, but like
August 1st something's happening.
>> Yeah, they're expecting they're like I
said, they're expecting price increases
either through the parts, but it's not
going to be, you know, a fixed
percentage on the retail price of the
vehicle.
>> It's going to be it's going to be up in
the air. It's going to be like they're
going to roll the dice on every car.
>> Yeah. And trust me, I get I get not
wanting to go put the deposit on that um
you know, the deposit does reserve your
vehicle, but one thing I can say about
you know, the Stokes family, they're
they're pretty good with taking care of
their customers. And what I mean by that
is if you order the vehicle and let's
say you came in to test drive it and it
just was not good, you know, we'll get
your deposit back.
>> Okay. Um
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I don't want to put a
deposit on something yet, but I
appreciate it.
>> I got you. I'm going to keep on lookout
for you cuz I know you want the
specifically heavy metal on black hybrid
limited on the Grand Highlander. So, if
one were to pop in, let's say I get my
allocation update and we have one due
that's within the month and then that
retail price shows on the spec sheet
what it is and it's a number that's
within the range of what you're looking
for, that's one you would be interested
in. Correct.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, as long as you
can find one, that'd be great.
>> I got you. Cuz like I said, all I'm
waiting for is just to find one that's,
you know, that build. Um, and then once
I get a spec sheet on it, then I'll can
be a little firm on the price.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> All right. So, I'll be on the lookout
for you and once I get anything. Is
there any other vehicle configuration
that you might be interested in?
>> Nope, that's the only one.
>> All right. Well, let me go be on the
lookout for you. I'll check as soon as
we get our allocation update and then I
will reach out to you. Okay.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> All right. Sounds good. Thank you,
Tommy.
>> My Okay. No problem. Bye.
>> Mhm.
>> Okay. So, I'm going to confirm this, but
last time, so first off, you guys have
to understand that year-over-year model
years go up in price like every year.
Like, that's not something new. If you
looked at a car in 2020 compared to now,
it's thousands of dollars more
expensive. But last time that I heard
any announcement from Toyota, it was
going to be like a $2 to $300 price
raise.
>> Tommy Mu L.
>> How many do you do buy a month for your
client? 150 to 200 deals a month. Relax,
dude. Anyway, uh hey, um is did Toyota
make some type of announcement about
raising all their prices in August 1st?
>> No.
>> Are you sure? Can you check the your
Toyota site?
>> I'm positive. They actually they don't
even make they really won't even make an
announcement. What will happen? I think
I've sent you a screenshot before. Uh a
car with a temp VIN will have a base
TSRP, let's say, of 35,000. And then
when the car actually gets here and you
relook at the specs and it has the
normal VIN, it has a T TPRS of 30,500.
They'll just bump it while it's a temp
bin. Um, but that only happens like
maybe once a year, maybe twice a year.
>> Yeah, but like from what I saw it was
like two to 300 bucks they were going to
raise it. I couldn't imagine any more
than like I mean 500 would be a crazy
raise, but I don't think it's going to
be any more than that. But it's not
>> they did a 500 on the 4Runner recently,
but typically it's between this is a
weird number. It's between $80 to about
300.
>> Yeah. Because they did it on the Tundra,
right? They raised the Tundra by like 85
bucks. I made a video on that.
>> Yep.
>> Yeah. Okay.
>> So, they won't just say the Toy won't
just reach out to a dealer and be like,
"Hey, you know, uh we're actually going
to start raising the prices uh August
21st at 2 p.m. It doesn't work like
that."
>> Okay, cool, cool, cool. Cha chill. Uh
okay, cool. Uh I do you have this Grand
Highlander yet without with a black
interior?
>> Uh hybrid.
>> Hybrid limited. hybrid and limited.
>> No white.
>> No, I only have that gray interior one.
I think it pre-sold already.
>> I know, but allocation comes out in a
few days.
>> Yeah, we should kill it in allocation
cuz we've been selling out, you know, 20
of these at a time each allocation.
>> Yeah, I know. I'll have to just waste
all your time again when allocation
comes out.
>> Yeah. The one thing that I hate about
you is that you just waste so much of my
time, dude.
>> Honestly, it's so much waste of time.
Anybody
that was smart would be all up in your
chats on your live trying to sell cars.
>> I know. I know. It's cuz I don't do any
deals. These are all fake. I just have
my friends. I mean was like, "You just
have friends you keep calling." I'm
like, "Yeah, I just do this for hours
with I don't even have this many
friends."
>> So true.
>> Okay, I will let you go. Go sell some
cars.
>> All right, man. Hopefully, we could be
friends one day.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> Later.
>> Later. I think the majority of people
would enjoy buying a car if there just
wasn't lying involved. I think that's
one of the biggest problems people have.
There's such a lack of trust at the
dealership. And the default answer for a
lot of sales people in general, not only
in car sales, is to lie. Be honest, and
I promise you'll sell more cars.
[Music]