I don't love the idea that I might not
get the best deal by calling you and
that I know that I'm leaving money on
the table by not being there. That seems
kind of crazy. You know, I'm living a
dream. I haven't determined yet if it's
a good one or a bad one, but it's a
dream nonetheless. Oh my god, this
dealership is blowing me up. You You got
my interest. You got my interest. You
got me You got me intrigued. Who doesn't
allow Hyundai doesn't allow you to dis
like the the rebate comes from Hyundai.
Like you Hyundai reimburses you that
money.
>> That's correct. Yeah. So they they don't
they don't care what you sell the car
at,
>> but they're we're not like jacking the
price up crazy. This is actually a
product that every single one of our
vehicles gets because of the problems
with the paint and the screens breaking.
>> So should I even be buying this car?
That seems crazy. What? Like should I
even just be looking at something
different is chipping and the screens
are cracking. We can paint it. I'm just
kidding. No, it's fine.
>> That's the house break painted for free.
>> I'm going Santa Fe calligraphy in
Florida. Uh, calligraphy white with
brown or beige interior.
Calligraphy. They only want serenity
white. I think black. They'll take a
black if it's a good deal. I'm okay with
a front-wheel drive, but hybrid is okay
if good deal. So, it doesn't want a
hybrid unless it's a good deal. So,
let's go gas only.
>> Thank you for calling. Hyundai. My
name's Ally.
>> Hey. Hey, Ally. Are you in new car
sales?
>> Uh, yeah. I'm with internet sales. How
can I help you?
>> Awesome. Bada boom, bada bing. Hey, I
just want to see if you guys have a car
available.
>> Sure thing. What's the stock number?
>> I have a stock. The stock number is
26022.
>> Gotcha. All right. Give me just one
second. Is that pre-owned or new? It
>> is brand new.
>> Hold on. I got it. Yeah. Okay. I got it.
Hey, bear with me.
>> No, you got it. Take all the time you
need.
>> Okay. Yeah, the uh Santa Fe calligraphy.
>> Yeah, Santa Fe calligraphy with a peon
brown interior.
>> Yep, that's it. I see here. And I'm
showing that it is available. Were you
trying to come in today? Maybe tomorrow.
Take a look at it. Uh, well, hey, you
already I already know I want it
already. Love it. Want more of it.
Really just trying to get some great
pricing.
>> Okay. All right. Well, listen. This is
what I can do. I'm sorry. What is your
name?
>> My name's Donnie.
>> Donnie. Okay, Donnie. My name is Ally.
Thank you so much for calling in. I
really appreciate it. I do pride myself
on my honesty and transparency with my
customers. I will go ahead and let you
know. Yeah, I'll go ahead and let you
know. I can give you some out the door
figures. Keep in mind that this would be
just kind of like a ballpark range. We
can't really determine anything un, you
know, without running credit. um with
you in here in store, that kind of
thing. We do reserve our best pricing
for customers that are willing to come
in unless it's like at an out ofstate
deal, then we'll definitely work with
you. But are you local?
>> Uh I mean I'm I'm north of uh Orlando. I
mean I could drive to Georgia if that
makes gets me better pricing and then
call you. That would that make more
sense?
>> I I understand. But that's fine. Um no,
I wouldn't have you do that obviously.
Orlando is about maybe an hour, maybe an
hour and a half, give or take with
traffic. So, I just want to make sure
that you'd be able to come in once we
agree on figures. So,
>> yeah, once we I mean, as long as they're
fair numbers, you know, I don't I don't
I won't lie. You love I love the honesty
from you. I appreciate that. Just the
honesty for me. I don't love the idea
that I might not get the best deal by
calling you and that I know that I'm
leaving money on the table by not being
there. That seems kind of crazy, but it
it almost inspires me to call Georgia
dealerships. I won't lie, because that
makes it seem like I might just get a
better deal and I don't have to deal
with it.
>> Well, the thing is, anybody can give you
a price over the phone, okay? It's only
whenever it gets better that you're here
in person. That's what I mean. So, you
know, you calling a Georgia dealership,
they could give you any number that they
want to, but you know, once you actually
go up there, you never know. It could be
a different story. Here, the way we do
things is, you know, we always give you
a better deal in person because our
pricing is negotiable. We just rather
negotiate in person. But that's fine.
That's, you know, like I said, I can get
you some out the door numbers. It is no
problem, Donnie.
>> Perfect.
>> All right. And Donnie is spelled D O N I
E. Right.
>> It's actually Tommy, but that's okay.
>> Oh, I'm sorry. I'm
>> No, it's all good. It happens. Tommy,
Tommy, Donnie. It's similar.
>> That's okay. I get called Ally, Sally.
Like, my name is Ally. Okay. But I've
been called Sally and all this kind of
other stuff. So, I got you.
>> Yeah. Let me see. What is your zip code?
What would where would the vehicle be
registered?
>> Yeah.
>> All right. Uh, any military? Are you
active military or?
>> No, not military. And I'm not I was
looking to pay in cash for the car. The
only reason I'd finance is for the
rebate. So, you know, on the pay payment
side, I know you said you need to know
my credit. I'm 850 plus rockstar going
for the high score.
>> Okay. So, did you want me to get you
some finance numbers or based on that uh
credit or did you want me to get you a
cash price?
>> Let's just get the cash price. Let's
keep it simple here. And if we can agree
to numbers, that's great. Hopefully, we
can make some aggressive numbers and
maybe I'll just never know the crazy
aggressive numbers. You guys will see.
>> Okay. All right. And Okay. You said no
military. Oh, a transfer tag or a new
tag?
>> Uh, I can transfer tag.
>> Okay. And do you happen to have a trade
or anything like that?
>> I don't have a trade. No,
>> no trade. Okay. All right. Let me go
ahead and get these numbers for you. Um,
I'll give you a call back or I might
have a product specialist call you back
because, you know, you sound like you
kind of want to negotiate a little bit
if need be. So, I can go ahead and do
that for you. Okay.
>> Yeah, that'd be great. I appreciate it.
>> All right, Tommy, I'll give you a call
right back.
>> Yeah, it sounds good.
>> All right. Have a great day. Bye-bye.
>> Bye-bye.
>> Hello.
>> Hello. Is this Nelson?
>> Tommy, how are you?
>> Hey, man. I did well. I missed your
first four calls, but I I got you now.
>> No problem. No problem. So, I've been
working with Ali. Uh, he requested a
quote on a 26 Santa Fe. Bada boom, bada
bing. That's it. That's the dream in the
driveway.
>> Oh yeah.
>> Okay. Yeah. So, we happen to have, I
believe, like two or three different
ones in stock. That's when we have it in
stock. Just wanted to hear, did she tell
you everything about a 25? We have a 0%
running right now.
>> She didn't tell me anything about the
25. Nope.
>> Okay. So, I know you're looking for a
deal. There's a big promotion on the
25s. Okay.
>> Got it. We're whispering. Okay. A
secret.
>> 0%. They're running on on those. And
it's not a secret. It's advertised all
over.
>> Oh, okay. Sorry. You kind of whispered
it like you should go for the 25.
>> I know. I was walking right behind that
customer.
>> Oh god. We don't We don't want that
customer to learn about it. I can know
about it. Okay. So 25.
>> I've looked at some 25s. I'm willing to
do a 25. You're willing to give me that
like not rockolid crazy deal. I'm
willing to hear it. We'll take the
interest.
>> So I got some numbers for you on the 26
that you especially the one you request.
Okay. Got it.
>> So and and that'll be including you said
transfer tag, right? Yep. Transferring
the tags.
>> Okay. We have it here. We could do 51130
and that taxes. Yeah.
>> Okay. What's the Just so I know like
what's the MSRP? What's the discount?
What's the rebate? Break it. Break it
down for me.
>> MSRP you're looking at 50,620
on this car.
>> Okay.
>> And the selling price we given it for
you is 46884.
>> 46884.
Okay. So, you're giving me about four
grand off. So, $1,500 rebate plus the
$2,500 discount. I did. I gave you way
better than whatever rebates is out
there just to make it happen. So, if you
want a deal, I'm giving you a deal on
that. Mind you, if you're looking to get
0%, you could get it on the 25s.
>> Okay. What would be the I guess is there
a crazier discount on the 25? Is the 25
something I should be listening for?
>> No, on the 25s, they're not doing
they're doing either or. Either you
could say 3500 up front or you could
take 0%. So, either or.
>> Okay. Well, I'm I'm looking to pay cash.
So, for me, cash is king, but I'm
willing to hear 25. You have a 25 white
with a peacon or brown gray interior.
You you you got my interest. You got my
interest. You got me. You got me
intrigued.
>> Okay. Yeah, we have 25s here. I just
have to see we have it on that
combination.
>> Cool. Yeah.
>> Will you be willing to do uh financing
on it? That's how you're going to get
the the 0% if you're looking for that.
>> No, I'm looking for the 3500. The 3500
seemed cooler.
>> Okay. But mind you, on the 26, I'm able
to save you more than that. I'm saving
you 3736 on that.
>> But the but the 3500 is just a rebate,
right? So like just like like that the
other one's a 15.
>> Just a rebate. But it's not like I could
combine them with anything else.
>> What do you mean? You can't combine a
discount and a rebate?
>> I I can, but the rebate is so heavy on
those that they don't allow me to do
anything else in that.
>> Wait, who doesn't allow Hyundai doesn't
allow you to dis like the the rebate
comes from Hyundai. Like you Hyundai
reimburses you that money.
>> That's correct. Yeah.
>> So they they don't they don't care what
you sell the car at.
>> I could look into a specific one if you
want me to. If
>> Yeah, you can go just go look at the
rebate form. The rebate form is
literally just saying that you're going
to either I can take the rebate or you
can take the rebate, but you normally
take it off the price of the car and get
the rebate. Hyundai's just incentivizing
buy the car because nobody's buying them
because of the 25.
>> Yeah. So my question to you will you be
more interested on a 25 or on a 26?
>> Let's go 25. But I mean if you I'll be
very transparent. If you're just going
to give me $3,500 off and you're
charging me MSRP, bye-bye. Like no, I'm
not interested. I don't want to waste
your time.
>> Okay.
>> Okay. So 25. And you said white. And
what's the interior color?
>> Uh any color but black. Any color but
black. Okay, let me see if I have
something and I'll call you back about
it.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> All right, Tommy. Bye-bye.
>> Message to you.
>> Hey, can I speak to somebody in new car
sales?
>> Yeah, I can get you right over. Uh, what
vehicle is that you're looking for so I
can let them know?
>> A Hyundai.
>> Okay. A new one or a used one?
>> Uh, brand new.
>> New. Okay, perfect. And then may I have
your name as well?
>> My name's Tommy.
>> Perfect. All righty, Tommy. I'll go
ahead and get you over in case we get
disconnected. Can we beat you back at
this number?
>> That's correct.
>> All right, perfect. Lovely. One moment.
>> Hi, Tommy. This is Danny. How are you?
>> Hey, Danny. I'm doing well. How about
yourself?
>> Pretty good.
>> Hey, awesome. I just want to see if you
guys have help with
>> Hey, I just want to see if you guys have
a car available.
>> Okay. What kind of car?
>> Uh, I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Sure.
>> Uh, stock number 126016.
>> I know exactly what that is.
>> Nice. Perfect. I love it.
>> If I if I think properly, is it the
Palisade?
>> It is not. No,
>> most of those are. Okay, hang on a
second. Let me look. Browse. New
inventory. Well, we just got a new truck
in, so there's so so many.
>> Oh, awesome. That's great. That means
that means that this car is probably
less value.
>> Oh, I have to check cuz I just sold one
of these. The Santa Fe calligraphy
frontwheel drive and tell me it has the
peanut butter. I would be very happy to
sell you that car because somebody came
down here the other day from
Jacksonville and he was going to pay
cash for it. He was supposed to get back
to me um by the end of business. You
know what? Do me a favor. You want to
come in and take it for a ride because
it's absolutely beautiful and there's
only one.
>> Well, I've already driven one. I already
know I wanted it. If we can get a
numbers over the phone, I'll buy it
right over the phone.
>> Okay, I can do that. Where are you? Let
me see. Well, I don't have any of your
info. Where are you from? Do you live
around here?
>> I'm I'm north of Orlando.
>> Okay. All right. Let me get a little bit
of info. Um, were you looking to trade a
car in? No. Were you looking to finance
or pay cash?
>> I'm moving to financing just to get the
rebate cuz I know that's there, but um,
you know, I could pay cash if needed.
>> Okay. Um, let me see what the rebates
are cuz you know what? I'm a big I'm a
big fan of rebates.
>> Yeah, I'm a big fan of rebates, too. I
put them on my wall
>> Yeah, usually on the calligraphy there
it Nope, this one isn't the hybrid.
Yeah, it's 1,500, it looks like.
>> Nice
>> for the rebate on that one. Yeah, you
finance it. There's two There's two
choices. 3.99%
for 60 months or $1,500 off. You have
one or the other.
>> Awesome. Awesome. Perfect. Okay, cool.
Let's just Okay.
>> Uh, if you can give me the, you know,
the rest of the out the door numbers.
Looking to buy a car today. Hopefully
get a good deal. Call it today. Bada
boom, bada bing.
>> All right, that sounds good to me. What
is your last name? Is your first name
Thomas?
>> You're sure you can call me Thomas.
Tommy Thomas love TomTom. Don't call me
Tom. I don't know. Nobody call me.
>> That's right. My name is Danielle and
everybody calls me Danny. I'm like,
that's because I'm from New York. It's
like Danny, Bobby, Joey, Chrissy, you
know, you can't just be Dan.
>> Absolutely. You got to add it.
>> Uhhuh. Okay. All right. What's your last
name?
>> Last name Makula. M as in Mary. I K U L
A.
>> Okay. What's your phone number?
>> Uh phone number is going to be 9.
>> Okay. And what is your address?
>> Well, I can give you my zip code.
>> That works. Yeah.
>> Okay. And um let's go into your vehicle.
Do you Did you say you had a vehicle to
trade?
>> Nope. Nope. No vehicle to trade. Just
adding.
>> All right. No trade. Do you have a tag
to transfer?
>> I do have a tag to transfer.
>> Okay. And if you're going to finance,
um, how much did you want to put down?
>> 510,000, but I'm not really worried
about the financing. More worried about
just getting the out the doors.
>> Out the door. Okay. Uh, it looks like
this vehicle is $52,580
plus tad, tax, and title.
>> Oh, what county do you live in?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Where I guess where did the
price go? The MSRP is 50,580, and
there's a rebate. How do we get up to
52, just so I know?
>> 50. There is a clear shield product on
the vehicle that protects the screens
and the paint for life. It is necessary
because we have had some issues with
people breaking those screens are over
$1,000 plus $300 labor. So for the
entire life of that vehicle if you drop
a phone or somebody throws something and
hits the big I mean that's one huge LED
screen
>> that the paint on the door jams and the
bumper the the the back paint. And you
said it was 52 plus tax plus the $1,500
rebate. So is that like $3500 bucks for
all that?
>> No. Minus the $1,500 rebate. I'm going
to have him I'm going to have my manager
give you the actual numbers for it
including, you know, itemize.
>> Yeah, that' be great. That'd be great.
Just maybe read it and see it and
understand it a little bit better.
>> Mhm. What else was I going to ask you?
All right. No. Oh, were you ever in the
military?
>> I was never in the military. No stolen
valor here. Oh,
>> okay. Military. No. I'm trying to think
of if there's any other rebates. It
looks like there's there might be
something, but the I'll be honest with
you, between the like you said, between
the financing and the um dealer choice
cash rebate, one of them really isn't
any better than the other. So, if you
were going to pay cash out the door
afterwards, the $1,500 is probably the
way I would go. But this particular
white vehicle with the pecan brown
interior,
>> there aren't any. That's why everybody's
calling us. There's only one. But
they're we're not like jacking the price
up crazy. This is actually a product
that every single one of our vehicles
gets because of the problems with the
paint and the screens breaking.
>> So, should I even be buying this car?
That seems crazy. What? Like, should I
even just be looking at something
different is chipping and the screens
are cracking?
>> Well, yeah. Well, no. I mean, that it's
not just that they crack. If something
happens, somebody breaks it. I mean, we
have the flyers. You're going to spend
$50,000 on a vehicle. You're going to
want to make sure that that is
protected. I mean, if something happens
and you hit it just right, you're going
to be you won't be able to drive it.
You'll be blind. You know what I mean?
Cuz if the dash goes out,
>> you said it was a thousand bucks. So,
like I could buy I could buy three
screens before that pays for itself.
Call me crazy, but I've never thrown my
phone in my dash before or anything on
my dash really. Like, the chance that
that happens seems slim.
>> Well, that Yeah, that is what it's for.
It's It's called a mobile clear shield,
and it's an actual product that we have
someone come in.
>> And that and that protects the screen
from cracking, not just scratches.
>> No. No. No. If it does, we replace it. I
don't care how many times it happens
over the lifetime, right? It's a
lifetime warranty that we will fix. And
well, not even fix, we replace the LED
screens, the doors. When you chip the
paint on the doors, depending on how you
do it, we put protective coating over
the edges. Like, you know, when you open
the door and you hit a wall or you hit
another car, you may have to paint the
entire door. So, we fix and repair that
for life.
>> So, you'll paint my entire door if I
ever get a chip in it. if that's if
that's what's necessary. Whatever it
takes to fix the car back to the way it
was supposed to be because of the dings,
the dents on the door jam, the LED
screen and the back bumper when you you
know when you pull stuff in and out of
your car back
>> bumper. Yeah. I would love to see the
just the if you have the the literature
on that. I've heard of PDR repair. Yeah.
Yeah. If you want to send that to me,
text it over to me cuz normally that's
not on paint repair. The idea that you
guys would paint an entire door seems
crazy. It says almost every time you
reach for the door, you create a scratch
on a road trip. Multiply that by
hundreds for every door. Yeah. So, you
know, when you grab the door, your door
handle, and people wear rings or
whatever, and it scratches the inside of
the door jambing
your doors. Yeah. That's that protective
coating that. And outside of the doors,
you guys are going to paint the entire
car for me, the side of the car.
>> No, I never said that. I said the door
jams. The Right. So
>> the door jam. But why would the door
jambs get scratched if I open the door?
You are you talking about just like the
door handle?
>> I'm talking about the door handle. And
when you open the door, if you hit your
door jam, you'll see it. I'll take a
picture of what it looks like cuz it's
natural. You can't really see it unless
I take a really good picture. So I'll do
that.
>> Yeah. Yeah, that would make more sense.
I'm just trying to understand the value.
I could maybe see the value if you guys
are willing to pay my whole car. But if
it's just the I just send me the stuff.
I guess I'll look at it.
>> Yeah. It says, "Nearly invisible
protection against scratches, wear, and
corrosion. Rigorously tested for gravel
chip resistance as well as cracking,
chalking, and dulling due to
weathering." So, there's like a screen
protector. Basically, you can barely see
it, but it's on that big screen.
Absorption of impacts and resistance
against staining and yellowing.
Protecting the integrity of painted
finishes. Excellent clarity, gloss
retention, tensil strength, and
resistance uh res excuse me, resistance
to elongation and shrinkage. developed
specifically for protecting automotive
surfaces from galvanic corrosion,
abrasion, and wear. And here in Florida,
that's a big deal.
>> Sure. Yeah. Yeah.
>> I'll send it to you.
>> Yeah. Yeah. That that would that
>> I'll give you the pricing. Have you
found this particular car anywhere? Is
this specific? This is the car that you
want. Color
>> I want to take all the uh basically
everything but a black interior, but
you're the first dealership I've called.
>> All right. Give me a second because I'm
going to print this out and then if I
could You said your number is
>> That's it. That's my number.
>> All right. I'm going to call you back
and I'm What I'll do is I'm going to get
you the quote with the rebate out and
then the out the door cuz it doesn't
really matter what the I mean, are you
going to end up paying cash for it
afterwards or do you want the monthly
payment?
>> Yeah, I'm not worried about the monthly
payment. Let's let's let's start off
with the uh price of the vehicle and go
from there.
>> Okay, we'll do. Give me about 10 minutes
and I'll do that for you.
>> 10 minutes. Bada boom. Bada bing. Sounds
great.
>> I'll call is All right. Great. Thank
you.
>> Okay. No problem. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> Again, if we if we end up taking, let's
just say $4,000 off that car, they were
going to charge $3,000 for that. So,
that's seven grand we just saved our
client if we get even just four grand
off the car. But, you know, I only I
only I only save I only charge a,000 to
save a,000. Golly G willilickers.
>> Thank you for holding. This is Eric.
>> Eric, how's it going, man?
>> Doing well. How are you? Hey, I'm living
a dream. Uh, I just want to see if you
guys have a car available.
>> Absolutely. Which one are we looking
for?
>> I have a stock number if that helps you
out.
>> Absolutely. Fire away, please.
>> Uh, H is in Honda 9109.
>> One moment, please.
>> Of course. Take a time.
>> How's your day going so far?
>> You know, I'm living a dream. I haven't
determined yet if it's a good one or a
bad one, but it's a dream nonetheless.
How about yourself?
>> You know what? It's a beautiful day here
in Florida.
>> That's what my mom always said.
>> Let me take one look here. I apologize
for the delay while I get this pulled
up.
>> Of course.
>> Let's see. H9110009.
Got that. All right. Looks like it's
going to be one of my 26 Santa Fe
calligraphy.
>> That's it. You're good.
>> All right. Yep. It appears that a
vehicle is available.
>> Awesome. Perfect. Well, I've already
driven one. Already love it. Want more
of it. Ready to buy one today or
tomorrow. Really just trying to get some
good pricing and I'll come buy one
today.
>> Tommy, we can make it happen.
>> Bada boom, bada bing. That's what I
want.
>> I follow you on TikTok. I'm live
streaming right now. Aren't you?
>> You know what? 30 33% of the time I get
recognized every time. Yep. That's it.
You're
>> within 5 seconds. Within 5 seconds, I
knew it was you, man.
>> Dang it. Well, I will tell you the bar
is that low today. You got you got a I
think you got a few grand few thousand
people watching you right now. So, make
it good. Let's go.
>> Let's clients in Florida, so that's
great. Let's Let's do it. I love it.
Appreciate you watching.
>> You got it. So, let's go ahead.
>> Okay.
>> All right. So, I have this one here.
Looks like it's available. Tell me where
I need to be and I'll do my best.
>> Uh, normally I get like 10% off these
things.
>> Okay. Give me one moment here. All
right. You know the routine? Any
military first responder help? Oh,
military first responder and they're
willing to finance to get the additional
rebate.
>> All right, let me go talk to the GM. How
does this work? Do you want me to call
you back? Do you want me to put you on?
>> Call me back so you can get the the the
live in there, too. But see if I have
any other Hyundai deals over here to see
if we can put we'll make one or two. I
do have another one if you are feeling
frisky and crazy and you want to do an
Elantra inline.
>> Gotcha. Uh, checking real quick here.
>> You're good. We can do two deals at the
same time. Bada boom, bada bing.
>> Buy one get one free. Pay 60 grand for
this one, get the other one free.
>> Okay, that's fair. One client would be
super happy. The other one would be very
confused.
>> All right. I don't have any launcher
ends yet.
>> They're probably willing to wait if you
have one in the pipeline.
>> I have one in the pipeline and it's not
our color. It's going to be the Hampton
gray.
>> We can paint it. I'm just kidding. No,
it's fine. Um
>> I'll spray paint it for free.
>> Yeah, they said no gray. Darn. Okay,
let's not worry about that one. Um
>> best phone number for you, sir.
>> Uh best. Thank you for not just saying
it. Uh
>> allow me less than 10 minutes here. I'll
get an answer on the calligraphy hybrid
Santa Fe for us. Uh, also if you don't
mind, text me to the number you're going
to call me so then I make sure I answer
it. I just don't want to ignore you.
>> Yeah, you got it. I'll text you for
myself.
>> Yeah. Okay. Awesome.
>> Awesome. Thanks, Tommy.
>> Hey, no problem. Bye.
>> Thank you for calling, guys. This is
Justin.
>> Justin, how's it going?
>> It's going all right. How are you? Who
you're speaking with?
>> My name is Tommy.
>> How's it going, Tommy?
>> Hey, man. I'm living the dream. I just
want to see if you guys have a car
available.
>> Which one?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> I know who you are,
>> man. I was making I was making an
argument with my stream. They were like,
you don't ever get recognized. People
don't know who you are. This is like two
phone calls in a row.
>> I know who you are.
>> Oh, I know. Um, what up, dog? I got I
got a I got a customer in Orlando. I got
two deals. We can do two deals. Bada
boom, bada bing.
>> Okay. Yeah. Yeah. What up? Two different
customers. One customer. What do we got?
>> Two different customers.
>> Okay. Yeah. What are we looking for?
Stock number.
>> Stock number Y is in Yale 106297.
>> Looks like we got a calligraphy should
be here. I believe I do have the
vehicle.
>> Okay. 2025. And then is that $6,000 plus
rebate or
>> it's good discount plus rebate? Yeah.
>> Okay. So, you guys are going $9,500 off
that car.
>> It looks like it, painfully enough.
>> And no dealer ads.
>> Uh, dealer ads. 1897.
>> Can you get rid of the dealer ads?
>> I mean, that'd be pretty pretty
disgusting. I mean, I'm willing to bring
anything to him. We had a pretty rough
last month, so
>> Oh, dude. Let's do it.
>> Let's bring it to him and see what he
says. And then, uh, the other one's a
little bit weirder. I wasn't planning on
doing it, but if you recognize me, then
I'll do it because you might have it,
which is an Elantra N, blue or red.
>> I'll be I'll be honest with you, man.
Those cars fly off my shelves.
>> Trust me, that that one's going to be a
little bit tougher. I don't expect to
get nine grand off that car.
>> Oh, yeah. That No, we don't really
discount them all. The 25 I have no
problem discounting, but the launcher
ends I've gotten like two in in a year,
you know.
>> No, I got I got you. Yeah, just let me
know what you can do on that one. I'm
trying to close it ASAP. I'm live, just
so you know. So, um let's uh let's put
this together.
>> All right. Let me um What do you want me
to call you back at?
>> Uh call me back at this. Sorry, I muted.
Call me back at this number.
>> Okay. It's 98.
>> All right. I didn't want to put it on
stream there.
>> No, I know.
>> Um and what's the process like cuz I
know you do the negotiations for the
people.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So, what happens if we agree
to numbers and you send me writing on
the deal? Uh, then I will then go
through and give uh it to the client.
Client says yes. I give you the client's
phone number. You reach out to them and
you do the paperwork. It's as if it's
just just think about it as like the
craziest lead you ever got where the
deal's already closed and you just have
to sign paperwork.
>> Okay. I just hopped on your stream.
>> You can say you can say hi to everybody.
You're here. Yeah, this is real live.
You're you live. Get the deal done. You
can shout out your stream call today.
We're calling deal. Let me let me go
ahead and uh I'll pop over to the GM,
let him know what's going on, and then
uh I'll give you a shout back. Okay,
Tommy.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> Tommy.
>> Hey, what up, dog?
>> Not much, sir. How are you,
>> man? I'm living the dream. Living the
dream.
>> All right. I'm at 2500 under MSRP,
including the rebate.
>> Including the rebate.
>> Indeed, sir.
>> You're killing me, Smalls. You're not
Smalls. I'm not saying you're Smalls.
That's what I meant. Are you talking
about the Elantre N? Is that what you
really meant?
>> I wish that was on the Sami. Do you have
any like 25s that you just want to get
rid of?
>> Yeah, but I can't beat Justin's offer.
That's an insane deal and your client
needs to hop on that immediately.
>> Well, I need to see if it's actually
real, too. That's that's the other
thing. But dang.
>> Yeah. Which dealership was that?
>> Can't I won't say it yet cuz I don't
want to give him I don't want to give
him a shout out and then him charge me
10 grand on
>> Trust me, the amount of people that'll
say the little crazy deal and then they
never come to fruition is crazy. Oh my
god, this dealership is blowing me up.
Oh my gosh, these guys called me. Do you
know?
>> Never heard of them.
>> They've called me five times. Literally
spam call me. Jeez. Okay. Okay. Well,
ma'am, maybe we'll put the next one
together. I feel bad, but I mean,
technically, that's still the best offer
I have right now.
>> I mean, let me ask you Oh. Oh, god. I
just did the old Let me ask you. Um,
>> let me ask you this. Maybe another 500.
>> It's a h it's a habit. Uh, so obviously
the rebate's 1500. If I did 1,500 plus
match the re No, match the rebate. So,
three grand under.
>> I don't know if there's a specific
number your client is trying to be at,
but you I'm trying to be closer to an
out the door price of 50.
>> I'm trying to be where I can.
>> And Do you have any You don't have any
ads?
>> Uh, no ads. We We do, but you're not
going to pay him.
>> Okay.
>> So, I even charge you.
>> Yeah. Yeah. No, no. I appreciate that.
Let me Let me do this. Uh cuz you are
closer, too. Let me Let me make sure
this deal is real. I'm waiting. Oh my
god. This guy's text me again. Holy
moly. This guy's insane. Sorry. Um some
of you are insane. Okay. So, you're
saying maybe you could do three grand
off plus rebate potentially. Maybe,
maybe, maybe. Times 10.
>> That's what I That's what I'm going to
have to propose, but I'm I'm looking at
to see what you know invoice is on it.
So, I'd like to try to make this happen
with It's definitely definitely a little
off on there, but let me I'm text to my
client right now and seeing uh if he has
a preference on the interior cuz theirs
is the forest beige and yours is the
pecon and I think he liked the precon a
little more. So, let me see what he says
on that.
>> And I'm much more handsome than the
other guys, too. So, that's
>> that helps. Hey, that helps. I love it.
Um I will be there. Perfect. Uh okay,
cool. Let me text him right now and see
what he says.
>> Thanks, Tommy.
>> Hey, no problem. Bye.
>> This is Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. It's Justin.
>> Oh, what up, man? Oh, you got good news.
Yeah, I got 9,500 no ads.
>> Send that to me, man. We'll close that
up in a heartbeat. Were you Were you
watching the stream? Did you see what
your competition said?
>> No. What did he say?
>> He said that he can give me $3,500 off
the 25, but he can't do a discount on
top of that because Hyundai doesn't
allow it.
>> That's a lie.
>> Wonder. Okay, man. Send me this deal.
Let's wrap it up. Bada boom, bada bing.
This is great.
>> Let me go ahead and uh Do you want me to
just text it over this number? You got
an email for me?
>> Uh can you text it to me, man? It's just
easier.
>> Yeah, I'll text you over a picture right
now. Okay. I'm out of everything works
and uh I'll be watching the stream. All
right.
>> I love it, man. Let's put more deals
together. I like this.
>> All right. Told you I'll make it easy.
I'm losing.
>> Hey, I love it. And and again, once we
get this deal out, I'll let people know
where to find you.
>> All righty. Thanks, brother.
>> Hey, no problem. Bye.
>> Bye.
[Music]
>> Hi, Eric.
>> Hey, Tommy.
>> How's it going?
>> Doing all right. Did you close on your
Santa Fe client?
>> Uh I I think they're giving me 9500 off
no ads.
>> Yeah, you got to take that. That's a
>> I know. I feel I'd feel stupid not to,
right? Like that'd be
>> makes that watch have like 4,000 miles
and it's a demo.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Well, well, that'd be crazy.
Then I would feel I would feel
bamboozled.
>> Bamboozled.
>> But that's okay. Whatever. Do you got
the line? Did you get the inline for me?
>> No, but I have an active uh search on it
for it right now. So, if I put something
together, I'll shoot you a text and I
appreciate it all the same.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I appreciate that. Sorry.
I'm
>> That color looks great on you, by the
way.
>> Thank you. I appreciate that.
>> Wait, wait, what do you got? Are you
just Were you just calling to see if I
had the deal done?
>> Yo, the Santa Fe. I'm three grand under
the Santa Fe. You got 3K under. Okay.
I'm gonna run I'll run both by my client
and let him make the decision, but I
can't imagine he's not going to take
$9,500. That's just insane.
>> Yeah. No, absolutely. I mean, not a
tremendous amount has really changed
between the two in my opinion.
>> I Yeah. And I think more of like both of
you guys recognize me. So, you just got
really unfortunate to have somebody else
recognize me at the same time. And he
just had a 25.
>> You are so popular.
>> I know. I'm so so popular.
>> Okay, cool, man. Let's do Let's do
another one. You have my number. U we'll
we'll find another deal to put together.
Let me know if you have that one and
we'll we'll we'll rock that deal.
>> And I'm working with the put a Genesis
deal together for you, too. So, we'll
talk soon.
>> Okay, perfect. You're also working with
my team already. I didn't realize that.
My bad.
>> Thanks again.
>> Hey, no problem, man. I appreciate it.
Bye.
>> Bye. Let's talk about the person I just
talked to, Justin. The deal I just did.
He spent a total four minutes on the
phone plus a text. So, he was on the
phone. I asked him the number, called it
a day. He's going to spend, let's just
say he waited 10 minutes in front of his
manager to get numbers. He spent 15
minutes on this deal, and he's getting a
mini out of it. Yeah, you did 15 minutes
of work. Okay, now I take off. Bada
boom, bada bing. I'm out. Peace out,
girl scouts. Bye-bye.
[Music]