I tell you, this is how you advertise
cars.
You guys didn't even get to know the
price. Uh, the price is $1 off. I just
need something in writing. Even if it's
not perfect in writing, just something
to work with.
>> Can I send you a quote? No. I mean,
manager here might try to chop my head
off for trying to trying to send you the
deal in writing, as you probably know.
>> So, we are looking for some Mazda CX50
hybrid Sarasota. Now, with this, I'm
going to be looking really in a few
different places, but really looking all
through Florida in order to find this
deal. I have told the client that we
might ship this car if it makes sense.
We're going to make the first phone call
here. My goal with this deal, just so
we're clear, is I would like to get to
about 12 to 13% off plus any applicable
rebates. I'd consider that being a
pretty decent deal, right? I want to be
very clear when I talk about discounts
or percentage of discounts. I am always
talking about a dealer discount. What is
the dealer discounting the car? What I
am never adding into that number is
rebates because that inflates the
number. It makes it seem like I am
giving you a better deal than I actually
am. And it makes it seem like I've done
more work than I've actually am. So,
dealerships will do this. they'll be
misleading and they'll say like
something like, "I got you 13% off the
car, but 5% of that is rebates." So,
they really got you 8% off the car,
which doesn't make it that good of a
deal. But to inflate the dealership's
ego, they say, "I got you 13% off the
car." And again, if you don't know this,
you'll fall for it and be like, "Wow,
Tommy says 10%. Tommy says 12%. He got
me 13. I'm doing better than Tommy.
Maybe I should open my own negotiation
company cuz I got 13%. No, I'm telling
you the dealerships, what they'll do is
make you feel really good. They'll make
you feel like you could open your whole
entire negotiation company cuz you think
that's what it is.
>> Hello, this is Joe who I have the
pleasure of speaking with.
>> Hey, my name is Tommy. How's it going?
>> Yeah, Tommy. I'm doing good. How are you
doing?
>> I'm doing well.
>> And how can I help you?
>> Uh, hey, I just want to see if you guys
have a car available.
>> Okay, I can check for you. What ve was
it a new or pre-owned?
>> It is a brand new vehicle. Okay, let me
pull up my inventory here. Okay, what
vehicle were you looking for?
>> Uh, I have a stock number that helps.
>> Okay, go ahead with the stock number.
>> Stock number M is in Mazda. F is in
financial 56565.
>> That's easy enough.
>> It's the easiest.
>> Yes, the X50 2025 hybrid. Yes,
>> that's it. Awesome. Uh, is that
available?
>> Yes, it is here and available. I I
remember I had a customer on this uh
last week because he only wanted a
hybrid, but he ended up deciding he
didn't want a Mazda, but he did come in.
>> That makes sense. Well, good news for
you is I'm super interested in the
Mazda. That's the exact one I want.
That's the hybrid I want. Already driven
it, you know. I love it. Really just
trying to get the best numbers, and I'm
hoping you can help me out.
>> Well, generally they they put the best
number on the internet, which is the
42,000.
And um and then we we got the $8.99
dealer fee here, and then your tax and
tag would be the other charges.
>> Okay. And just to make sure I'm on the
same page, so you guys are at MSRP on
the car?
>> Well, we we do negotiate here at the
dealership. As a salesman, I can only
give you $500 off. I can't give any more
than that. Uh but the managers are, you
know, more flexible.
>> Okay. So you what you can do is $500 off
the car. So you guys would be $500 off
MSRP
>> plus the th000 that's already uh Mazda's
offering.
>> Customer cash. Correct. That's just a
rebate through Mazda. So if I want to do
the 1.99, I wouldn't get that.
>> Correct. The the Oh. Um that yeah,
that's usually true. If you take the APR
rate, they usually don't give the uh
rebate. That's correct.
>> Okay. Well, I was looking to do a little
bit better than MSRP just for
transparency or even 500 bucks off. I've
heard some pretty crazy deals. There's a
good amount of inventory on the ground.
So, you know, I understand that you
can't negotiate. Is there somebody I can
talk to that will
>> uh hold on, let me get see if my
manager's free. Hold on one moment.
>> That's exactly what I said. And what a
lot of people will do will go through um
and try to add that rebate on there and
activate the discount. You could see
like multiple times he said, "Hey, we're
giving $1,000 over. That's already the
deal we're doing. That's just a rebate
from the manufacturer. If I want to do
$1.99, I lose that rebate." So, we don't
want to fall for that.
>> Okay, Tommy. Yeah, my manager is going
to price that out for you and get back
to you. Um, what's the best phone number
for you?
>> Yeah. Uh,
>> okay. And what's your zip code? Cuz
that's going to affect the taxes.
>> Yeah. Yeah, it's
>> Yep. Perfect. Okay. And, um, were you
financing or um, buying it out cash?
Yeah, I was looking to do the 1.99%.
>> 1.99. Okay, perfect. Let me see what we
can do and I'll get back to you in a
little bit. It'll either be me or my
manager.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> Okay, thank you very Oh, what's your
last name, Tommy?
>> My last name is Makula.
>> It's M I K U L A.
>> You nailed it. Actually, that's really
good. Most people don't get that. That's
good.
>> Very good. Okay. Thank you very much for
your time. We'll be in Have a great day.
>> Okay, you too. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> I am not trying to go through and get
the craziest deal from day one. Really,
for me, I feel confident because I know
what discounts I'm looking for. I might
ask for that discount. If you're trying
to negotiate a car deal, competition
drives the price down. Uh, it's not your
brother, sisters, uncle-in-law that
bought a car last week and you're using
that to negotiate. What happened last
week is completely different to what
happens today. If you guys don't know
who I am, my name's Tommy. I negotiate
car deals for a living. My goal, save
you time, energy, anxiety. Do we save
money? Sure. But that's a byproduct.
Don't hire me to do that. Hire me
because you don't want to deal with it.
But if you're like, "Hey, Tommy, I just
want to learn. Follow my tips. Follow my
tricks. You're going to do it great."
Mazda. Carson, how may I help you?
>> Hey, Carson. This is Tommy from my
house. I just wanted to see if you guys
have a car available.
>> Okay. Do you have a stock number for me?
>> I do. Whenever you're ready.
>> All righty. I'm ready.
>> Okay. Uh, stock number is S is in Super.
N is in Niagara Falls 128624.
>> The 2025 Mazda. You're looking at that
CX50, the hybrid premium. Okay.
>> CX50 hybrid premium plus. You got it.
>> Yep.
>> We do. We do have that baby in stock.
>> I love it. Great. So, so already ready
already know I want it. Really just
trying to get the best pricing. I'm
hoping you can help me out.
>> So, pricing I won't be able to really do
anything over the phone and and nobody
really will be. More often than not, you
know, most of the time when we're going
to our bigger, you know, sales managers
and we're asking, "Hey, what's the best
we can do on this vehicle right here?"
Nine times out of 10, what they're going
to ask me is, "Is the customer here? Can
I speak to him? Is he here?" You know,
so for pricing, I I I don't really do
too much over the phone just cuz we
don't handle any of that. But I would
love to get you in for like a 105 minute
visit just for you to check it out,
maybe talk to our salesman. And if
anything, you know, I can get the get
get all your information in the system
and have them send over some snap sale
images of the vehicles and whatnot.
>> Well, uh, the one thing I love that you
said right there is that 90% of them you
don't do over the phone, but that means
there's another 10 still there. And I'd
like to be part of the 10% group. Uh,
call me crazy, but I'm like the type of
person that likes to sit back, relax,
and do this all at home rather than
going to the dealership. I appreciate
you saying it's going to take 10 to 15
minutes, but it takes me 30 minutes to
drive through traffic to get to your
dealership. 10 to 15 minutes turns into
an hour and then you spend two hours
doing this rather than a 5minute phone
call. But I am here. I'm ready to buy
know I want it. And I will tell you, um,
you're the second dealership I've called
and the first one was willing to give me
numbers. So, uh, I'm I'm batting a 50%
right now on people giving me numbers
over the phone.
>> All right. Um, and what was your number?
my phone number.
>> And then may I have your first and last
name just so I can update this all in
the system for you?
>> Yeah, if I can get
>> Gotcha. All righty. Give me one second
so I can set everything up for you. And
then give a call. All right. So,
perfect. So, I have your number.
>> 2025 Mazda CX50 Hybrid Premium. All
right. Sounds good. What I'm going to do
is I'm going to take all this
information. I am gonna get it all set
up in our system. Probably give you the
call back in about 10 minutes, 15
minutes, just so I could see if I can
get a a sales representative on the
phone with you and uh kind of maybe talk
about those numbers that you want to
see.
>> Okay. Yeah, absolutely.
>> All righty. Sounds good. So, expect a
call back from from one of us in about
10 minutes. 10 15 minutes.
>> Uh I'll be here.
>> All righty. Sounds good. I appreciate
your time.
>> All right. Sounds good. Bye.
>> All right. Byebye.
>> If you've ever negotiated a car deal,
you've probably heard the lines, "Your
presence is power." Hey, I can give you
some numbers over the phone, but guess
what? Your presence is your power. Or
they might say, you know, we don't even
know numbers over the phone at all. We
only take care of because we're so busy.
I had time to answer the phone, but I
don't have time for that. If you guys
want my like real argument to fix the
industry, right? Uh I actually don't
think the problem is car salesmen. I
actually think the problem is managers.
The reason why this happens isn't
because car salesmen don't want to do
numbers, so they can't. So everything
gets funneled to a sales manager because
that's the most profitable way. Because
a lot of car salesmen would honestly
just give away cars cuz they'd rather
sell a car and call it a day. In my
opinion, one of the best ways to fix the
industry is get rid of sales managers
and have all sales people be able to
give numbers. Numbers would happen much
more efficiently. Car salesmen would be
less salty about giving numbers cuz they
could do it in 2 minutes. They would
just shoot them out, call it a day. It'd
be super simple, super easy. And that's
that would actually solve most of the
problems, which is my caller's client
second option. We we're getting a phone
call, so I want to answer that first.
This is Tommy.
>> Hey, good afternoon. This is Cameron.
I'm one of the managers here with How
are you today?
>> Hey man, I'm doing well. How about
yourself?
>> I'm doing pretty good. Thanks for
asking. I'm reaching out to you just
really quick. So, I understand that you
were trying to get into the CX50 Hybrid
Premium Plus that we have available
here.
>> Correct. Yeah, dream car.
>> Okay, perfect. So, I did just double
check that one's here. It's still
available. Let's see really quick. It
looks like you guys are going to be
thinking about trading. Is it the It's a
2011 Camry.
>> We have a 2011 Camry. Honestly, I have a
really great offer with CarMax. Um
they're they offer stupid money on those
old cars. I just imagine you guys will
probably struggle to match that. If you
guys can, that's great. But more worried
about the price of the car. The trade is
worth a few grand. So,
>> okay, understood. Really quick, is there
a Mazda in the household, either leased
or financed or anything like that or one
that you guys own out, right?
>> There's no current Mazda in the
household right now.
>> Okay. The zip code for where you guys
will register, is that going to be
>> That's it.
>> Okay, perfect. All right. And I mean,
you know, whether we talk about the
trade or not, I mean, you know, overall
price on this vehicle, I mean, did you
guys have like an idea where you were
trying to be? You know, I'm definitely
heard that there's some great deals on
these cars. You know, I've gotten no
sets of numbers right now, so I'm kind
of starting fresh, but definitely, you
know, I've heard there's some pretty
darn good deals going on these cars
right now as the model year is changing
over.
>> Okay. Okay. With that being said, I
mean, did you have like an idea of a
number you were looking to be at?
>> You know, ideally in a perfect world, if
we were at 13% off plus rebates, that'd
be, you know, that would be incredible.
>> Okay. I mean, that sounds like a pretty
aggressive number to get to. I'm not
saying that it's not impossible. I mean,
I'll definitely work to get there, but
just want to have an idea of where you
guys are looking to be.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I mean, 13%, you know, 13%
is definitely what I would love to be at
right now in a perfect world.
>> Okay. And this is something you mean
you're thinking about financing,
correct?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Correct. Yeah. 13% off with
the 1.99% is what I'm looking for.
>> Okay. All right.
>> You got to get that free money, right?
>> Of course. You got to take advantage of
that when you can. For sure. Let me do
this. Um, I'm going to work on this for
a second. Are you going to be able to
speak in like 10 to 15 minutes?
>> Yeah. I'm not going anywhere.
>> Okay, perfect. Just stay by your phone.
I'm going to get with one of my
counterparts as well. If it's not myself
who gives you a call back, it might be
one of my counterparts. So, just be on
the lookout for a call right back from
us. Okay.
>> All right. Sounds good.
>> All right. Thanks so much. Talk to you
soon.
>> Okay. Bye.
>> Byebye.
>> Now, I do want to look for these gray
ones. So, I'm going to look at the gray.
I'm going to look at this second color.
Really, what we want to do in my client
service by making sure we're looking for
all the cars. 25 versus 26. The
difference in cars are very slim. I know
you guys probably care about all of the
USBC's that are in this car. I'm not
going through that. If you guys want to
look up how this car is built, this is a
premium plus, which is the highest end
trim. We're going to go through. Now,
this car is in
which is in. So, this is the client's
local dealership.
>> Hello, Jose. I just want to see if you
guys have a car available.
>> Sure. Hold on a second, please.
>> I can hold on as long as you need me to.
>> The stock number.
>> I would give you the stock number, but I
warn you, it's like 16 digits. Super
long.
>> That's the VIN. What's the car?
>> It is a Mazda CX50 Premium Plus hybrid.
>> Premium Plus.
>> And I do agree that is the VIN, but it
also repeats as the sock number.
>> Yeah. Hold on a second.
>> Doors. You didn't have to correct me
like that. Like, I I see it. It's
clearly the VIN and and just so you guys
can see as well like it's
>> all right. So I only have one stock. Let
me give you the last
>> the VIN and you tell me if that's it.
Okay.
>> Okay.
>> All right. 129968
>> negative.
>> Okay. Yeah, that's the only one we have.
>> Okay. So the 147990 is just a ghost. Not
real.
>> It's sold.
>> Oh, it's sold.
>> Yeah, it's sold.
>> You sure it's not maybe in transit?
>> If it says transit, I'm not on the
website. Check for you.
>> Sure, that'd be great. Yeah, but if it's
in transit, we don't have a confirmation
date because of tariffs and it's a 25.
>> Uh, I think it's a 26.
>> Oh, we definitely don't have no 26s.
>> Okay. And those aren't available to buy.
We just look at them and
>> No, you won't see those till like
January.
>> You won't see them till even though
they're allocated to your dealers.
>> Mhm. Yeah, we have no no 26ers coming
in. I can look them up and see.
>> So Mazda allocated them to you 3 months
early.
>> No, no, no. Definitely. Everything's
pushed back because of what happened.
So, we're like,
>> "No, I get that, but it's on your
website." Like, I'm not crazy. I didn't
like make I didn't call Mazda and say,
"Hey, we're this car that's going to be
built in 3 months." It's on your
website.
>> Okay. So, yeah, let me check for you.
Hold on a second.
>> Sure. That'd be great. I appreciate your
help. So, like small little lies, I
think, are really a big thing that
people don't like, right? Which is small
little lies, which is without even like
doing the research of finding where this
car is, what the one I'm looking for,
what I'm looking for to see maybe
there's another one available.
Immediately went, "Sorry, that one's
sold. Have a nice life." Right? Like,
and I know it's not sold. It's on their
website. It says in transit. There's no
way it's sold in transit. But he just
lied to get rid of me, I guess. And if
you really think that I'm the problem
here, like genuinely, genuinely, if you
think that I'm the condescending guy
that everybody says, good luck. I wish
you the best of luck in life. I wish
you, you know, should read a little bit
more, get out of the house, stop
watching Tik Tok as much, and maybe like
maybe get off a Sora.
>> Oh, that one you're talking about
schedule in November. Okay.
>> November. Oh, so it's here two months
earlier. That's so exciting. I'm willing
to wait till November. That's great.
>> Okay.
>> Is that allowed? Is that okay? I don't I
mean I I like I mean, if you have
another one that similar build, I'm
willing to hear it out. But I'm glad
that's here till November. That's much
more exciting than like January, you
know, new year, new me, new car. I I was
hoping 2025 car.
>> You said new me, new car. All right. And
as far as uh do you want me to call you
when it comes?
>> Yeah. I mean, you know, I already know
I've driven one of these. I know I love
them. I've driven 25. 26 is the same.
Uh, if you can give numbers on it and
you guys can do them before they get
there, I'd love to do that. If not, I
totally get it and I'll find one or wait
for this. I mean, I'm in Sarasota, so
like I mean I guess I can call the
dealerships around the state, but I was
hoping to buy from my local dealership.
>> Yeah. Do you give numbers on cars that
are being built?
>> No.
>> No, he doesn't have any information on
it.
>> Oh, okay. So, there's no way to do
numbers on this car. Nothing.
>> It just says in production.
>> Okay. I guess I'll uh figure out another
plan.
>> Thank you.
>> Bye. I want to be very very transparent
here just so you guys can understand.
This is the client's local dealership.
So I want to talk to you what happens to
a delivered client right now. What
happens is normally they start looking
for a car, right? Start looking for a
car. This is the dealership they call.
They have this experience. So then they
go into TikTok and realize like, oh my
gosh, other people are having this
experience. I don't have to deal with
this. If this client or this dealership
just made it easier to buy a car and
wasn't like this, I wouldn't have a job.
One of the biggest problems with
dealerships is they can't look
themselves in the mirror and realize
that they're the problems a lot of the
times. Instead, they want to pass the
blame to a lot of different people. Not
every dealership does this, but I do
feel like some do.
>> This is Tommy.
>> Hey, Tom. This is Cameron. So, we just
spoke.
>> Yeah, absolutely.
>> All right. Perfect. Okay. So, here's
what here's what we'll do for you. I
understand that you're coming from the
West Coast on this vehicle, so I'm I'm
not sure what the inventory is like out
there. I want to be as aggressive as
possible. So, what I'll do for you is
this. We have a dealer fee. It's $8.99.
So, what I'll do is I'll do $8.99 less
the dealer invoice. Our dealer invoice
on the car is like4822.
Um, so what I'll do for you is I'll do
you know 40,822
plus you know your fees and stuff like
that. So plus tax, tag and dealer fee.
>> 40,822. So uh just just so I can
understand it. So what is the total
discount? Is it about 2400?
>> Um so I mean MSRP on that car is 43,110.
So that's the complete MSRP on it. So,
do 43,110
minus the 40,822.
That's a $2,288 discount on that car for
you.
>> Okay. You know, I am hoping to do a
little bit better than that. And by West
Coast, I I think you mean the West Coast
of Florida, just to make sure we're on
the same page, right? Uh not the West
Coast. I'm not I'm not in Cali calling
you,
>> right? No. Right. Cuz yeah, we're we're
here in which is like and such.
>> Yeah, we we travel. I you know, we're
Florida's a great place. We're willing
to drive a few hours for a good deal. I
appreciate it. You know, I am looking to
get a little bit better than that, but
I'll be also honest. It's the best deal
I have so far today. So, you know, I
appreciate you giving me that. You know,
if we can, you know, if this is the best
deal I have by the end of the day, I'm
all for doing it. I'm looking to buy a
car today. But I I feel like I can do a
little bit better than that. Call me
crazy.
>> I mean, if you can do a little bit
better than that, I mean, I'd say run
and get it. I mean, me uh me putting it,
you know, below that dealer invoice
cost, even giving you that that dealer
fee off. I mean, that that's my very
best. That's the very best that I'm able
to do. if you do get better or if you
even have an offer, I mean, we're always
open to offers. But, I mean, that that
is my absolute best right there.
>> Yeah. And that's fine. I appreciate it.
You know, obviously, you're one of the
closer dealerships to me. So, you know,
what I can do is uh if you're willing to
u send me that, I'll look at it and uh
if it makes sense, that's great. If not,
if I find a better offer, I'll call you
and see if you guys can, you know,
compete. If not, no big deal. No hard
feelings.
>> Okay. Understood. Understood. Yeah. Um,
what I mean, I can shoot that to you
over in a text. Can I send you a quote?
No. I mean, manager here might try to
chop my head off for trying to trying to
send you the deal in writing, as you
probably know, but like like I said, I'm
more than happy to go ahead and send
that to you over in a text message. If
it's something you want to do, you want
to move forward on, you know, get me the
rest. Even if it's the the trade
involved into the deal, if you want
better on that, I'll I'll even try to
extend on the trade as much as possible.
I know you have the car max figure
already, but I'll do what I can.
>> Okay. Yeah, I appreciate it.
>> No problem at all. Give me a call back
at this number with what you decide. All
right.
>> Okay. Sounds good. I appreciate it. Just
send me that text. That'd be great. All
right.
>> All right. Thanks so much. Talk to you
soon.
>> No problem. Bye.
>> Bye.
So, at least the guy's professional,
right? Second thing here is it's okay.
We don't expect to just close this in
one call. If we called this and the
first person that gave us the first
offer and we closed it and we're like
call day, that's that's not the best.
That's normally meaning that we could
also do better. We asked for 13% off, he
gave us six. I just need something in
writing, even if it's not perfect in
writing, just something to work with,
right? So, I have more competition to
drive the price down. That is the goal.
So again, all we're trying to do in this
phase, right, buying a car doesn't
always take 5 or 10 minutes. We want to
be as quickly as possible, but we're
going to get numbers. We're going to
have those dealerships compete each
other. Call it a day. We're trying to
buy cars is what we're trying to do.
We're trying to help a client here on
this particular deal. Clients want to go
anywhere. Now, I did see two things that
I want to touch on. First off, somebody
says, "Why don't you just talk to the
manager?" You have to remember part of
the thing that we've done this I've been
doing this for two and a half year,
really almost three years. We're about
two months away from three years. I have
tested every single method. We have
people we've trained to do this that are
my employees that are some of the best
people that work are hardest working
people in the world. When you're doing
this in volume, right? What I've learned
very quickly is if I ask for the manager
over 80% of the time I will not get an
answer at all. I'll get sent to a
voicemail. So now I'm leaving voicemails
for dealerships across the country.
Plenty of people don't ever check your
emails. Call it a day. Third, I know a
lot of people like to say that I'm a
Karen, right? But I'm telling you, you
going to the sales manager, skipping the
process that that manager is teaching
everybody to do is the ultimate Karen
move. It is 100%. Sales managers don't
want to deal with your BS, right? I just
want to guys, this dealership, I think
we're going to take this deal. If this
dealership honors this deal, cuz this
might be the best deal that I have seen
all day. I'm going to I'm not going to
spoil you with the deal this dealership
is offering. But when I tell you this is
how you advertise cars.
No thank you. Inside Mazda.
>> Hi Mazda. Tommy Makula.
>> How can I help you?
>> Hey, are you in new car sales?
>> Uh, I can be.
>> You can be like today you are. Tomorrow
you weren't.
>> Uh, no. I'm I'm in sales. Yes, sir.
>> Okay, awesome. Cool. Hey, I just want to
first off see if you guys have a car
available.
>> Sure.
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Okay. Yes, sir. Go ahead.
>> Uh, stock numbers M is in Maserati.
45137.
>> 5137. All right. Let's go to inventory
here and look. Is it a new or pre-owned?
>> It is a brand new car.
>> Brand new. All right. So, I've got 2026.
>> So, you're super quiet, too. It's just
on my side, but you're like mile away
from the headset or something.
>> Uh, let's see. 20. It looks like to be a
2026 hybrid premium plus carbon with red
interior.
>> Yeah.
>> Yes, sir. It shows I have it. Now, this
is what I do. This kind of sells
>> and carbon. It should be machine gray.
Is that correct? Sorry.
>> Yeah, it is. It's Well, it's poly metal.
It's poly metal gray. Yeah.
>> Oh, it says it says exterior color on my
side as as machine gray metallic.
>> Let me see here. Machine gray. Yeah. So,
seeing that it doesn't have pictures up
there yet, what I do is I take your name
and number and I get keys to this car
and I go out on the lot and I touch it
and feel it and make sure it's actually
here cuz sometimes it says it's in stock
and that means it's still at the
Jacksonville uh Jacksonville port. Okay.
>> So, let me What is your name and phone
number?
>> Yeah, my name is Tommy. Uh, my phone
>> last name, Tommy.
>> Last name is Makula. M I K U L A.
>> Uh, my name is Matt. M A T. If you will
give me uh 10 minutes, I will go touch
this car, make sure it's on our
property, confirm the color, and call
you right back. Okay.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> Thank you, Tommy. Bye.
>> No problem. Bye.
>> You guys didn't even get to hear the
price. Uh, the price is $1 off if you're
curious. So, how I do deals, right? This
is the delivered process. We start
local. We try to find what we can local.
We'll go out of state and see what's out
there out of state. Again, we want to
use those good shipping paths, right?
So, I want to find something that
shipping is going to cost 500 to 800
bucks. If shipping cost 500 to 800 bucks
and I can get 13% off, that beats this
8% off deal all day and we can get a
cheaper documentation fee because doc
fees are crazy. On this one, we only
have a $700 doc fee. So, the doc fee is
not horrible. Uh, it's it's not great,
but in Florida, that's not bad.
>> Hey Tommy, how's it going man? Hey man.
Doing well. How about yourself?
>> I'm no bad here.
>> Did I cut you? I'm
>> watching you stream for
>> Yeah, sure.
>> Oh, okay. You're watching a stream then.
You know what I'm looking for?
>> Yeah. Well, good.
>> Okay. So, I'm looking Well, I was, but I
haven't watched it. I'm actually
>> Oh, okay. Uh, I'm I'm hoping you can
help me out. I have a client in Florida
CX50 Premium Plus Hybrid. Looking for a
really big discount.
>> What color are you looking for? Uh, I'm
looking for ideally white with red
interior, but secondary color would be
magnetic gray.
>> Machine gray. What's the red interior?
>> Yeah, magnetic is Toyota. Sorry.
Interior red. Red. They do not want
black.
>> Okay, gotcha. Pending that I have the
car and I can check that when I get back
home in a little bit if that's okay.
What I mean, what do you pick realistic
what you need on it? I mean,
>> normal deals that we normally do.
>> We normally do 10%, but uh these 202 are
kind of sitting around. I'm really
trying to get to 13 plus
>> rebates.
Okay, that's fine. I'll do it. It's just
no shipping, right? 13 plus rebates.
>> 13. I mean, do you want to throw
shipping in? That'd be great.
>> No, I mean, well,
13 plus rebate, I'm good with it. 13 13%
off MSRP and whatever applicable rebates
I qualify for.
>> Can you send me that in
>> What's that?
>> Can you send me that? Can you send me
that deal? As long as you can get the
car.
>> Yeah. Yeah, let me just as soon as I get
home, I'll check the inventory. I'll
send you a worksheet like always with a
bundle sticker. I'm pretty sure I have
it actually, too. I'm pretty sure I have
the white one, too.
If you have white, that's the that's the
dream color.
>> Yeah. If I don't have it, I'll be exit.
I'll still be
>> And just make sure you guys don't do any
dealer ads, anything crazy. And then if
I wanted to take the cash deal, it' be
$1,500 on top of that. Correct.
>> You know, you can money.
>> Yeah. I don't do any I don't do any of
that nonsense. It's just fee plus u tax
and taxes.
>> Okay, cool. Awesome. Let's let's uh let
me u once you get home, let me know and
we'll try to put this together.
>> All right, cool. I'll send it to you
shortly.
>> No problem. Bye.
>> Thanks. Thanks. Bye. So, just so you
guys know what the discount on this car
would be, MSRP of this car for a premium
plus is 42630.
42360.
We're going to be timesing 13%. So,
that's $5500 off. Now, if the client
wanted to take the rebate, right,
there's a rebate available of 1,500
bucks. They could. And this is where a
lot of dealerships will manipulate you.
That would mean the total discount is
$7,06,
which would be $7,06 / 42,000, which
would be a total of a 17% discount.
Again, that's not how I advertise
because there's 1.99% available, right?
You might want the 1.99% available,
which means you don't get the $1,500 in
rebate. So, on this deal, on this
particular situation, we got 13% off.
I'm still working the deal. That's
currently where we're at with it. Uh,
the next steps here is we kind of text a
whole bunch of dealerships. We're going
to keep trying to pin these dealerships
against each other. We've already
reached all of the dealerships in
Florida. Now we're just going to keep
working them and texting them. So
remember, dealerships are saying they
can't beat deals. They can't beat deals.
They can't beat deals. Now that I'm
saying I have 13% off, can you send me
that offer? I if I can have I'm going to
have a manager match it. I'm going to
see if I can have a manager match it.
Now we have a movement, right? Because
competition drives the price down. He
just texted me saying, "I've got it. Is
it okay to get to you? I just sent you
over the window sticker. Let me send
over the window sticker. Let me look at
this car. Make sure it's a good match."
Step one. Hybrid Premium Plus. It is a
windshill with red leather premium plus
MSRP 42755.
They're giving $5500
off the car plus any applicable rebates.
Okay. So, I'm going to text this over to
my client so they have it, right? So,
they know what's going on. So, what
we're going to do now is we're going to
we're going to wait on this deal a
little bit. I'm going to let it simmer.
So, one of the things you guys don't
always see is sometimes we start deals
on stream before, sometimes we do after.
This one we put a little bit of work
into. We have 13% off out of state. I
want to see if I can get a local
dealership to match it. So, I'm having
one of my team members, one of my deal
deal coordinator supports, start texting
these dealerships to start working these
deals in the background because at this
point, I've done the hard part, right?
I've got numbers call a day. They're
going to start pinning these dealerships
against each other and I'm going to move
on. And that's how our process works for
efficiency, right? I'm doing one thing,
they're doing another. We're combined.
We have three people working your deal
at any given time. We got that Mazda
deal done. 13%. Looks like this
dealership might be um matching this
deal. So, I'm waiting on those confirmed
numbers. Local. So, we have 13% off plus
rebates, potentially local. If not, we
have it for $500 shipping. No big deal.
I appreciate each and every single one
of you. Thank you for dealing with all
the fun things. Thank you for the good.
Thank you for the bad. Tell your friends
and family. Tell your mom, your uncle,
your brother-in-law about us. I
appreciate all of you guys. Dead
serious. That means a lot.
[Music]