If I'm going to leave this phone call
disappointed, at least I'll have some
good hold music to walk out to.
>> Maybe they might have changed though.
So, who know?
>> Don't tell me that.
>> Put me on hold and I'll see if I'm
disappointed.
>> Check it out. Okay.
>> And I watch your streams to help me get
out get better at this. So,
>> our deal is you can pay MSRP at 37724.
>> That's That's not much of a deal. You're
going aggressive at Holy moly. Sheesh.
Sheesh. So, let's do the Prius start uh
because I can keep working on that
immediately. Let's do that. Let's start
with the Prius. It's on the East Coast,
so then I can call dealerships while
they're still open because it's 5:00.
There's not even that many options.
Okay, Prius, relax. You guys can all
calm down. New Nightshade, all-wheel
drive. 28 of these bad boys available.
There's not many. They want any
interior. Only looking for a Karachi
wanting to go. They live in Oh, let me
write down their zip code. So, people a
lot of people ask what I take notes for,
right? They're like, "What are the notes
that you're taking?" Really, it's just
like scribbling. It's just like I
there's nothing that's if you can
understand this, good for you. But
honestly, I just do it so I can keep
myself organized. And our system is we
put them in deal started, which means
we're starting their deal. And we let
them know that we're live streaming so
they can watch if they enjoy. Now I have
to zoom into Maryland cuz honestly I
don't like Maryland as a state just
because I'm a Steelers fan. The thing's
back here. Let's make some phone calls.
>> Good evening. Thanks for calling. This
is Michael.
>> Hey Michael, this is Thomas Slav. How's
it going?
>> Hi Thomas. How are you today?
>> I'm doing well. I just want to see if
you guys have a car available.
>> Sure. What is that?
>> I don't have a like VIN. I have a VIN,
but I don't have like a stock number or
whatever. I have whatever floats your
boat. What do you need?
>> What? Whatever floats my boat. Great.
Thomas, uh, just in case we get
disconnected, what's the best way to
reach you, my friend?
>> Yeah. Uh, phone number is
>> Thank you for that, Thomas. What kind of
vehicle is it that you're looking at?
>> Uh, it is a 2026 Prius Nightshade
Edition all-wheel drive. All-wheel drive
in the Karachi yellow. Last VIN is 369.
>> Hold on one second. Okay, Thomas,
>> take your time.
>> Thank you. Can you repeat the last six
of the VIN, please, for me?
>> Last six of the VIN, of course. It is
369.
>> Okay, hold on one second.
>> You're good.
[Music]
>> Two seconds later. Thomas.
>> Hey. Sorry. I was just jamming out to
some old music. I apologize.
>> I was going solo.
>> I'm gonna I'm gonna hook you up with one
of my sales consultants, Bill. He's
going to be able to tell you exactly if
that vehicle is available, if there's a
deposit on it, if it's incoming, or when
it'll be here. Okay.
>> I love it.
>> Okay. Thank you.
>> Hello, Bill.
>> Hey, sales. This is Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. How are you doing,
>> man? I'm living a dream. Living a dream.
Uh, you have the best hold music I've
heard all day.
>> You're looking at Prius.
>> The first phone call. It's a good song.
>> Looking for a Prius?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Sorry. Back to business.
Serious. Yes. Prius.
>> 2026. The one that's incoming. Be here
end of uh October.
>> Uh, yeah. The the website says October
2nd to October 13th, but the end should
>> Yeah, probably it's right in late.
>> Okay. Japan. Yeah. Japan. Yeah. Probably
like midocctober at the earliest.
>> Got it. Okay. Right in late. Um. Yeah,
but it's the one. Cool. Yep. Is that
available?
>> It's available.
>> Bada boom, bada bing. I love it. Want
more of it. Ready driven one. Love the
color. It's great. Really just trying to
get some pricing and I'm hoping you can
help me get more.
>> Sure. What are you looking to do?
>> Buy it.
>> Okay. You know, you got the price on it.
>> Well, I it says unlock best price. Get
our best price with arrows and blinking
on the website. So, I don't have that
price. No, I don't have the best one. I
just have the TSRP.
>> Our best. Yeah, probably because Yeah.
MSRP 38123.
>> Oh, so like the blinking arrow and the
best price. That's that's that's just to
tell me that the price is exactly what
it says there.
>> Yeah, exactly.
>> Oh, okay. So, you guys don't do any
deals or anything crazy?
>> No, cuz there's no vehicles to do kind
of any kind of deal. Just limited
inventory.
>> Got it. Limited inventory on the Prius.
>> Oh, yeah. Limited inventory on
everything.
>> Got it. Limited.
Eight new cars. Yeah, we get everything.
Yeah.
>> Okay. I guess that ends. I mean, I'm
ready to buy one today, but I don't want
to pay the the TSRP, MSRP. So, I guess
if you you guys aren't willing to do
anything, then I guess I'll leave.
>> Yeah. I don't know what What are you
looking to pay?
>> Uh, I mean, I'm looking to at least get
two grand off.
>> Oh, yeah. I can't do that.
>> Oh,
I can't buy it at MSRP. I'd be disowned
by my mom.
>> Well, then I don't know where you can
get that deal. Maybe Where are you from?
Maryland.
>> Maryland. Yeah. Maybe maybe they have
something over there inventory-wise that
they're doing something with. I don't
know. But yeah, we we won't be able to
do that.
>> Okay, cool. Uh I guess if you change
your mind.
>> Yep. I got your number.
>> Okay.
>> Two grand off.
>> Gotcha.
>> Yep. Super easy.
>> All righty. I'll make a note. All right.
>> Make put a put a sticky note down.
>> Yeah, I got it.
>> Mhm. Okay. Well, it was good talking to
you. If you want to put me on hold for a
minute, that'd be great. I'd love to get
back to the old music. This the best
part of the call.
>> The old the old music.
>> Yeah, put me back on hold for a minute.
I wanna If I'm gonna leave this phone
call disappointed, at least I'll have
some good old music to walk out to.
>> Maybe they might have changed though, so
don't tell me that. Put me on hold and
I'll see if I'm disappointed.
>> Okay. All right, Tommy.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> I'm disappointed twice. the back of you.
I'm going to get copyrighted when I
upload this video. Dang it. Why would I
not continue that conversation? Cuz
sometimes you guys see me like dig deep
into those and other times you won't. I
can normally get a good vibe if they're
willing to move at all. And just like
the way he was talking, his mentality,
his attitude, like it was I I just it's
not going anywhere. Sometimes I believe
I can get him somewhere. Sometimes I
can't, but not when I wasn't. Uh if you
guys don't know, my name's Tommy. I
negotiate car deals for a living. My
goal is to save you time, energy, and
anxiety. If you're like, "Hey, Tommy, I
don't want to pay you $1,000 to do it.
I'd rather just watch you. You can sit
back, relax. Tuesday, Wednesday,
Thursday. We negotiate car deals from
3:00 p.m. Eastern to about whenever I
stop, which is normally around 6:00, but
yesterday we went till like 9:00. So,
understand that. We will keep going
until I decide I'm done. I don't make
the I make the rules, you don't."
>> Hi there. Thanks so much for calling.
How can I direct your call?
>> Hello. Can I speak to somebody in new
car sales?
>> Sure thing. One moment, please hold.
Okay, we'll hold.
>> A few moments later.
>> Thank you for holding. This is Connor.
How can I help?
>> Hello, Connor. This is Tommy. I just
wanted to see if you guys have a car
available.
>> Okay. What car are you looking for?
>> Uh, I have the VIN TSRP make, model.
What makes the most sense for you?
>> The VIN. What you got for me?
>> Vin. Do you want the last six of it?
Last 12 of it? Last all 16?
>> Last six is great. And is it a new or
pre-owned car?
>> It's brand new. And the last six 32 491.
>> I have this incoming and available to be
reserved. It's not physically here, but
it is available to be reserved.
>> All right. See, you're speaking my
language right now. Uh, I love it. I
want more of it. Really? I'm interested
in it. We're good at pricing. I'll I'll
put a deposit on it.
>> Sounds good. And are you local?
>> Uh, I am in Maryland. Yeah.
>> Maryland. Cool.
>> So, in every everybody's local Maryland,
you know,
>> fair enough. That is not far. Let me do
this for you. I can send you pricing
details, all that over to you and then
um basically our process is a $1,000
refundable deposit. I'd send you a link.
You put that down and we can move
forward.
>> I love it. Want more of it? This is
great.
>> What is a good email address I can send
it to? Tommy,
>> can you just text it to me? My life is
so much easier via text.
>> Sure, no problem. This phone number,
best one to text you on.
>> That is the best number for me. If you
don't mind, call, text, email.
>> Cool. Not a problem. And let's see here.
Okay. So, process-wise, what I would do
is I'll send you a specification sheet.
I'll send you a price breakdown. I do
need a zip code for where you are in
Maryland for taxes and fees. Uh, what is
that for me?
>> It's Awesome.
And uh what's your last name, Tommy?
>> Last name Makula. M I K U L A.
>> And then once I get that over to you, I
will need an email address for the
$1,000 deposit just so I have that, too.
What's a good email address for you,
Tommy?
>> Yeah. Uh can you just text it? I just
don't use email.
>> Yeah, sure. That's fine. But so I'll
text you over the specification sheet.
I'll text you over the price breakdown.
You know, you decide you want to move
forward with reserving the vehicle. I
will need an email address. I can I can
send the deposit link to your phone as a
text message, but I will need an like an
email just on file before I can send it.
But let me get that over to you in the
meantime and then yeah, I'll get that
over to you.
>> Awesome. Yeah, let's uh let's rock and
roll. Call it a day. Get it over to me.
We'll go.
>> We'll do.
>> Hey, thank you, man.
>> Yep. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> My real goal is to get about $3,000 off
this car. I gave 2,000 to the first one
because because I just didn't think it
was going to move anywhere. So, getting
something was better than nothing.
Hey, how can I help you?
>> Hello, this is Tommy and buying Can I
see if a car is bell?
>> What was it? I'm sorry.
>> Oh, sorry. I just want to speak more
clearly. Uh, can you tell me if a car is
available?
>> Yeah. Is it new or pre-owned?
>> Uh, it is brand new.
>> Do you have a stock number by chance?
>> I do. I can give it to you whenever
you're ready.
>> Yep. I'm ready.
>> Let me get my scroll real quick. One
sec.
>> Okay. It is K is in kilo. T is in tango.
W is in whiskey. 261583.
>> All right. Okay, it looks like it is a
Prius Nightshade Edition all-wheel drive
in the brand new Karashi all-wheel
drive.
>> That's it. That's the dream in the
driveway.
>> Sweet. All righty. It looks like it is
still in transit here. It should be
arriving. It's a little tough. I'm
seeing the second end of this month or
possibly even early November.
>> Awesome. Perfect. Well, I'm patient. Uh
I want this car. This is the one I want.
Really just trying to get the best
possible pricing and I was hoping to
call you guys, see where you guys are at
and seeing what I can do.
>> Yeah, no worries there. Let's pull this
up. All righty. Looks like we're
currently discounted about close to
$2,000. We're at 35737.
>> And is there a number you're looking to
try to get at the sale price?
>> Uh I'm trying to get to about 10% off.
So I'm trying to be at like 3,700 off.
>> Okay. And where would you be registering
a vehicle? What zip it?
>> In Maryland. You guys are a hop in a
skip away for me.
>> Sweet.
>> Makes my life 10 times easier.
>> That's what my mom always said.
>> Love it. And so you just looking to get
some numbers sent over to you?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I mean, if you get those
numbers, I'll put a deposit on it. Bada
boom, bada bing. Wait for the car. We'll
sign the paperwork. Call it a day.
>> Sweet, man. All right. And what was your
first name?
>> My first name is Tommy.
>> Is this delivered?
>> Sorry. Who
>> is this? Uh delivered.
>> Um no, it's Tommy.
>> Gotcha. What's your last name, Tommy?
>> Delivered.
>> Yeah, it's me. You got me. You're live.
>> I had a feeling I watch you pretty
often, my man.
>> You're you're live in front of
thousands. I don't know how many people
actually, but we have a good We have a
good audience here. So,
>> I love to hear it. Yeah. Let me um
>> Bada boom, bada. make this as
competitive as I possibly can do for
you. Um, you said you're looking to be
around the $3,500 under the MSRP mark.
>> Yeah. Yeah, you get that. That's what I
normally get on these. I have I have a
deal on one just in Texas. The clients
lives in uh Maryland, though, so I'd
prefer to keep it in Maryland.
>> Yeah, it makes life 10 times easier, I'm
sure.
>> Yeah. Easier for you. I mean, easier for
the client, but also I like to keep
local business local.
>> Yeah, I like that. Um, if I were to text
you over, you know, our numbers and
everything, would you be able to text me
over their offer? That way I could show
it to my manager, you know, have a
little leg to stand on. If not, I'm
still going to do my due diligence and
I'm going to go.
>> I'll be honest, I do enough business
with the dealership that is I've just
done enough business with so I know
where their deal is. I don't have like
an official offer sheet, but I can tell
you for a fact it's there. I can give
you their uh
>> Okay.
>> their Vspec if needed, but they just
give me a Vspec and a discount. They've
never played a game with me before, so
>> yeah. No, I can respect that. And I'm
not going to repeat your phone number
over here, but I'm guessing the one
you're calling off is okay to text you.
>> The amount of people that recognize me
and then also then just says the number
out loud, it's it's great. But yeah, no,
this is the best
>> and I' I've watched enough streams to
know not to ask these questions. It's
funny. Uh I got into this uh role about
it's five months ago and I watch your
streams to help me get out get better at
this. So,
>> dude, I love it. I'm glad you're
watching it. A lot of people don't like
it, but I'm glad you're watching it to
do better and get better things. That's
great. That's awesome, my man. That's
what I love it for. But yeah, let me um
let me get this down. Let me go talk to
my GSM. See if I can make something
happen for you. And um if it all works
out, you want me to text you over these
numbers?
>> Yeah, let's rock let's rock and roll.
Yeah, man. If you get, like I said, you
get this deal done, we'll wrap it up
right now.
>> You got it, Tommy. My name is Brendan.
Um, you can give me a call back here. If
not, um, but I'll reach out to you. I'll
text you and we'll get this done.
>> Okay. Awesome. Let's rock and roll.
>> All right. Sounds good, man.
>> All right. Bye. I just want to give like
some props, right? He watches the
stream. He's using it to learn. He got
in the role five months ago. Rather than
being somebody that's like, "This guy's
a jerk and a meanie butt." Uh, he's
like, "Hey, like I'm going to learn to
figure out what this guy is." And now he
knows who I am. He knows that this is
going to be a deal. And as long as he
gets to the numbers, it's great. So
yeah, I think more dealerships you
should use this as sales training
because you learn so much about how not
to be on the phone. Our business is you.
Is this dealership slogan? I like that
he's coming in chat right now. Yeah. We
won't give him a shout out until I get
the deal done. Sweet. I like the I like
the
>> Hi, you've reached
>> Hey, this is Tommy. I just wanted to
talk to somebody in new car sales.
>> Uh yes, you're talking to sales. How can
I help?
>> Awesome. Love it. Sales. Uh I just want
to see if you guys have a car available.
Uh, yeah, sure thing. Can you just give
me one moment? Uh, do you have a stock
number?
>> I do. Yeah. I mean, take all the time
you need. I have nowhere to be.
>> It's okay. I have a paper ready. What's
the stock number?
>> Stock number is 26
05.
>> Okay. All right. Just give me one moment
and I'll get you to someone that can
help. Okay.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> This is like the like like if I ask for
sales and you say, "Oh, I'm sales." I
bet how much we would bet that I'm going
have to do a
>> What else would you be doing? He said he
was sales. I'm I'm on hold just so you
guys know. I'm just muting.
>> Hi, this is Jenna with Toyota. How you
doing today?
>> Hey, I'm doing well, Jenna. How about
yourself?
>> I'm good, thank you. Uh, I was told you
were looking at a 2026 Prius Night
Shade.
>> That's it. You got it. Nailed it.
>> All right.
>> Put my money where my mouth is.
>> So, that vehicle is here and available.
Are you looking to stop in today to take
a test drive in it?
>> I've already driven one. I already know
I love it. really just trying to get
some really good numbers and hoping you
can help me out.
>> Gotcha. All right. Absolutely. So, this
vehicle is right now. So, this is priced
at 38,123.
That's before tax, tags, fees. Is that
something that would work for you? I
>> was hoping to get a little bit better
than that.
>> Okay, gotcha. Where are you looking to
be price-wise?
>> So, I have a deal for $2,000 off, but
what I told them was the same thing. I'm
trying to be at 3500 off. If I get 3,500
off, I will buy a car today. So,
typically with with new vehicles, we are
at MSRP, especially with the 2026s right
now. Did you have a trade in or are you
looking to finance leads?
>> No. Uh, I'm open to financing. I don't
have a trade. Um, but I know a few other
dealerships on these Priuses just like
the Tundras and Tacomaomas that aren't
as popular are doing some discounts. So,
I already have an offer for 2 off. I get
if you guys can't, but hoping to do a
little bit better than that.
>> What zip code are you located in?
>> Yeah. Uh,
>> okay. So, you're down in Maryland. Yeah.
Yeah. Really close though. Not having a
scap.
>> Let me see. Let me see if I can talk
with my manager real quick. Let me see
if there's anything we can do for you.
>> Yeah. Awesome. You can talk to your
manager. Hopefully, we can get a deal
together and I can buy a car today.
>> Yeah, absolutely. Give me just a second.
Let me go speak with him.
>> Okay, cool. I'll wait.
>> I bet she doesn't move more than 500
bucks. That's my bet. 500 bucks. I think
she's talking to her manager. I will say
I am I am impressed that they actually
transferred the stock number. I will
tell you nine times out of 10 they don't
transfer the stock number and they just
transfer me to sales and I have to
repeat myself. So no matter what props
to this dealership for at least doing
the bare minimum. I know I'm making a
joke about that. In reality it's
probably more than 9 out of 10. It's
probably 95 out of 10 or 100 that don't
give us anything. If you think it's not
going to work out, why continue? Well,
first off, I'm paid to keep trying to
work it out. So
>> all right. Thank you so much for
holding. And your name was again I don't
think I caught it at the beginning.
>> Oh yeah, my name's Tommy.
>> Pleasure speaking with you, Tommy. So, I
spoke with my manager. Unfortunately, we
wouldn't be able to take the 3500 off.
Um, we are at MSRP for the Prius.
>> Oh, so you guys wouldn't come down at
all?
>> Wow.
>> No, we're Yeah, we're uh we're at MSRP
up here, unfortunately.
>> No worries. Um I I completely get it. I
will keep going around to find somebody
or otherwise I'll take this deal for the
two grand off.
>> Gotcha. Yeah, I do apologize and I do
wish you luck in your search for a
vehicle.
>> Thank you. Appreciate it.
>> Absolutely. Have a good rest of your
day.
>> You too. Bye.
>> Thanks. Bye-bye. And so like a lot of
people like be like, "Oh, Tommy, you got
owned. You got schooled." Like not every
dealership's willing to do the deal.
It's fine if they're not.
>> Good evening. Thank you for calling
here. How may I take your call?
>> Hello. Can I speak to somebody in the
new car sales department?
>> You are speaking to someone.
>> I love it. Awesome. I I just want to see
if you guys have a car available.
>> Okay. Which one would that be? We have
several.
>> Uh Okay, that's good. I'm glad you guys
have several cars. I'm calling
dealership. So nice. Uh I have a stock
number if that helps.
>> Okay.
>> Let me know when you're ready for What
is it? I'm ready.
>> Uh, it is 58187.
>> All right. Give me a moment here.
>> You're good.
>> It is not showing up, but let me try
again. One minute.
>> You're just a little quiet, too, just so
you know. I don't know.
>> Not coming up. Don't have it. It's not
in our record.
>> So, the the just the website's wrong.
>> What What actual kind of car is it?
>> It is a Prius Nightshade.
>> Is it white?
>> It's it's Karachi.
>> That's the yellow. We do not have that.
I think that's a new one.
>> It is. Yeah. It says it's it's in the
build phase.
>> Yeah, we don't have it yet. Um I can
take your name and number and when we
get it in, I can give you a call or if
we can locate one when when they send
them out.
>> Okay. Yeah, I know a lot of these
Toyotas they do deposits before they get
there. So, uh if that's not something
you do, I get it. Um you know,
>> well, you want to give me your name and
number and I'll just hang on to it and
then when we get something in, I'll call
you.
>> No, don't worry. This car is not going
to arrive till November. I'm hoping to
put a deposit on one before it arrives.
So, um, if you guys can't do that, no
big deal.
>> Okay. Well, hang on one second. Let me
just double check. All right.
>> Okay. Sounds good. It It's really sad
when I'm having to navigate the
conversation. Like, this is like part of
the problem I have, right? She's nice,
but like I'm navigating the
conversation. I'm the one that is like
saying maybe I can put a deposit on it
rather than just like letting the deal
fall apart. Um, because most people,
most consumers would be like, "Oh, it's
not available. I guess have a nice day.
Bye." Like like that would be it. Like
I'm trying to get the deal.
>> Hello.
>> Hi. Yes. Are you local?
>> Uh I'm in Maryland. So I mean like I
mean it's kind of local cuz you guys are
on the border.
>> Okay. Me too. So my manager just told me
that basically um if you want to come
in, we can Do you have a trade that
you'd be trading it in for?
>> No, I don't have a trade. But um you you
the car is not there, you said, right?
>> No, not yet.
>> So So just help me understand why why
would I come in?
>> Why? Oh, because we like to do like all
the paperwork first and then just have
it reserved. So when it comes in, you
don't have to do all that. We could just
call you.
>> So you guys would do all the paperwork
first?
>> Yeah, we just want to take care of all
the details before we take it out of the
market.
>> And you can't do that over the phone?
>> No, you would have to come in.
>> Well, who where does he live?
>> He lives well on the line.
>> Well, um
>> Okay, that's I guess odd.
>> He said I'm sorry, my manager's right
here. He's
>> You want to just transfer him to me?
>> Sure.
>> All right. I'm going to transfer you to
the manager. I'm kind of new, so I'm
learning all of this, but he's he's
answering and I'm trying to talk to you,
too, so he can tell you exactly what it
is. So, did you hang on one moment? All
right. Thank you.
>> Hello, this is Ryan.
>> Hi, Ryan. It's Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. How are you?
>> I'm living a dream.
>> Nothing better, right?
>> Yeah.
>> Um calling about the uh Karachi Prius
that we have coming in.
>> That's it. Cool. So, I understand that
you'd kind of like to reserve it for
yourself.
>> Yeah. I mean, I'm just curious like what
your guys' out the door numbers are and
uh if it makes sense, I'm willing to
reserve it. Uh if not, no big deal.
>> Okay, that's perfectly fine. Are you
going to be trading a vehicle in?
>> Nope. No trade?
>> Nope. Okay. Is this going to be
registered Pennsylvania, Maryland?
>> Maryland.
>> In Maryland. Okay. And is this going to
be a cash or finance deal?
>> Uh I'm open to cash. Open to finance.
>> Okay. I only ask because uh there is a
lean fee associated. It's it's $20 in
Maryland, but I just want to make sure
I'm giving you accurate numbers before
for whatever I send you. So, that's why
I ask. It's
>> okay.
>> Completely up to you. How would you like
to pay for the vehicle? So, you like
area or you kind of further into the
state?
>> Yeah. I mean, I'm in uh
>> Okay, cool. I worked in all the time and
all of our uh our phone calls, our
outbound calls are it would come up as a
number. So, it's kind of funny. So, we
don't have any uh additional dealer
markup on these vehicles. They don't
build a whole lot in this color. So,
just kind of rough numbers, 6 12% for
Maryland and then tag, title,
registration, dock fee. Bottom line,
looks like it's going to be around 41
19675.
>> Okay. And do you guys have And just to
make sure, is that just all taxes and
then doc fee? There's no ads or dealer
ads or anything crazy?
>> Nope. No. No dealer add-ons? No. No prep
fees? No, nothing like that. It's just
the car, your your sales tax, tag,
title, registration, and uh 477 doc fee
in Pennsylvania as opposed to that. I
think it's like 800 bucks in Maryland
now.
>> Okay. Uh yeah, I mean, well, I'm super
interested in the car. Uh I don't want
to pay MSRP on it. I get that's where
you're at with it, but uh I do have an
offer for 2K off. I was trying to get to
3K off is where I was trying to be, but
yeah, that's kind of where I'm at with
the car.
>> Okay. Well, I can appreciate that. I can
I can tell you 3,000 probably won't
happen with anybody, but I I'm flexible.
You know, I ultimately I'd like to sell
a car. So, I'd be willing to do the
2,000 if you'd like to reserve this one
if
>> you guys do 35724.
>> Yeah. So, it' be Yep. 35724, which gets
you to a bottom line of 39066 and.75.
>> All right. I appreciate that. Um I do
want to try to get to this 3K. So, let
me do this. Let me look around. If I
can't find anybody to give me the 3K
like you're saying, then I'll come and
call you right back.
>> All right, Tommy, you can just ask for
me directly. My name's Ryan. I'm one of
the sales managers here and uh I'll do
what I can to help. Okay.
>> Hey, I appreciate it, man.
>> Thanks, Tommy.
>> All right, bye. So, like a lot of people
always ask Tommy, how do you know when
it's a good deal? We have a database
that we have here delivered um that goes
through and I'm going to go through the
deals that I've done on Priuses, just so
you know. 3.8K off, 3K off, 4K off, 4K
off, 5.5K off. That was off of Prime
though, so I'm going to put that on.
4.2K off, 3K off, 3K off, 3K off, 3K
off, 4K off, 4.5K off. So, the reason
why we're going with 3,000 on this
number comes down to the color and the
availability. Uh, a lot of these, the
higher discounts are going to be
frontwheel drive versions. Uh, the
bigger discounts, uh, the smaller
discounts are going to be normally
all-wheel drive versions.
>> Thank you for calling. Like,
>> Judy, may I help you?
>> Hello, Judy. This is Tommy. Uh, are you
a new car sales?
>> I am.
>> Love it. Hey, I just want to see if you
guys have a car available.
>> Okay,
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Hold on one second.
>> You're good.
>> Okay, go ahead. Stock number.
>> Stock number 24073.
>> I do have that. When do you want to come
in and take a look at it?
>> You know what? Even easier. I've already
driven it. Already know I love it. Want
more of it? Really? Just trying to get
to the right deal and if I can do that,
I'll buy it right now.
>> Our deal is you can pay MSRP at 37724.
>> That's that that's that's not much of a
deal.
>> Okay. Are you titling it locally
>> in Maryland? Yeah.
>> Yep. We're at MSRP.
>> Okay. I mean, Maryland is really close
to you. It's not like you're crazy.
>> Okay.
>> Cool.
>> Are you Are you interested?
>> I've just never MSRP. You're going
aggressive at Holy moly. Sheesh. Sheesh.
I didn't real Again, that's um No, I
wouldn't be interested at MSRP, but if
that's how you want to talk to me, then
I will just hang up the phone. I
appreciate your time.
>> Sorry. Have a good day.
So, if you don't want to deal with this
time, energy, and anxiety it takes to
buy a car, just talk to people that want
to speak to you like that. Um, flat fee
of a thousand bucks. I handle
everything. Thank you. Uh, what was her
name? I don't know her name, but thank
you for the free advertisement.
>> Thank you for calling. Scott, speaking.
How may I help you?
>> Hey, uh, I just want to see if you guys
have a car available. Sorry, I lost my
words.
>> Of course. No problem. And what vehicle
were you taking a look at? Oh, I have a
stock number available.
>> Oh, okay. That's perfect.
>> Let me know when you're ready for it.
>> Uh, yep. I'm ready.
>> Uh, it's T as in Toyota 3032548.
>> Mhm. All right. Give me one second while
I look this up here. And may I ask your
name?
>> My name's Tommy.
>> Perfect, Tommy. Thank you. Give me one
second. Um, and this is a new vehicle,
correct?
>> Yeah.
>> Perfect. All right, Tommy, do you mind
holding just one quick second? I'm
having some trouble putting that up
here.
>> You're good. Take a confirm that all
day.
>> Thank you. Thank you.
>> No problem.
>> All right.
>> Like, it doesn't matter. Even if you
think it's a crazy thing, you can be
nicer about it, right?
>> Even if she knew I was live, right?
Let's say she knew I was live. It's the
worst thing you can do. If you are live,
you exactly what the first person did.
Oh my god, I'm a big fan. Or don't even
say I'm a big fan. Hey, yeah, I know
your content. That's great. You know, we
can't do a deal on it. I appreciate it.
You're great. You're awesome. I love
what you're doing.
>> Hey, can you hear me?
>> I can hear you. Can you hear me?
>> Yep, I can hear you. Yeah. So, I was
able to pull this vehicle up here and it
looks like it is available and it is on
the way to us expected the first the
last two weeks of October.
>> Awesome. Love it. Well, this is the car
I want. I've already driven one. Already
know I love it. Love the color. The
cross looks sick. Really just trying to
get the best pricing. Um really trying
to get to a certain number. If I do it,
I'll put a deposit and buy it today.
>> Okay, sounds good. Yeah, I can send that
over to you. Is there a good email I can
reach you?
>> You know, I don't use email, but you can
text it to me. That'd be great. Oh, of
course I can do that, too. And is this a
good number to text it to you?
>> This is the best number to text it to.
>> Okay, perfect. And what is your last
name, Tommy?
>> Last name is Makula. M I K U L A.
>> U L A. Okay. And what is your zip code?
>> My zip code is going to be Are you ready
for
>> Okay, perfect. So, I'll send that over.
Let me know your thoughts and then we
can discuss further options.
>> Okay, I love it. Thank you so much.
>> You're very welcome. Have a great one.
>> You too. Bye. So, I just want to get
into this. I'm not mad that the
dealership wouldn't give a discount.
We've been on calls today, right? Like
you can listen to this whole stream and
you can see the calls where somebody
said I can't do a discount. That's cool.
Like you're allowed to say no to a
discount. It's not hard. Hey, you know
what, dude? These Priuses, we only get a
few of them. We will sell it at MSRP. I
feel confident you probably, if you look
hard enough, you'll find somebody that's
want to give a discount. Unfortunately,
that's just not our dealership. I
appreciate you calling us and you know,
if something changes, let me know. But
we're going to be pretty firm at MSRP.
That's it, right? Like that's it. Like
super simple, super easy. Not the deal
is MSRP. Yeah. No. Bye. Peace.
>> Carlos speaking. How can I help you?
>> Carlos, it's Tommy. How's it going?
>> Hey, how you doing?
>> Hey, I'm doing well. Uh, I wanted to see
if you guys have a car available.
>> Okay, sure. Uh, what vehicle you looking
for?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Okay. Uh, give me one second. Let me
just pull up my uh inventory.
>> No, you're good. Take your time.
>> You mind sharing the stock number with
me in the meantime?
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah. Stock number is T is
in tango 3031446.
>> Okay. This is a new vehicle or a used
vehicle.
>> Uh this would be a brand new car.
>> Okay. It's for the Prius Nightshade, the
the new color that we just received.
>> Uh yes, the Karashi yellow. Yep. That's
it.
>> Yep. That's available right now. It is
in the showroom.
>> Okay, awesome. Well, I love it. Uh I've
already driven one. Already know I love
it. Want more of it? Been looking around
trying to get to a certain number on a
price. If we can get there, I'm willing
to buy it today.
>> Okay, let me let me get your
information. I'm going put it down in
our system and I'm going transfer this
over to my manager so we can get you an
exact number.
>> I love it.
>> Your first name again?
>> My first name is Tommy.
>> Last name,
>> Makula. M I K U L A.
>> And your phone number is the number
you're calling me from.
>> That is correct.
>> Okay. Your zip code, please.
>> Yeah, zip code is
making your profile right now and add
the car you're interested in and then I
can get you a worksheet showing you I
mean saying all the numbers and whatnot.
>> Okay, that'd be great. I appreciate it.
Okay. Okay. Give me one second. I'll be
right back. I'm going go see if I can
get those numbers for you.
>> Perfect. Sounds good.
>> You guys hear me say the same things
every single time, which I've already
driven it. Know I love it. Want more of
it. Looking for numbers. The reason
being is that a dealership's number one
goal when you're calling them is not to
sell you a car. They don't want to sell
you a car. Their number one goal is to
get you in the store. Like that's their
goal. They want to get you in the store.
And one of the easiest ways to get you
in the store if you say, "Oh, I haven't
driven that color or I haven't seen that
color." Is, "Hey, well, I don't want to
put numbers on a car that you don't
know, you don't love, and you don't want
more of it. So, let's get you. It's an
objection that I know is coming, and
every salesperson BDC is trained to get
them in it." So, if I can say, "I've
already driven one. I already know I
love it. Want more of it." There's no
way to overcome that. There's no way to
say, "Oh, well, you should drive ours
because ours drives different." So,
that's why I say that every single time.
It eliminates that objection. So, I can
get right to pricing.
>> Hey, Tommy, thank you for your patience.
>> Um, I have the numbers now. Uh, if I'm
I'mma send it to you through text so you
can have a better look at it rather than
me just explaining everything.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh, over the phone. Give me one second.
Let me just get your number in my
system.
>> Perfect. That'd be great.
>> It's sent now. It might take a couple
seconds to go through.
>> I'm waiting for it. I got an image. I'm
looking at set image. Okay. Um, boom.
Boom. Okay. So, you guys are selling the
car for 38213.
Tax fees, all the fun stuff. Brings me
up to 42 349. So, you guys are just
selling it at TSRP.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. I was I was hoping to do a little
bit better than that.
>> Well, what what did you have in mind?
>> Yeah. So, I already have a deal for
$2,000 off. I told that last dealership
and I actually have two for $2,000 off.
Uh, I told the the both dealerships I'm
trying to be a $3,000 off. So, I get
$3,000 off, I try to buy the car. I I
will buy that car and if not, I'll just
go take the $2,000 off that I have at
the other dealership, but I'm trying to
get 3,000.
>> Okay. Um, just give me one second. I'm
going to see what we what we can work
with.
>> Sure.
>> A few moments later.
>> Hey, Tom, you still there?
>> I am. Hello.
>> I'm here. Hello.
>> Oh, okay. Um, I'm going to transfer you
to my manager now. He uh wants to have a
word just to explain some things.
>> Sure. Yeah, please have a word. Okay.
One second.
>> Good afternoon.
>> Hey.
>> Hey. Nice to meet you.
>> Hey, how you doing, Tommy?
>> I'm doing well. Doing well.
>> Yeah. My name is Lanni. I run the store
here to I want to thank you for reaching
out to us, man. What What can I do?
>> Uh, like I said, I'm trying to buy a
car. Um, I've been looking around for
it. I'm in Maryland just trying to rock
and roll this. Have a number in my mind.
If I can get there, I'll buy it today.
If not, I'll buy another one.
>> What number do you have in mind?
>> I'm trying to be at three grand off.
>> We can be at three grand off. We can be
at three grand off. There's a It's not a
It's not a lot of uh this vehicle in the
country.
>> I get that. But I have two grand off in
Maryland already. So, I mean, I already
have some deals for two grand off. So,
you you guys might not be able to do it,
but Yeah. I mean, I would have three
better than that.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Like three grand in my head
that if I get it,
>> there's only if somebody gave you 2,000
off, buy it. And I'm being very honest
with you, there's only four right now in
the all Maryland, DC, Virginia,
Delaware, uh, Pennsylvania. There's only
four right now on ground. So, if
somebody gave you 2,000 off by better do
than what I would give, and I'll be very
honest with you, sir.
>> I appreciate the advice. Life advice is
good, but uh, yeah. I mean, I'm looking
to do better than 2K. I mean, that's the
goal, right? But I already have 2K, so I
wouldn't take worse than that, but I got
a few offers at 2K. 2K doesn't seem
unreasonable. Can you do 2500? I'm, you
know, I'm thinking outside the box.
>> No, I I would only I'll do a thousand on
them. That's my best.
>> Yeah, I appreciate that. I really do.
But, um, I wouldn't take a $1,000 less.
I don't like you that much.
>> That's fine. That's fine. Yeah, that
that's that's the best we do.
>> Okay. Well, I'm looking to like I said,
I'm putting deposit on one here probably
in the next hour or so. So, if you guys
change your mind, let me know.
Otherwise, I'll rock and roll. I'll do
something else.
>> No problem, sir. No problem. Thank you
for reaching out to us, sir.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> All right. Bye-bye.
>> All right. Bye.
>> I'm going to call this person back. I
missed this phone call. If you guys have
it, make sure you guys like, like,
follow, subscribe.
>> Good evening,
>> uh, I missed a call from you. I'm so
sorry.
>> Um, I spoke to you already.
>> Yeah, I missed a call from you at 6:15,
so you called me a little bit later. No,
no, I did not, sir.
>> My phone doesn't lie, but I I guess
that's totally cool. I must have been It
must have been the win.
>> Maybe Maybe it was my saleserson that
that called you back, but I promise I I
didn't call you.
>> Okay, no problem. My phone must have
>> What happened was I had called before,
it went to voicemail, then I called
again, then you answered, so I don't
know which which one.
>> Okay, no problem. I was just calling
back. Thank you.
>> Okay, awesome. Sounds good.
>> All right. All right.
>> Bye.
>> Thank you guys so much. I appreciate
each and every one of you. If you guys
want to hire me, link is in the bio. I
charge a flat fee of a,000 bucks. I
handle everything for you. Price of car,
trade, add-ons, accessories, I charge a
flat fee of a,000 bucks. I handle
everything. Bada boom, bada bing. Thank
you guys so much for the support.
[Music]