Hopefully hopefully I didn't say
anything to offend you. I'm just trying
to buy a car. You got me all excited
there for a minute, Karen. I got I was
ready to come run out to your dealership
and sign it right now.
>> So, for all pricing, I do need you to
come into the dealership. Is that a
possibility?
>> Uh, ideally not. No.
>> And can I ask why not?
>> Uh, you know, I have a I have a fear of
the public. I'm scared to be inside of
public.
>> And what's the pricing we're hoping to
accomplish on the vehicle?
>> Just an easy 10% off.
>> I'm not going to be there,
unfortunately.
>> So, you're saying that if I keep going
around, I won't find anybody give me 10%
off?
>> No. Nobody's going to discount a 2026
Honda Odyssey $5,000.
>> All right. I feel like this is a
challenge. Challenge accepted. Kyle,
sorry. I got I got a I got a voicemail.
It's calling me a little b. So, I was
just uh just wanted to see if you wanted
to talk to me or not.
>> I apologize. I let my emotions get a
little bit of the better of me. Not who
I am. Yeah. I I just wanted to
apologize.
>> That is not who I am.
>> This would be the craziest turnaround
that I've ever seen. The redemption arc
of a lifetime. So, we're going to do is
Honda Odyssey Touring. So, this person
wants a Honda Odyssey Touring, ideally a
2026. They want the Touring Gray on
Gray. There's 78 of these Odysseies in
the country. They live in the great
state of New York 2026. Gray on gray.
So, we're going for 11% off. Let's just
go. We're just going for 11% off. That's
what we're going to do today. Most live
>> sales. This is Karen. How can I help
you? Hey sales Karen, this is Tommy
buying. I just want to see if you guys
have a car available.
>> What is it?
>> I have a stock number whenever you're
ready.
>> Sure.
>> T is in Tom. B is in Brady. 000175.
>> And is it a new or a pre-owned vehicle?
>> It's a brand new one.
>> Okay, hang on one second.
>> Sure. She was so happy when that phone
call started.
>> An Odyssey Touring.
>> That's it.
>> Okay, hang on one second. Let me just
see.
>> I'll hang on all day here. Okay, hang
on. That vehicle is currently here and
showing available.
>> Awesome. I'm so excited. I love it. Uh,
hey, so I'm super interested in this
car. I've already driven one, fell in
love with it. It's awesome. It's great.
Fits all the family needs. Really just
trying to get some numbers. And I heard
there was nobody better to call but
Karen.
>> Okay. How can I help you? Are you
looking at cash or financing or leasing?
>> I'm open to cash. Open to financing.
Whatever makes the the most sense for
you guys.
>> And where's the vehicle going to be
registered?
>> Oh, in New York.
>> Okay.
>> I know the answer. Okay. Are you trading
in a vehicle?
>> I'm not trading in. Not this time.
>> Okay.
>> We're a little car accident. So,
>> oh, sorry to hear about that. Is
everybody okay?
>> Everybody's great. Thanks for asking.
>> Hang on one second. Let me just see what
I can do on that for you. Hold on.
>> Of course. I just wanted to see if she
was going to be sympathetic. I Nobody
was in an accident, but I did want to
see if she was going to be sympathetic.
I wanted to see if she I do think she
knows who I am and she's not happy I'm
calling her. That's that's that's my
only guess because the way I said like,
"Oh, it was an accident." She's like,
"Ah,
>> okay." So, on that particular vehicle, I
can do 47445.
>> $4,700 off. Oh my gosh, Karen, you
really are the winner. Wow, that's
great. So, $4,700 off the 48945.
>> Nope, I can do $1,500 off, which would
bring the the number to 47445.
>> Oh, you can only do 50 15. Oh, you got
me all excited there for a minute,
Karen. I got I was ready to come run out
to your dealership and sign it right
now.
>> You should be running out to the
dealership at 1500 off. Oh, I'm not as
excited for $1,500. I was I was hoping
to be closer to that $4,700 off than the
$1,500 off.
>> No. No, it's not.
>> Okay. Hopefully hopefully I didn't say
anything to offend you. I'm just trying
to buy a car.
>> I know I can do it for $47445.
That's
>> okay. Well, I I don't want to waste any
more of your time, Karen. I bet you have
a lot of other calls, so uh I'm hoping
to do a little bit better than that. If
you uh can do a little bit better than
that, you can let me know.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> Okay. Bye.
>> Thank you. Bye-bye.
in Honda sales. Adrian speaking. How can
I help you?
>> Hey Adrian, I just want to see if you
guys have a car available.
>> What car are you looking for?
>> Uh, I have a stock number if that helps
you.
>> Is it brand new or pre-owned?
>> It is brand new.
>> Okay. What stock number is it?
>> Stock number is 56216.
>> All right. You're looking at a 26 Honda
Odyssey touring.
>> 26 Honda Odyssey Tour. And you got it.
How'd you know that?
>> Yeah. The car is here. It is car
>> is here. I love it. Awesome. I already
driven one. Fell in love with it. Uh,
really just trying to get the best
numbers and I've heard there's nobody
better to call but you guys. Really just
trying to get the best pricing and I've
heard you guys are like the king dogs.
Hey, I'm I'm been waiting for this phone
call. I'm so excited to hear what the
best dealership in that side of the
Mississippi has.
>> Okay. Typically, we don't give out
numbers over the phone. We like to do
all that in the showroom. Uh, have you
spoken to any other dealerships
regarding pricing? Have you gotten
anything?
>> I mean, I've I've talked to like one or
two different dealerships, but nothing
crazy. Nothing serious. I'm not like in
a serious dealership relationship yet if
that's what you're asking me.
>> Okay.
>> I'm in a serious relationship. I am
engaged, but like dealership
relationship, I feel like it's a little
different. You know, I haven't
committed. I haven't said yes to the
dress, you know, any of that stuff.
>> Congratulations first off. And second, I
was just wondering to see if you gotten
any offers cuz while we don't we don't
typically discuss pricing over the
phone. If you have any written offers
from other dealerships, we would be more
than happy to try and beat it.
>> Oh, so if I say yes to Oh, is that the
secret? Oh, yes. Yes. I've talked to
other num dealerships and I've gotten
numbers in writing. Wink. You would need
to bring it in. We'd have to take a look
at it first.
>> Okay. What's What's the What? Can you
give me the passcode to get the numbers
over the phone, please?
>> I can get you over to a salesperson.
They might be able to work something out
for you in that regard.
>> I love it. Put Put me through your
sales, Captain.
>> Gotcha. All right. Can I get a first and
last name, please?
>> First name Tommy, last name, Mula.
>> Where are you calling from, Tommy?
>> I'm calling from Farmingdale.
>> That's in New Jersey, correct?
>> New York.
>> New York. Okay. All right. Good. So, I'm
going to put you in a brief hold. Get a
hold of a salesperson and see where they
can go from there. Yeah. One sounds
good.
>> His name is Kyle. He'll be helping you
out. Give me one moment.
>> Nice. I love Kyle. Sounds great.
>> All right. Give me one moment.
>> Meanwhile,
>> this Kyle
>> Kyle. Oh my goodness. You are welcome.
Loudly in change. That's good. Sorry.
Your speaker My speaker almost blew up.
>> I apologize. How can I
>> No, you did. It was all me. Has my
phone. Uh, hey. Uh, I was looking at a
car and I was told that uh Kyle had the
keys to the kingdom and I had to talk to
you.
>> And what are we looking for? An Odyssey
Touring.
>> Odyssey Touring. You got it. Gray on
gray.
>> Awesome. And when can we set up to meet
each other?
>> Uh the second we agree to numbers.
>> So for all pricing, I do need you to
come into the dealership. Is that a
possibility?
>> Uh ideally not. No.
>> And can I ask why not?
>> Uh you know I have a I have a fear of
the public. I'm scared to be inside of
public.
>> Okay. Well, I mean I wouldn't need you
here in public to sign all the paperwork
cuz
>> Oh yeah, that's fine. I can sign. I can
go in there and sign, but
>> And what's the pricing we're hoping to
accomplish on the vehicle?
>> Just just an easy 10% off. I'm not going
to be there, unfortunately.
>> Okay. Can you do anything?
>> I won't be at 10% off. Do you have
another offer you would like for me to
present to my boss?
>> 9.5% off.
>> No, I won't be at 9.5% off.
>> Again, I haven't really I haven't gotten
a serious relationship with the
dealership yet, as I told the last
person. And then he told me to call you
and Kyle could hopefully get me taken
care of. So, yeah. I don't like that.
You know, I'm super simple. I don't want
to play the back. That's where I want to
be. If you guys don't want to do that,
but you can do 7% off and cool. want to
hear it, but I'm not going to keep just
giving you numbers until eventually you
say yes. That then mean there's a number
that you guys will do.
>> And what's your zip code?
>> Yeah.
>> And can I ask why you're calling me from
that distance?
>> I mean, can I not call you? It's not
that far.
>> I mean, you're shopping very far outside
of your your area. We've got to be
looking for something here. If you're
asking for 10% off, I'm not going to be
at 10% off. What are the dealerships
that are in your area of Farmingdale,
New York, showing you in terms of a sale
price?
>> They are. I have one deal at $1,500 off
and one at $2250 off. You're down to
business, Kyle. I like it. I'll put my
serious face on for a minute.
>> Absolutely. I mean, based on those
numbers, where are we hoping to land?
Again, you're hoping open to land. So
>> So you have somebody giving you 1,500
off and another one giving you how much
off?
>> 2250 off.
>> 2250. And if I can give you 2500 off, is
that enough?
>> I was really hoping to be at 10%.
>> I'm not Again, I'm not going to be at
10%.
>> 25%'s like 5%. I'm I'm looking to do
better than 5%. Yeah, I'm just not going
to be there unfortunately. In your area
is about $1,100 off the car.
>> That's why I'm looking at your area, not
my area.
>> Correct.
>> Yeah. Why would my market off your
market? That's why I'm calling in your
market.
>> Correct. But with with the distance
between me and you, if I'm going to take
a shorter deal on my car, it's going to
be somebody that I'm going to have come
back to my service department at, you
know, be a word of mouth, more business,
full picture type thing. You know, I can
get you a good deal on I can get you a
good deal on the car. Asking for 6% or
or more than, you know, more than that
from this
>> bet. My word of mouth and referral means
a lot. And if I told people about you
guys, I bet there's thousands of people
that would listen to me.
>> Okay. Again, what is the all-in price
that we are hoping to accomplish on this
vehicle?
>> Let's I I'll calm it down a little bit.
I'll go 9% off.
>> I'm not there.
>> Well, you just told me. I told you. I
have I have I have friends. I can refer
friends.
>> I got I got I got thousands of friends.
>> Is there another number that that makes
this make financial sense for you?
>> 8.5%.
>> Not going to be there either. Again, if
I'm able to get my ball 25% off,
>> you're asking me to throw the number
out. So, I'm giving you like number like
I'm not going to just go I'll take 2200
out. Like you already have 2250 off.
>> I mean, but I'm asking for a realistic
number based on what your your research
is. If you have your your local
dealerships are giving you 1,100 and
2250 calling me in the middle of New
Jersey, why would I take 10% 9% 8 8 1.5%
off a vehicle? Those are the deals that
people that are right next to you would
be taking, not calling further away.
>> So, you're saying that if I keep going
around, I won't find anybody give me 10%
off.
>> No, nobody's going to discount a 2026
Honda Odyssey $5,000. There's not that
much of wiggle room unless they hit you
for a ton of fees to bring your your out
the door to the same. No, deal does not
exist at the moment.
>> Well, I feel confident I I'll find
something at least at 8% off if not 10%.
>> Okay.
>> All right. I feel like this is a
challenge. Challenge accepted, Kyle.
>> Okay. Let me know. I'm going to check in
in a couple days. See how you're doing
cuz I don't think it's out there to be
honest with you cuz 8% Let's do the
math. 8% at 48908
would be 4 grand off the car. There's
just not. Unless they're adding an
additional fees and and packages and
everything on the side to make up for
set discounts, it's not going to be a
clean 4 grand off the car, tax, dock,
DMV, that type stuff.
>> I feel confident I will find somebody
that will do that for me, but it's an
aggressive deal. I get it. But yeah, I
will keep calling around until I find
one.
>> Absolutely. Best of luck. I'll check in
with you in a couple days. All right.
>> Hey, no problem. Have a great day.
>> You too. Bye-bye.
>> Bye.
>> Guys, you understand that not every deal
is going to have a deal. Like that's
okay if the guy doesn't want to do a
deal. But I got I got almost everything
I needed out of that conversation. We
went the guy wouldn't give me numbers at
all to starting to negotiate over the
phone. Remember he said we don't
negotiate over the phone. Like and then
all of a sudden now he's saying, "Okay,
what number will we do?" Then he started
negotiating. He said he would do 2500
off. If I would have said yes to 2500
off, he would have taken my deal. And if
you guys don't know that, that's an hour
and a half drive. He was acting like I
called him from a whole different
market.
>> Sales speaking. Hey, are you in sales?
>> Yes, we are.
>> Hey, I just want to see if you guys have
a car available.
>> Used or new?
>> Brand new.
>> Sure. What is the year and model?
>> It is a 2026 Honda Odyssey Touring.
>> I don't think we had the 26s in yet, but
we'll check.
>> I have a stock number if that helps. I
see some pictures of it.
>> Sure. Let's see. I do have a gray with a
gray, a silver with a gray.
>> Gray with a gray. A bada boom. Bada
bang. You found it. I love it.
>> There you go. That vehicle is here. When
would you like to come see it?
>> Well, the second we can agree to
numbers, I'll be right on down.
>> So, as far as I know, they're at MSRP on
that car.
>> Oh, I was hoping to get a little bit
better than MSRP.
>> You are welcome to come in and make that
offer, but right now they are at MSRP on
the 26s.
>> Can I just make the offer here? I'm very
comfortable.
>> No, that's all right. We're at 20. We're
at MSRP right here.
>> Okay. So, so just so I'm clear, you guys
you guys are willing to take offers or
you guys won't take offers and you guys
don't negotiate? That's fine if you guys
are one of those non-negotiation
dealerships.
>> No, they'll negotiate if you come in.
How much they will off? Because it's a
like I say, it's a 26 and Odysseies get
deposits on them before they come in.
So, I mean, it is here and uh it's
available to you. You're welcome to make
an offer. You know, it's a manager's
decision at that time, you know. So, do
remember though, we only charge tax
motor vehicle 175. So, if there is any
deals made over the phone, you're not
going to get clobbered when you do come
in. But it's 48 property inside, outside
or left or right. I just want a good
deal.
>> You want to come in and make an offer. I
wouldn't think if you're thinking of
making thousands off, that's not going
to happen. But they will, you know,
accept an offer, you know, when you come
in.
>> I had to do everything in the comfort of
my own home. Like I said, my chair is
very comfortable. Probably not as
comfortable as your guys' chair. So
>> So you do everything over the phone? I
mean, how would you I don't know, buy a
TV. I mean,
>> pants by.com.
>> Okay. Really? All right.
>> Have you never bought a TV online? Yeah.
No, I would do.
>> You want to buy I buy my groceries
online. I do. I mean, I buy basically
>> Well, I mean, a steak is a steak, but a
TV you want to find out things about.
You want to see it. I mean, I went and
bought my lawn mower. I went out and
looked at it and made sure I knew. I
mean, it's, you know,
>> Did you test drive the lawn mower first?
Did you uh like take it online?
>> You No, but you do look at it and see if
it's got all the things you need and
taught how to use it before I bought it.
Yeah. Yeah.
>> Well, I'm the type of person that does
all the research online. I watched I
watched Doug Demiro do a video on this
bad boy. So, you know, that's if Doug
says it's a good minivan and it got a
Doug score of 76, it's a good vehicle
for me, even though Doug is advertising
some crazy stuff nowadays. He's taking
some weird ad deals, but that's that's a
whole different conversation we can
have. But yeah, no, I I would want a
better deal than that.
>> Okay. You would have to come in and
negotiate that other people. Well, I
know other people will immediate over
the phone. That's why we try to be
transparent about it and this way when
you come in, you're not, you know,
bombarded with things that are not that
shouldn't happen. So, that's how we do
business. Okay,
>> no worries. I appreciate you being
transparent about that. And if your
managers were like, "Hey, I want to sell
this car and it's a slow Wednesday, they
can buy a car today."
>> Yeah, Odyssey's move very, very quickly.
>> You guys don't even need to sell it.
Somebody else will buy it.
>> We need to sell it, right? And just
somebody will buy it, right? That's the
question. There's no reason to lose
money on something where the next
person's going to buy it. You see what
I'm saying? I mean, it's business, you
know?
>> Yeah, I get it. Yeah. 43 of them. The
only one you guys have more is HRV. So,
>> I just said you have two Odysseies in
stock and you have 43. Yeah, two. I have
two.
>> You have two 26s. But how many 25s?
>> Oh, I don't think I any 25 touring left
to be honest with you.
>> And looking on your website, you guys
have 1 2 3 4 5 pictures. They all have
deposits. All the brokers buy them up
like you would not believe.
>> Wow, those brokers.
>> I have a red one.
>> You'll get a better deal if I was a
broker. Should I should I call someone
of those guys? Can I get one?
>> I don't think so. But they do leave
deposits.
>> You don't get the better dealer. They
just have a lot of people who want that
car.
>> So, you guys just sell you guys just
sell to those brokers.
>> No, that's not what I said. That's not
true. That's not what I said.
>> Be I don't want to waste any more of
your time, you know.
>> All right. No problem. This is uh if
your manager decides he doesn't want to
sell it to anybody other than a
customer, don't be afraid to have him
call me. You can have my number. I'm
going to buy a car by the end of the
day. So,
>> all righty. I will do. If he wants to
come off the MSP, I'll let you know.
>> Okay, sounds good. All right. Bye.
>> All 43 of these not only have pictures
on the website, but are have deposits on
them. Come on, bro.
>> Speaking.
>> I just want to see if you guys have a
car available.
>> Yes. Do you have a stock number? I do.
Whenever you're ready.
>> Yes.
>> Okay. It's H is in Honda, C is in
Chantilli, T is in Tom, B is in Brady,
312.
>> Okay, let me check that for you real
quick. Is it 2026 uh Odyssey XL?
>> Yeah, I have that available.
>> Awesome. Perfect. Well, I love it. Want
more of it. Already driven one. Really
just trying to get the best pricing. And
I've heard you guys are like the king
dogs. So, here I am.
>> Yes, we are.
>> That's exactly what I heard. I heard if
I want a good deal, I got to call you
guys. So, I skipped everybody else and I
just called right to you.
>> Absolutely. And plus, not everybody has
a pleasure to have a train 26 Odyssey's
on their lot.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh what would be the uh zip code for
your registration?
>> The zip code of my registration is
>> and your first and last name?
>> My first name Tommy, last name Makula.
>> Let me uh get these numbers together and
then I'll give you a call back on this
number. Is this number good phone number
to reach out back to you? Yeah, this is
the best number and I'm hoping for the
best number is the
>> give me like 5 to 10 minutes and I'll
give you a call back.
>> Okay,
>> just spoke over the phone.
>> Hey, I'm I'm been waiting for this phone
call. I'm so excited to hear what the
best dealership in that side of the
Mississippi has.
>> Okay, so I got the pricing here for you.
So, that's going to be the uh 48,945 is
the selling price for the vehicle plus
the dealer processing fee of 9.89, 89
sales tax of 4,390
and then your pool balance will be
54324.
>> The selling price is 48945.
>> 48,945.
>> Oh, you guys are just selling the car at
MSRP.
>> Yes, this is 2026 and then there is no
really inventory for that.
>> I guess the legend is not true, huh?
>> We just want a car which is high demand
and low.
>> The Odyssey is a low production car
>> for now 2026. If it was a 2025, I can do
different offer.
>> Okay. Do you have a 2025 Gray on Grey
Touring?
>> Can I actually uh call you back because
I have a customer here walked in?
>> Oh, sure. Yeah. Okay, sounds good.
>> Thank you for calling. This is Isaiah in
sales.
>> Hey, Isaiah and sales. This is Tommy. I
just want to see if you guys have a car
available.
>> Is it a used or a new car?
>> Brand new.
>> You have a stock number?
>> I do. It is Y as in yellow. H is in
hello. 260169.
>> The Odyssey Touring.
>> The Odyssey Touring. You got it.
>> Let me check. I got to go back and get
eyes on it. What is your name?
>> My name's Tommy.
>> Tommy. All right, let me go check.
>> Okay, Kyle's calling me back.
>> I guess I just see his voicemail. We're
going to call him back after I hear
that.
>> There.
>> I am.
>> So, that Odyssey is currently in route.
It'll be here by Saturday.
>> Awesome. Perfect. Well, I'm super
interested in it. Just trying to get out
some out the door numbers and hoping you
can help me out.
>> Or you you trying to pay cash?
>> I'm looking for cash or finance,
whatever makes the most sense. I'm going
to have to have my manager run those
numbers. Uh, what county do you live in?
>> Uh, I have a zip code.
>> Well, what what what part of New York do
you live in?
>> Uh, Farmingdale.
>> All right. What is your last name,
Tommy?
>> Last name Aula. M as in Mary. I K U L A.
>> All right. I'll tell you what, rather
than you sit on hold for 10 15 minutes
cuz I know they're working on some deals
right now. I can call you back with the
out the door price. Does that sound
good?
>> Sure. Um, yeah, absolutely. Sounds good.
>> All right. I'll call you here in a
little bit.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> Bye bye.
Do we call back Kyle that knows who I
am? Do you think it says Kyle in chat?
I'll call him back.
>> Can I help you?
>> Hey, can I speak to Kyle?
>> Sorry. Give me one sec. Let me put you
in a brief hold. Can I get your name?
>> Uh, my name's Tommy.
>> Gotcha. One sec. Hey, I checked with
Kyle's desk. He's with a customer right
now. I'm going to put you in voicemail
as soon as I can. Yeah.
>> Sorry. I got I got a I got a voicemail.
It's calling me a little So, I
was just uh just wanted to see if you
wanted to talk to me or not.
>> Strange.
>> Kind of crazy. I've got a voicemail like
that all day. So, just wanted to uh
figured he wanted to talk to me if he
was going to leave me that kind of
voicemail.
>> Okay. Uh would you like me to put you in
his voicemail?
>> No, I I don't leave voicemails like
that. Uh but I mean, if you can tell him
to call me back.
>> Oh, I'll pass that along to him.
>> Okay, sounds good. Um if not, I'll call
back in a few hours. I guess I'll talk
to the manager after.
>> All right, we'll do.
>> All right, bye.
>> Byebye.
>> Oh, yeah. No, no, he 100% did that. Just
so you guys know, I'm not making that
up.
>> Couldn't make it in the car business,
you little
>> Like, that's the voicemail he left. If
we if you guys are clear, u my my
company did 198 car deals last month. I
imagine that we sold more new cars than
his entire dealership did. Good job,
Kyle.
>> Mr. Tommy Mula, please.
>> This is him.
>> Hey, Tommy. This is Alex, the sales
manager here at you. I know you um
talked to my sales associate about a
2026 Honda Odyssey um in a touring
edition.
>> Yeah, absolutely.
>> Gotcha. Okay. Now, is this car for you
or for somebody else? I'm the one
helping out. But I mean, technically
it's for the lady in charge.
>> What does that mean?
>> The lady in charge. The one that tells
me what to do.
>> Okay. Okay. So, you're you're a broker.
Is that what it is?
>> I'm not a broker now. They're buying the
car. I'm just helping.
>> That sounds good. What do we got to do
to earn a deal for um for your client?
>> I'm trying to be at 10% off.
>> 10% off on a 2026 that just hit the
stores about a week ago.
>> I would take a 2025 if you have one.
Gray on Grey Odyssey Touring.
>> I don't have a gray on gray. You're
looking only for a touring. Is that
correct?
>> Correct. Gotcha. Yeah. I wish I wish I
had 10% off to to get there. That's
almost close to about what is it like
almost like $4,000 off price of a car.
4,800 off. I wish we could get there,
but still want to help you out. Where
are you going to be registering a car
at?
>> Uh New York.
>> Trading anything?
>> I know they have some offers from
Carvana. We can go through those and see
if it makes sense for you guys to buy
them or not.
>> Okay. Well, we're, you know, we work
with CarMax directly and we can try to
match it if we can. What kind of cars
are they?
>> MDX and a Sienna.
>> What kind of MDX is? What year is the
MDX?
>> I can get you all the information. I
don't have that right in front of me,
unfortunately. We can definitely work
both numbers together for her to get her
a deal, get her, you know, kind of
consolidate. I want to know if we can
put a deal together today and make a
deal happen. What have I got to do?
>> Well, I have $2,500 off already. So,
>> okay. So, where is that at?
>> Uh, that is at
>> Wow. Okay. How come you didn't guys pull
the trigger on that one yet?
>> I told you I'm trying to be at 10%. I'm
I'm a straight shooter.
>> 10% is pretty steep on that.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I've helped a few
people buy cars. Yeah.
>> Okay. I'm not going to BS you in any
way. That's where we are. So, in terms
of uh a price relief on that, you know,
you got $2500. I think it's a pretty
good deal. If you got $2,500 off the
price of the car, that's pretty solid.
That means that the other dealer is
probably making about about 1,400 bucks,
give or take. But, you know, I'm I'm in
the business of also selling cars and
trying to keep the lights on as well.
And uh but still give her an ultimate
experience. If if I can't reduce that
much on the price of my car, at least I
can work with her in terms of those
trades. Plus, I think isn't it with New
York or New Jersey if she's registering
she gets a little bit of a tax credit.
So, that can offset a few dollars there.
We could work that out and uh help her
out with the financing aspect of it as
well. So, if we could do that,
>> sure, in theory, but we're not even
close on the price. So, you know,
obviously, sure, you might not be making
any money. You might be losing a little
bit money on the Odyssey, but you can
make that money back on the trades.
>> Now, the question is, is she registering
the car in Virginia or in DC, Maryland?
Where where she's registering?
>> In New York.
>> Gotcha. Okay. So, the the pricing that I
give to her, is this going to be the
same kind of pricing that's going to go
to her or are you getting
>> Yeah, I'm not a broker. I'm not a
broker. As I said, you'll talk to her.
She's just she just doesn't want to deal
with it. So, she asked me to help and I
said I'd help. The numbers look right. I
give you all of her information. You
finish this deal up with her.
>> Okay. All right. So, if I get you $1,000
relief on this car and I have this car
in stock, this is a gray on gray touring
that just landed. Um, pulling up the
information right now. It landed 9 days
ago. Can we work a deal?
>> No. Okay. Okay. I mean, like I said,
we're we're like I said, I have 2500 on
it already. So, like, we'd have to at
least we we that that's like where the
bar is set at.
>> So, that's where the bar is at, but but
she hasn't pulled the trigger because
maybe the color doesn't exist there or
>> No, no, it's gray on gray. Like I said,
I told you what the number I'm trying to
be at. So, I'm telling you like that's
that's the bare minimum bar where we' be
it be I mean, obviously it'd be silly
for us to go down and go down to $1,000.
Like, why would I go down to a,000?
>> Okay. So, let me ask you this then.
Since you've got 2500 off of that, you
have something that corroborates that?
something that I got to take obviously
to upper management to to show and say,
you know what, I got another dealer
that's standing offer of 2500 off. Can
we match it, beat it, work something out
around that?
>> Sure. Which one do you want to see?
>> Well, obviously the lowest one that you
have, right? I mean, at the end of the
day, we're trying to achieve my am I
beating 1,700 or am I beating 2500? I'm
trying to
>> I'm just I'm just giving you a hard
time. I'm I'm just letting you know that
a lot of I have this is $1,000 off
doesn't you know that that's our lowest
offer of the day. So,
>> I want to earn your business and I want
to help the client. I'm sure you've been
in the business before. uh judging by,
you know, the the conversation we're
having. So, it's all good. I've ran a
two stores over in Northern California
and over here in the East Coast, so I
can definitely hang with that.
>> Yeah. I mean, I can I can text that over
to you. I can text it over to the number
that was texting me earlier and we can
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I think I think Saba,
my sales guy, sent that over to me. Uh I
sent you a text. I can see that. It's a
online text CRM text we got. So yeah, if
you don't mind sharing that worksheet
with me and if I can beat it, match it,
whatever, maybe work that deal out, your
client's happy, we can work something
out ourselves, we can make a deal, why
not, right?
>> I love it. Let's let's put it together.
>> I'll I'll wait to hear back from you
and, you know, I'll call you back. Just
send me that text and I'll put it
together right by the GM, make sure
everything's good and call you right
back.
>> Okay, sounds good. I will get that sound
right now.
>> Thanks for calling Honda Sales
Department. This is Alex. How can I help
you?
>> Hey, Alex, it's Tommy.
>> So, I I appreciate you sending me that
text over. So I noticed here anyway the
dock fee is going to be a little bit
lower than ours. Our doc fee is $9.89
but you know if matching at 2500 off the
sticker price of the car that puts my
out the door for your client at 51854
which is you know a little bit under the
51938 that you have there. I got a 2025
Odyssey in an EXL gray with black.
>> They really want a tour ring but I
appreciate it. Like I said, I really
want you to get that 10%, but this is
the best number we have so far. So, if
we can't beat this, then the deal will
be yours.
>> I want to earn your business. Like I
said,
>> I'm on a vengeance to get this deal done
today.
>> I'm sure you are. Well, let me know. I
want to make it happen. This is the
store here at Honda. Ranked top 10 in
the nation. We're going to do everything
we can to make that deal happen. So,
>> I appreciate it.
>> All right, man. You let me know.
>> Okay, sounds good. I'll let you know
here soon.
>> Thank you, sir. All right. Bye.
>> Bye.
[Music]
>> Kyle's calling me back.
>> This is Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. How are you?
>> Hey, how's it going?
>> Doing well. Listen, I just want to call
clear the air. Um, I apologize. I let my
emotions get a little bit of the better
of me. Not who I am. Yeah, I I just
wanted to apologize. That is not who I
am.
>> Well, I appreciate the apology, man. Um,
that's that's uh takes a big man to do
that. I do have $3,900 off. You want to
beat this deal so I can close this deal
with my client?
>> I wish I can't. You're just you're like
like you said just before, great points.
You're too far away. Is your client
located near me or are they out in New
York?
>> Close. I mean, they're 2 hours away from
you. I mean, they're way closer than
this deal.
>> Yeah. I just can't do it, unfortunately.
>> Invoice, man. Like, come on. Let's just
Let's imagine the story. You go from
call me a little to closing the
deal up. Dude, that'd be like the crazy
horror or the story of a lifetime.
>> Hold on. I think you're Do do your I
think your followers want my boss on the
phone.
>> No. Oh, dude. You don't need Dude, I All
I want to do is close this deal. You get
this deal done. We rock and roll. This I
have 10% off in Maryland. Free shipping.
It's just blue. He wants gray. I'd be if
we could do 4K off. That's two hours
away from my client. That makes sense.
It's grand and gray.
>> Let me run it up the food uh the food
chain. All right. I'll give you a call
right back.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Just give me a call
back. I'll wait and less.
>> Absolutely.
>> Okay. Bye.
>> Bye-bye.
>> All I care about is closing the deal.
That is what I care about. This would be
the craziest turnaround that I've ever
seen. The redemption arc of a lifetime.
Clearly, he's watching the live, guys.
So, that's where it was. He was watching
the live calling it a day because he
even said, "You made a good point right
there." So, that's fine. In reality, I'm
trying to make a quick car deal. Even
with all of the craziness me and Kyle
have gone through, Kyle has spent he
spent a total of 12 minutes on this car
deal. That's everything. So, even if
everybody's like, "Oh my god, that
that's not worth it." It's 12 minutes.
It's 12 minutes of phone call with me to
get this deal done. Wait, here we go.
How's it going, Kyle?
>> Hey, Tommy. How are you
>> doing? Well, my client also says he'll
bring the car for service cuz he comes
through New Jersey monthly. So,
>> awesome. All right. So, what I need is
at this moment I am going to have to let
you know I have not given permission to
record me. I'm going to ask you to give
me a call off of live to finalize and
talk about final figures.
>> Okay. Uh yeah, that's that is
>> You have a pen and paper to call my
direct line instead of the uh
>> Can I just mute mute everything? You can
verify I'm muting everything.
>> Uh sure.
>> Yeah, I'll just let me just mute. That's
easy.
>> Okay. Uh a little unconventional. Uh,
but you guys have to remember first off,
my job is always to get a deal for my
client, not to always make you guys
happy. So, first off, uh, everybody
needs to remove their Google review if
you haven't. Uh, dead serious. Go do
that. If I can I I don't condone that
behavior and if I can track that you're
leaving Google reviews while watching my
stream, I'll just ban you from the
stream. That's not what we do. So, boom.
Step two. The dealership is going to the
deal a deal that I need, but they've
specifically asked me not to say the
number. That is their prerogative. I can
understand why they don't want to say
the number, but I can tell you my client
and I are very happy with this deal. It
is a win. This is good. Client's deal is
done. It is above and beyond
expectation. I just can't They don't
want to give the exact number out.
That's And that's that's fair. That's
fair.
[Music]