Let's cut the cheese. Cut to the chase.
Do you know what kind of pricing you
would be? Like, let's just say it's
95,000 bucks. What kind of discount are
you guys doing on orders right now? You
know, I'm asking for the hard cheese,
the the, you know, the the cheddar
cheese. What What would be the dealer
discount?
>> Yeah. I mean, I'd love that. You know,
I'm not I'm the type of person that
needs to know what kind of cheese he is
before he you know, eats it. So, I'd
like to know what kind of cheese uh we
have and what the price of that cheese
is. There's some expensive cheese out
there and some people try to overpric
their cheese. It's insane, you know. So,
I mean, MSRP should be in the '9s. Rear
Entertainment because my kids do not
watch TV cuz that will brain rot their
mind. We are going to negotiate a car
deal. Yukon Denali Ultimate 2500 diesel.
That one kind of sounds fun. Denali
Ultimates are $100,000 cars. So, I'm
going to take on this deal. So, the
client is looking for a diesel, white
exterior, shale teak interior. She
doesn't want a front license plate,
wants a pano moon roof. Uh, she doesn't
want the no rear entertainment. And she
wants the exterior step lighting. I like
it.
>> This is Ian. How can I help you?
>> Hey, Ian. I just wanted to see if you
guys have a car available.
>> Yeah, go for it. Which one are you
looking for?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh, it is G as in Google. 404140.
>> The uh 25 Yukon Denali.
>> 25 Yukon Denali. You You took the words
right out of my mouth. just dropped some
off and I just came back in. So, I don't
know if that was one of them they had
dropped off or not, but let me check
really quick for you. Oh,
>> you're good.
>> So, it looks like it's at our pickup
pickup location in Georgia. It's not
quite here yet, but we should have it
anytime between now and it's estimating
kind of like the second week of
September, but that's estimate it.
They're they can arrive anytime between
now and then.
>> Awesome. I love it. Well, I'm super
interested in this one or, you know, be
open. I'm also even open to ordering
one, the 2026. I don't mind whatever
gets me, you know, the best deal and I
heard there's nobody better to call.
>> Where'd you hear that from?
>> Um the internet.
>> Oh, awesome. Yeah, definitely be happy
to to help you out either way. Uh we can
let me get if you don't mind, let me get
a little bit of information from you
just so I can kind of put you in here
and that way I can make myself a note
letting them know I talked to somebody.
What's a good phone number for you? The
best phone number for me would be the
one that I am calling off of, which is
My name is Tommy.
>> Tommy, what's your last name?
>> Makula. M I K U L A.
>> Gotcha. And you got a good email address
for in case I need to send you anything,
I could send it over to you.
>> I use email, you know. I'm just I'm I'm
old school, new school. Sounds cool.
>> Gotcha. Yeah. So, uh, are you
specifically looking for like a Denali?
Are you looking for like a just a Yukon
in general that's kind of like got some
features, extra features on it?
>> Uh, yeah. I'm looking for, like I said,
this is basically the perfect build. I
mean, I have a build in mind, which is,
you know, diesel, white exterior, shale
teak interior, no front license plate,
panoramic moon roof, no entertainment in
the back cuz I don't like my kids and
exterior.
>> Yeah. Okay, I got you.
>> I'm kidding. We do like the kids. They
just like iPads.
>> I've got four myself. So, they they get
the iPads. I think they forget about me
as a parent. I do have some that
similar, you know, it's kind of, you
know, kind of hit and miss. So, it's
always, you know, to get exactly what
you want, the best way is to order it
because that way you can get everything
you want and then you don't have to pay
for everything you don't want. You know,
I do have like a Yukon Elevation here
that's white. However, it doesn't have
the the shell interior. It It's got the
black interior, but it's a it's a
diesel, so it's kind of like a
trade-off. The Elevation that we got is
kind of packaged out almost like a
Yukon. It it does have it's an elevation
kind of on steroids. It has a lot of
extra options. It's got the the
panoramic sunroof, moon roof. It does
have the rear media system. It does have
the super cruise. It's got the heated
and ventilated front seats. It's got the
bucket seats in the middle, the max
trailering package, heads-up display,
stuff like that. So, it is packaged out
almost like a like a uh a Denali would
be, but it's an elevation trim that
that's been upfitted. However, if you
were looking specifically for that that
shell trim, you know, that that is
something this one that we have coming
in would have. Uh it would just be a
matter of till it got here and then you
know if you can kind of handle waiting
for a little bit till it gets here.
>> Yeah. No, I appreciate all that. I I'm
I'm such a patient person that uh I'm
willing to just order one if I need to.
You know, I appreciate the the the
loaded out elevation, but you know, I
couldn't be caught dead in an elevation.
I got I got at least a Yukon, you know.
>> Yeah. No, I got you. The easiest way to
kind of get an idea of, at least for me,
and and I'm sure if you ask different
sales people, everybody's different, is
to go on the GMC website and do like a
build-in price and you can kind of look
at the different options, different
packages that you can put in one. And
then at the very end of that, you
actually have an option to email it to
somebody. And if you'd like, I could
give you my email or, you know, I know
you said you don't like doing email a
lot, but you could send me one saying,
"Hey, this is exactly what I'm looking
for. I want to order it." and then I
could get a build sheet together for
you, send it over and just have you
>> know, sorry, continue.
>> No, I was gonna say and then that way we
can, you know, if you wanted to go the
order route, if you didn't want to go
the order route, you wanted to wait for
this one coming in because it would be
quicker for this one coming in obviously
than ordering it. We can definitely look
at that. Um then we'd start digging in
on, you know, confirming, you know, if
you had a trade or not and and going
through that the sales process of if you
had a trade, uh just getting it
appraised or or if you were just looking
to purchase, you know, just agreeing to
numbers and getting everything locked
down for you.
>> Okay. Yeah. Yeah. You know, now I
appreciate all of that. Right. But let's
you know, let's cut let's cut the
cheese. Cut to the chase. Do you know
what kind of pricing you would be? Like
let's just say it's 95,000 bucks. What
kind of discount are you guys doing on
orders right now? So, with ordering the
rebates that's on it would be the
rebates that's on it at delivery. Uh, so
that's one thing with with ordering it
that I couldn't tell you exactly just
because I don't know. So, if we order it
today and then it's 3 months from now
when it comes in, you know, you're
looking at December, it's possible GM's
doing some stuff for year rebates. I
don't know what they would have, but the
rebates that would be applied would be
the rebates that that would be available
at time of delivery versus rebates that
are now. Oh, I get I get the rebates are
what the rebates are. What I'm really
asking is that you know that that you
know I'm asking for the hard cheese, the
the you know the the cheddar cheese.
What what would be the dealer discount?
>> Yeah. So I would just have to you know
we want to be aggressive. We want to
earn everybody's business. You know we
we want to have that reputation of
people can come to us. And so I tell
everybody I don't know for sure what
kind of discount we can do. That would
be kind of up to my sales manager. I
would just kind of be the information
gather and take everything to them and
let them at it. And of course, we'd put
our best foot forward to see what we
could do to earn your business if that
was something you wanted to do.
>> Yeah. I mean, I'd love that. You know,
I'm not I'm the type of person that
needs to know what kind of cheese he is
before he, you know, eats it. So, I'd
like to know what kind of cheese uh we
have and what the price of that cheese
is. There's some expensive cheese out
there and some people try to overpric
their cheese. It's insane.
>> No, I completely understand. like we
want to earn your business and we want
to do everything that we can to earn
that and to do what's best for our
customers. I would just have to, you
know, come and see, you know, hey, what
works for them and what works for you
and finding that common ground to where
everybody's happy and want to make a
deal.
>> Yeah, I agree. I think we should all be
happy. This should be, you know, I'm
kumbaya type situation. Yeah, I I've
I've been in this business for a little
bit and you know, I've learned profit's
not a a bad word, but greed is and and
you know, I don't you know, we're not
greedy here and and you know, obviously
we're here to make a business and you're
here to make a a good So, it's just
making sure that everything works for
everybody and and you know, I I look at
my job as I work for you. So, I'm kind
of that middleman for you that goes to
my bosses and say, "Hey, this is what I
need to do in order to make this deal,
make this customer happy."
>> I I love it. Can you can you can you go
like make me some pizza? That'd be cool.
You said you work.
>> Yeah, I'm down. I had the early lunch,
so I'm starting to get hungry now. So,
as long as I don't like mushrooms, so as
long as we do anything without
mushrooms, I'm good to go.
>> I'm not a big fan of mushrooms either.
Now, we're on the same page. But Melo
Mushroom's good. Have you ever been
there? It's a good good little spot.
>> I haven't been there. I've had a pizza
picked up from there before, but I I
haven't ate it, so
>> Oh, okay. That's fair. That's fair. But
yeah, I mean depending on, you know,
which route you want to go and and which
route works best for you, whether it's
ordering it and getting it custom to
exactly how you want it or or if it's,
you know, us coming to an agreement on
the one that we have coming in in a
couple of weeks, you know, we definitely
would love an opportunity to earn your
business and do what it takes to to make
a deal for you.
>> Uh well, I'm definitely down to order
one um just to make sure we get the
perfect awesome great option, right?
>> Yeah. Uh, if you can just figure out
what kind of pricing you guys can do on
that, bada boom, bada bing, I would be
really excited.
>> Okay. I'm trying to think what would be
the best way to do it because again with
ordering, I just want to make sure that
we get it specifically the the way you
want to do it. I mean, if you had time
now, I can kind of go through the
options and the packages and we could
kind of do everything now. Or if you
wanted to, if you if you didn't have
time right now, like I said, I encourage
you go to the GMC website and you do a
build and price and then that would kind
of let you look at the packages, look at
each one specifically and what it offers
you. And then um we could actually email
that over, print that, bring I've had
people print out a paper and bring the
paper in. Um and then that way that
would let me dial in exactly what we
were looking for because we could be
different on the packages. Like just
kind of looking at it right now, like if
you got the technology package, that's
about $1,600. But then if you wanted uh
the all-w weather formats with the
interior protection package, that's
going to add 500 versus if you didn't do
that, you know, my pricing could be off.
So it'd be hard to to know exactly what
kind of price we'd be without knowing
what what features and what packages you
actually wanted specifically.
>> Yeah. Yeah. No, and I like I said, I can
I can build one. That's totally fine. Uh
and we could do that together. Really
what I'm trying to figure out is like
what kind of rough discount because
it'll be pretty pretty pretty decent. I
know I want the diesel. I know I want
the moon roof. I know I don't want the
rear entertainment, the exterior step
lighting, you know. So, I mean MSRP
should be in the '9s.
>> Yeah. Let me I'm just going to kind of
go through like a rough build on one and
just kind of give you a rough idea. Any
You said you were looking for the the
white was the type
>> the white the white with the diesel. You
got to have the diesel. I got to have
that diesel with the Shell Teak
interior.
>> Okay. And any special packages that
you're looking for? You looking for like
the Super Cruise with a hands-free
driving or anything?
>> The big thing for me is the panoramic
sunroof. That that's a big one thing.
The exterior step lighting.
>> Okay.
>> And then obviously I know there's like
the advanced tech package that comes
with the uh pan or with with basically
everything. That's that's not a we we're
go with that package.
>> Yeah. So, the advanced uh technology
package offers you a super cruise uh the
rear camera that does give you the rear
seat media. The advanced uh technology
package gives you that and it gives you
max trailering also. So, I don't know if
you're looking um to to let's just see
where you guys pricing would be if we
order one because obviously the discount
percentage would be the same. So, let's
go through and do that and go from
there.
>> Let's see here. So, if we do that and
then let me get the sunroof. So again,
and this is just kind of a rough build
without like diving into it too deeply.
It looks like, you know, for that you'd
be, let me just make sure I got the
diesel. We'd be about 87,000y
on on that MSRP. So that's before taxes
and everything. Do you live in North
Carolina?
>> I live in Tennessee.
>> Gotcha. Uh I think Tennessee, if I'm not
mistaken, I believe Tennessee 7% on
Sounds about right. I guess the big
thing is, yeah, I know the MSRP is, you
know, 87 88. What would be the selling
price?
>> If you would give me like a little bit,
I can call you back because I can kind
of take it to to Tucker, uh, who's my
sales manager. I could, it's possible
that we could even maybe even find one
at another dealership. I don't want to
ever promise anybody that. And we might
be able to trade and get it here. And I
could get him to say, "Hey, if we were
to order this for somebody, you know,
what kind of uh what kind of deal could
we make this customer?" Again, I I just
don't want to stick my foot in my mouth
and tell you, you know, overpromise you
something that I'm not able to do.
>> Got it. Cool. I'm all good talking with
Tucker. Tucker seems like a great guy.
I've never met a bad Tucker in my life.
So,
>> yeah. No, no, Tucker's really good. But
if it's something, you know, I can talk
to him and then I can get back to you
with, is it something that maybe, you
know, you want to do, you know, quickly,
like to, you know, try to put an order
in as quickly as possible, you know,
today or the next couple of days? I know
we're kind of toward the end of the day,
obviously.
>> Yeah. I mean, I would I would put in I
would put in a order today. I would I'm
I'm I'm ready to put a deposit. Whatever
it takes. As long as I can agree to the
price, I'm all for it.
>> Okay. Yeah. I just want to get with him.
Uh I hope that's okay. I just want to
get with him because like I said, I
don't want to tell you something that I
cannot do because that that's the worst
feeling in the world in sales is me
having to go back and be like, "Yeah,
you know what? Sorry, I can't do what I
said."
>> Yeah, that's that is the worst. gives me
an idea of what you're looking for and
and I can go to him and I can just say,
"Hey, Tucker, what kind of what kind of
deal can we look at? If somebody's
looking to place an order today for this
vehicle, what can we do for them?" And
then um I can get back with you and then
hopefully we can lock this down today
and get an order placed for you.
>> That'd be great. Yeah, let's get let's
get uh typical Tucker on it and uh see
if he can u you know, rock and roll.
>> Yeah, that that works. But do you have
any other questions for me or anything
that I might be able to answer for you?
>> You know what? I'm out of questions. I'm
questioned out. I appreciate it. So, if
you can just get me with Tucker or you
get me to Tucker, get the price and bada
boom, bada bing. Let's uh put an order
in on a car.
>> Yeah, man. I appreciate that. And again,
my name's Ian. So, uh I'll see what I
can do and and I'll give you a shout
back just as quickly as I can. Okay.
>> Okay. You know what? I'll be just
patiently by the phone.
>> All right. Thank you so much.
>> No problem. Bye.
>> Thank you for calling.
This is Victoria speaking. How can I
help you? Hey, Victoria. It's Tommy.
How's it going?
>> Good. How are you?
>> Hey, doing well. Doing well. I just
wanted to see I wanted to get uh I'm
looking on buying a 2026 GMC Yukon
Denali with the reserve package and
really was hoping that you can help me,
you know, bada boom, bada bing, get a
deal on it. Bada boom, bada bing. We'll
get an order in whatever it calls.
>> Yes, sir. Um well, I'd be happy to
assist you with that. Um so, we're
looking for the Yukon Denali. Um we're
just we don't want the XL. Correct.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I'm looking for Yukon Denali
with the diesel with the reserve
package.
>> Yes, sir. Um I'd be happy to assist you
with that. Now, I do want to ask um are
we going to be looking to possibly trade
anything in? Are we just looking to
purchase?
>> No trade in. Just just buying.
>> Absolutely. Um reason I was asking is we
do have our trade event that's going on
right now. So, if it was something you
were considering, I did want to make
sure I gave you that information for
that as well. But, if you will give me
just a moment, Tommy, I'm going to put
you on a brief hold. Let me reach out
with our sales manager over here and let
me verify that we do have one available
for you. If not, then we can definitely
look into helping you get one ordered.
>> Yeah, that's totally fine.
>> Perfect. I'm going to put you just on a
brief hold just in case we get
disconnected. I do see I have a good
number for you for 9.
>> Is that right?
>> You nailed it.
>> Oh, perfect. All right. And um tell me
what's your what's your last name?
>> Oh, last name Makula. M I K U L A.
>> Perfect. All right. Well, tell me, give
me just a moment.
>> No problem.
>> Meanwhile,
>> this is Bethany. How can I help you?
>> Hey Bethany, I was speaking to somebody
else. I totally forgot her name and I
was on hold waiting for somebody and now
I'm here.
>> Uhoh. Okay. Let me see who it was you
were speaking with. Give me just a
moment.
>> Maybe Victoria. Maybe.
>> Yes. Let me see if she if I can get her
back on the phone for you. Okay.
>> Yeah, that'd be great.
>> Thank you.
>> They just hung up on me. Nice. I love
when things just hang up.
>> It's Michael.
>> Hey, Michael. How's it going?
>> I'm doing good. How are you,
>> Michael? I'm I'm living a dream. I don't
know if it's a good one yet, but it's
still a dream. Um, hey, I just want to
see if you guys have a car available.
>> All right, hold on just a second.
>> I'll hold on 20 5 seconds for you.
>> All right, so cool. You got a stock
number?
>> You know what? I do have a stock number.
I'm ready when you are.
>> I'm ready.
>> Uh, it's M is in Monopoly 25804.
And this one's not a perfect option. So,
and it's hard to find. So, I am willing
to order one, too, if that if we can
agree to making a deal that makes sense.
Yeah, it looks like looks like this one
is still available. Let me just double
check one other area here because there
was a gentleman talking about putting
the deposit down with another
salesperson.
>> Yeah, I mean otherwise I'm totally good
to I'm totally good uh to just order
one, too. I'm an order I'm an order type
of guy. I like to custom build it to the
perfect spec.
>> Okay. Where are you calling from?
>> Uh I'm actually calling from Tennessee.
>> Okay. So, you're wanting a regular uh
Denali or you want XL?
>> I'm looking for Denali Reserve.
>> Denali Reserve. Okay. Just regular old
Denali Reserve with with a turbo diesel.
>> Yeah. Okay. With the 3.0.
>> You got to have the 3.0.
>> All right. One second here. Let me look
up this fan.
>> You're good. I got nowhere else to be.
It's not like I'm eating crab today, you
know. Are you a crab fan? I like crab.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Crab cakes are my favorite, though.
>> So, this one is actually not on the site
yet. It says it's bade. Uh, which means
it's ready. It's at the final stage of
being transported. So, it's ready for
the truck to pick it up.
>> Okay. Awesome. So, what's the ETA on
this one? Probably uh midepptember.
>> Midepptember. Okay. So, like ordering
one would only like take a month or two
longer.
>> No, I mean 3 to six months is what we're
telling people on order.
>> Three to six months. Holy moly. I heard
three months from the last person I
called. Six months. Whoa.
>> Well, we'd rather overshoot, you know.
>> Oh, I get it. I get it.
>> I had I had a guy order a Denali. Uh
wasn't supposed to be here till
September and it showed up uh Friday.
So, I'd rather a few weeks early. That's
awesome. I'd rather, you know,
underpromise and overd deliver than do
the opposite.
>> Okay. Yeah. I mean, I'm all for
underpromising, over and delivering.
Really? Really? Do you know what kind of
pricing you guys are doing on the orders
then?
>> I don't I don't do all that. I I've got
a sales manager that handles all that
for me.
>> Oh, awesome. Perfect. Can I speak to
him?
>> Yeah. I was What I was going to say is
what he's actually got some people with
him. If I could get your name and
number, put you in a system here, and
then me and him can call you and see
exactly what you're wanting to do.
>> Yeah, that'd be great. I can give you my
name, number, um, I can give you that,
but what else do you need? I can give
you those two things.
>> All right. What What was your first
name?
>> My first name is Tommy.
>> T O M Y.
>> Sure. I mean, that's one way to spell
it. I spell it weird. It doesn't matter.
It's It's all It's all French.
>> What's the right way? I want to put it
in the system right way.
>> Oh, T O M I.
>> And then what's your uh last name?
>> Mula. M I K U L A.
>> And then a good phone number for you.
>> Uh, best phone number for me is
>> And you want a GMC
Denali? Denali reserve.
>> Denali reserve.
>> All right. Well, sounds good. Let me get
some stuff put in the system here and
then soon as he frees up, we'll reach
back out to you.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> All righty. Do you have like a list of
options and everything you want?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I even have a build
code, but basically it's just the Denali
reserve package. And if I can remove the
rear entertainment, uh, we don't watch
TV in our house, so it's it's it's
against the work of the god himself.
>> All right. Well, we'll see what I can
do.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> All right. Thank you.
>> No problem. Bye. I'm start making up
reasons. To be fair, my client did not
tell me why she doesn't want Rear
Entertainment, but I'm just like
guessing random reasons. And to be fair,
they're all probably a really legitimate
reason, but I'm just making this up.
Hopefully, you understand. I'm just
making jokes. So, like one of my always
goals is I try to get a deal out of
state, right? I always I'm really
competitive. And once I get a
competitive deal, I try to bring it to
the most local dealership I can, but I
also do target a dealership that is in a
bigger city. Like because if she has a
small dealership in our small little
town, the chances of them taking that
are slim compared to one in a bigger
city just because they normally are a
little bit more competitive. These are
all normal things.
>> Here it is.
>> Hello.
>> It is speaking.
>> Hey, are you in new car sales?
>> I am.
>> Awesome. I'm in the right place at the
right time and I'm hopefully to be the
right person to buy a car from. Hey.
Well, hey, I am looking for a 2026 uh
GMC Yukon uh with the Denali Reserve
package. I've already done a lot of
research. You're my local dealership, so
I'm hoping that all this research pays
off and we can make a quick, easy
transaction.
>> Well, we could if we had any.
>> Well, I Oh, I know. I'm going to order
one. Yeah. Yeah. I'm
>> I did all the research.
>> Yeah. I don't have any right now.
>> Yeah. I don't think anybody has them. I
don't think that's
>> We can We can Have you built one?
>> I have. I already built one, already
gotten pricing on it out of out of the
area. So, you know, I'm like nice and
easy. I'm just trying to buy from my
local dealership.
>> Well, basically, is it a Denali? You say
a Denali reserve?
>> Denali with the reserve package. You got
it. White diesel.
>> Well, basically, what we do is we we
sell them at sticker price.
>> Oh, okay. Well, that's that's that's
unfortunate because I've I've got a much
better deal out of the area.
>> Yeah, I I can appreciate that. But, uh,
right now the wholesaler, the fleet
people, they're they're paying as much
as $2,000 over invoice for them
themselves. If I sold them below that,
then just not making any money on them.
And that particular vehicle is is the
money maker for your dealerships. Now, I
don't know what anybody's selling a 26
for, a Denali Reserve, but but um I
mean, I might as well be upfront about
it.
>> Yeah. No, I I guess I appreciate you
being upfront about it. I get I get that
maybe to buy it. Sorry.
>> I'd love to be your dealer, but I mean
that's the way we sell them and you know
that's what I got to do.
>> No, I guess I guess I get that if that's
what you want to do. Get your
wholesalers are buying them for $2,000
above invoice, but I imagine you'd want
like a local client that's going to do
service with you and all that stuff
rather than a wholesaler.
>> Well, we would much rather. We don't
wholesale them to them. We don't sell
them to them primarily because
everything that we can get our hands on
we sell. But we do sell it at sticker
price.
>> Okay. Oh, I don't want to waste any more
of your time. I I'm about to buy one
today. So, sorry.
>> Um Yeah, I see you guys have some 24s
even on your lot still. So, I get it.
>> Well, now that's that's different.
There's a couple demos. Yeah.
>> Oh, yeah. 24.
>> We use those in courtesy transportation.
Yeah,
>> I get it. And you guys have a few 25
still on the website, too. I get it.
That's a couple. Make your make your
money. make your make your money. I'll
I'll just go buy it elsewhere and I'll
bring it in uh and let you guys look how
pretty it is.
>> Sure. No problem. We'll be glad to
service it, too.
>> Oh, yeah. I mean I mean Well, you know,
I'm going to call I guess there's like
one other one or two other dealerships
in Knoxville. I guess I'll call them and
they can sell me the car and even be
entertained to hear my offer then.
That's cool. But that's cool. You guys
sell them a sticker.
>> Be best to tell you up front.
>> I appreciate it. Not
>> that we do sell them at that especially
a Denali. Now, if you're if you're going
to get one of the other packages other
than a Denali or Denali Ultimate, then
we will work with you some on them. The
Denali's and Denali Ultimates are are
sticker price.
>> Okay. I appreciate that. Yeah, I s Yeah,
I appreciate it. You have a great day.
>> I appreciate you,
>> GMC.
>> Hey, how's it going?
>> Good. What can I do for you?
>> Hey, I was actually looking to uh buy a
car. I'm looking to order a 26 Yukon
Denali with the reserve package.
>> Okay. And you said that was a Yukon
Denali.
>> Yukon Denali. I've tried to make it as
easy as possible. I've done all the
research possible. I've done all the
hard work. You're my local dealership,
so I'm just trying to order one with one
of you guys with all the work I've done
to quick and easy call it a day.
>> That is what I love to hear.
>> My mom taught me that was the best way
to buy a car.
>> It makes the process smooth. So, um,
have you done an online build on it or
anything? I I already have. I told you
I'm gonna be a pro. There's not gonna be
a question you're going to stunt me on
today.
>> Nice. So, the easiest way to go about
this is this your direct number?
>> Yeah. This is the best number there ever
has been.
>> Okay. And what was your name again? One
more time. My name's Tommy.
>> Mr. Tommy. Well, Mr. Tommy, my name's
Chase. What I can do for you there,
Tommy. I can get you my email and if you
will email me the build that you did
online or if you would just want to
bring it in one day and uh we can put it
in and get an allocation for it. We can
do either one. Which one do you think
would work best for you?
>> I mean, can I text it to you? That's I'm
a big texter.
>> Yeah. Yeah, 100%. Um on that build,
there should be like an email to dealer
thing and I'll just give you my email
and I can get that allocation put in.
One question though, is it a is it
four-wheel drive that you auctioned?
Yeah, it is a four-wheel drive, correct?
>> Okay. Yeah. The the only time that we'd
need like a um a deposit on anything is
if it was something very uh peculiar,
like if it was two wheel drive or if it
was minimally optioned, something like
that. We we might request a deposit on
that. Other than that, yeah, I can just
uh I can shoot you a text with my email
if you want to email that through to me
and I can put it up in allocation board.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Do you know I mean the big
thing for us is just the pricing on it,
right? We're trying to figure out what
the pricing is. You guys know I've done
some even with some work on trying to
figure that out first. I don't normally
use email, but I can email it if if I
have to, but really just trying to
figure out what kind of pricing you guys
are doing. Some dealerships have said
they're not moving on the price at all.
I have a pretty competitive offer out of
the state, so willing to order it if I
have to, but I'd like to shop local.
>> Yeah, absolutely. And if it's something
we do to order for you, it'll be built
to spec, so whatever it is from GM is
usually what it will be, unless there
are incentives or any type of rebates on
it. Now, right now, and really to be
honest with you, rarely do we run
rebates or incentives on Yukons other
than maybe special financing because
they have no problem selling themselves.
Two things could happen. At the time of
order, they wouldn't be applied, but if
there were rebates or uh any type of
incentives at the time of pickup, those
can be applied, but that'd be the
biggest thing. Now, as far as like a a
discount on an ordered item, do you have
like a GM supplier number or anything
like that?
>> Nope. But I do have a I do have a
dealership that's willing to still give
me a discount.
>> Okay. Well, what kind of discount are
they looking at? And was it a specific
build that you had?
>> Uh it is a Yukon Denali with the reserve
package, the illumination package, and
ideally if you can remove the back rear
entertainment because my kids do not
watch TV cuz that will brain rot their
mind. And I have 8 and 12% off MSRP.
>> Okay. 8 and a half% off MSRP. Correct.
>> Plus a dock fee plus tax total license.
>> Yeah. Yeah, the the the normal goodies.
Now, we don't do anything other than
dock fee and state taxes, of course. Um,
our dock fee is $5.99. I don't know what
theirs looks like, but depending if it's
out of state. I know Tennessee caps it.
Okay, good deal. I know Tennessee caps
them at a level, but like places like
Georgia, they're a little more uh
liberal with us things.
>> But yeah, what I'll do, Tommy, I will
get with you. I'll shoot you my number.
shoot me over what you have and let me
run it up through my management and see
what we can do to get that ordered and
if there's any type of, you know,
discount or anything we can get applied
to that that'd be beneficial to you.
What is your last name, Tommy?
>> Last name, Mula. M I K U L A.
>> Perfect. All right, Tommy, then what
I'll do, buddy? Um, I'm going to shoot
you my text number and I with my
management once you shoot over that
build order, so that way we can kind of
piece it together and uh see what we can
get done for you, buddy.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I love it.
>> Perfect then. Yeah, I'll text you here
in just a second and uh we'll get the
ball rolling for you.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> Appreciate it, Tommy. Have a good one,
buddy. Speak with you soon.
>> Bye.
>> Okay, wait. We got we have a legitimate
answer. She said, "I have been dying
laughing at the rear entertainment
thing. My kids are older and even when
toddlers, we never used them. My son
played baseball and I was always afraid
his bat would hit the screen and break
it. Plus, I don't like the look of the
screens hanging on to the back seat.
Happy to do the 26 and wait." So, we
have the legitimate answer. She doesn't
want to brainwash her kid. And just you
guys know, that wasn't just like out of
the nowhere. This is the person I was
texting. So, I just confirm uh that that
deal is going to be good. Make sure
there's no things. We'll have the car by
Christmas. I mean, I think that's the
deal. I don't think we're going to beat
that. I'm going to let my client know.
That's That's probably the answer. Yeah.
I don't think I'm beating 8 1.5%. If I
could get Yeah. So, shipping from that
distance is about a,000 bucks. Let me
I'll call my client. My client is
watching. So, if you do not want to
answer, just don't answer. But I'll call
you and ask what you want to do.
>> Okay. You are live. Just so you know, I
think you're watching.
Um, so 8 12% on this car on a 2026 is
really strong. I'm going to wait on this
other one, but I think that's going to
be the play. Shipping from that
distance, probably about,200
bucks. So, ends up being like a net
discount of like 7 and 12% which is
still strong compared to your local
deals.
>> I'm also I don't know where you're
getting the deal from, but
>> I'm not opposed to flying and picking it
up either and driving it home or my
husband and I going and getting it cuz
we've done that before.
>> Yeah. The Yeah. So we we could do that
as well. So we can discuss. We have some
time. It would be about till Christmas
when the card get here,
>> which is actually not a bad aotment
either. But yeah, you get a perfect
build. The only thing I don't know is if
we can customize your screen. That's a
good question. I have no I don't have a
real answer for you, but I'll figure out
if we can not have a back rear
entertainment. I'm all for it.
>> Okay. That part was really funny.
>> I appreciate Hey, as long as you're
laughing, that's all that matters.
>> I was laughing the whole time cuz it's
it's such a weird thing. But like I
said, the last one it was I didn't
custom order my 21. It was someone had
custom ordered it. I ended up getting it
because they backed out of it. So I
don't know how they ordered it on the I
actually might have that old build
sheet. I could have to find it. But I
don't know how they did it, but there
was Yeah, there was no rear DVDs in that
one. I love
>> Okay, awesome. So, let me do this. Let
me I'm going to wait on this last call
real quick, but I'm going to start
setting this up as if this this
dealership will probably ask you for
like a $500 deposit. But I think this is
probably going to be the best as it
gets. I do want to just make sure that
this local dealership won't. But I
didn't feel confident based on the phone
call by him saying we don't normally
discount these. So yeah, but he just
asked me for the build. So I texted that
over to him, so I should have an answer
from him shortly.
>> Okay, perfect. I'm so happy.
>> Either way, congratulations and I'll
talk to you soon.
>> Wonderful. Thank you, Tommy.
>> No problem. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> Yeah. So I I think this is going to be
good. Yeah, she's I mean she can
definitely fly. She's awesome. U and
this is what like this is what most of
our clients are. Our clients are super
easy to work with. They just want a good
deal. They don't want to play any games.
They just want to, hey, let me know what
it is. Give me a good deal and I'll make
it work.
[Music]