Oh, I see. I do see it on your website.
It's right there. I I'm looking at it.
>> But there's going to be one coming our
way and maybe two, but not
>> perfect. I'll take that one. If you're
getting a oneofone limited edition car
to your dealership, as a salesperson, I
don't care if the owner is actually
buying it. You never tell a customer.
>> And if I can get it, I will take it to
her house. I don't care if we got to
drive 3 hours. We don't care about that.
We don't care the distance. But if she
wants to go blue, I'll get it for her.
We're going to look for an LC500
convertible.
So, my search says there are five of
these bad boys in the country. My client
lives in the great state.
Now, I've already called on one of
these, which is in Texas. That one's not
available. So, there's only I call this
the four horseman, five horseins, cuz if
we look at this car, I can't do that.
Never mind. I'm not going to show you
guys um because there's no way to show
you. I'm going to call this one in
California first. Uh, let's call this
one. Now, this is going to be the one if
we're going to have add-ons and fees.
This is the car.
>> Hello, thanks for calling. My name is
David. How may I help you?
>> Hey, David, this is Tommy. I just want
to see if you guys have a car available.
>> Hi, Tommy. Which car? Uh,
>> I have a stock number if it helps.
>> It's a brand new or used car.
>> It's brand new.
>> Okay, one second.
>> Okay, you can go ahead. Mhm.
>> Uh, it's T is in Tango, A is an alpha
11248.
>> Okay, one second. And what model is it?
>> It is an LC.
>> By any chance, is it inspiration?
>> Uh, it it is an inspirational car,
correct?
>> Yes, I have that car. It's right in
front of me in the middle of showroom.
>> You know what? I love it. Want more of
it. That's what I want to hear. Bada
boom, bada bing. I want to get some
pricing.
>> Let me check. One second.
>> Sure. We're on hold, hold, hold, hold.
>> A few moments later.
>> One question is the phone number that
you're calling me from is the best.
>> Yep, that is.
>> That's it.
>> All right. My manager will call you back
in a bit. He's with the customer and
he'll go over the numbers with you.
>> Okay, sounds good. I can't wait to hear
it.
>> All right, no problem. See you.
>> Okay, let's call the other dealership
while I wait for this dealership. Okay,
this this one's going to be Oh, this
one's going to be interesting. This
one's going to be I'm in Miami.
>> Thank you for choosing sales department.
This is Carol. With whom do I have the
pleasure of speaking?
>> Hey, Carol. My name is Tommy. It's so
nice to meet you.
>> Nice to meet you, too, sir. Thank you so
much. And how can I help you?
>> Awesome. I just wanted to see if you
guys have a car available. And what's
that car? The stock number.
>> I could see a stock number word. I just
blank after. So I don't know. I just
blank.
>> That's fine. Tell me what it is and I'll
find it for you. Tell me.
>> It's an LC500.
>> Brand new or pre-owned?
>> It says new in all caps.
>> Okay. So I'm going to put you on hold
for a minute. It must be something that
just arrived. I may put you on hold. Is
that okay?
>> Sure. Absolutely.
>> Thanks. Thanks. Tell me, what is your
phone number?
>> Yeah, my phone number is going to
>> Thank you so much.
>> A few moments later.
Tommy. So, you saw this in our website?
>> I did. Yeah. The flexus.com website.
>> Yeah. Because I have one that just is it
a convertible or a hard top?
>> I'm open to either or as long as it's
it's this particular trim car.
>> Okay. The thing is that all of the ones
that are here have been reserved and
they're sold. So, that's why I said you
saw it in the website. Maybe it's
because it just dropped from transit to
ground and it got published because I
don't see any available.
>> Okay. So, you don't have any on the way.
I don't know if your website says in
transit cars or I don't I I don't I
don't work there. I'm unsure.
>> Okay. No, no worries. I have what's
here. I have two in transit and two
allocated and they're all reserved
already. So,
>> Okay. So, you don't have a single LC500
available? No, we get allocations every
couple of weeks and I can definitely let
you know what what are you looking for
so that I can nail you 500 inspiration.
>> Oh, no. Oh, that you did not see. I
promise you didn't see that in the
website. Oh,
>> I do see it on your website. It's right
there. I'm looking at it.
>> Yeah. Okay. But let me tell you about
those cars. They're going to If we get
two of them, we'll get lucky. We're only
we're one we will get one for sure and
hopefully two. They're very limited
edition of these cars. So, they're
sending very few to each of the of the
dealerships around the world, I guess.
So, um we don't have one. We don't have
an inspiration here. I'm pretty sure
that whatever is coming in already has a
name attached. I'm not going to, you
know, give you false hopes here. Are you
there?
>> Yep. I'm here. So, sorry.
>> Okay. So, um inspiration. I know it's
very it's going to be hard to find. Are
you in this area?
That's a North Carolina zip code or
area.
>> North Carolina. Have you tried in your
area? I guess you have.
>> I heard No, I heard good things for your
dealership. That's why I called you
guys.
>> Yeah. Thank you. I appreciate you. Yeah,
but that's going to be very hard. I
haven't seen them. We don't even have
them in a location yet.
>> I wouldn't call my local dealership if
it was easy. I called you guys cuz I
thought you guys could handle the hard
task.
>> Yes, we can. But there's going to be one
coming our way and maybe two, but not
sure.
>> Oh, perfect. I'll take that one.
>> As I mentioned, our clients have called
about it. That's why when you said
inspiration, I said, "Oh, okay." So, I
know that the director of sales,
>> how do I become a client? I guess I'm
I'm a little confused. How do I become a
client? I know you said your clients are
asking about, but I understand I'm not a
client. Do I have to
first?
>> No, no. Just that our I meant to say our
clients have been calling about it.
That's why I know what's happening to
the inspiration and there's a waiting
list already and I'll be happy to add
your name and see what goes on.
>> One and there's a waiting list.
waiting for like 10 years.
>> No, not even because we're only they're
only going to produce x amount of them.
So that's it.
>> Well, just help me understand how many
if if there's five people on the waiting
list and you get maybe one a year, I'd
be waiting for 5 years for the car.
Correct.
>> No, we're not getting one a year because
we're not going to be producing this
cars every year. This is a special one
time edition.
>> But if you're only going to get one,
then how could I be on the just just
help me understand because you said
you're only going to get one if you're
lucky. So I could join the wait list.
You know, I'm interested in that, but if
there's five people on the waiting list,
I probably would never get one, right?
>> That's true, sir. Absolutely. That's why
I say I don't want to get anybody's
hold. Yeah, absolutely true, Tommy.
Yeah.
>> Okay. Yeah. I don't Yeah. I don't want
to be, you know, the second option. I
want to be the first. So,
>> I got it. I understand. I'm so sorry. I
know. I thought it was a regular LC and
those I can try to get for you, but not.
>> Yeah. And I have the last four of the
stock or the VIN of the one I'm looking
for, but you're you're saying that it
doesn't matter. It's sold. Do you have a
VIN already of an of an inspiration?
>> Yeah, one on your website. Remember when
I said the one on your website? It just
doesn't have a stock. It has a VIN.
>> Okay. What's the last four of the VIN?
>> 2280.
>> It's an LC500 convertible.
>> Mhm.
>> In transit.
>> Can arrive any day.
>> And it does have a name already. Uh it's
sold to the owner of the company. So,
Mr. So, Yep.
>> He probably want to sell it to a
customer, right? Rather than sell it to
himself.
>> No, no, no. This is No, he's going to
keep it. Let me see something. Hold on,
sir. Hold on. I guess this is It's very
interesting. Hold on.
>> Sometimes they keep all the good stuff,
right?
>> Well, and it doesn't even say
inspiration. It just says convertible.
>> I know, but the Amazon is definitely If
that's not an inspiration, I don't know.
>> Inspiration TM series. Yeah. Yeah. Oh,
that's why I couldn't see it before. It
was reserved.
>> Yeah. Sometimes the inspirations, they
hide.
>> Oh, okay. They do. They do for sure.
Okay.
>> Oh, it's been lovely speaking with you,
Tommy. I'm sorry. I wish I could say yes
and sell you the car, but I can't.
>> Okay, no, no worries. I I hope the owner
gets to enjoy uh his convertible
>> in his convertible. Yes, sir. Thank you.
>> Yeah, he's going to have a fun drive.
Make sure he sends me a picture with him
in it with his new car.
>> You have a good day, Tommy. Thank you so
much for calling us. Bye-bye.
>> Okay, no problem. Bye.
>> Just a just a small note. If you're
getting a oneofone limited edition car
to your dealership, as a salesperson, I
don't care if the owner is actually
buying it. You never tell a customer
that the owner is buying the oneofone
car. What? That's insane. What are you
What are you going to do? Buy it and
resell it? Like, she was very good. I
mean, she didn't even ask me for like
she didn't even look up the car. I'm
sorry, but if you think she was good,
she didn't even look up the car I was
looking for. She just went and be like,
"Eh, it's not available."
>> Good speaking. Uh, hey, I just want to
see if you guys have a car available.
>> Okay. What car is it?
>> Uh, I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Um, is it new or pre-owned?
>> Uh, it does say new on the website.
>> Okay. All right. What's the stock
number?
>> Uh, stock number is S is in Subaru
265149.
>> Uh, that one is sold. It's a 26 LC,
right?
>> It is.
>> Yes, it is sold. It's coming in, but
it's already got reserved for someone.
>> It's already sold. Bada bing, bada boom.
That's a sad one.
>> Yeah,
>> it's okay. I guess I'll uh
>> both already sold those two 2026s coming
in.
>> Okay. Yeah, I mean that's the exact one
I'm looking for. So, I guess I'll get
walking away.
>> Sorry about that.
>> No problem. Talk to you later.
>> All right. Thanks. Bye.
>> Bye. If you guys don't know who I am, my
name's Tommy. I negotiate car deals for
a living. My goal is to save you time,
energy, and anxiety. We save you money,
but that's a byproduct. I charge a flat
fee of a,000 bucks. Again, we handle
everything for you. I don't advertise it
as a money-saving service because guess
what? You can do this on your own. You
don't need me. But people hire me
because they don't want to deal with the
anxiety. They also can get a little bit
of a dinner and a show, which is
something people like. I do this all
online so people can see how easy or how
hard it is you get to make that
decision. I want you guys to be
transparent. Okay, I have one more I can
call on this one before we go to the
next car. Okay, we have one more that's
available in the country.
>> Hello. Can I speak to somebody at new
car sales?
>> That's me.
>> Awesome. Perfect. Hey, I just want to
see if you guys have a car available.
What car were you looking for?
>> I have the last six of the VIN. Make
model. What makes the most sense for
you?
>> All right, let's do the VIN.
>> VIN. Do you want the whole thing?
>> Last five.
>> Last five. Okay, we're going to count. 1
2 3 4. Okay. 2 A Alpha Beta 73.
>> All right. Is it the LC500?
>> That's it.
>> It's available.
>> Okay. Awesome. Do you guys know you guys
are what kind of pricing you guys are
doing on it?
>> Uh, let me see here. One second. Let me
get the confirmed pricing.
>> Sure. This is the last one available.
So, if this is available, we're just
like we need to jump on this. There's
not this is a very limited edition car.
So, like we already told the client, we
prepped the client that we're just going
to have to call. They gave us a 3-month
timeline on when they were trying to get
it done. So,
>> hello.
>> Hey, I'm so sorry. I just I pushed the
mute button.
>> Oh. Oh, no worries. Hi, thanks for
holding. I got the out the door price or
not out the door, sorry, the price of
the vehicle. 128569.
>> 569.
>> And then as a dealership,
>> that does include some protection items
that as a dealership we do install on
this vehicle.
>> Okay. What are those? full hood tip. So,
PPF film, polyurethane film all over the
hood, the side view mirrors, the
fenders, the door cups, door edges, and
then we also tint the vehicle. We put
ceramic coating on the vehicle as well.
>> And that cost seven grand. Is that
correct?
>> What was that?
>> That cost seven grand. Is that what
you're saying?
>> Correct. And we also installed the pulse
rear collision deterrent on it.
>> Okay. Um, I appreciate all that. Is Is
there any way I can just say no to all
that? I know the car is not there yet.
So,
>> are you declining all of it? Is that
>> Yeah. I mean, ideally, yeah, I wouldn't
want any of that stuff. Uh, I mean, what
I do is I get all my cars personally
ceramic coated from a shop that I really
like and they PPF it. So, like just cuz
it's $120,000 car, I like to have my
people do it. They're really good.
>> 100%. I hear you. Let me get some more
information on that before I get you off
the phone. One second. Okay.
>> Oh, yeah. Of course. It's 121K MSRP.
That's why I just did the math and it
was 7K of add-ons. But it makes a It
makes a legitimate reason why I don't
want to have the add-ons, right? It
gives me a legitimate reason if I'm
trying to do it professionally rather
than doing it through their shop. and
they should understand it's $120,000
vehicle for them. Hello.
>> Hi. I appreciate the hold. So,
unfortunately, we do not sell these
vehicles without the protection items
that we have listed.
>> There's no way around. I just, you know,
I just I'm just going to rip it all off.
You know, is there like an alternative
option or something like a warranty or
something? I'm just trying to think
outside the box.
>> Let me help you out here. Okay. One
second.
>> Yeah, of course. Thank you.
>> Okay. So, unfortunately, that will not
be the case. We are going to be selling
the car with the seven grand of
protection items, but you could get the
warranty maintenance on top of that if
you'd like to.
>> I appreciate you. I don't even know I
can do that on top of it. Okay. Is there
I mean 7K is a lot for these things that
I'm going to tear off the car. So,
anyway, you can help me out on that
part. I
>> I get I get where you guys are coming
from. It's a hard car to get. Like I'm
not like denying any of that, but like
the idea that I'm going to literally
tear it all off
>> 100%. I hear you. Unfortunately, not. We
are going to be selling the car with the
add-ons, with the protection.
That's disappointing. Okay. And if I'm
an out ofstate buyer, is that okay?
>> What was that?
>> If I'm an out ofstate buyer, is that
okay?
>> Are you out of state?
>> I am.
>> Yeah, that should be all right.
>> Okay. So, like I said, I really would
like to be like 7K is a lot of add-ons,
right? Like that's like I just hate
tearing it all off. There's nothing your
manager can do to help me out. I mean,
again, I'm willing to buy a warranty
instead. Willing to do a maintenance
plan instead. Want to do like half the
cost of maybe a warranty? I'm trying to
think of anything outside the box. I
just feel like seven grand I'm throwing
it away. I get you guys are trying to
add value to it, but it's the same as
just marking up the car. You're gonna
have a tech you're paying to do this
that's just gonna get torn off.
>> I hear you. And then I just wanted to
make a note that since you are out of
state that you would need to fly in
before you purchase the vehicle. Would
that be all right?
>> Yeah, that's fine. And again, that's
also like I'll fly in, I'll do all like
all these things I will want to do, but
I need to like you got to help me out a
little.
>> Yeah, 100%. I hear everything that
you're saying right now. Um, so as of
right now, we will be selling the car
with seven grand of add-ons. Um, I did
write your number down. And what's a
good name for you?
>> My my good name is Tommy.
>> Tommy. Good last name.
>> Makula. M I K U L A.
>> All right. Well, I have your information
down, Tommy. Um, and all the information
that you shared with me, I'll share that
with my managers and I'll see where
there's any room to help you out. But if
not, then what I've been saying will be
the case.
>> Yeah, I mean, yeah, you can you can have
a manager maybe call me to get it
figured out. Like I said, I'm trying to
think of something creative. I
understand you guys are want to get
above MSRP. I'm not even like arguing on
that on this car. It's more of a I'd
like to get some value out of what I'm
getting. So, I like the idea of a
warranty. I was going to buy a warranty.
That's I get. But like the idea of
putting PPF in a car that I'm just going
to tear off, call it a day. That that's
just me throwing money away rather than
me at least overpaying for something I
was going to pay for anyway, right?
>> Yeah. 100%. I hear where you're coming
from and I appreciate your honesty and
transparency with me. I'm going to share
some information um on our end and we'll
get back to you.
>> Okay. Sounds good. I appreciate it.
>> All right. Thanks for calling, Tommy.
We'll be back.
>> No problem. Thank you. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> So, just give you guys a thought on this
one, right? There's five of them in the
United States. This is the last one, the
only one that's available. We want to
make sure that we're going to do
everything we can, right? Like, we're
going to go through. We told this client
at the very, very beginning that, hey,
this car is going to be almost
impossible to find. This is going to be
something that it might be above MSRP.
We have no idea. We've not done an
inspiration. There's one of these
available and it's a limited run car.
We're going to go through, do our
effort. As you guys can see, we'll go
through here. The reason why we like the
idea of a warranty is warranties just
have better value. And B, you can cancel
a warranty if you really don't want the
warranty and get a partial refund back
or a full refund back. Compared to PPF
and ceramic, there's no way to ever get
that money back. The option is either
this car or nothing. So, that's why
we're willing to have a conversation. Oh
gosh. Hello, Shell Ashley.
>> Hey, can you move this?
Hey guys, I'm going to give you guys the
rundown. Uh, this is an unfortunate
situation. Sometimes life happens,
right? So, I want to make sure we're on
the same page. We did a deal earlier
today. We were originally looking for a
Civic sedan. We switched to a hatchback.
We went very clear we needed a
hatchback. He gave us a second set of
numbers on hatchback. We agreed to the
deal. Client went in to go pick up the
car and now all of a sudden they're
saying it was never a hatchback. It was
a sedan. It's been a hatchback. We've
talked about a hatchback. It's been a
hatchback. So, now I got to call this
dealership while the client is in the
dealership to see if we can figure out
some type of resolution. So, we're going
to call this one live.
>> Hello.
>> Hey, man. Let's We got to figure out a
solution here.
>> Hey,
>> what can what can we do to make this
right here? Cuz I know we asked for a
hatchback.
>> So, right. She's right here. I'm talking
to her right now. So, I can get I can
get the sport touring hatchback. It's
just that nobody has this car in Urban
Ray. I can get in another color, but I
looked at the allocations. Nobody has
this color in urban gray. I can get a
black with black, but I don't think
that's the one they want. So,
>> boost blue. I think it was the second
color.
>> No, she doesn't even like the boost blue
because I have one here and she didn't
like it.
>> Okay. Doesn't want the boost blue. Only
wants the Urban Gray.
>> Yeah. Only wants Urban Gray. So, I'm
looking at the allocations here and
there is not one closed for the for the
next five or 6 hours, you know. Let me
let me double check. Yeah.
>> Let me double check. Give me one second.
>> Yep.
>> Yeah. All right. So, let me get that and
let's see where
>> I didn't push it.
>> I'm assum I don't know all the details
here because I'm not here. I've approved
this deal. I gave the thumbs up. I
already did this deal. This is my deal.
This is why they're not arguing that we
what they sent us isn't there. Like at
this point, he could be arguing and say
he I muted him just so you know. Showing
him the showing him the recording. He
hasn't he's not saying that I'm lying.
Like he knows he knows he messed up. So
now the problem is they don't have
something else. Yes, we have everything
that we need. Like again, he's not
arguing that he's wrong, that we're
wrong. He's trying to find a solution,
which we like, right? Like that's okay.
This is life, right? This happens like
one out of every 500 deals.
Unfortunately, it's happening. Um this
is a local dealership. I don't love it,
right? But that's what we're here for.
We're going to deal with it. We're going
to call them a day. No, the client won't
never refund. This isn't our We'll make
it right for the client either way.
We'll find something for the client just
because this I mean, this is out of
everybody's control. We're going to make
it right. Um but making it right is
finding a car to call it a day, right? I
wish that every time the dealer I mean I
I bet dealers should be really happy
that every time that they made a mistake
that we have to refund our money like no
unfortunately it sucks but we're gonna
make it right. We're a lot and this is
where this is where I'd say a lot of
people that attempt to do this job or do
this this is where a lot of people fall
short right which is when something
happens which it occasionally does. It's
rare right? We jump in and take care of
it. So uh since it's out of our control
of a service to make car buying easy and
simple but not easy and simple. So
wouldn't that warrant a refund? We don't
have a money back guarantee. That being
said, if you want to go that route,
sure. I can just say, "Hey, I'll refund
you. Have a nice life and go find your
own car." That's not right either,
right? This sucks. It's not good. But
does the client want me just to abandon
them and just say, "Have a nice life.
Bye. Sorry. Here's a refund. Call
today." This it honestly be easier.
You're right. I could just refund the
thousand call a day. That's not what the
best thing to do is. We go look at that
Hummer deal. It would have been much
easier for me to refund the $1,000 than
it was to call a hundred dealerships and
have stress at the end of the moment.
Well, that's not the right thing to do.
We're going to we're going to try to
make it right. It's completely out of
our control. But yeah, dealerships do
this. Like this is something this but
this is what they're paying for, right?
They're paying for somebody to be there
to have that experience, right? They're
paying for something. When something
goes wrong, I don't want to deal with
it. I'm going to call I'm going to have
you call and you're going to deal with
it. That's what we're doing. I have him
muted so he can't hear me.
>> Hello. Hello.
>> Oh, you got good news.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So, I got the allocation
right here. Yeah. I mean, it's the urban
rates for me. It's impossible to get.
Nobody has this car. Nobody has this
car. I can get black, gray, and black
and blue. So, I can get the meteorite
gray. I can get the black and the blues
blue.
>> Okay. So, just to make sure I'm on the
same page on everything here. You have
There is no urban grays that I can find
in in your region at all. There's If I
go look right now, I can't find a single
one
>> at all. I'm looking at Jacksonville,
Pensacola,
Panama City, Tampa.
>> Yep. Okay.
>> Miami. And you have a boost blue Civic
Touring in stock.
>> I do not, but I I do not, but I can get
one.
>> Okay. So, I'm gonna
>> And if I can get it, I will take it to
her house. I don't care if we got to
drive 3 hours. We don't care about that.
We don't care the distance. But if she
wants the boo, I'll get it for her.
>> Okay. And and then, you know, obviously
for all the inconvenience here, can we
can we get a better discount on that
deal?
>> A better discount? I could probably get
you
>> to the dealership to get that car. And
>> what's that? He just came all the way to
the dealership just to get that car. So,
I'm hoping that we can get, you know,
something a little, you know, a little
bit better for him. Then we can deliver
call today.
>> Yeah, I will. I'll I'll deliver it to
them. I'll drive the 3 hours. But, you
know, the the the the deal that, you
know, I even beat the deal that you had
from the other dealership.
>> I understand you did, but then then the
client came in 3 hours drive and
>> Yeah.
>> which I think which they were using. So,
you know, when you tell me if we can get
a better price, what what are we looking
at? Are we looking at another thousand?
No, I cannot do another thousand.
>> I mean, that's I mean, 500 bucks off.
Give them something for the
inconvenience, you know.
>> Can we do 200 bucks? I
>> mean, 500 and delivering to them seems
like it's And I have to talk to make
sure they're okay with getting that
blue, which that that was our second
favorite color. So, I got to make sure
they're okay with that.
>> No, I get it. Yeah. I mean, I will do
200 bucks. You know, I got to I got to
tell my boss that, you know, it's he's
probably going to tell me it's going to
come out of my pocket, which I don't
care. I don't care.
>> Okay. Let me So, can you do 400 bucks
off extra and uh free delivery and I'll
talk to him? I'll call him right now.
>> 400 bucks.
>> 400 bucks extra off free delivery and
I'll talk to him right now. That's
that's that's worth their time for being
out there.
>> I know.
>> And we'll figure out we'll make sure the
next one doesn't go like that, you know.
>> No, no, of course. I'm trying to think
over here. Let me ask. Let me let me
>> I'll call the cl You go ask. I'll call
call the client and uh we'll we'll see
if we can
>> But don't promise anything for the 400.
I'm not call I'm not I'm not promising
anything right now, but but that that
I'm going to make sure they're they're
willing to do the second favorite color
um before we do anything. So, yeah, you
go ask your boss and you can do that.
>> All right, go ahead. Let me go ask my
boss. All right.
>> Okay, sounds good. Bye. Okay, guys. For
privacy, I'm going to mute for a minute.
Uh it's a client. I'm not going to I'm
going to go through um give me one
second.
Hey.
>> Okay. So, I just talked to them. They'll
do a black sport touring hybrid.
>> They'll do the black one.
>> Yep. Do that. And then I'm um if you can
deliver it and do the extra discount,
that's great. And then uh we're gonna
make it worthwhile for their trip. We're
gonna help them with some dinner
tonight. So uh they're gonna go out to
dinner so they're not upset or angry. So
if you can get the black one for me, get
an extra 400 bucks off delivered. It's
going to pay for their dinner tonight.
So you don't have to worry about that.
And then everybody's happy. Everybody's
wins. But we they need a black sport
touring.
>> Okay. All right. Let me get on that. I'm
still waiting for my boss to come
downstairs.
>> Okay.
>> Uh he's upstairs in a meeting. So as
soon as I get that, but I'm going to try
and get the black one. Of course, it's
not going to be for today. And then I'm
going to need wet signatures.
>> Yeah, that's fine. As long as you want
to deliver it to them, that's fine.
>> All right. Okay. So, all right. Deliver
to them. Okay.
>> Okay. Yep. Let's let's let's get that
rock and roll. They're willing to do
black. They don't want to do the blue
anymore. They originally wanted to and
they said it looked like a Lego now, so
they don't want to do that.
>> All right.
>> Okay. Let's rock and roll. Um let's
let's let's got it. Bada boom, bada
bing. Call it a day.
>> Yeah. Bada bing, bada bing. Like you
said, let's move on.
>> Hey, hey, the second you hear from your
manager, I want to be the first one to
know what you have an answer to. Okay.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> All right.
Okay, they're okay, right? They're not
blaming us. They understand it's the
dealership's fault. What we're doing is
I try to make things right. Like, we
don't One thing that we don't do is this
is not our fault, but obviously the
client just drove to the dealership. We
want to make the experience right for
them. So, we've just told them to don't
go take their family out to dinner, go
pick a place, I don't care. Send me the
receipt. We'll give them we'll get them
a reimbursement for that. So, at least
on delivered side, again, this isn't our
fault. We didn't do anything wrong, but
I want to make sure the client is having
that magical experience. So, they're
going to have that. We're going to make
sure we get an extra discount for them.
We're also going to make sure that uh
they get the car delivered to their
house. So basically this will just be a
trip for them to go out to dinner and
that makes it right for the client. And
I they did make a joke about Ruth Chris.
I said uh I mean I just send me a
receipt, call it a day. It sucks, right?
It sucks. It's it's it sucks. It's fine.
Deliver is going to eat some money out
of it. How often this happen is very
rare. I love to see you guys is uh the
truth of this business, right? And what
I will tell you is this is the
difference where you know a lot of
people say, "What's the difference
between us and a broker? What's the
difference between us and our
competition? 95% of people would have
just hung up the phone and called it a
day cuz they did their job.
Legitimately, you can ask other car
salesman. Why car salesman don't like
brokers a lot of the times? It's why a
lot of people get a bad name in this
industry. They just hang up and call a
day. They did their job. They got you
the deal. It's not my fault that they
sold like none of this my fault. Have a
nice life. Lock your number. I already
have your money. Like that's what a lot
of people would do. For us, let's make
it right. It sucks, but it such is life.
Why didn't you pay for the LC500? We
already sent it to the client. let them
know. We're waiting on the dealership to
call us back. I don't think the car is
going to sell today, but if it does, it
is what it is. We We've told the client
about the deal. That's where we're at
with that one. I can't force a client to
pay 120 grand. That's it. We're leaving.
Go finish up. Have a nice day. I got to
go take some time off, guys. I need to
go get some dinner. I've been working
since 7:00 this morning. I got to give
myself a minute to breathe. So, give me
a minute. Talk to you guys tomorrow.
Peace out, Girl Scouts. Bye-bye.