I thought you were going to fight as
hard as you could for 355.
>> Okay,
>> it's 200 bucks. Come on, you can make
that work.
>> Well, it's more than 200 bucks. Right
now, it's 400 bucks.
>> What's 200 bucks for the number you said
you felt confident you can do?
>> Uh, you know, every every dollar counts
uh on both sides, right? For you, for
me, it has to make sense. You know,
again, I'm pretty confident that I can
get another 200 bucks, but I don't know
about the whole 400. If anything
changes, I have a 3532
sitting here waiting for you.
>> Oh my gosh. I don't take money from
dealerships. That's against my morality.
I want to look for a car. We got I got
to do make a few phone calls in Florida
for a Camry. Then I think we're going to
do a fun car. My boy. Um he wants a
convenience package. Moon roof. 158 of
these cars. We are going to start making
some phone calls just like right out of
the gate. Like we're not messing around
today. So we're going to make some phone
calls in this car basically immediately.
>> It's a great day. This is Ed. How can I
help you?
>> I'm sorry. What was your name?
>> Ed.
>> Ed. I think you said. I was like, whoa,
that's a name. Uh Hey Ed, how's it
going? I just want to see if you guys
have a car available.
>> New or used?
>> Brand new.
>> Brand new. All right, give me one
second. Let me get to the right screen
here.
>> I'll give you seven seconds.
>> Seven. Okay. All right. What kind is
What is it?
>> Fast. Uh, okay. It is I have the last
six of the VIN if that helps. Make
model. What makes most sense?
>> Let's start with make, model, and then
I'll get the stock number or the VIN
number that you got there.
>> Got it. Last. It is a Camry SE
frontwheel drive.
>> Camry SE. What color? But is blue
reservoir blue.
>> Okay. I think I only have one of those
here. So, it's gonna probably make it
real easy to see if it's still here or
not. It's an SE, right?
>> SE.
>> Yeah.
>> I see E the car on your website.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. What's the last six of
the VIN?
>> Last six of the VIN is 1730.
>> That is an inbound unit. It Oh, no. It
should be here on the lot. Let me go.
Uh, let me put my hands on it and can I
give you a call right back?
>> Sure. Whatever makes more sense for you.
I'll be here.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. 980.
>> That is the best number to reach me at.
>> And what was your name, sir?
>> My name is Tommy.
>> Tommy? Yeah.
>> Tommy, give me just a couple minutes and
I'll call you right back.
>> Are you going to give you all time you
need?
>> All right. Thank you, sir. I born in 7
seconds.
>> You know, I'll give you I'll give you 17
minutes here.
>> 17 minutes. All right. I'll get you I'll
call you back in 16.
>> 16? Got it. Set a timer for 16 minutes.
Got it. All right, Tommy. I'll be I'll
be right back with you. Okay.
>> Okay. Sounds good. Bye.
>> All right. Thank you. Bye.
>> We got some good energy today, folks. We
got some good energy.
>> Hey, Tommy.
>> Holy moly. Yeah, those are the fastest
I've ever seen anybody run.
>> I'm not too far. The lot's not It's not
a huge like location and lot. So, um I
just don't like to leave people on hold.
So, uh I just walked over there real
quick and and just made sure it was
there. But it's here.
>> Awesome. Perfect. Love it. Want more of
it. Literally want the car. All right,
Alice, let's just talk the fun part, the
number
there. That bad boy.
>> So, yeah. So, I was just kind of taking
a look here. Looks like I have it listed
online at 33 and change or something.
Let me pull it back up here. Why did I
lose it? It's literally just on it.
>> $982 is change. Then you're doing pretty
well, son. I got like 92 cents in
change, but you got 982.
>> I can't even I can't I can't even rub
two pennies together right now, man. Uh
I have a it's MSRP of 35885. We have it
advertised at 33982.
To that we would have taxes, tags, and
fees. Where would this vehicle be uh
registered at?
>> It would be registered in funny enough
North Carolina. Sorry, Texas. I don't
know why I said North Carolina. I'm
going crazy.
>> Texas. Texas. Yeah, we vacation all the
time, but we live in Texas.
>> Nice. Nice. Nice. Okay. What I can do
for you, Tommy, is I can have my manager
put some uh figures together for us real
quick. Uh what's the zip code of where
it would be uh titled and registered?
>> Yes.
>> All right. And would you have a tag to
transfer or would we need to apply for
new uh Texas plates?
>> Oh, we need uh I would need a Texas
plate.
>> New plates. Okay. And did you want me to
send over the numbers with some finance
options or just
>> pay cash over the financing? Really
focused on that out the door number.
That's
>> okay. Absolutely. Absolutely. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. No problem. No problem. No
problem. Okay. Any other questions on
the vehicle?
>> No questions I have on the vehicle. I
just I just want to remind you I'm from
Texas and everything's bigger in Texas,
including the deals. So, I'm just tell
>> I was going to say the opposite. If if
everything's bigger in Texas, then the
price must be higher there, too.
>> Nah, the price isn't higher. They just
don't have the color I want. So, now I'm
looking for the I'll go I'll call go
number two. I got a great color. I got a
great deal already.
>> Okay. What uh what color? Uh
>> I have one on a supersonic red.
>> Okay. Okay. Perfect. All right. And
Yeah. Yeah. Let me uh let me get this
worked up for you. And did you want me
to text it to you, email it to you, call
you back with it? What works best for
you?
>> Call me. Call me is fine. It's cool. You
can call me, text me. If you want to
beat me, it's okay.
>> Okay. Okay. Yeah. Just give me uh give
me a couple more minutes and I'll get
back with you.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> All right. Thank you, sir.
>> No problem. Bye.
>> Mhm. Yes, sir. Bye.
>> This is Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. Ed calling you back, sir.
>> Ed. Ted. Ned. How's it going?
>> Ed. Ted. Dead. Yes, sir. Yes, sir. All
right. So, I was able to get you a
little bit better than uh internet
price. And then obviously, we'll talk
about taxes and and everything else. So,
uh your total selling price would be
$32770.
Uh like I said, I had it listed online
for $33,9.82.
So, it's about $1,200 less than my
advertised internet price. Add your car.
Uh yes, sir. Uh well, the MSRP is
358.885.
So, yeah. Yeah. About Yeah. about three
grand. Yes, sir. Yes, sir. A little bit
over three. Um remaining. Yes, sir.
Remaining uh taxes. We do have a 99.98
dealer fee and then tag, which is an
estimate because we're not 100% sure
what Texas charges until my finance
manager jumps into the nationwide DMV.
That being said, out the door. If you
want to write a check, I'm at 367.82
and 83.
>> How do we go up 4 grand? Just the dock
fee.
>> Uh so doc fee is a,000 bucks. Taxes is
$2,129.
And then between the Texas, state of
Texas fees and state of Texas t or not
taxes, state of Texas tag, we're
estimating there's about another $800 to
$900 in in fees from the state of Texas.
>> Okay. So, $8 to $900 in fees from Texas,
$9.98 for you guys, and then $2,100 in
taxes. So, you guys don't have any
dealer add-ons, fees, anything crazy. I
well we we do have a protection package
but that's factored into the discount
and then the the the purchase price
where all the breakdown no problem in
reality it's a selling price of 30,982
and then every vehicle that we have on
my lot gets a protection package which
is window tint all the way around all
weather mats and wheel locks.
>> You got me lost, Captain.
>> Sorry. No problem. No problem. Let me I
can start over. I can start over. Okay.
>> So, what is the TSRP of the car? You're
saying I thought it was 35885.
>> 35885. Okay. I'm going to discount it
$4,93,
which brings you down to 30,982.
I'm going to add back to it my
protection package, which is already on
the car. It's window tint all the way
around, all weather mats on the
interior, and then wheel locks for those
beautiful black wheels that are on it.
Brings your total purchase price to
32770. From there, we add the taxes,
tags, and fees, and that gets us back to
the 36,782, and 83 cents.
>> Okay. So, you guys added stuff,
discounted stuff, and just kind of throw
I I see I see what you've done. Really,
I was trying to get about a $4,500 net
discount on it without ads. So, I guess
that would be $6,500 off then with your
deal
>> with my 1788 protection package.
>> Yeah, I was trying to get $4,500 off is
what I was trying to get.
>> So, $4,500 off of MSRP is what you were
looking for,
>> correct? Yeah, without the ads. But you
want to do 6,500 to make it so your ads
are like I understand what you're
saying, but
>> uh so let's see here. So,
>> and those fees do seem high. I imagine
if you overestimate the fees then I
would get
>> refunded. Yeah. Yeah. That Yep. Yep.
Those are all estimates. So, you know,
it's one of those things that for me
it's like it's in reality it's 32770
plus the 998 and then taxes and and
state of Texas is is non-negotiable
because it's the state, right?
>> Yeah. Sure. Sure. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. It looks like I'm about $1,385
away from where you want to be.
>> That's that's that's what my I was doing
the same calculator math, too. That
seems I think we're on the same math,
Ed.
>> Okay. You know, obviously being in Texas
and and knowing that uh you know, you're
going to shop or you have the
availability to shop. Uh I went right to
my I
don't have the car. I I only have a red
one here. So, that's why I'm calling all
the way out here. So, I don't have an
option to shop. You give me $4,500. This
is a done deal. I do have a red one
though here that I have for $4,500 off
which is why we're calling.
>> I don't think I can do another $1,385.
Just again what I was saying is I went
right to my general manager on this one
because you are in Texas. So generally
when I have somebody that's far away, I
try not to beat around the bush too much
cuz I know that my I know that I don't
really get a lot of opportunity to
continue to keep you on the hook for
something.
>> So I don't think I have another $1,385
to give. You know, can we maybe find a
little bit more on your end to to try to
help put this together?
>> You can give me $1,300 more off instead
of 1385.
>> What if I could do like another 500
bucks? Like get you down to like 362 out
the door.
>> No.
>> Okay. What if I was at 36? It's more
than half.
>> I'll come down to 1250 cuz I like you
and your name reminds me of Ted and I
like Ted Mosby. So Ted Mosby is my
favorite favorite person on a TV show.
So I'm willing to go to 1250 for you
because that's where I'm at. But I
wouldn't go any less. But if you say you
don't know who Ted Mosby is, then that
goes right back up to 1350. So you
better lie your way through that.
>> Again, you know, talking in dealing with
the general manager, uh, typically I
don't leave myself that much room, but I
can definitely go ask. You know, I'm not
the decision maker. So, uh, you know,
it's it's one of those things that I'll
definitely go ask. And the worst he can
say is no. And if he says no, then he'll
probably give me his absolute bottom
price. But I know with the general
manager, I'm usually pretty close to the
bottom whenever I uh whenever I get
numbers from them. So
>> I get it. You are the intermediary of
this purchase. That is that is what
you're doing. I get it. Yeah. You are
just the person behind it. And in the
end, you get a commission out of it all.
So I like it. Uh yeah. I mean, this is
where I'm at with the number. So uh if
it makes sense, it makes sense. If not,
no big deal.
>> Okay. So 13, you'll do 1250 more. You
ask for 1385. Let me go see what I can
do. And um I've never really watched the
show, but it does look like it's
interesting. And I see who Ted Mosley is
now.
>> It's okay. It's the best show of all
time.
>> So yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I' I've watched a
little bit of it and it seems like it's
very very good, but I just have never
committed myself to try to sit down and
watch it.
>> Yeah. It's okay. You know, I'll forgive
you. I'll also give you 1250 out as long
as you commit to watching three
episodes.
>> Three episodes. Okay.
>> I'm actually
Which is why I'm doing this.
>> Oh,
>> I'm just kidding. That's a joke. Imagine
if I
know that would be that would be crazy.
I'd be like, "Well, then you got enough
money to pay stickers. So why are you
asking me for a discount?"
>> No, dude. They didn't pay me for the
show. I volunteered.
>> Okay, Tommy, what's your last name?
>> Last name Mosby.
>> Oh, come on.
>> Makula. M I K U L A. No, it's literally
in the show. What are the chances?
>> I don't know. I mean, all right, Tommy,
give me a couple minutes. Let me go
fight for you and see what I can do.
real quick. You go bey
real quick cuz he is going to ask me how
are we planning on getting the vehicle
to you.
>> I'm open to shipping it, open to picking
it up, you know, whatever makes the most
sense. Tomato, tomato, we'll figure that
out.
>> Okay. And how soon could you be here if
we could come to an agreement
>> ASAP? I mean, we were willing to sign it
remotely just to get the deal done
before the end of the month for you.
>> Right. Right. Okay. Um, I can't do
Docyign for out of state. So, typically
the way it works with out of state is we
take a deposit to secure the deal. My
finance manager calls you, kind of make
sure that everything is uh right as far
as the paperwork. He'll get everything
printed out. We overnight it. Once you
get it, you sign it, send it back, and
then, you know, we can worry about the
vehic picking up the vehicle after that.
>> Perfect. I like it. I like the way you
work, Ed. Let's put a deal together and
put the dream in my driveway.
>> I'm going to try, sir. I'm going to try.
Let me go Let me go talk to him and see
what I can do. Okay.
>> No. Thank you so much.
>> Yes, sir. Thank you.
>> Bye.
>> Mhm. Bye.
Hey Tommy, this is Antonio from
>> Antonio, you're back and ready, loud and
in charge.
>> Yep. Um, I sent you over a text with the
breakdown of the of the vehicles
pricing. Out the door, you'd be looking
at 35250 and we take care of all your
title work and all that here. Um, even
if it's out of state.
>> Okay, let's let's let me let me converse
these numbers real quick. Okay, so you
up your discount. Wow. Okay, I'm we're
at $41.70 discount is what you stepped
it up. You did step up. Things are
bigger in Texas. And you you you're
almost there. Um Okay. So then we have
$2,000 in taxes, $8.50 fee, electronic
fee, $1.99 reg. I think we're close. I
think we're super close. What about we
just make it 35K out the door even peasy
lemon squeezy and wrap this bad boy up?
>> Honestly, I'm pretty sure I can get my
manager to do that. Um, I mean, yeah, if
you're good with that, we would just
take that $2,500 deposit. I'm not even
going to ask my manager. I'm just going
to be like, "Hey, we're we're doing
this."
>> And this car this car is out 20 days,
you said.
>> Yep. About 20 days. So, it's expected
here the 19th or the 20th, sometime
around there. Could always get here a
little bit sooner.
>> And you And you said I have to come in
store. You guys can't do it remotely or
you said you can't do it remotely.
>> Uh, realistically, it would be easiest
if you do it in store. guys have to
figure out like getting I have to look
at flights and see if that's possible.
>> Let me see something here.
I have one with the with the convenience
package and the multimedia, but it
doesn't have the roof.
>> Oh, I really want the moon roof. I got
to howl at the moon, you know.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So, it'll have to be that
one about 20 days out. Um but yeah,
let's get it secured here for you. And
then how are you looking to pay? Were
you going to pay for the vehicle
outright or were you looking to finance?
>> I'm looking at pay in cash. Looking to
pay finance. I just have to confirm that
I can actually make it out there on the
19th or whenever that is. That's my only
tricky part.
>> Well, if you you know, if you need a
couple days, that's not a problem.
>> Yeah, I know. I just got to see what if
it makes sense. You guys can't do this
deal remotely at all.
>> If you wanted to pay for shipping, I can
find out about that.
>> Yeah, I'd pay for shipping, obviously.
Yeah. Yeah, I wouldn't do that to you.
Can you just double check to see if you
can pay for shipping and just just text
me real quick and then text me a deposit
link and let's rock and roll.
>> Um, so the deposit would be over the
phone. Let me uh let me double check
something though. You're in Dallas,
right?
>> Yep. There should be near you, I
believe.
>> Yeah, I think there is. Am I muted? I
shouldn't be muted.
>> Yeah. Okay. So, um yeah, what we can do
is we can send out the paperwork to the
near you. Basically, you would just go
there and sign. Okay.
>> And Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> Let me uh
>> and then I can pay for shipping. Okay.
Let me go get a quick shipping quote
real quick. Give me two seconds.
>> Um well, we can actually, if you want, I
can just find out with my manager. He
can get he can get me a quote as well.
>> Yeah, we can both do that real quick.
Yeah, just give me like two seconds. Let
me just let me arrange this and I'll
look at a flight real quick and then uh
yeah, we'll get this wrapped up just and
then give me the 35k.
>> All right. Um yeah, sounds good. Give me
a call back when you're uh when you're
ready. I'll send you my number. All
right.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> All right. Bye.
>> Bye,
>> Tommy.
>> Ed.
>> Yes, sir. All right.
>> Call me. I call you.
>> I know. I know. Are you Am I buying a
car or you buying a car? I don't know
what's going on.
>> I don't I don't know. I mean, hopefully
hopefully we're buying a car for you.
>> All right. All right. All right. So,
here's what I got, man. I went to the uh
back to the general manager and I got
you to Well, here you asked me for
35532.
I'm at 35932.
>> Dude, I hate to do this, man, for you,
but while we were waiting here, I had a
dealership that just called me back and
said they were 35 out the door
>> on the red one.
>> No, on a blue one just south of you
guys.
>> On a blue one.
>> Yeah, there's a whole bunch of these
blue ones in Florida. There's like
nothing in Texas. They don't like blue
in Texas. Um, I mean the only the only
thing I could say is that we got to
obviously make sure that we're
comparing, you know, apples to apples as
far as equipment. You know, if theirs
has, you know, maybe an accessory or
something that mine doesn't have that
allows them to get to uh to that price.
So, you know, that's the only thing that
would that would be of my concern, you
know, is is is that. But I'm fighting
for you, man. That's pretty good. I got
you within 400 bucks of what you asked
me to get you, man. That's that's pretty
good.
>> I know. I I get it. That's is close. And
your guys' car is on the ground today.
It's on the ground right now. Yep.
>> If you guys get to 355, that makes it a
little more appealing because that car's
other car is 20 days out. So then I can
get a car today versus 20 days, but not
for 900 bucks. Not not 9. It's too much
of a difference.
>> Okay. If I can get you another couple
hundred, I can get you like 357.
>> 355, man. That's that's the number. I
mean, for me, $500 more to have it 20
days earlier. I don't mind that.
>> Well, like I said, you asked me for
35532. I'm at 35932. Can I Can we do
357?
>> We moved. We We got here. I told I told
you my number. I'm not I'm not I'm not a
changer.
>> I know. So, well, here here's here's the
thing, man. Ultimately, it's it's a
negotiation, right? It's got to make
sense for you. It's got to make sense
for me. So, your number hasn't moved.
Mine has. So, can you help me out a
little bit?
>> My number. I I I moved my number. You're
asking me to move my number a second
time.
>> Yep. I've moved I've moved twice and and
you've moved once. So, now can you move
the second time to to meet me to meet me
a little bit closer to where my my
manager wants to be? 357. I know I can
get that done. I had to really really go
fight for the 355. So, it's less than
200 bucks that we're talking about.
>> I thought you were the intermediary
acting on my behalf. I thought you were
going to fight as hard as you could for
the 355.
>> I did. I did. Now, now I got to now I
got to turn it around and fight for him
because he asked me to.
>> Ed, I need you to go watch how you made
your mother cuz Ted Mosby did not give
up at all. He was a fighter and you
remind me of Ted. So, yeah. No, I uh I
like I said, I'm giving you my number
and I'm being serious with it. Okay.
>> It's 200 bucks. Come on. You can make
that work. Well, it's more than 200
bucks. Right now, it's 400 bucks.
>> What's 200 bucks for the number you said
you felt confident you could do?
>> I understand. I just, you know,
obviously for us when we start to get
this deep into the deal, uh, you know,
every every dollar counts, uh, on both
sides, right? For you, for me, it has to
make sense. So, I will go try, but I
can't promise anything. You know, again,
I'm pretty confident that I can get
another 200 bucks, but I don't know
about the whole 400.
>> Okay. Well, I do have that offer that's
going to be in 20 days for 35,000 out
the door for Myers. Uh, I would just if
I can get one 20 days earlier. You're
you're speaking my language a little
bit.
>> That's got to be worth something, right?
>> It is. It's worth about
>> be worth that's got it's worth it's
worth about 500 bucks. It's got to be
worth a little bit more than that if you
can get it that much.
>> 550 bucks cuz that's that would be the
difference.
>> Uh, Tommy, I love it. Let me uh let me
go fight for you, sir. I I I do
appreciate the opportunity. Let me go
fight. Okay.
>> No problem. Thank you.
>> All right. Yes, sir. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> No, Ed is good. Like, guys, get me
wrong. Like, Ed is doing his job. Like,
I'm not mad. Like people get like, "Oh,
you don't like this." Ed is doing his
job. He's trying to He's trying to
negotiate up. He's trying to do this. Um
he's doing good. This car is in the
build phase. I don't want a car that's
going to be here later. That doesn't
make any sense. So, I'm looking for a
car that'll be here sooner. I have
deals. I texted them to my client. Those
would be the best two options. Okay. The
red one. Uh here. Wait. Who guess? Okay.
>> Why are you making your life so
difficult?
>> I I'm I'm reading your text. See, this
is what's confusing about you Toyota
folks. Okay, so the estimated arrival is
8:23 of 2025. What was it before?
>> Uh 92, but it I mean it firms up along
the way. I just didn't feel like sitting
there going back and forth with the
customer. I'm just like, okay.
>> Okay. So 8 823 and you're at 334 out the
door with no shipping.
>> Yep. Blackout package and moon roof.
>> Okay. Let me let me let me talk to
Isaiah. Let me call him real quick.
>> Homeboy be crazy if he doesn't take
that.
>> Yeah, it's a stupid deal. I knew it was
a stupid video at the very beginning,
but you don't have the color.
>> It's reservoir blue, right?
>> I know you do have that one. Okay, let
me
>> What color is he? Wait, what color is he
wanting?
>> No, no, no. You have the right color.
You have the reservoir is the right
color. But your color, let me call him
real quick.
>> Reservoir blue, black and No.
>> Ed, you're going to be mad at me.
>> Don't even do it,
>> dude. I just got a deal that I can't say
no to. I have to take it.
>> What is it,
>> Ed? If I tell you this deal, you're not
going to believe me, and I I get it, but
I I have to take it.
>> Okay. What is it? Tell me.
>> It's 336 out the door. and free
shipping. $6,000 discount.
>> 33 what now?
>> 336 out the door
>> on what car?
>> On a Camry SE with a moon roof and a
convenience package. It just doesn't
have all the port installed accessories
and they're willing to give me a crazy
deal on it.
>> Wow. Where's that from?
>> A little bit closer to me, but they're
also paying for the shipping, too. But
they were they weren't even near me
before. They were saying they weren't
going to do a deal and the car was too
far away and now they they just made it
all work. So, I'm sorry. Yeah,
>> everybody. And
>> you were great, Ed. You were great.
Dang, I feel bad.
>> Well, then just pay the extra and get
mine. What's a couple What's a What's a
couple What's a couple grand between
friends?
>> I know, Ed. Ed, and you know, I I really
do appreciate you. And uh
>> Yep.
>> And I hope uh I hope you get some
business, but I have to take this deal.
>> Okay. If anything changes, I have a
sitting here waiting for you.
>> Oh my gosh. Don't don't. Okay. If
anybody in the world that I know knows
wants a 35532 out the door.
>> No, no, no, no, no. If you send anybody
to me, they I got to try to make money
off of them. So, you know, you got you
send them to me. I make money and then I
can send you
>> and what if I got thousands of friends
right now?
>> That's awesome. Yeah. Yeah. Send them
over to me and we can try to make money
and then I'll break you off I'll break
you off a 100 bucks for everybody that
you
>> I don't I don't take money from
dealerships. That's against my morality.
>> Oh jeez. Why?
>> Oh. Uh it's it's it's it's a whole
thing. You wouldn't understand. It's
okay.
>> You'll you'll learn Ed. You'll learn Ed.
But uh but you're great.
>> Okay. If anything changes, if uh for
some reason they uh go back on their
number or anything like that, let me
know. this offer is good through the end
of the month, which is tomorrow, or if
the car sells.
>> Okay, awesome, man. I'm excited.
>> All right, Tommy. Thank you.
>> Talk to you later. Bye.
>> Yep. Bye.
>> So, the three options we have, shipping
from this distance is about a,000 bucks,
uh, would be what it cost us. So, we
have one that'll be here at 35,000 out
the door, and that'll be 1,000 bucks to
ship, but it'll be here in 20 days. I
have one that I think I'm going to get
down to 355 that's on the ground today,
and it'll cost 1,000 bucks to ship.
Otherwise, I just talked to the
dealership that we were talking to at
the first place, the one we originally
closed the deal out. That car estimated
arrival now is 823. So, it's 23 days and
they're down to 334 out the door with no
shipping. I guess little shipping from
>> Houston told me about
>> Yeah, the the original one, the one we
were going to close that was going to be
here in September is now going to be
here in 20 days.
>> Oh, I'll do that.
>> Okay, cool. Let's just wrap it 334. Call
it a day. That's crazy. That's a crazy
deal.
>> You said 33 what? Uh 334 out the door.
>> Out the door. Oh, perfect.
>> Yeah, that's what And it'll be here in
about 20 days.
>> Yeah, that's that that works for me.
>> Okay, perfect. I know before it was
going to be here in September and that
was the problem. So now this will be
here faster. Bada boom, bada bing.
Congratulations. That's a crazy deal.
That's almost 6K off. So
>> awesome. Thank you so much. Appreciate
it.
>> Hey, no problem. I'll talk to you later.
>> Bye.
>> Boom. Okay, that one worked. So you guys
know, just so you guys explain what what
is going on. So we originally had this
deal closed for the client, right? We
originally had this deal closed for the
client for like a $6,000 discount.
Insane discount on this car. Okay, guys.
I'm going to jump off here. I got I got
stuff to do. I got to go. Please like,
follow, subscribe, go watch my YouTube
video, and I will talk to you guys here
soon.
[Music]