Holy moly. Is it a party at your
dealership? Yeah. I don't want to give
an address to a person that I just met.
My mom told me stranger danger and I I
don't know you.
>> Yeah. It's one of the worst audios I've
heard in a while. No, that's fine. You
can get one earlier. I'm not I'm not
arguing with you. Let's just let's I
guess next step is let's let's agree to
numbers. What's the numbers?
>> And then you want this one specifically
the SC with the convenience package. The
moon roof. It's
>> got to have the moon roof. I got to look
I got to howl how you know. All right. I
want to look for a car. We got I got to
do make a few phone calls in Florida for
a Camry. Then I think we're going to do
a fun car room. He wants a convenience
package, moon roof, 158 of these cars.
We are going to start making some phone
calls just like right out of the gate.
Like we're not messing around today. So
we're going to make some phone calls in
this car basically immediately.
>> Thank you for calling
TV. Who I have a pleasure speaking to.
>> Hey, my name is Tommy. How's it going?
>> Good Tommy. How are you? Hey, I am doing
just fantast.
Holy moly. Is it a party at your
dealership?
>> Let me just move around. Is that a new
car or
>> It's a It's a brand new car.
>> What kind of vehicle is it?
>> I have a stock number if that helps. A
stock number is going to be 53484.
>> All right. 53484.
>> That's correct. Toyota Camry
Toyota Camry SE and the color is blue
color that we have and it looks like it
is available. Are you planning to stop
by today to take a look at it?
>> I already drove it. I know. I want it.
Just looking for the best price.
>> I got you. I got you. Let me do this for
you. Let me put your information here
and make a profile for you. I'll send
you the best price. How about that?
>> Sounds great.
>> All right. And if the number is the best
for you, will you be here today or
what's your plan? I could commit today
if that works.
>> Yes, sir. All right. Tell me how you
spell your first and last name. T O.
>> First name is T O M I.
>> Last name M I K U L A.
>> We can
>> I can give you my zip code. Does that
help?
>> No, I mean it helps, but they want the
full address, sir. I mean, I'm just
taking all the information that helps me
to get the number for you right away.
>> Uh, yeah. My zip code is sorry the
office got really loud here too.
>> Supposed to be and this is a out of
state of Florida right? What state is
it?
>> It is not Florida. Seven is not Florida.
>> Yeah. So in that case I got to have a
full address for out of Florida so we
can calculate the taxes.
>> No I don't even need you to calculate my
taxes. Let's just let's just let's just
jump on the numbers first.
>> I can't s there. I mean Tommy if you
these are the things that help me to get
the number for you. If you won't give me
this information they won't give me the
number. So, I mean, if you want, I can
have the manager to call you back. Maybe
they can, but as far as that, they won't
give me anything. So,
>> yeah. Yeah. I don't want to give an
address to a person that I just met. My
mom told me stranger danger, and I I
don't know you.
>> I don't understand like the whole
conversation here. You want the best
number, I told you what we need. You
don't want to give it to me, I give you
a man, I just call you back. You don't
have to insult anybody. I mean, I just
don't understand the concept of you
talking like this.
>> I'm not trying to insult you. I
literally can barely hear you. That's
the That's the meme.
>> I got you. But
>> and as you get louder, somehow the
background noise somehow gets louder.
It's like It's like It's like all at the
same time.
>> I got you. I got you. I mean, you assume
that I'm in a call center, which I'm
not. But let me just have a manager to
call you back so you can get the
numbers. Okay.
>> Yeah, that'd be somebody that can give
me numbers. That would be awesome.
>> You don't have to even hang up. Let me
see if I can transfer you. Just give me
one second.
>> Okay. Sounds good.
>> All right, Tommy. Nice talking to you.
Uh, I mean the the the pleasure was all
yours.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Absolutely.
>> Somebody's going to be like, "Tommy,
Tommy, why are you giving this guy a
hard time?" Dealerships, if you're
watching this, that would be what maybe
your dealership sounds like when
somebody's trying to spend 30 something
thousand at your dealership. Maybe maybe
you should invest in your BDC to have
better headphones. Some AirPod Pros can
knock out all that noise in two seconds.
>> You live on TikTok? Yeah, I'm live
trying to buy a car.
>> Sure. I don't think so.
>> What do you mean? No. No. Literally, I'm
live on TikTok trying to buy a car.
>> Thank you for calling Toyota,
>> familyowned and operated dealer since
Toyota.
>> Meanwhile,
>> hey Tommy.
>> Hey. What's up,
>> Mr.
>> Hey. I got you the manager right now.
>> Your audience.
>> Hey, sir. How you doing today?
>> Hey, I'm doing well by yourself.
>> Very good. How can I help you? I'm just
trying to get some numbers on this car.
>> Not a problem. What was it? What was the
hold up? I'm sorry. I just got involved
in the conversation. Hold up.
>> I mean, I was told that I needed an
address. I had a zip code. I said you
could just do plus tax. I just don't
want to give the address out to
somebody.
>> No, it's 75243. It's out of state.
>> And what city and state?
>> Uh, it is Texas.
>> We're in Texas.
>> Uh, yep. I'm getting that right now.
>> I can just Google as
>> But it's the zip code is
>> fine. Are we going to email to you or we
going to do you want to email it or text
me?
>> Just texting me is great.
>> All right. So, what I'm going to do is
I'm going to send it over to you with no
tax. There's not going to be any tag
fees. We can't figure that out till we
get the address. So, let's just go
through the price to make sure that
looks right. As soon as that looks
right, then we can go further in we can
go further in the date and get the rest
of the info.
>> Okay. Hey, and and now because you guys
know that I'm live on TikTok, my advice
would be to like listen to the phone
call and like how like crazy the
background noise is, man, because this
is insane. Like I it sounds like a call
center that I'm calling right now. I bet
like you just remodel your might need to
get some different headsets cuz it
sounds crazy. Just go listen to it and
you'll be like, "Oh, wow. That sounds
great." Like I can hear the
conversations going on right next to you
right now.
>> Yeah.
I appreciate that very much. But we'll
go through that and I'll get to say it
to you later.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> All right. Thanks.
>> I will say to this point, I have no idea
what the last sentence he just said at
all. I'm assuming he said something
something something something. I'll get
back to you, brother. Yeah, it was one
of the worst audios I've heard in a
while. Good afternoon.
Speaking my director call.
>> Hello. Can I speak to new car sales?
>> One minute.
>> Hello, Jim.
>> Is Is your name Jim?
>> Thank you for call.
>> Yeah, thanks. Thank you for calling.
What can we do for you?
>> Hi, Jim. Uh, I just wanted to see if you
guys have a car available.
>> Yeah, of course. I can I can definitely
double check for you. What kind of car
is it?
>> I have the last four of a VIN number. I
have a make, model. What makes the most
sense? Give me one second. And you said,
"What was the um the number you gave me?
The last four or the last six that you
gave me for that car?"
>> Yeah. 32 F as in Frankie 076.
>> Oh, it's a new car.
>> It's brand new. I'm I'm a new guy.
>> What kind of car is it?
>> Uh it is a Toyota Camry hybrid.
>> Toyota Camry. Uh let me check for you
because usually when there once the
fourth number is an F that mean the car
is in production and it's not um in
stock yet.
>> Oh okay. So
>> yeah. Yeah. Once once you see when the
la last four number if it is not a
number if it is a letter that mean it's
not in um that's that's mean it's in
production. It's not here yet. It's
still a good thing but it's just in
production. Uh let me take a look real
quick.
>> Yeah double check. Maybe you have 17 of
them just sitting right in front of you.
You never know.
>> Yeah. I see which one you're looking
for. I can definitely get I'll try to
get that for you a little bit earlier if
you need ones um earlier. Oh, this one
is 20 days out.
>> Oh, 20 days out. That's not that bad.
>> Oh, it's not that bad. Okay.
>> Yeah. I mean, if you can find one
sooner, that's great. I mean, as long as
I get a deal, I'm happy.
>> If you want one right away, I can get
you one right away, though.
>> Okay. Yeah. I mean, I'd like one sooner
rather than
>> because what happened? When do you want
to come in so we can work a deal on it?
Uh, never. Preferably. I'd prefer to do
this all at home.
>> Oh, you want to do it at home?
>> Yeah, I like to I'm sitting in a in my
desk chair. That's really nice. Like, I
like it.
>> What do you want me to do? Um, I can get
the car tomorrow, as early as tomorrow
for you.
>> Wow. You can get one as early as
tomorrow. That's this this spec.
>> I got five stores. I got one sitting at
the other store. But this actual one
you're looking at is 20 days out.
>> No, that's fine. You can get one
earlier. I'm not I'm not arguing with
you. Let's just let's I guess next step
is let's agree to numbers. What's the
numbers?
>> All right. Um, I'm going to text you
from my phone.
>> Nice.
>> What's your phone number again?
>> Yeah, my phone number is
>> And your first name is?
>> My first name is Tommy.
>> And what's your last name, Mr. Tom?
>> My last name is Mula. M I K U L A.
>> All right. I'll go ahead and put you in
the system and stuff with um with that
information I get with with my manager
real quick and then you're going to give
me a quote and then I send it back your
ways. Now, do you have an idea where you
what you're looking at? What is that
number if you can see that?
>> Easy peasy. $4,000 off MSRP.
>> All right. All right. I know it's not
good for you.
>> Okay. Awesome.
>> But let me see if I can do that, sir.
And then um I text the information in a
few. Okay.
>> Yeah. Abs. Absolutely. Yeah. Take all
take take all the time that you need.
Whenever you're ready, let me know.
>> Yes, sir. Yes, sir. Byebye.
>> All right. Bye.
It's a great day. This is Ed. How can I
help you?
>> I'm sorry. What was your name?
>> Ed.
>> Ed. I thought you said dead. I was like,
whoa, that's a name. Uh,
>> hey, Ed. How's it going? I just want to
see if you guys have a car available.
>> New or used?
>> Brand new.
>> Brand new. All right. Give me one
second. Let me get to the right screen
here.
>> Seven seconds.
>> All right. What kind is What is it?
>> Fast. Uh, okay. It is I have the last
six of the VIN if that helps. Make
model. What makes most sense? All right,
let's start with make, model, and then
I'll get the stock number or the VIN
number that you got there.
>> Got it. Last, it is a Camry SE
frontwheel drive.
>> Camry SE. What color?
>> It is blue. Reservoir blue.
>> Okay. I think I only have one of those
here. So, it's going to probably make it
real easy to see if it's still here or
not. Uh, it's an SE, right?
>> SE.
>> Yeah.
>> I see the car on your website.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. What's the last
six of the VIN?
>> Last six of the VIN is 173050.
>> That is an inbound unit. It Oh, no. It
should be here on the lot. Let me go uh
let me put my hands on it. And can I
give you a call right back?
>> Sure. Whatever makes more sense for you.
I'll be here.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Tommy, give me just a
couple minutes and I'll call you right
back.
>> Are you going to give me all the time
you need?
>> All right. Thank you, sir. I born in 7
seconds.
>> You know, I'll give you I'll give you 17
minutes here.
>> 17 minutes. All right. I'll get you I'll
call you back in 16.
>> 16. Got it. Set a timer for 16 minutes.
Got it.
>> All right, Tommy. I'll be I'll be right
back with you. Okay.
>> Okay. Sounds good. Bye.
>> All right. Thank you. Bye,
>> Antonio. How can I help you?
>> Antonio, I just want to see if you guys
have a car available.
>> All right. Give me one second. I can
help you out with that. Is it a new or
pre-owned vehicle?
>> It is a brand new vehicle.
>> All right. Uh, what's your name, by the
way?
>> Uh, my name is Tommy. What is your name?
Antonio, I know your name. That was a
joke. That was a test. You failed.
>> Uh, what vehicle was it that you wanted
to see if it was available?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Perfect. What is it?
>> Stock number is S is in SAM, U is in
uranium, 32, D is in dog,
152.
>> All right. So, I have good news. The
cart is available. The only thing it's
not here yet.
>> That's okay. How when is it going to be
there?
>> Uh, it's estimated right now about 20
days out. And then you wanted this one
specifically, the SC with the
convenience package, the moon roof.
>> It's got to have the moon roof. I got to
look. I gotta howl how, you know.
>> All right. So, I mean, yeah, the vehicle
is available. If you like what we can
do, we can go over numbers, try to get
an agreement on that. If everything
looks good, we secure the vehicle for
you. We take a $2,500 deposit and go
from there.
>> 25% of deposit. Holy moly, that's a
strong one. But if the deal is worth it,
you know, my mom always said, "Put your
money where your mouth is." So, let's
hear this deal. then I'm I'm I'm
interested.
>> All right. So, let me get my manager to
do the numbers. I don't really have any
control over that. Um I'm going to send
you over a text right now. If you can
say yes to that, I will send you over a
um a breakdown of the numbers and I'll
give you a call as well so we can go
over it and if everything looks good, we
can uh go ahead and secure that vehicle
for you. All right.
>> Yep. No problem.
>> All right. Awesome. I'll send that over
here shortly and we'll be in touch.
>> Hey, no problem. Bye.
>> Hey, Tommy.
>> Holy moly. Yeah, that was the fastest
I've ever seen anybody run.
I'm not too far. The lot's not it's not
a huge like location and lot. So, I just
don't like to leave people on hold. So,
uh I just walked over there real quick
and and just made sure it was there. But
it's here.
>> Awesome. Perfect. Love it. Want more of
it. Literally want the car. Now, let's
let's just talk the fun part, the
number,
that bad boy.
>> So, yeah. So, I was just kind of taking
a look here. here. Looks like I have it
listed online at
33 and change or something. Let me pull
it back up here. Why did I lose it?
Literally just on it.
>> $982 is change. Then you're doing pretty
well, son. I got like 92 cents in
change, but you got $98.
>> I can't even I can't I can't even rub
two pennies together right now, man. Uh
I have a It's MSRP of 358.885. We have
it advertised at 33,982.
to that we would have taxes, tags, and
fees. Where would this vehicle be uh
registered at?
>> It would be registered in, funny enough,
North Car No, North Carolina. Sorry,
Texas. I don't know why I said North
Carolina. I'm going crazy.
>> Texas. Texas. Yeah, we vacation all the
time, but we live in Texas.
>> Nice, nice, nice. Okay, what I can do
for you, Tommy, is I can have my manager
put some uh figures together for us real
quick. And would you have a tag to
transfer or would we need to apply for
new Texas plates? I we need uh I would
need a Texas plate.
>> New plates. Okay. And did you want me to
send over the numbers with some finance
options or
>> just open cash open financing? Really
focused on that out the door number.
That's
>> okay. Absolutely. Absolutely. Any other
questions on the vehicle?
>> No questions having the vehicle. I just
I just want to remind you I'm from Texas
and everything's bigger in Texas,
including the deals. So,
>> I'm just I was going to say the
opposite. If if if everything's bigger
in Texas, then the price must be higher
there, too.
>> N the price isn't higher. They just
don't have the color I want. So, now I'm
looking for the I'll go I'll call go
number two. I got a great color. I got a
great deal already.
>> Okay. What uh what color?
>> Uh I have one on a supersonic red.
>> All right. And Yeah. Yeah. Let me uh let
me get this worked up for you. And did
you want me to text it to you, email it
to you, call you back with it? What
works best?
>> Call me. Call me is fine. It's cool. You
can call me, text me. If you want to
beat me, it's okay.
>> Okay. Okay. Yeah. Just give me uh give
me a couple more minutes and I'll get
back with you.
>> Okay, sounds good.
>> All right. Thank you, sir.
>> No problem. Bye.
>> Mhm. Yes, sir. Bye.
[Music]
>> My name is Tommy. I negotiate car deals
for a living. I own a company called
Delivered. My goal is to save you time,
energy, and anxiety. We save you money,
but that's a byproduct. We take care of
the whole car buying process for you so
you don't have to deal with it. We will
negotiate the price of the car, the
tray, the add-ons, the accessories. You
sit back, relax the entire time. We
charge a flat fee of a,000 bucks. I
don't advertise this as a money-saving
service because guess what? You can do
this on your own. Just like you can mow
your own grass, you can represent
yourself in legal court, and you can do
your own taxes. But people hire us cuz
they don't want to deal with the hassle.
If you want to learn more, you can sit
back, relax, and enjoy the show.
[Music]