You can kind of hear him breathe. See,
like that. Like he's hearing that.
>> Well, it's not a question of making me
more happy. If there's an incentive I
can give you, I'll happily give it to
you. But
>> this is worse than my open mic, though.
Did you Did you fall down? Are you okay?
I do want to know what happened to Sam.
The more I think about it, the more I
think it was a hit. Actually, I feel so
unprofessional. I'm going to tighten my
tie. I'm sorry. Are you right? It was
good that Sam fell down the well. So, if
you guys don't know who I am, right? A
lot of people are like, "Who is this?
Who is this nerdy little 5-year-old
that's on the stream telling people how
to buy a car? If you guys don't know, my
name's Tommy. I own a company called
Delivered. We negotiate car deals for a
living. My goal with all this company is
to save you time, energy, and anxiety.
We save you money, but that's a
byproduct of it all. You can do this on
your own. You don't have to hire me to
do this. You can literally watch my
tips, watch my videos, watch these
streams, and learn how to do this. I
don't have a magic wand or a secret
sauce that saves you thousands of
dollars more than you can your own. I I
am very good at what I do. I know how to
have the conversations. I know the games
the dealerships play and I'm just
willing to put up with a lot of the BS
because you know that's what we do. We
are going to be negotiating on
an EV9. Okay. Anyway, let's go. One of
the other reasons why they said they
hated me on the Facebook group is that
they said I'm so annoying and so rude
because I make I use different letters
than the the phonetic alphabet or
whatever. They're like, "It's so rude
and disrespectful and not taking us
seriously to use different letters in
the phonetic alphabet." Oh, also for the
pe for the people who thought that I was
actually going to be serious, get out of
here. We don't change for nobody. But I
do need to fix one thing cuz I got to be
more serious because I want to be more
serious. I want people to take me more
seriously and understand I'm a
professional. I'll be right back.
>> Meanwhile,
>> I wanted people to see that I'm more
professional. So, I brought my tie and
then my my medal from the Royal
Caribbean, which obviously was given to
me cuz I was a professional. I'm really
going to show people that I'm different
and I'm not like those other guys. I'm
not like the people they think I am.
>> Sales is Tim.
>> I'm sorry. You said this is him.
>> Tim?
>> Tim? Oh my goodness. I'm so sorry. My my
I'm getting old. My memory is not what
it used to be. I want to see if you guys
have a car available.
>> Okay. What are you looking for?
>> I have a stock number if that helps.
>> Okay. What's up?
>> Okay, stock number is K as in kind of. M
is in maybe. 3697.
>> EV9 GT line.
>> EV9 GT line. All-wheel drive. Bada boom,
bada bing. That is the one I'm looking
for. Already know I want it. Already
love it. Fell in love with it. Want more
of it. Uh really just trying to get a
deal by the end of the month like
everybody else. And hoping you can help
me out.
>> Yeah, I'm sorry. Where are you calling
from?
>> I'm calling from New Hampshire. Is that
okay?
>> Okay. No, no, that's perfectly fine. It
says Alton, North Carolina on my phone.
>> Oh, I used to once upon a time live in
North Carolina, which is is why it's a
North Carolina number, but no. Hopefully
that's okay. Yeah. Hopefully you're okay
with people that used to be the North
Carolina that have North Carolina
numbers.
>> Uh, it could be worse. It could be from
New York and a Yankees fan.
>> That's true. My mom always said anybody
who's a Yankees fan needs to be thrown
in the river. She didn't even know what
baseball was. That was the crazy part.
>> There we go. 3697 Wolf G.
>> You're good. Take all the time in the
world. I have nowhere to be.
>> Okay. When did you want to come in?
>> The second we agree to numbers, I'll be
there.
>> Okay. Well, are you leasing, purchasing?
>> Looking to either 0% or finance the car
with the bigger rebate without the 0%.
Okay.
>> Open either one.
I'm not muting. He's just not saying
anything. I just muted myself to him,
but he's not muting. He's just He's just
not saying any words. There's no mute
happening here. I I muted my mic so he
can't hear me, but he's still there. You
can kind of hear him breathe. See
>> like that. Like he's right there.
>> Sorry. The technology is the greatest
thing in the world until it's not
working.
>> You know what? My mom told me if I ever
used Chat GPT, she'd disown me.
>> I don't know. That's a little excessive.
It sounds like she was looking for an
excuse.
>> She doesn't She doesn't Again, she
doesn't like technology. She said she's
just like you. She said technology is
the worst. She says it gets in your mind
and controls you. But again, she's the
one that didn't like the Yankees and uh
wanted to throw them in the river and
she doesn't know the Yankees are. Kind
of crazy lady. I do love her. You got to
love your mom.
>> Uh let me see. Um are you uh in the
military? Active or retired?
>> No, they wouldn't take me.
>> I'm sorry. What's your name, sir?
>> My name's Tommy.
>> Tommy. Nice to meet you, Tommy. I'm Tim.
>> Tommy? Tim? I'll never forget it. Some
people call me Tim, but my name's not
Tim. though. But they think Tommy is
too.
>> And I get called. Yeah. No, I get I get
Jim, Kim, Ken. I get all kinds of
>> the worst people that don't get names
right the first time. They're the worst.
>> Okay. Can I put you on hold for one
second, Tony?
>> You can put me on hold as long as you
want. I have nowhere to be.
>> All right. Thanks, sir.
>> The car salesman said I'm not being
serious enough and they don't like me
because I'm wasting their time and not
being serious. So, I'm changing my ways
and I'm being more of a serious person.
Still trying to buy a car. But everybody
would love to work with a car salesman
like Tim that has no sense of
personality. That just was like that
that everybody would love that. That's a
way better experience than dealing with
somebody that makes a few funny jokes
that half of them are funny, but you're
like, "He's trying."
>> Hello.
>> Oh, hello. I thought I lost you.
>> No, no, sorry. I was just uh I was just
talking about my mom.
>> What? Uh I just want to try to make sure
I give her the uh all the incentives
that I can. What are you currently
driving now or have registered in your
name?
>> Oh, we have a Kia right now.
>> You have a Kia? What uh what model?
>> Uh Kia Sarrento.
>> STO. Okay. Does that help me? Do I get
bonus points for that?
>> Well, that I'm trying to see if I can do
like apply like an order loyalty.
>> Oh, okay. I just didn't know if it was
the right question. If not, I don't have
a Kia. Like I I can say that whatever
answer makes you more happy.
>> Well, it's not a question making me more
happy. If there's an incentive I can
give you, I'll happily give it to you,
but I would need proof of ownership of
said Kia. So, do you actually own a
Santo?
>> No, I do own a Kia. I do own a Kia. Yes.
>> Okay.
>> This is worse than my open mic, though.
So, if you want to finance, there's a 0%
option or notebook.
>> Essentially, you can finance at 0% for
up to 48 months.
>> Got it.
>> But there's no
>> Sorry, I was taking notes.
>> But no, it's okay. So, 0% is available
for up to 48 months, but there's no
incentive to do so.
>> No incentive 0%. That's bad then.
>> Meaning obviously 0% is the incentive in
and of itself. But you can do there's
like conventional financing through Kia
the rates higher. you'd be 7.75% but
they gave you $5,000 to do that. So
depending on how long you're actually
going to keep the financing, like if
you're going to keep it for the full
term, that's up to 72 months. So if
you're going to keep it the full 72
months, obviously you're going to pay
more than 5,000 in interest just making
a minimum payment. But you know, a lot
of our cash customers even like they
will they'll do the financing, put a
chunk down, do the financing, and then
just pay it off early. So there's really
only no wrong way to do it. Like it just
you know what I mean? Cool. Awesome. So,
the rebates 5,500 or no rebate with 0%.
Those are my two incentives.
>> 5,000 for financing and 1,000 bonus cash
and 1,000 for owner loyalty. So, it
would be 7,000 total. Uh, and incentive
>> 5,000 total. I'm sorry. I wait. Oh, the
loyalty gets me how much?
>> Loyalty is 1,000.
>> Loyalty is a 1,000. Got it.
>> And I would need like an active
registration with qualifying VIN and uh
registered to you or somebody that's
going to be on the deal. So, if it was
like you and a spouse or a partner,
whatever it is, if you're both on the
paperwork, the the owner loyalty could
apply to whoever it's registered to. It
just needs to be an active registration.
>> So, the price, the MSRP of the car is
78,430
and you guys are giving $7,000 off with
the incentive money bringing it down to
71430.
>> Yes.
>> Is that all? Curious what would have
happened if I didn't ask if that's all.
I think you would have charged me MSRP
to make more money.
>> You're not trading anything in correct?
Uh, no, nothing that we need to worry
about.
>> Okay. To be registered in New Hampshire.
>> Uh, it would be registered in New
Hampshire. Correct. Seems like you guys
are old school. You guys do match your
abacus. I like that. I'm an abacus type
of guy.
>> Whatever get you there, brother.
>> Well, speed the speed's good. Rather
slow but steady. I was always won the
race.
>> Well, my New Hampshire templates not
loading, so I can't do the New Hampshire
like fees and everything else for the
moment, but So, I mean, I can do like I
mean, I could take a,000 off the MSRP.
>> Oh, you guys going to get $1,000 off the
MSRP? Wow. Okay. Okay. So, yours are now
at $70,430.
Is that correct?
>> Yeah. I mean, it sale price minus
incentives, but then obviously fees and
like registry fees, everything else
would have to be added back in, but
>> Yeah. Yeah. Plus, plus TTL. Okay.
>> Plus, plus Yeah.
>> Plus, plus Yeah. Plus, plus I don't know
if that's proper math, but I I I think I
see what you're doing. Okay. 70,430.
That's all you can do. I mean, if you
want to take the ride down and we can
sit down. I'll do the best I can for
you, but I would imagine I'm getting
worked against the rest of the world
between here in New Hampshire and
Martial, too. So,
>> I mean, there's I mean, it's the last 5
days of the EV incentive. I imagine
everybody's either buying these cars or
not buying these cars, you know, like in
5 days, this this car becomes a little
bit more of a paper weight.
>> Yeah. Well, I mean, the the the
incentives really that are are EVs don't
apply to this cuz it's too it's above uh
$55,000.
>> So, Kia is not doing any type of
incentive on this car. Well, I said
there's there's the $5,000 for financing
through Kia, but those and then the
owner loyalty and military things like
that that you know that would apply to
this, but there's no like like on like
narrow EVs that are like $40,000 there
is you know the extra 75 plus I think
another three grand. So, there's a lot
more incentives on the lower priced EV
vehicles, but at this price point, like
this is what's available.
>> And none of that incentive money is like
Kia doesn't do like an EV tax credit for
their leases. And that's part of the way
they're selling them. And
>> not through Kia. No.
>> So, there's no there's no lease EV
credit. If I if I lease a car, the
rebates, I don't get any ext
There is lease EV credit on the lower
price point vehicles.
>> Okay. So, you're saying on an EV9 that
isn't a GT line or just not the EV9 as a
whole?
>> The EV9 at $70,000 like the the vehicles
that we're talking about are like 55,000
and below.
>> I thought on leasing the the get around
to that is to just offer it on the
lease. I've seen other dealerships
offering it on the EV9 offering some
type of incentive above and beyond. Now,
if you tell me it's not on the GT line,
we can have that conversation. And you
know, I'm not I'm not I'm not the car
buying expert here, but I thought it was
on some of the V9s at the very least.
>> Can you hold on one second, Tommy? I'm
going to send you over to uh one of my
other sales managers, Sam. Hold on one
second.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Give me to one of the other.
>> This is Sam.
>> Hey, this is Tom. You just said it was
Tim.
>> Sam.
>> Sam. Tim. He was telling me that he told
you about the rebates we have on the
finance option. There's anything I can
help to make the things. Uh so, there's
any specific car you're looking to
>> Yeah, I'm looking at this deal. I asked,
he said he was doing $1,000 off and I
said, "Can you do any better than that?"
He said, "No, everybody's trying to buy
this car right now. I've seen
dealerships offering two, three, four,
five grand off these cars. I know a lot
of people were trying to sell EVs before
the tax credit ends." And he said, "This
car isn't impacted by that and people
were going to still buy them after." And
then I was questioning that and now
we're here.
>> Oh, no. Whatever we can offer, uh, we
offer. So, there's any specific stock
number you're looking to or any specific
car or like a wind edition or GT line or
>> It's a GT line. Uh, but I can certainly
pull it up. Give me one second. I just
went away from it because I was now
doing all the research to figure out if
I was going crazy because I think I'm
going crazy. It should have been K is in
kind of, M is in maybe 3697.
>> Okay, 3697. This one it has the if you
go for the low APR as I think he
mentioned to you, there's um zero APR if
you go up to 48 months or 2.9. I don't
know how many months you want to finance
it, but you get the rebates 5,000 if you
finance through KIA plus 1,000 bonus
cash. And then uh if you're trading any
EV or plug-in hybrid, you get a,000.
Military, if you own a Kia and you have
a registration under your name, you get
another,000. So the total there is not
too many on on a EV9 because it's over
any car over 55,000. It doesn't have the
in Massachusetts the more EV, which is
the $3,500 rebate. So
>> I mean the major question I had was I
thought there was some type of tax
credit if I decided to lease this car
and you said there wasn't a tax credit
if I lease this car. like they they have
lease cash of like 8,500 bucks or
something or 8,000 bucks if I decide to
lease it. And then he said that wasn't
right. So then it made me think I'm
crazy. So now I don't even know
>> if you lease the car.
>> Yeah. If I decide to lease the car,
>> if you lease the car, yeah, there is a
$8,000 uh lease uh rebate on 36 months
and then there's a $1,000 uh lease bonus
cash without any other the spec the
specialty program. There is $9,000
rebate and then the maximum I can do
$1,000 of the MSRP.
>> Okay. And that that's where I think
where the sticking point happened where
me and Tim we we got in a little bit of
a disagreement there um with his kiss uh
because he was saying that $1,000 is
best he do and I was just like can you
do any better than that and kind of went
in a little bit of a
>> unfortunately unfortunately uh no we
can't do more than that.
>> Okay. Yeah. I I know some dealerships
around you guys are all doing bare
minimum two to three grand offs on that
car. So $1,000 wouldn't be enough to
earn my business even though you guys
are pretty close but a bummer. That's
sad.
>> Sorry, man. I'm really sorry. He can go
more than that.
>> No, I know. I know these cars are and
that's what I think that's where I think
the the meme came in cuz I said these
cars are going to be a paperw paper
weight in a week and he was like, "Nah,
they're going to they'll be fine because
I want to finish it with him." So,
relax. We will be involved. We'll make
it work.
>> Did you Did you fall down? Are you okay?
You need to call 911.
Hello.
Oh my gosh. Should I call 911?
>> Hello, Jeremy.
>> I Hi. I don't know. I was talking to
somebody and then it looked sounded like
he fell down and then I got transferred
to you. Who is he okay?
>> I don't know what happened.
>> I don't know. I think his name was I
forgot his name. I'm so sorry. I'm
freaking out. Should I call 911? Is he
going to be okay? I heard his phone fall
down and then here I am.
>> Oh, no. Don't worry about it. So,
>> don't worry about it. I mean, the dude
seemed like he fell and got hurt. Sam, I
think his name is Sam. Do you want to go
check on him?
>> He's all right.
>> I mean, I was in the middle of a
conversation with him and literally I've
heard a tumble and then some hold music.
>> That's all right.
>> Is that what you guys do in
Massachusetts?
>> All right. So, what kind of car are you
interested in?
>> I have a stock number if you if uh that
helps.
>> Sure. Go ahead. Stock number is K is in
kind of M as in maybe 3697.
>> And where are you registering in the
car?
>> Uh, New Hampshire. Zip code zero. I had
to untighten my tie a little bit. Sorry,
I was getting tight.
>> That's right.
>> And you want to buy it, right?
>> Yeah, I'm looking to do the 0% or the
low or the low APR or the I'm willing to
compare and contrast the bigger discount
or bigger rebate with the higher APR.
Actually, I feel so unprofessional. I'm
going to tighten my tie. I'm sorry. I
felt like a buffoon for a minute.
>> And do you have like an EV or a plug-in
hybrid in your household?
>> I I don't have a plug-in hybrid or a EV
right now, but I do have a Kia. The
whole dealership uses abacuses. Huh. Not
just you, not just Tim or Sam.
>> All right. So, I can sell you that car
for $6699.
>> Okay. Who sold? 66
>> 6699.
>> 66999. Okay. So, we went down four
$3,500 more. So, we're at $4,500 off.
>> That's correct.
>> Wow. It's changed with you. That's
crazy. Yeah, you're right. It was good
that Sam fell down the well. Okay.
$4,500 off. Uh, is that with the 0% or
is that with the low APR, just so I
know? Or sorry, with the high APR?
>> With the That's with the 0%.
>> Oh, that's with the 0%.
>> Yes.
>> Yeah. Great. Send me those numbers. I'll
buy it right now.
>> What is your phone number?
>> Yeah. Uh,
>> yeah. It's incredible. I talked to the
right guy. Sam can fall down a well for
all I care.
>> And what's your first name?
>> My name's Tommy.
>> And what's your last name, Tommy?
>> Makula. M I K U L A
>> and your email address.
>> I don't use email. Do you mind texting
to me? It'll be easier that way.
>> So, what I'll do is I'm going to send
you a text and you just need to press
yes and then I'll be able to send you
the code.
>> Awesome. Great. I'm super excited, man.
Thank you, man. This is a great deal.
>> Give me a few minutes.
>> Hey, no problem.
>> All right. Take care.
>> Bye. Bye. It took me 29 minutes to talk
to three different people that had the
personality of a rock where two people
just gave up on me and this deal of guys
give me 12 grand off all of a sudden
with 0%. That's insane.
>> Hey Tommy,
>> what up Costa?
>> What's up? I'm not on live, am I?
>> You are on live.
>> Oh, damn. How many people you got in the
chat right now?
>> How many people? I don't know. A few a
few thousand.
>> All right, man. I can't talk right now,
man. Actually, let me call you back.
>> Wait, can I ask you one question?
Literally just one question.
>> All right. All right. Go ahead.
>> EV9 GT. If I take 0%, do I get any type
of $7,500 credit?
>> It's No, you don't get with low APR. You
only get a standard.
>> Okay, that's what I thought. Okay,
thanks. That's all I need to know. Thank
you. Bye.
>> This is a deal then. Like 100%. He sent
me the deal. That's insane. It's 66,
guys. So, the discount is a total of
$11,431
off. Hi, Dakota.
>> Hey, Tommy.
>> Hey, you're live. Hey, I'm I'm working
I'm working your uh EV9 deal, the one
you told me to. And uh surprisingly, I
don't ever work any of the EV9 deals
here delivered. So, I am just lost and
either I've just got myself an
incredible deal or I'm just a dumb dumb.
It's one of the few. So, I have a
discount for $11,431
off with 0%.
>> With 0%. Is that Do you get the
Can you combine the five grand?
>> I don't know. That's Yeah. No, I know.
That's the same question I had, which is
why I called you.
I feel like you've been doing I We
always just add all the rebates in. We
never do it. But I don't think you get
the five grand. I think it's the five
grand if you do the
>> or the zero.
>> Or the zero. I think it's one or the
other. So if that's the case, 11,431 is
crazy.
>> That is crazy. Like 40 four grand is on
an 89 what I have done. Uh and that's
been super strong and I've had to call
around a lot to get it. So that's that's
crazy.
>> I might have unal alive man in order to
get it happen, but
>> Oh boy. You turned your camera off
>> and well, no, he fell down the well and
then somebody else picked up the phone
and it was like it was like the mafia
like Sopranos. I was talking to one
person and then you fall you hear a
phone fall
>> and then all of a sudden somebody else
picks up the phone and says I'm like is
he okay and he said
>> don't worry about him.
>> Honestly, now that thinking about it, I
think he got I think I think he got a
hit. I think he got I think
>> was a brick wall.
>> It was it it wasn't maybe it was Eigor.
>> Could have been
>> could have been Eigore. Oh, I bet it was
Eigore. Uh okay. Anyway, uh so if you
want to present this deal to the client,
I'm going to tag you in it right now. I
mean, this is a I mean, this seems like
incredible. I don't want to lose it.
Again, I was at $1,000 discount and then
I got $11,000 off. So, yeah,
>> I I'll have you look at it. I just
tagged you on it. It's under my primary
one of my other primary phones. I think
you have access to it.
>> Okay. Uh I don't see the tag yet.
>> Oh, wait. Here. Got you. Boom. Okay. I
just added you. Boom. You have access to
this phone now. I tag you again.
>> Yeah. You You just do just do more check
than I can do on live. Normally, I do a
little more investigating. I honestly
thought I was going to make a few more
phone calls in Uh, I made up a few last
night, but this seems like an incredible
deal. So, I don't want
>> Yeah, there's not many of these. The
only thing this one has is the
relaxation package, the VIP package that
they might not want, but $11,000 off.
Relax in the back row all day.
>> Yeah, I actually already already cleared
that if if it's on there. Awesome.
>> Okay. And cuz there's only based on the
colors I want they want. There's there's
two in Boston that have called both of
those. I was waiting on the other color
and then the rest of the options are
like Ohio. So, we'd have to ship.
>> Okay.
>> So, this is this is near this is new
this is near New Hampshire. is a driving
distance. So,
>> cool. We'll switch you out. Plug it up.
We'll talk to them and bada bing, bada
boom,
>> bada boom, bada bing. Call it.
>> Sounds good.
>> Fine. I like to say I know most things
on most cars. It's It's not an unknown
thing that Kia with their EVs is super
weird with their rebates. I do want to
know what happened to Sam. The more I
think about it, the more I think it was
a hit. Like, let's be real for a minute.
We were talking to somebody and then we
heard a tumble and then we heard just
somebody else pick up the phone. I'm not
calling him back. You don't mess with
the mafia, guys. cuz I don't actually
think it was a hit, but it was crazy how
somebody fell through and then all of a
sudden I got a crazy deal. Yeah, I mean
I get and it was just his response.
>> Don't worry about Sam. He's fine.
>> For the record here for the video here.
If this turns out to be a deal, so many
people will say, "Hey, Tommy, this is a
bad salesman. Just hang up the phone.
Call somebody else. Call somebody else.
You're wasting your time. 30 minutes and
you're making these jokes. You're
wasting your time." That is what we're
paid to do. Stay on the phone. Get the
numbers. Work the cardio. Sometimes
staying on the phone, even through all
of that, can get us $11,000
off the car. Dude, I'm not I'm not going
to lie. That first person threw me off
so hard.
>> This is Tommy.
>> Hey, Tommy. It's Ramy.
>> Oh, hey. How's it going?
>> Good. Did you get the numbers?
>> Uh, let me check. Sorry, I don't think I
checked my text here. Okay, I think I
have them here. The the $11,431
off.
>> That's correct.
>> Okay. And then just to confirm, make
sure because I'm going because I've
talked to three different people and
they all threw me off is what rebates
are included in this discount.
>> So you have the owner loyalty rebates is
a,000. You get the bonus cash of
the,000. You also get the tax credit of
7500.
>> Oh, so you are including the 7500 in
there.
>> Yes.
>> Oh, okay. That makes more sense. See,
this is where I was. I asked the first
person and he said that the tax credit
didn't become available and now you're
saying that is available. So that's part
So you're not discount. You're g the tax
credit. That makes more sense. This
seems like a way crazier deal than what
it was cuz you guys are then discounting
the car
>> 2000
>> 2000 1. Okay, this isn't that crazy of a
deal. Correction. Okay, that's all I
needed to know. Sorry. The first person
told me that there was no tax credit and
I thought there was a tax credit and
then he told me there wasn't and I
almost got gas lit into it. So now I
know. Thank you.
>> The tax credit is good till the end of
the month.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You know, I I understand all
of that. Yeah. No, I was I was looking
to get Okay, I'm going to I'm going to
go call my partner now. But yeah, no, we
were I've seen deals for like four four
or five off plus the rebate. So,
>> all right. All right.
>> Awesome, man. I appreciate your time.
>> All right. Thank you. Bye.
>> Bye. Bye.
>> At the very least, we didn't get the
first lesson, but we got the second
lesson, right? Which is a always double
check the work, right? We always want to
Let's talk like real lesson, right? It's
still not 11K off MSRP, though, Thrive
Dress cuz $7500. It's $7,500 in tax
rebate plus another $2,000 in normal
rebates. So, it ends up being $9,500
rebate with about a what, like less than
$2,000 discount. That's not a strong
deal, dude. You know what's actually
crazy? I just need a I just need a
minute. I've just learned that if you
talk to a car salesman for 30 minutes
and talk to three different car
salesmen, you can get gas lit into
believing a lot of things. Wow.
Insanity. I almost fell for that.
[Music]